Chapter 604 – Why Don’t You Come Down and Play With Me?

At this moment, Lin Ming grasped the Purple Comet Spear and pointed it towards Yan Chi.

Yan Chi’s complexion suddenly became extremely ugly.

He had carefully arranged his tactics and also used his battle spirit; this was the strongest strike that he could use. But even so, it had still failed. If they continued to fight, then the result was almost already decided!

“Lin Ming! Stop here! Don’t force me!” Yan Chi grasped his black sword as he grit out the words between clenched teeth.

“Force you?” Lin Ming smiled, “Are you joking with me? When the three you thought to continuously fight me and wear me down, you think that I was forcing you? At that time, you should have thought of this moment. This is a life or death battle. If I was the one losing, do you really think that you would have stopped here? Now that I’m winning, you’re telling me not to force you? Is there anything so ridiculous in this world?”

Lin Ming sneered. With a flick of the Purple Comet Spear, arcs of electricity and fire began to twine together at the spearpoint.

“Don’t think that I’m really afraid of you. If I detonate this battle spirit that I obtained from the Road of Emperor, I will make it so that both of us die!” Yan Chi’s eyes flashed with madness. Now that Yan Chi was pushed this far, he had abandoned his cowardice. He would absolutely do what he said he would.

“Battle spirit? Oh?” Lin Ming thought for a moment, “So that thing was called a battle spirit? I seem to have some impression of it…”

The soul fragments that Lin Ming had inherited from the Magic Cube were incomplete, but he had some vague recollections about battle spirits. Battle spirits and martial intents were both called two facets of a martial artist’s Concept of Martial Arts.

However, martial intents were usually supportive skills, there were very few of them that could actually be transformed into something with actual striking power. But, a battle spirit was just the opposite. Most of time they were directly used to increase one’s attack power. They could be attached to anything, and could enhance a martial artist’s attack to the limit.

“I’ll say it again. If I detonate this battle spirit, then I will undoubtedly suffer greatly, I might even die, but you won’t be any better off. I will drag you all the way down with me!” As Yan Chi spoke, his black sword began to burn with a gray flame. The flame became more and more vibrant; just looking at it made the soul feel drowned in ice!

Yan Chi had bet everything on this single gamble. In his desperation, he had called up every single ounce of battle spirit in his body!

Lin Ming simply didn’t care. He raised his long spear and pointed it towards Yan Chi’s throat. The cold and sharp purple spearpoint hissed as arcs of electricity pierced the air.

“Let’s stop here! I will tell you everything I have comprehended about battle spirits.” Yan Chi used a true essence sound transmission to speak. Although it was humiliating, when it concerned his life, he could only endure it.

“Oh?” Lin Ming smiled, “Tell me what you’ve understood about battle spirits, and add three pigeon egg-sized Demon God Bones. If you do then I’ll spare your pathetic life.”

“Three pigeon egg-sized Demon God Bones!?” Yan Chi fumed. “You think that Demon God Bones are some cabbage you can pick up at the local market? After so many years at Skysplit Tower, the most I’ve gotten are two longan sized Demon God Bones, and I’ve already used them! Where can I possibly give you three even larger ones!”

“Well then, since that’s the case, go die!”

Lin Ming coldly shouted and thrust out his spear. The Concepts of Thunder and Fire twined together…

Penetrating Rainbow!

“You bastard! Since you want to die so badly, let us perish together!” Yan Chi’s eyes flashed manically, his face twisting like a lunatic’s, “Combust, Emperor battle spirit!!”

Hoo-!

Atop of Yan Chi’s black sword, dark gray flames spewed forth like an erupting volcano. Blue veins twisted on his face, and all the blood vessels on his arms began to stick out.

With a maddening shout, Yan Chi grasped his sword in both hands and cut down at Lin Ming!

Gray flames exploded in the air. As the explosion raged on, one could hear the wailing sounds of tortured ghosts. These sounds were obviously illusions, but for some reason they echoed directly in one’s ears, sneaking through their brains and causing their spiritual seas to tremble.

Facing this overwhelming battle spirit fire that covered the skies, Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. The Heretical God Force’s compressed true essence erupted to the limit and the blood of the Ancient Phoenix burned within him!

The space under his feet began to strangely twist. Lin Ming became one with his spear, and the power of thunder and fire twisted together faster and faster until it became a tornado, the spiraling force repelling all of the battle spirit power nearby.

Bang bang bang!

Like a flying beam of light, Lin Ming grasped the Purple Comet Spear and cut through the void, tearing apart the battle spirit flames. However, this was still an Emperor battle spirit. Even if it was only a trace, as it bloomed with its final light, its final dregs of power still created a terrifying impact. In the intense collision of energy, the battle spirit fire was a like a knife that cut through Lin Ming’s bodily protective true essence and stabbed into his flesh.

However, after Lin Ming had completed 100% Tempering Marrow and even opened the first door of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates, his bodily defensive power was incomparably tough. Despite the power of the battle spirit stabbing into his body, it was only a minor flesh wound.

Ca!

Lin Ming passed through the screen of flame and shot towards Yan Chi!

“What!?!?”

Yan Chi was immensely shocked. At this point he had already used over 70% of his true essence. Clenching his teeth, Yan Chi bet his last ounce of strength on a single attack and thrust his sword towards Lin Ming’s throat. This was an attack that had absolutely no defense behind it. Yan Chi knew that he was dead. Since things were like this, then he would bring Lin Ming with him!

“How naïve…”

Two indifferent words echoed in Yan Chi’s ears. This was also the last voice that he heard. In the next moment, Yan Chi’s head exploded like an impacted watermelon. Lin Ming’s spear ran through Yan Chi’s head like a blazing meteor. The powerful impact along with the explosive force of the twisted thunder and fire caused Yan Chi’s head to be directly smashed into pieces, his brains and blood instantly evaporating!

As bits of skull and flesh still flew in the air, Lin Ming had already landed on the other side, hundreds of feet away. Behind him, Yan Chi’s sword was only half-raised, and it would never go any higher ever again.

This was the difference of absolute speed.

“It’s over.”

Lin Ming put away the Purple Comet Spear. In this battle, in a situation where he hadn’t opened the Eight Inner Hidden Gates, his victory hadn’t come easily. His clothes had been torn apart, and his body was covered with cuts from the battle spirit’s power, dozens of areas on his body were bleeding. After all, Yan Chi’s battle spirit still came from an Emperor level powerhouse. When it erupted in that final burst with all its might, the strength it displayed was extremely terrifying. In the end, it had even cut open Lin Ming’s protective bodily true essence.

In truth, these several dozen bloody cuts on his body couldn’t even be considered injuries to him, they just made him look a bit distressed. Perhaps there were some haughty and proud martial artists that cared about their image and would always want to win in a beautiful and spectacular manner, but to Lin Ming that was nothing at all.

Bang!

Yan Chi’s headless corpse fell to the ground.

This was how he had died.

This third match was also the last. With Yan Chi dead, it was Lin Ming’s complete victory!

The audience had fallen silent. In three continuous revolving matches that were designed to wear him down, Lin Ming had battled to the last one. Judging from his appearance, he may have been wounded, but he still had strength left!

These three had all been part of the Heavenly Demon Seven Stars, and not just that, but they had all entered the Road of Emperor, causing their strength to be greatly increased. Originally, no one thought that Lin Ming would win. Everyone simply thought he was too brash and reckless, but, the true final result had defied all expectations. All three great masters had been completely killed off by Lin Ming!

At the start of the fight, who could imagine that Lin Ming, who had only just finished the King’s Cage, would have his strength rise by such a ridiculous degree!

“This is freaking me out. I think that Lin Ming still has at least 50 to 60% of his strength left. I can’t imagine just how much true essence he has within him.”

“Three continuous matches, and all three opponents were from the Heavenly Demon Seven Stars. There were even top characters like Yan Chi and Maha, but even so, Lin Ming killed all of them while just receiving some minor wounds.”

These minor flesh wounds, not to mention Lin Ming, but they weren’t anything at all to every other martial artist on the third floor. They would be fully healed in just a few hours.

“Truly worthy of being a Titled Asura. Truly worthy of being known as the number one talent of the Holy Demon Continent’s last 10,000 years. His cultivation is only at the extreme Xiantian realm, but he already has such potential. After he becomes a Peerless Emperor, that will truly be terrifying!”

“Hey, what do you… how many stages of Life Destruction do you think Lin Ming will be able to cross?” A martial artist asked out loud.

Humans were weak, but that was only before they became Peerless Emperors. Humans were talented in their perception, and their compatibility with Laws was only second to the Fey’s. The main limiter of their strength was their body. These weak and frail bodies caused humans to be limited in both striking power and defensive power.

But the heavens were fair. Before becoming Peerless Emperors, humans had to experience Life Destruction. Life Destruction was the door of death for humanity. The mortality rate of every single crossing was extremely high. This was also the reason that there was a far smaller number of human Emperor powerhouses than every other race.

However, correspondingly, when one successfully crossed Life Destruction, their body would be remolded. The strength of human powerhouses would rapidly rise. If one could cross eight stages of Life Destruction, their strength would far surpass every other race!

Lin Ming’s current strength was already high to the point of being ridiculously freakish. If he crossed eight stages of Life Destruction in the future, just how formidable would he become?

Thinking of this, the martial artists present didn’t dare to imagine any further…

…………………..

In the special guest section, Feng Shen was listening to the martial artists around him who were talking and expressing their opinions.

He shook his head. These people didn’t understand just how terrifying that battle was.

That was the detonation of an Emperor battle spirit. Even so, it was still fended off by Lin Ming!

An Emperor battle spirit, even if it was just the faintest of wisps, still contained an extremely terrifying explosive power!

Unfortunately, Yan Chi couldn’t control this strength. All he could do was let this battle spirit explode as it wished, spreading the energy in all directions. This caused most of the energy to be wasted, and only a small portion had fallen on Lin Ming.

And when Lin Ming had become one with his spear, he had also used the spiraling power of his spear to deflect the power of the battle spirit, finally receiving only minor wounds at the end.

Feng Shen had extraordinarily good vision. He had seen profound and mysterious principles that Lin Ming had used to avert the power of the battle spirit. This caused him to admire Lin Ming even more. Lin Ming not only had terrifying strength but also a cool mind. In a tense situation he had still chosen to use the most appropriate tactic at the key moment!

‘I… I am not his match.’

Feng Shen was ashamed of his own inadequacy. He was confident that he could have defeated Yan Chi, but to defeat Lin Ming at his peak condition… this was impossible.

Let alone his peak condition, even if Feng Shen went onstage now and challenged Lin Ming, who had already consumed a great deal of his strength, he had to admit that the chances of him defeating Lin Ming were no more than 50-50.

On the arena stage, Lin Ming calmly took Yan Chi’s spatial ring and his black treasure sword. At this time, the infernal energy within Yan Chi’s body flowed into Lin Ming. The fourth pair of wings on his Heavenly Demon Tattoo widened once again. Now he had reached the very peak of an eight-winged Heavenly Demon, and was only a single step away from being a ten-winged Heavenly Demon.

However, crossing this last step wouldn’t be easy. The only way would be to kill someone at the level of a Heavenly Demon Seven Star or higher, otherwise there was no way for this Heavenly Demon Tattoo to grow any more.

“How unfortunate.” Lin Ming shook his head. He was just a little bit off!

“Humph!”

In the seat of honor, High Lord Heian coldly snorted. Everything that Feng Shen had thought of, he too had thought the same. He stood up with a dour expression, not interested in staying another half minute, and then turned around to leave.

But at this moment, Lin Ming looked up. He smiled, smirking as he said, “Heian, running away so soon? Why don’t you come down and play with me?”

What?

High Lord Heian was startled, instantly stiffening on the spot. All of the other martial artists present were beyond shucked. Everyone had incredulous expressions as they looked at Lin Ming.

Just now… what… what did he say?

Chapter 608 – Becoming A High Lord

On the ruined martial arena stage, Lin Ming’s entire body was stained crimson with blood. His clavicle was broken, and he was supporting himself with the Purple Comet Spear. He looked like a god of death that had crawled up from an Asura battlefield.

At this time, just looking at Lin Ming made one feel as if their heart was being squeezed tight. No one dared to look Lin Ming in the eyes.

To allow himself to suffer a grievous injury in exchange for High Lord Heian’s life, Lin Ming’s decisive and ruthless actions had frightened all of the martial artists present, sending chills up their spines.

They had originally thought this would be an even match, and even if victory and defeat were decided, killing the opponent wasn’t possible. Normally, one side would admit defeat and the other side would settle for their hard earned victory.

No one ever dreamed that High Lord Heian would be killed underneath Lin Ming’s spear.

Within Skysplit Tower, the High Lords were synonymous with kings. They were haughty, inviolable, and their will was absolute.

Such a strong High Lord Heian had actually died by Lin Ming’s hands. The impact that this had on everyone was earthshaking.

“Lin Ming had always been hiding his ability. If he erupted with his complete strength from the start then he might have forced High Lord Heian into defeat, but he patiently waited, waited, and waited more, all until that final moment when he was able to kill High Lord Heian with a single spear. From the very beginning, he had been planning on killing High Lord Heian. This is too scary!”

“We can understand this tactic, but who could actually carry it out? Even if we are as strong as Lin Ming, we don’t have his endurance! Lin Ming had only been a tad stronger than High Lord Heian at the start, but as time passed, High Lord Heian’s condition slowly changed and his combat strength began to decline. But Lin Ming was actually able to maintain 80 to 90% of his full strength until that final moment when he exploded with everything he had! This is simply inhuman. Before this he had even fought in three fierce battles!

From the beginning, no one thought that Lin Ming would be able to win the revolving battle against Kai Yang, Maha, and Yan Chi, but, what had happened was that Lin Ming had easily killed all three of them. And the madman didn’t even finish there. In a single go, he continued onwards and killed High Lord Heian!

“He came up with this tactic from the start. In order to kill High Lord Heian, he didn’t even hesitate to seriously wound himself. Formidable strength, terrifying talent, inhuman stamina, a calm, decisive, and ruthless mind and tactics, he killed without hesitation all in order to rid himself of future problems. Such a terrifying person and yet he’s only 20 some years old. Who knows what his achievements will be in the future!”

To the audience, Lin Ming becoming a Peerless Emperor was as good as settled. But, the question was whether or not Lin Ming could maintain this momentum, how many stages of Life Destruction he would pass, and whether or not he would become the number one powerhouse of the Holy Demon Continent!

Being able to look down on all rivals in his youth didn’t mean that he would be able to dominate the continent in the future. After all, the chances that a genius would fall in the future were difficult to speculate.

“To kill High Lord Heian, Lin Ming’s actions were too flashy this time. Although this was a battle in the martial arena, and killing the opponent is in line with Skysplit Tower’s rules, the other High Lords won’t give up here. This is a challenge to their authority!”

“Not necessarily. The 12 High Lords have never been on the best of terms with each other. One less High Lord Heian means that the other 11 High Lords will be able to divide more resources for themselves and obtain even more wealth and authority.” As the martial artists were discussing, they suddenly saw a black mass of infernal energy fly up from High Lord Heian’s corpse. This mass of infernal energy turned into a grim demon in the air. This demon had five pairs of wings; it was a ten-winged Heavenly Demon!

In this instant, the martial artists present finally realized that they had forgotten something. Lin Ming was already a peak eight-winged Heavenly Demon. If he killed High Lord Heian then…

Woosh!

The ten-winged Heavenly Demon rushed towards Lin Ming. At this time, Lin Ming was seriously injured, and he didn’t even have 30% of his strength left. Even so, he wouldn’t be defeated by something like a mass of infernal energy!

The Heavenly Demon force field opened, a tide of pressure swept out!

Peng!

The ten-winged Heavenly Demon fiercely trembled and half of its body dispersed. Lin Ming’s right shoulder was nearly split apart so he used his left hand to lift the spear. With a thrust, thunder burst out!

Chi-la!

The ten-winged Heavenly Demon’s body was pierced through by Lin Ming’s spear. It turned into pure infernal energy that merged into Lin Ming’s body.

With it, the eight-winged Heavenly Demon on Lin Ming’s arm began to slowly grow a fifth pair of wings, becoming increasingly clear. This pair was larger than the first four, and the feathers looked as sharp as swords.

Ten-winged Heavenly Demon! This was a High Lord!

“Lin Ming became a High Lord?”

The martial artists present didn’t know how to respond, this was truly difficult reality to accept! In Polar Skysplit Tower, it had been ages since a human High Lord had appeared. Moreover, Lin Ming was younger than everyone present.

Just six months ago, Lin Ming had been a newcomer to Skysplit Tower’s third floor.

“High Lord… holy…”

“What will the other 11 High Lords do?”

According to the usual practices of Skysplit Tower, before a martial artist became a High Lord they would either be won over, suppressed, threatened, bribed, or even forced to leave. None of these were unusual or surprising situations. Once one became a ten-winged Heavenly Demon, they were a High Lord. This was the rule of Skysplit Tower.

In fact, in a sense, of those geniuses that were suppressed or forced away, most of them were far too weak.

For instance, Da Gu. As the fourth ranked amongst Heavenly Demon Seven Stars, if he hadn’t heeded the warning of Skysplit Tower’s High Lords and continued to his next match, then it was possible that they would have arranged for Yan Chi to be his opponent. When that time came, the results could be imagined.

However, towards this monstrous genius Lin Ming whose strength already surpassed High Lord Heian, the High Lords of Skysplit Tower were no longer capable of threatening him. Even that revolving battle of Kai Yang, Maha, and Yan Chi was easily won by Lin Ming. Who else could do anything to him?

In order to kill Lin Ming, that was only possible if four or five High Lords acted together, causing a heaven-shaking and earth-shattering battle!

At that time when the entirety of Skysplit Tower knew of this, it would become impossible to explain why they killed another High Lord without any reason.

Now, it could be said that Polar Skysplit Tower didn’t have any way to manage Lin Ming.

“Is this real… there is going to be another High Lord? A human High Lord?”

All of the martial artists present thought they were in a dream. In the last several thousands of years, Lin Ming would be the fastest High Lord born within the entire Blood Slaughter Steppes, as well as the youngest High Lord.

Moreover, he was a human!

Lin Ming swallowed a healing pill. Underneath the dual function of the pill and his own formidable resilience, the wound on his arm was already regenerating. He could even feel the muscles rapidly growing underneath, causing an itching feeling to spread there. The healing of his clavicle would be slower, but it wouldn’t take any longer than a few hours.

Lin Ming put out his hand and High Lord Heian’s spatial ring dropped into his palm. This black and plain spatial ring was heavy and a size larger than a normal spatial ring.

This was impressively a high-grade earth-step spatial ring!

A spatial ring was rarer than other treasures of the same level. The value of this high-grade earth-step spatial ring was probably no less than Lin Ming’s own Purple Comet Spear!

‘A High Lord of Skysplit Tower, who knows how much wealth he’s gathered over the years!’ Lin Ming sighed in his heart. High Lord Heian’s cultivation was only equal to a human Revolving Core powerhouse; in terms of combat strength, he was far inferior to a Life Destruction powerhouse. Even in this case, he still had a suspected heaven-step treasure black sword and a high-grade earth-step spatial ring.

It had to be known that Mu Fengxian was only a single stage Life Destruction master as well as the Highest Elder of Divine Phoenix Island. Still, the weapon she used was only a normal high-grade earth-step treasure.

‘If this ring is so valuable, then what would be in it?’ Lin Ming was filled with anticipation.

As for the suspected heaven-step Crimson Ruby Snake Sword, Lin Ming naturally couldn’t forget it, he also received it. If he didn’t count the Cosmic Melting Furnace, then this was the highest quality treasure that Lin Ming had seen up until now. Although he couldn’t use it himself, he could still exchange it for massive amounts of resources.

Seeing Lin Ming take all of High Lord Heian’s wealth, the martial artists’ eyes turned red with envy. This was the total wealth that a Blood Slaughter Steppes High Lord had accumulated for over ten years. Its total value would absolutely surpass that of an ordinary fifth-grade sect Sovereign!

Such a great amount of wealth would be of enormous help to walking down one’s future road of martial arts. Even someone like Feng Shen couldn’t ignore it.

After Lin Ming received everything, he didn’t leave the martial arena but instead sat there and meditated. He was currently in a very poor state and his combat strength had drastically dropped. If someone on the same level as High Lord Heian came now, then they would be able to kill him without a doubt.

Although this possibility was very low, Lin Ming didn’t want to be taken by surprise. Restoring his strength to 70 to 80% in the martial arena and then returning to his practice area was the safest bet.

As long as he could restore his strength, then who could do anything to Lin Ming? Not to mention that he also had the ephemeral Golden Roc Shattering the Void. If he truly tried to run away with his full ability, then not even four or five High Lord Heians would be able to stop him.

Even if their speed could keep up with Lin Ming, their endurance would be inferior to his. Lin Ming could maintain his peak speed the entire time. As for others, even if they popped pills constantly while flying, their speed would become more and more slow.

In this case, Lin Ming no longer had any fear of Polar Skysplit Tower!

Seeing that Lin Ming didn’t intend to leave yet, the other martial artists invariably also decided not to go, sitting in their seats and discussing what just happened.

And at this time, on Skysplit Tower’s first floor and second floor, there were many martial artists gathered in pubs, restaurants, teahouses, and other places discussing Lin Ming’s three continuous fights with Yan Chi, Maha, and Kai Yang. The second floor martial artists didn’t feel as great a pressure as those martial artists on the third floor did. They were free to choose the time of their match, and if they didn’t want to compete they could just ignore it. They had a relatively great amount of time to chat and relax.

Lin Ming’s revolving fight with Yan Chi, Maha, and Kai Yang had already spread through the entire Skysplit Tower 10 days ago like a raging storm. Everyone was a martial artist, so who didn’t want to see such a peak battle? But those that could truly go to the third floor and watch the match were the extraordinary individuals or absurdly wealthy of the second floor.

As for the weaker rung of martial artists, let alone having the qualifications, but even if they did have the qualifications to go up they still wouldn’t be able to afford a ticket.

In a restaurant on the second floor, a mixed race old storyteller was carrying a walking stick in one hand as he made rapid hand gestures in the air with the other.

He was making up completely fantastical fabrications of Lin Ming’s three man revolving fight with Yan Chi, Maha, and Kai Yang.

The martial artists of the first and second floor that didn’t have the qualifications to enter the third floor and watch this battle could only use their imaginations to fill it in. The storytelling old man had found business in this opportunity, and was casting Lin Ming’s three man revolving battle with great gusto.

For a mortal, if they could receive a single Blood Demon Crystal as a reward, this would be enough for them to live in Skysplit Tower for an entire year.

“Pah!” The old man pounded his walking stick against the ground. “…In that very moment, Kai Yang cut down with his saber, using his ultimate technique. But at this time, Lin Ming stood his ground, unmoving. He flourished his long spear, thrusting it out, and at that moment the heavens shook and the earth shattered, gods cried and ghosts wept… Kai Yang spat out a mouthful of blood and Lin Ming chased him down…”

“Hold on! F*ck you, what the f*ck are you making up all this shit for!” An Imp martial artist pounded the table. The storytelling old man had said that Kai Yang had been beaten up by Lin Ming. As both he and Kai Yang were Imps, he naturally didn’t want to listen to this nonsense.

Previous Chapter

Chapter 609 – High Lord Heian’s Inheritance

The storytelling old man was scared. He quickly apologized, “I’m sorry, I’m sorry, this lowly one has only heard everyone say this so that’s why I…”

“You’re just a mortal, so what the hell do you understand.” The Imp martial artist angrily said.

“Consider it over.” The Imp martial artist’s companion waved his hand. “Kai Yang probably isn’t Lin Ming’s match. Lin Ming entered the King’s Cage for 108 days. After he came out, he probably had the strength to rank near the front of the Heavenly Demon Seven Stars.”

“It’s already been several quarter hours since the match started. I think that the results have already come out. Lin Ming should be able to defeat Kai Yang, but I wonder how his fight with Maha went?”

“F*ck, I wish I could watch the match. This sucks!”

As the martial artists in the restaurant talked amongst themselves, the storytelling old man didn’t know if he should continue.

And at this time, the martial artists suddenly heard a loud noise outside of the restaurant, growing louder and more excited with every passing moment.

“What’s going on?”

The several martial artists were suspicious and were preparing to go out to take a look, when suddenly a martial artist ran in, almost crashing into the group.

The several martial artists were about to lose their temper until they discovered that this person was their companion.

“Big news! Big news!” The martial artist yelled as soon as he passed the door.

“What’s going on? Why are you so freaked out?”

“Skysplit Tower’s High Lords have changed. Lin Ming has replaced High Lord Heian as a new one of the 12 High Lords, given the title of High Lord Evil God!” The martial artist frantically said.

“What did you just say?” The martial artists were stunned. Their first reactions were disbelief, “Lin Ming replaced High Lord Heian? How is that possible? Then what about High Lord Heian?”

“High Lord Heian seems… seems to be dead… dead…”

As the martial artist spoke with ambiguity, everyone present was shocked, completely petrified.

High Lord Heian… died?

…………………………

Within Skysplit Tower, the news of Lin Ming killing High Lord Heian was spreading at a terrifying speed!

Nearly every martial artist on the third floor was in the martial arena at the moment, so they of course knew the moment that Lin Ming killed High Lord Heian. Of course, the martial artists of the first floor and second floor were much slower in finding out the news.

But this didn’t take over an hour.

A High Lord was killed! This was the greatest event that had happened in Skysplit Tower for the last few hundreds of years!

When people heard this news, many of them were filled with disbelief, because these were basically rumors. But as the news began to spread through the entire Skysplit Tower, and with the high-level figures of Skysplit Tower not standing up to clarify these rumors, they had no choice but to believe.

Ten days ago, the news of Lin Ming’s three man revolving fight with Yan Chi, Maha, and Kai Yang had spread through the entirety of Skysplit Tower. But now, compared to today’s news, that was simply child’s play!

Initially, people had thought that Lin Ming would likely die in this three man revolving fight, but they never imagined the result would be like it was. It was simply unbelievable. Lin Ming killed Yan Chi and the rest, and then continued to kill High Lord Heian in a single go, becoming one of the current High Lords!

A High Lord was a legendary existence. On the second floor, there basically weren’t any martial artists that had seen a High Lord before. And for the mortals of Skysplit Tower, a High Lord was no different from a god, a being that they couldn’t even look up to.

……

At this time, Skysplit Tower’s third floor, practice area.

Lin Ming was sitting cross-legged on a stone bed.

He didn’t know about the discussions happening outside nor did he care. In fact, even the title of High Lord Evil God was given to him by the martial artists of the third floor, spreading out from that point afterwards. This was naturally a title that originated from Lin Ming’s title given to him by the King Tablet, Evil God Asura.

Lin Ming sat in meditation for a while, restoring his condition to its peak state. Then, he took out the four spatial rings he had obtained, one at a time. These spatial rings were respectively obtained from Kai Yang, Maha, Yan Chi, and High Lord Heian.

Of these four spatial rings, three were medium-grade earth-step and one was a high-grade earth-step.

Lin Ming picked up Kai Yang’s spatial ring first. Kai Yang was the weakest of the bunch, so he was naturally the poorest too.

After taking out everything within the spatial ring, Lin Ming quickly swept through it all. There wasn’t anything too valuable inside. There were pills, jade slips, various treasure, and also over 9000 high-grade Blood Demon Crystals. The value of these wasn’t too small, but Lin Ming didn’t even bother to glance at them.

Lin Ming quickly sorted everything out and put everything he didn’t need in one spatial ring and the Blood Demon Crystals in another. There wasn’t anything in Kai Yang’s spatial ring that had interested him, but this was also within his expectations.

Then, Lin Ming picked up Maha’s spatial ring.

The contents were similar oKai Yang’s spatial ring, except even more abundant. There were around 15,000 high-grade Blood Demon Crystals, which was always a great and useful wealth.

There were even some acceptably adequate pills. Lin Ming took them out and reserved them for future use.

Then, Lin Ming picked up Yan Chi’s spatial ring.

After taking out the contents, there were actually just around 20,000 high-grade Blood Demon Crystals as well as all sorts of pills. Even the treasures were the highest of high quality.

After sweeping through everything, Lin Ming picked out a jade slip from the chaotic mess. After sweeping his mind through it, he was surprised.

This was Yan Chi’s records about his experience with battle spirits.

Battle spirit…

Lin Ming pondered for a moment. When one reached a higher level in the road of martial arts, a battle spirit would become an essential part of a martial artist’s strength.

A battle spirit could grow along with a martial artist’s own growth, slowly strengthening. Thus, the earlier one comprehended a battle spirit, the more room for growth there would be.

However, if a martial artist had bad luck, poor perception, or their martial arts cultivation had already reached an exceedingly high realm, they would slowly be unable to comprehend a battle spirit.

A battle spirit was in itself an elusive and enigmatic existence, a mysterious and obscure boundary. Sometimes the more one wanted to comprehend a battle spirit, the less successful they would be. Sometimes the less one thought about it, the higher their chances of comprehending it would be. It was an indescribable factor.

The memories that Lin Ming inherited were incomplete and there was very little concerning battle spirits. With Yan Chi’s recorded experiences, even though it was probably riddled with errors and rough spots, at least it could be used as a reference point. In the end, it was better than nothing.

Putting this jade slip aside, Lin Ming waved his hand and put everything else inside a spatial ring.

These three spatial rings had contributed over 40,000 high-grade Blood Demon Crystals to Lin Ming. This was enough for Lin Ming to squander them as quickly as he could for dozens of years.

Finally, it was time for the main event. This was High Lord Heian’s spatial ring.

Lin Ming picked up the spatial ring and sank his mind inside. in the next moment, everything inside was taken out.

For a time, the entire practice area was filled with massive piles of various jade slips, pills, treasures, and several dozens of large boxes.

A rich infernal energy and blood vitality coiled around these boxes – they were obviously Blood Demon Crystals.

Every large box had 5000 Blood Demon Crystals. With several dozen of these large boxes, there were around 200,000 to 300,000 high-grade Blood Demon Crystals. Compared to the total combined wealth of Kai Yang, Maha, and Yan Chi, it was at least seven or eight times more.

It wouldn’t be an exaggeration to say that the wealth of a High Lord from Skysplit Tower was equal to an entire sect.

“Mm… this is…”

Lin Ming felt that within these dozens of boxes, one of them had an especially rich infernal energy. Lin Ming put out his hand and this box fell into his palm.

This box was a third of the size of the other ones. It was crafted from jade and was engraved with a sealing array formation. This array formation was used to prevent the leakage of energy.

“There’s a sealing array formation but the energy coming from it is still so potent. What could be inside?”

Lin Ming unraveled the box’s array formation and opened the lid. Instantly, an energy so thick that it condensed into substance began to escape.

Within the box, just the bottom was covered with a layer of light grape-sized red crystal. Every crystal was bright, translucent, and extremely shiny.

“These are… top grade Blood Demon Crystals?”

Above high-grade Blood Demon Crystals was top-grade Blood Demon Crystals. This sort of Blood Demon Crystal would only originate from the highest quality of Blood Demon Crystal mines. But in these mines, there was only a very, very small amount of top-quality Blood Demon Crystals that would be produced, thus they were incomparably precious.

This sort of thing was too wasteful if used to practice. Even a High Lord of Skysplit Tower wasn’t willing to be so extravagant and luxurious.

A top-grade Blood Demon Crystal was mainly used to make breakthroughs in bottlenecks. For instance, if Lin Ming cultivated to the extreme Xiantian realm and wanted to make a breakthrough to Revolving Core, then he could use a top-grade Blood Demon Crystal to greatly shorten the time needed to make a breakthrough.

“This is the good stuff.”

Lin Ming roughly counted them. Within this box, there were only several dozen top-grade Blood Demon Crystals. These weren’t something that could be bought with money alone. Even Yan Chi, Maha, or Kai Yang didn’t have a single top-grade Blood Demon Crystal in their spatial rings, but High Lord Heian actually had several dozen of them at once. From this alone, one could see just how wealthy the High Lords of Skysplit Tower were.

“High Lord Heian collected so many top-grade Blood Demon Crystals… he was probably preparing to make his breakthrough to a four-star Demon King.”

To martial artists from the demon races, such as the Giant Demons or Imps, the step from a three-star Demon King to four-star Demon King was similar to a human martial artist’s leap from Revolving Core to Life Destruction. It was not a small hurdle.

After a Skysplit Tower High Lord broke through to a four-star Demon King, they would then leave Skysplit Tower. Otherwise, if they stayed within the Blood Slaughter Steppes for too long, then there was a chance they would be killed by the mystical power within the Eternal Demon Abyss.

As Lin Ming was putting away these several dozen top-grade Blood Demon Crystals, his mind suddenly stirred. “There seems to be something here…”

Taking out all of the top-grade Blood Demon Crystals, Lin Ming found that there was actually a hidden space at the bottom of the jade box. He pulled open the cover to reveal a small space just several inches wide.

Within this space were two glass beads, one black and one white.

As Lin Ming saw these two colored glass beads, he sucked in a deep breath. These were… Demon God Bones!

Two Demon God Bones! And both of them were much larger than the one that Xing Tian had!

Lin Ming was secretly flabbergasted.

It was impossible to measure the value of a Demon God Bone with Blood Demon Crystals.

Every 10 years, the Eternal Demon Abyss would have a period where it became relatively quiet and tranquil. During this time, Skysplit Tower’s High Lords would send out teams of people to scour the boundary edge of the Eternal Demon Abyss, sometimes even going themselves.

Demon God Bones were formed when the rich energy within the Eternal Demon Abyss became thick to the point that it was a liquid and then condensed over a period of tens of thousands of years or even a hundred thousand years; it was far incomparable with Blood Demon Crystals. It was of tremendous help to the cultivation of martial artists from any race. Demon God Bones could even help a Demon King or Life Destruction powerhouse attack the bottleneck to becoming an Emperor level powerhouse. Just from this alone, one could see that its effects were similar to the Nirvana Dragon Root, and in fact, the value of a Demon God Bone was comparable to a Nirvana Dragon Root.

Although the Nirvana Dragon Root was rare, it was still only a medical plant found in the Demon Emperor’s medicine garden. The Demon Emperor had initially only been a very strong Emperor level powerhouse. But, the Demon God Bone originated from the Eternal Demon Abyss, and that mystical and strange presence within the Eternal Demon Abyss was far from what the Demon Emperor could compare with when he was still in the Sky Spill Continent.

Chapter 610 – You Either Leave Or Fight

When Lin Ming first swallowed a Demon God Bone, the Demon God Bone had fused together with the Heavenly Demon force field. This had been countered with the Nameless Divine Pill that had been refined from a Nirvana Dragon Root. With the energies together, it was a complete coincidence that their combined powers were able to completely open the Gate of Healing.

From this alone, one could see that a single Demon God Bone was somewhat inferior to the Nameless Divine Pill refined from a Nirvana Dragon Root.

However, it had to be said that regardless of whether it was Xing Tian or High Lord Heian’s Demon God Bones, they had all come from the surrounding area of the Eternal Demon Abyss and were also the most common and ordinary level of Demon God Bones.

But within the Eternal Demon Abyss, there were actually higher grade Demon God Bones. There were completely legendary objects; it was almost impossible for anyone to get their hands on them.

Lin Ming browsed through the jade slips that High Lord Heian had left behind. Besides some top cultivation methods, there was a single jade slip that caught his attention.

The contents within were actually a record of the Eternal Demon Abyss!

“Eternal Demon Abyss…”

Lin Ming muttered. Mysterious lands always attracted eager people that desired to explore, especially a place like the Eternal Demon Abyss which contained seemingly infinite resources as well as countless dangerous and fatal traps. There were even some Emperor powerhouses that, when their time was about to come to an end, would choose enter the Eternal Demon Abyss. They not only wanted to find their own lucky chance but also longed to decipher that mystical land. They wanted to see with their own eyes just what was within the Eternal Demon Abyss.

Sinking his mind into the jade slip, the first thing that appeared within Lin Ming’s mind was a map. This was a map of the Eternal Demon Abyss.

On this map, the 12 Skysplit Towers were marked with red dots, and underneath these 12 Skysplit Towers was the tens of thousands of miles wide Eternal Demon Abyss.

This part of the Eternal Demon Abyss map was completely blank.

But several thousand miles around the Eternal Demon Abyss periphery, there were detailed signs, careful descriptions of dangerous zones, locations, spots, all meticulously portrayed and annotated.

In addition, there was even a mark on the map that indicated where it was easy to find Demon God Bones.

If one wanted to explore the Eternal Demon Abyss, the value of this map as a reference point was unimaginable.

Below all of this was all sorts of varied lore about the Eternal Demon Abyss. Its contents were similar to what Lin Ming already knew. For tens of thousands of years, every single character that entered the Eternal Demon Abyss, regardless of whether they were peerless geniuses or Emperor powerhouses, everyone would die there with no exception.

Let alone the inside of the Eternal Demon Abyss, even a thousand miles around the edges was a restricted death zone. Anyone that entered would die!

All martial artists that wanted to explore the Eternal Demon Abyss, including even High Lords, had to be at least 1000 miles from the edge of the Eternal Demon Abyss, or sometimes even 2000 miles away.

The closer one approached to the Eternal Demon Abyss, the higher grade of Demon God Bones there would be, but, the dangers would also be correspondingly greater and the chances of dying there that much higher!

“According to the records within this jade slip, in just this last millennium, over 170 High Lords have died within the Eternal Demon Abyss. Every time the Eternal Demon Abyss opens there would be one or two High Lords that die!”

Lin Ming was shocked as he saw the data within High Lord Heian’s jade slip. Every time that the Eternal Demon Abyss opened, High Lords would personally go, and the reason for this was those high grade Demon God Bones.

For a character on the level of a normal Heavenly Demon Seven Star, their strength was far worse compared to a High Lord. They could only stay in the extreme periphery. Finding one or two ordinary Demon God Bones was already considered very good for them.

To find anything of a higher grade was simply impossible.

With 12 Skysplit Towers, that would mean there were around 150 High Lords. Every time the Eternal Demon Abyss opened, one or two would die. That would also mean that the fatality rate of these High Lords was around 1%; this wasn’t a too exaggerated fatality rate.

On the road of martial arts, if one was too afraid to take risks then they might as well not practice martial arts and peacefully pass away from old age while enjoying themselves.

“Eternal Demon Abyss… if there’s a chance, I want to go too.” Lin Ming was very much interested in exploring this land where so many risks and chances coexisted together. Of course, he absolutely didn’t dare to enter into the 1000 mile death zone surrounding the edge of the Eternal Demon Abyss. He didn’t think that his life was much sturdier than those of ancient Emperor level powerhouses.

As Lin Ming continued to read through the jade slip it also described how the Eternal Demon Abyss erupted. It seemed that every several dozens of years, the Eternal Demon Abyss would also erupt once like a volcano, spitting out a massive amount of infernal energy as well as some hidden caches of Demon God Bones from within the Eternal Demon Abyss.

For the last several tens of thousands of years, people had searched the extreme outer edges of the Eternal Demon Abyss for these scattered Demon God Bones, all of them having come from the eruption of the Eternal Demon Abyss.

After every one of these special eruptions, the martial artists that entered the Eternal Demon Abyss would have much greater harvests. Of course, the risks would be higher too.

Because after the Eternal Demon Abyss erupted, that restless and vibrant energy and some strange life forms would form various danger spots, areas where one’s bones wouldn’t even be left over.

And in these cases of eruptions, the map would have massive changes to it. The old map would no longer be useful and one could only form a new map. This also meant that it was easier for people to randomly stumble into these danger zones.

It could be said that in the last 1000 years, of the over 170 High Lords that had died, over half of these deaths were because of the eruption of the Eternal Demon Abyss.

As Lin Ming finished reading through the jade slip, at this moment, a bright light flashed in his room, a sound then floating into Lin Ming’s mind. “I am High Lord Bloodfire. Young Hero Lin, please follow the servants to the fourth floor.”

“Fourth floor?”

Lin Ming’s mind stirred. The fourth floor was the exclusive residency of Skysplit Tower’s High Lords.

All remaining 11 High Lords were situated there!

Lin Ming thought for a moment and then left his practice area.

Just outside of Lin Ming’s practice area, a pair of beautiful Fey maids were already waiting. These two beautiful girls were the same height and both their stature and appearance could not be any more perfect. Their cultivation was also at the Houtian realm.

In Sky Fortune Kingdom, if there was ever a girl that could be so young and have a Houtian realm cultivation while having such a perfect appearance, then they would be the most proud amongst all proud women. However, within Skysplit Tower, they were actually nothing more than maids.

“Sir High Lord, we are here to lead you to the fourth floor and fulfill any desire you have.” A young Fey girl said in a soft lilting voice.

“Lead the way.” Lin Ming’s voice was calm and indifferent.

The third and fourth floors of Skysplit Tower were also connected by a transmission array. In this white hazy transmission array, one needed a token to enter.

As Lin Ming reached this transmission array he stopped and began to patiently study it. As he thought, it was undoubtedly an ancient transmission array. It stemmed from the same foundation as the Realm of the Gods’ transmission arrays.

Seeing this familiar transmission array, Lin Ming was much more relieved. This way, at least he wouldn’t be trapped on the fourth floor. His fleeting Golden Roc Shattering the Void movement technique combined with this ancient transmission array meant that he was confident that even if several High Lords sieged him together, he would still be able to safely withdraw.

With a step inside, a light flashed. In the next moment, Lin Ming and the two Fey maids arrived at Skysplit Tower’s fourth floor.

The legendary Road of Emperor was also here.

As he was led through a dimly lit corridor, the maids finally brought Lin Ming before a towering and sumptuous grand temple. The gate of this temple was over 100 feet tall and there were all sorts of ancient and mysterious runes carved into it. It was unknown just what material it was formed from.

As Lin Ming arrived at this great temple, the gates opened, making grinding noises as if the structure couldn’t resist its own vast weight.

Past the gate, there were 10 people in black robes, all of them uniformly wearing black cloaks. Some were tall, some were short, and all of them were sitting at a long black table.

With the ten people gathered together, the aura they emitted could be called terrifying.

And this aura was completed aimed towards Lin Ming alone!

Lin Ming’s mind went cold. The Heavenly Demon martial intent immediately erupted, offsetting the pressure from this combined aura. His body only shook for a split second but he hadn’t taken a single step back.

Without a doubt, these 10 black-robed individuals were all High Lords of Skysplit Tower. Facing Lin Ming, they were only subconsciously emitting their aura in order to frighten him.

“Only 10 of them. Isn’t there another High Lord?”

Lin Ming was puzzled. He swept over these 10 individuals. Of these 10, there was a pretty significant gap in strength between all of them. There were even some people that were unfathomably deep. Lin Ming had to admit that he wasn’t their match at this moment.

“Heroes truly come from the young!” A black-robed man sitting in the first seat laughed, his voice deep and loud. “High Lord Evil God, is that your title?”

Lin Ming calmly said, “Titles are meaningless to me. Feel free to call me what you will.” The black-robed man speaking was without a doubt the strongest powerhouse amongst the 10 High Lords here. Lin Ming had to confess that he didn’t have the slightest chance of defeating him.

“Good! I like your straightforward attitude. I don’t want to play games with you. I’ll ask you now, are you willing to leave Skysplit Tower?”

Lin Ming frowned, “You are a ten-winged Heavenly Demon and I am ten-winged Heavenly Demon, why do you want me to leave Skysplit Tower? Is it only because I am a human? Do you think that this Skysplit Tower only belongs to you Goliaths and Giant Demons?”

“Hehe, it’s not only because you’re a human.” The black-robed man in the first seat stood up, his deep and dark eyes like stars in the night. “I allow you to leave because those have been the rules of Skysplit Tower for the last 10,000 years! Skysplit Tower does not allow the existence of twelve-winged Heavenly Demons. But you… if you are freely allowed to grow as you wish, then in another year or two we might not even be your match anymore. When that day comes, who can prevent you from obtaining 12 wings? This is a lesson that was learnt from the Eightfall War Emperor; once is already more than enough. We do not wish for any volatile factors to appear which threaten the status of Skysplit Tower.”

Lin Ming sneered, not speaking. In the end, it seemed that the current rules of Skysplit Tower had already taken the entire Blood Slaughter Steppes as their own property.

Indeed, with the ability to amass such a massive amount of resources and wealth, as well as numerous high level practice areas, who would not be moved by these?

If the Blood Slaughter Steppes didn’t contain a mystical force that killed all high level martial artists that stepped into here, then this land would have already been aimed at by the many Emperor level powerhouses and Holy Lands of the Holy Demon Continent. At that time, an unrivalled great war would erupt over the Blood Slaughter Steppes, and the Blood Slaughter Steppes would eventually by carved up by the victors.

And such a war would probably erupt every thousand years, causing the land to be redistributed again.

Now, because of all these strange and secretive rules of the Blood Slaughter Steppes forming a pattern, in a sense, the current Blood Slaughter Steppes had become a special sort of sect. As for these High Lords, they were the same as the sect Elders.

“I can leave. I had no intention of becoming a High Lord to begin with, nor do I want to stay in the Blood Slaughter Steppes for a long time. I only want to stay in the Blood Slaughter Steppes for another three months and then enter the Road of Emperor. After I come out, I will immediately leave!” Lin Ming already made deep concessions. With his current strength, coming into direct confrontation with the Blood Slaughter Steppes was not wise or rational. It had to be known that the Blood Slaughter Steppes didn’t have just the Polar Skysplit Tower, but also 11 other Skysplit Towers. There were simply masters all around.

“Hehe.” The black-robed man smiled, “I’m sorry, but it’s impossible for me to agree to your request. You can either choose to leave now, or you can choose to fight with me!”

Chapter 615 – Entering the Road of Emperor

Lin Ming stepped onto the crimson altar. As he felt the thick bloody infernal energy emanating from the altar, he was secretly surprised.

This altar was carved from a massive chunk of pure Blood Demon Crystal. Not just that, but it was high-grade Blood Demon Crystal. Within a Blood Demon Crystal mine, they were usually found in small blocks and chunks; it was particularly rare to find such a massive hunk of Blood Demon Crystal like this one.

Lin Ming stood at the center of the altar and cut his own palm. He believed that High Lord Bloodfire wouldn’t have set any traps here for him. After all, High Lord Bloodfire still believed that he had a slave seal planted within him and was completely subservient to the Tower Master’s orders.

Blood flowed onto the altar and was instantly absorbed into the deep crimson stone. After several breaths of time, beneath Lin Ming’s feet, a massive deep red totem lit up. This was also in the pattern of a twelve-winged Heavenly Demon.

In the next moment, a radiant red light shot up into the sky, directly swallowing Lin Ming within.

Infernal energy, an evil, dangerous, and brutal energy directly smashed into Lin Ming’s spiritual sea, followed by a massive pressure on his soul. If it wasn’t for the fact that he had passed the King’s Cage and had already become accustomed to the Heavenly Demon force field, then this pressure would have caused him to nearly faint. In fact, many martial artists – including Yan Chi and Maha – would immediately faint upon first entering the Road of Emperor, only waking up after a long time.

The Heavenly Demon martial intent was released, and Lin Ming used the Asura force field to resist the pressure of the Road of Emperor. In the next instant, he had arrived in another space.

The place Lin Ming appeared at was still a deep red altar. This altar was the exact same as the one at the entrance to the Road of Emperor. As he looked beneath, he saw that under the altar was impressively the dark abyss. A rich infernal energy wafted up from this abyss. Lin Ming had a deepening suspicious that this abyss under the altar was the source of infernal energy. If he fell all the way down, then he would fall into the Eternal Demon Abyss!

Above this abyss was a ten foot wide wooden plank road. This road wasn’t supported by anything. Instead, it was firmly suspended in midair. Along this wooden plank path, every 100 feet or so, there would be a group of lights. Underneath these lights were statues carved from obsidian. These statues didn’t have any support either – they were also held up and suspended in the air through some mystical power.

As Lin Ming looked at these quietly burning ghostly blue flames, he could feel a very rich soul force coming from them. It was like these weren’t flames but rather the blaze coming from a burning soul.

What a strange place!

Lin Ming was startled. He tried to fly, but as he expected, flying was restricted in this area. But that was probably for the best. If he really tried to fly and fell down into this abyss then he would most likely die.

The Road of Emperor was the same as the King’s Cage: both were mere practice areas. But since ancient times, for those martial artists whose luck was poor, or those who misjudged their own strength, there would always be people that perished in here.

Without a doubt, this ten foot wide plank road was the Road of Emperor. Lin Ming didn’t hastily step onto the Road of Emperor. Instead, he sat down in meditation, adjusting his mental and physical state to their peak condition, and then stepped onto the plank road.

As soon as he entered the Road of Emperor, Lin Ming immediately felt a pressure cover him. This pressure was completely different from that of the Heavenly Demon force field’s pressure. This pressure came from soul and will, and Lin Ming was no stranger to this pressure either.

This pressure was the Emperor Will.

When Lin Ming fought with Yan Chi and Maha, he had once felt a part of the Emperor Will. When an Emperor level powerhouse died, the will they left behind would not fade away even after thousands of years. This was the so-called battle spirit.

A battle spirit was the condensed will that a martial artist could form after they reached a certain boundary. This will could be attached to any object, and could be used in a multitude of ways, such as killing people.

For instance, if one attached a battle spirit to the air, they could directly crush a massive boulder into powder.

If they attached a battle spirit to a skill or treasure, they could double their attack power, or even increase it by several times over!

“Emperor battle spirit… I wonder when I will be able to comprehend my own battle spirit.” Lin Ming was filled with expectations. When a martial artist reached the Emperor level they would normally have their own battle spirit. Of course, there were even some lucky individuals who didn’t need to be at the Emperor level. If they had a great enough destiny fall unto their body, they could often comprehend a battle spirit at the higher stages of Life Destruction.

This was only the situation within the Sky Spill Continent. If it were the Realm of the Gods, then it was probably even more abnormal. It wouldn’t be strange for those at the Revolving Core to be able to comprehend a battle spirit.

Thinking of this, Lin Ming asked, “Demonshine, when would a top talent of the Realm of the Gods usually comprehend their own battle spirit?”

Demonshine, who had been staying within Lin Ming’s spiritual sea the entire time, hadn’t replied. In fact, it was like Demonshine hadn’t even heard his question. This caused Lin Ming to be a bit surprised. As soon as they entered the Road of Emperor, Demonshine had been incomparably quiet, not even making the smallest noise.

“Demonshine?” Lin Ming asked, worried.

“Lin Ming, this Road of Emperor… I feel like I’ve been here before…” After being silent for a long time, Demonshine quietly and eerily spoke.

“Mm?” Lin Ming was slightly startled.

“Well, it’s more accurate to say that my big brother came here.” Demonshine sounded a bit sad. This sort of mood rarely ever happened to the proud and talkative dog.

“Your big brother?”

“My original body is that of a Three-headed Demonic Divine Hound, and my soul is also a trinity of three souls in one. My big brother was born first, and then as his strength grew, my second brother was born, and finally, me. When we sieged the Verdant Feather Holy Lands in the past, Big Brother and Second Brother tried to protect me, and because of that they were twisted to nothingness in the soul storm. Within my body are some of the remnant soul fragments of my big brother and second brother.”

As Demonshine finished speaking he let out a long sigh. In just the snap of the fingers, tens of thousands of years had passed. Recalling the past now really made one feel a bitterly painful nostalgia.

As Lin Ming heard Demonshine speak, he suddenly froze, a light seeming to go off in his mind. Yes! He had forgotten but something!

When Lin Ming was still on the second floor, he had killed Xue Man and obtained a nameless ancient tome from his spatial ring. This tome had vivid, lifelike images of people rubbed into all the pages; one could even faintly feel the aura and dignity of these characters as they were when they were alive. Near these images were written notes that listed out these character’s lives. As Lin Ming had read through them, he realized that every single one of these characters were all either Emperor level powerhouses or peak Emperor level talents of the last tens of thousands of years of the Holy Demon Continent!

This included the Netherworld Great Emperor, and even the Demon Emperor was impressively included in there.

Lin Ming immediately dug out the tome and quickly found the page that the Demon Emperor was listed on.

Within the tome, the Demon Emperor was holding onto the Great Desolate Blood Halberd, his ink-black hair recklessly flying in the wind. One could even vividly feel the terrifying aura and majesty of the Demon Emperor.

Beside the Demon Emperor’s picture was a note.

“Demon Emperor. His birth was ominous and his death was ominous. Cause of death is unclear.”

“This is…” Demonshine was stunned. He exclaimed, “This rubbing is exactly the same as the Demon Emperor himself.”

“Yes, it is exactly the same. Not just that, but the Demon Emperor died in the Realm of the Gods and he was an existence from tens of thousands of years ago. So, who carved the image of the Demon Emperor and how did they know that he died?”

Lin Ming’s mind was filled with doubts.

Demonshine said, “Lin Ming, look at the base of those lights.”

As Demonshine spoke, Lin Ming looked up and was suddenly astonished. In front of him, not too far away, was a carved relief of a Fey martial artist at the base of the lights. This Fey martial artist was handsome and held a longsword in his hands. He was a jade-like beauty with a heroic appearance.

Lin Ming suddenly remembered that this Fey martial artist was one of those whose images were rubbed within the tome!

Lin Ming opened the tome and found that the carved relief of this martial artist was the exact same as the rubbing!

“Lian Ku. Born in the Holy Demon Calendar year of 26,720, died in the Holy Demon Calendar year of 26,750. This person was a peerless talent of elegance and grace. He reached the Fey King realm at 24 years of age, and within his realm there was no worthy opponent for him. His path to becoming a Fey Emperor was inevitable, but what a pity, his destiny was lacking. As he was seeking his own lucky chance in a danger zone, he perished there, ending his life at 30 years of age.”

A Fey King was equal to the human Revolving Core. For someone to become a Fey King at the age of 24 was similar to reaching Revolving Core at an age of 24. This was a speed that would be around five or six years faster than Mu Qianyu. In fact, it wasn’t even that different from Lin Ming!

A peerless hero of his generation, his path to becoming an Emperor was a matter of time. However, he perished in the middle of his path.

“Lin Ming, I remember some things. In my big brother and second brother’s memories, these lights that you see each represent an Emperor level powerhouse. Even if they aren’t Emperor level powerhouses they are still peerless talents of their generation that should easily have become Emperor level characters. But these people all have two things in common. The first is that they are dead, and the second is… when they were young, they once stepped into the Road of Emperor!”

These lights each represented an Emperor level powerhouse that had once entered the Road of Emperor?

Lin Ming’s mind chilled. As he looked at these quietly burning ghostly blue flames, he couldn’t feel any heat from them. Rather, he felt a bone-biting chill, as if these flames were burning souls.

Of course, this was only a feeling. If they really were souls then they would have burnt out long ago.

Demonshine said, “The will lights of the Road of Emperor are not crafted by human hands, but naturally formed. Otherwise, across a span of tens of thousands of years, no one would have the ability to carve out a lifelike impression of all these peerless characters, perfectly keeping even their aura and majesty.”

“If I’m not wrong, then every peerless genius of their era who has entered the Road of Emperor will be remembered by the Road of Emperor. After they die, lights would form here as a symbol to them.

As Lin Ming heard Demonshine speak, he felt an inexplicable chill fill his heart.

The Road of Emperor… just what was it?

The force underneath the Eternal Demon Abyss that was behind the mystical curse… what was that too?

After every martial artist died, flames would light up as a symbol to them. Then, what was it that the Road of Emperor used to remember them?

A part of their will? Spiritual energy? Or maybe a soul mark?

Even a peerless existence like the Demon Emperor, a great character even within the Realm of the Gods, still couldn’t rid himself from the Road of Emperor’s memory. After he perished in the Realm of the Gods, the Road of Emperor also formed a group of lights that corresponded to him.

Like mortals that could not escape the cycle of samsara, those peerless geniuses that stepped into the Road of Emperor similarly couldn’t rid themselves of their destiny. No matter how unrivalled they were in their lives, they still returned here, ashes to ashes, dust to dust.

Lin Ming took a deep breath and clenched his fists. Regardless of what was at the end of the Road of Emperor, regardless of what was at the deepest depths of the Eternal Demon Abyss, he would not hesitate to continue forwards.

The world was large, far beyond what he could ever imagine. Even the Demon Emperor, standing before the true peak of martial artists, was probably just a minor, unworthy person.

In the past, in order to compete for the Magic Cube, he had died. This Magic Cube that had extinguished the lives of 10,000 powerhouses from the Realm of the Gods, just where had it come from also?

All of these powerful and mysterious existences did not cause Lin Ming to be crestfallen or even feel low. Instead, there was nothing in him but a limitless fighting spirit. He had already set firm his determination to step onto the highest peak of martial arts, and have a good look at what the scenery from that peak would be like.

Chapter 617 – One Light One World

“I will be more powerful in the will world than in reality?” Lin Ming asked, slightly startled. “Then what happens if I kill others in the will world? Will they die in the real world? Or would they be affected in some other way?”

Demonshine said, “If you can completely destroy someone else’s will within the world of will then they will also die in the real world!”

Lin Ming felt a chill crawl up his back as he heard this, “But I should have died just now. That bloody axe already cut me in half, but I’m not dead yet.”

Demonshine chuckled, “Hehe, this Saint said that you will only die if your will is destroyed in the will world. This Saint didn’t say that you would die if your body was cut in half in the will word. Destroying someone’s will isn’t as simple as it seems.”

“I see…” Lin Ming nodded. He had fallen into the mindset that being cut in half would kill him. But, the truth was that the world of will had a completely different set of laws that governed it. Perhaps, within the will world, being cut in half was the same as a minor wound.

Demonshine continued, “Within the will world, being split in half, beheaded, or even crushed won’t kill you. This is why there are many martial artists that when they reach a high level, such as your so-called Emperor level powerhouse, if they have confidence in their own willpower, will have matches in the world of will. In there, it’s not as easy to be injured. But of course, in a real life or death battle, they would combine the power of their will world and their actual combat strength into one whole and fight in the real world. This is also how they can use their highest degree of strength.

Every time Demonshine mentioned the Emperor level powerhouses and Emperor level talents of the Sky Spill Continent, he would usually add in something derisive before it, such as ‘so-called’. Obviously, to him, these powerhouses were nothing more than low grade minions. If they went to the higher level Realm of the Gods, they simply wouldn’t even enter Demonshine’s eyes.

“Combat in the world of will only looks at how strong or weak your willpower is – your actual combat strength is irrelevant! Within the will world, you are god. You can create and be anything you want. For instance, as long as your will is strong enough, you can create a heaven-step treasure, a saint-step treasure, a powerful summoned beast, contract beast, or if your willpower is at the very limit, you can even summon a God Beast. As long as your willpower is strong enough, you can completely sweep away all opponents even if they are several times stronger than you in reality.”

Create a saint treasure? Create a contract beast? Or even a God Beast? Lin Ming was shocked. “I can even create a God Beast? Would it really have the power of a God Beast though?”

“Within the world of will, the God Beast that you create will truly have the power of a God Beast. But, that is only limited to the will world. As this Saint has said, within that world, you are god!”

“The will is an important symbol of whether or not a high level martial artist is weak or strong. The sooner you comprehend a battle spirit, the greater its advantages will be towards your future. This is because a battle spirit, regardless of your perception, lucky chances, heart of martial arts, and other factors such as that, will often naturally grown along with your cultivation. Lin Ming, this Road of Emperor is your chance. Even if your strength doesn’t grow here, you still have to start forming the foundation for your battle spirit. When you reach a high boundary, your willpower, which is in essence your battle spirit, will be a great portion of your strength. Not just that, but at that level, it will even be an integral part of your combat style. People at that level will also respect a martial artist that has a formidable will more.”

“Mm, I’ve got it.” Lin Ming nodded. The same ability would often have different values for different people. For instance, within the Sky Fortune Kingdom, even if a landlord and merchant had the same amount of wealth, a landlord’s status would be higher than the merchant’s. This was because land farming was considered a more legitimate business, while being a merchant was much more low class, even if they earned the same amount of money. In fact, after many merchants earned a fortune, they would often purchase large swathes of property and became local landlords, even if the profits from these properties were far lower.

“Lin Ming, continue on. If you can use this Road of Emperor to thoroughly temper your will, then it will have a profound influence on your future growth. Don’t miss out on this chance!”

“I will!”

Lin Ming was overjoyed that he met Demonshine from the Magic Cube’s space. With his guidance it was much easier to see the path before him.

Otherwise, if he came to the Road of Emperor and used increasing his strength as the only goal, he would have missed this rare chance.

Continuing along the Road of Emperor, the will lights that appeared were from quasi Emperors, they burnt even more vividly than before.

As Lin Ming stepped forwards, a light flashed, and he once again appeared in the world of will.

“Hahahaha!”

Laughter echoed in Lin Ming’s ear like a thunderclap. This was a voice that came from this world of will. The more powerful the willpower was, the more heaven-shaking and earth-shattering the voices would be.

Kacha!

Between heaven and earth, a massive thunderbolt crashed into the ground. A Goliath martial artist with a full head of red hair grasped a halberd and rushed towards Lin Ming.

“Concept of Thunder?”

Lin Ming was surprised to discover that even in the world of will, there were still manifestations of Laws.

With the Concept of Thunder combined with this strange halberd skill, this quasi Emperor level powerhouse’s attack was certainly strong, it was just that its speed was slow.

It was obvious that the will that this quasi Emperor powerhouse left behind was very slow. Perhaps it was because it had been worn down through the long passage of time, or perhaps it was because the amount of will left behind in the light wasn’t much to begin with, otherwise, the momentum of this quasi Emperor powerhouse’s attack would be much more than this.

Lin Ming directly faced this Goliath powerhouse’s halberd. He did not dodge, only thrusting his spear out. This was because he knew that with his current speed, dodging was impossible.

Puff! Puff!

Two bursts of blood shot out like a rain shower. In the world of will, having his body pierced through was a horrific pain as if his soul was being shredded to pieces.

Lin Ming originally wasn’t a match for this quasi-Emperor’s will. However, the strength of this quasi-Emperor’s will wasn’t able to sustain itself; every time a bit of this strength was consumed, it would be gone. But as for Lin Ming, his will actually grew without end.

This was his greatest advantage.

After a harrowing and violent battle, Lin Ming successfully destroyed the Goliath quasi Emperor powerhouse.

Ho–

The corresponding will light was extinguished, and Lin Ming was ejected from the world of will.

“I can actually comprehend a great number of things from these seniors’ martial arts skills!”

Aside from tempering his will, when that quasi Emperor attacked just now, the moves that contained the Concept of Thunder gave Lin Ming some inspirations.

Because the will that this quasi Emperor had left behind was already very weak, the attacks were slow and the striking power was also low. This way, the mysteries within those attacks were much more clearly seen and easier to understand.

“If I’m not wrong, then most of the young heroic elites that enter the Road of Emperor probably use the majority of their energy to study their opponents’ moves and Concepts.

“Even Yan Chi and Maha, as Imps who are proficient in soul force, probably also tried to comprehend these Concepts and moves. It’s just that at the same time they were probably trying to figure out how to capture some of this Emperor Will for their own use. But, no matter how much Emperor Will they captured, in the end it wasn’t theirs, so it had no capacity for growth.”

The moves and Concepts of quasi Emperor and Emperor level powerhouses were no doubt valuable. But compared to tempering the will and forming a battle spirit, they were far less important. It was simply incomparable.

However, one couldn’t blame Yan Chi and Maha for being short-sighted. Their own willpower was limited, so the chances of them ever forming their own battle spirit was far too distant a goal. Normally in the Holy Demon Continent, a martial artist would form their own battle spirit around the time they became a Peerless Emperor. As for Yan Chi and Maha, the two of them only had a cultivation of a one and two star Demon King.

In addition, Yan Chi and Maha were only from relatively normal sect backgrounds. These sects had never produced an Emperor level powerhouse, so the knowledge and legacies they had of battle spirits was literally nothing at all. Yan Chi and Maha simply didn’t know the method to form a battle spirit, nor did they understand their importance.

Lin Ming carefully recalled the attacks of that Supreme Elder from just now, and after perceiving some insights, he decisively moved on to the next battle spirit light.

Compared to the last flame, this one was far too bright. It was extremely radiant and dazzling, like a smaller, darker, sun.

Lin Ming’s mind moved. His eyes locked onto the relief below the lights, and he saw that indeed, this will was left behind by a true Emperor level powerhouse that had died!

“Gu Xiao, Giant Demon. She walked the world 6000 years ago. She became a Demon Emperor at 109 years of age, and perished at 130 years of age. When she died, her cultivation was a one-star Demon Emperor.” Information about Gu Xiao appeared in Lin Ming’s mind.

Without a doubt, if this Gu Xiao could become a Demon Emperor then she was an Emperor level talent. However, after becoming a Demon Emperor, she was only the most ordinary of Demon Emperors. All those able to become Demon Emperors were Emperor level talents. Wanting to stand out in this crowd of monstrous geniuses was extremely difficult!

Gu Xiao had become a Demon Emperor at 109 years of age – this achievement wasn’t early. In fact, her talent was much worse than Xiao Yu and Gu Yu’s from before. Those two had earned the glory of becoming Titled Asuras. If they hadn’t died at such a young age, they definitely would have become existences capable of jumping ranks to fight even after becoming Emperor level powerhouses.

Lin Ming took a deep breath and adjusted himself to his peak state. What he was about to face was a true Emperor level powerhouse. Even if this person was the most ordinary of Emperor level powerhouses, they were still an existence he couldn’t even compare to. He naturally had to be extremely sincere in this battle.

Stepping into the range of Gu Xiao’s will lights, Lin Ming only felt as if he had crossed a space barrier, arriving at a completely different dimension.

One light, one world. The will of a true Emperor level powerhouse was enough to manifest their own world.

When Lin Ming’s will entered this world, he felt like a mortal that had been dropped naked into a field of winter snow. This kind of chilling cold was enough to freeze his marrow.

A thick killing intent suddenly filled the air. With a rustling sound, a massive python suddenly appeared out of thin air and killed its way towards Lin Ming.

“A transformation?”

Lin Ming recalled that Demonshine said that within the world of will, a martial artist was god. They could turn their will into different forms in order to kill their enemies.

This massive python in front of him was most likely the transformed shape of the Emperor Will.

This python was over 100 feet long and its body was as thick as Lin Ming’s waist. It opened its massive jaws and bit towards Lin Ming. Its speed was much quicker than the last several martial artists’!

With Lin Ming’s speed, it was impossible for him to dodge this bite. He fiercely grit his teeth and thrust the Purple Comet Spear into the python’s open mouth!

Bringing with it the Concept of Thunder, the Purple Comet Spear was like a bolt of lightning that shot into the python’s upper jaw. Blood sprayed out, but that python also bit down on Lin Ming.

Bang!

The earth was cracked apart as the python’s giant head crashed into it, and Lin Ming was swallowed into the python’s stomach.

“Lin Ming, you are not a match for this Emperor Will. Immediately withdraw!” Demonshine’s voice sounded out in Lin Ming’s mind.

Chapter 622 – Forming a Battle Spirit

“This is the 21st stone tablet. I’ve stayed here for a full month and 10 days and only just managed to break past it…”

Recalling the experience of these last 40 days, Duanmu Qun felt a lingering fear. These stone tablets were not as simple as they seemed. Once anyone touched upon them with their perception, they would have to withstand the terrifying impact force from the stone tablets. Let alone comprehending the mysteries within these stone tablets, touching their perception on these stone tablets could grievously injure them!

Walking all the way down, of the 20 stone tablets he had passed through earlier, the pressure would increase with every one. The first 10 stone tablets weren’t anything, he had easily passed those. For the 10 after that, the difficult had risen by a great margin, but Duanmu Qun had still been able to just barely cope with that.

After the 20th, the 21st stone tablet was the true terror. Duanmu Qun had spent a total of 40 days on this single stone tablet alone.

Persisting until he had broken this last stone tablet, it was already the limit that Duanmu Qun could withstand.

As he looked at all the Emperor stone tablets that lay in front of him, Duanmu Qun could only sigh in frustration. The disparity was just too great!

Just the 21st stone tablet had caused him to exhaust every last ounce of his potential. The difficulty of those stone tablets ahead could be imagined.

Actually, Duanmu Qun didn’t even know how many stone tablets were in front of him.

The Road of Emperor. After completing this road, one would become a Peerless Emperor.

This was certainly not a lie!

Moreover, those Emperor level powerhouses that were born from the Road of Emperor were surely not the ordinary kind, but those existences that peered down from the very pinnacle of strength!

“There’s no limit in this world; no matter how strong you are, there is always someone higher. I thought that my talent far surpassed every other heroic young elite of the Blood Slaughter Steppes, but I never that I would be pressured by a mere Lin Ming. If I was compared to those talents from ancient times, I would be even more pathetic!” Duanmu Qun shook his head in self-deprecation. This Road of Emperor was most likely constructed for those young talents of ancient times to gain experience. What he had seen was only the tip of the iceberg, and yet he had reached his limits. Just how strong could those young heroic elites of ancient times have been?

“I should leave now. After being in the Road of Emperor for 160 days, the increase of my strength has been immense. I wonder how I did compared to Lin Ming?”

Besides Lin Ming, Duanmu Qun was recognized as the number one talent of the Blood Slaughter Steppes. His background was that of the quasi sixth-grade sect, the Divine Wood Holy Land. He himself was a Fey, and his understandings of Laws had reached an extremely high degree. His perception was incomparably monstrous, and with his young age, he had already thoroughly studied his Divine Wood Holy Land’s core cultivation methods.

The Fey had a naturally superior compatibility with Laws than humans, and in addition to being personally directed and taught by the three-star Fey Emperor, the Highest Elder of the Divine Wood Holy Land, Duanmu Qun’s attainments in the Concepts of Space and Time were very high. In terms of the Concepts of Water and Wood, he was also satisfactory. In the comprehension of Concepts, he was confident that he wouldn’t lost to anyone.

Duanmu Qun thought that even if his overall talents were inferior to Lin Ming’s, that didn’t mean he was weaker. After all, he was a bit older.

Moreover, ignoring other aspects of talent, just in terms of the comprehension of Laws, Duanmu Qun felt he was above Lin Ming.

And in this Road of Emperor, it specifically tested one’s perception and comprehension of Laws. The stronger one was in these aspects, the more truths and mysteries they would be able to grasp from these Emperor stone tablets.

Towards the 21st stone tablet, even with Duanmu Qun’s understanding of Laws and Concepts, he had already exhausted everything he had. He very much wanted to know just how far Lin Ming had gone.

“Lin Ming, I wonder which stone tablet you’ve managed to reach? If you haven’t reached 20, then I will truly be disappointed… after leaving Skysplit Tower, I will be looking forwards to a match with you!” Duanmu Qun thought aloud, his eyes flashing with a vivid fighting spirit.

The average person would have thought that it was sad to be born in the same era as a monstrous genius, but Duanmu Qun didn’t think so. If he sat alone on the highest peak with nothing but his own desolate solitude, then that would only be an immeasurably chilly position, and he would be doing nothing more than wasting his own potential. On the other hand, if he had a rival, then both of them could try to surpass the other and they could both make great strides of progress beside each other.

This was the self-confidence that belonged to a true top talent.

After being in the Road of Emperor for 161 days, Duanmu Qun finally left!

Duanmu Qun’s exit caused a great stir within Heavenly Cloud Tower. Even the nearby Skysplit Towers were made aware of this news.

A rumor was passed on that after Duanmu Qun left the Road of Emperor, his every action would cause the power of space around him to be restlessly aroused.

This was an extremely high boundary that would only occur when one’s understandings of Laws reached a terrifying level. Like an order being followed once given, this was a similar truth. Duanmu Qun was far away from reaching this sort of boundary, but it was still enough to scare everyone.

The current Duanmu Qun gave off an unfathomably deep feeling.

At this point, of all the geniuses that had entered the Road of Emperor, the only one that hadn’t yet come out was Lin Ming. This made everyone especially want to know just what sorts of improvements Lin Ming had made within the Road of Emperor.

……………………

In the world of will, a dazzling flame flashed past. Lin Ming had become one with his spear, and he was like a meteor as he passed through the will body of an Emperor level powerhouse.

Bang!

The will body shattered into pieces, becoming countless streams of light that slowly flowed into Lin Ming;’s body. A feeling like a spring breeze spread to every corner of Lin Ming’s body.

“I’ve been in the Road of Emperor for five months and finally managed to adapt to the suppression of the Prime Emperor martial intent!”

Lin Ming withdrew from the world of will and swallowed a soul recovery pill.

At this time, all of the top-grade soul recovery pills had been eaten by him. Now whenever he withdrew from the world of will he could only take medium-grade and high-grade soul recovery pills to revitalize his soul. Luckily, every time that he destroyed the will body of an Emperor level powerhouse, a wisp of their will would remain and flow into him, a pure power of soul that was able to repair the damage done to his will body. Otherwise, there would probably have been hidden wounds left behind in Lin Ming’s spiritual sea already.

Looking at the endless will lights that extended to the far distance in front of him, Lin Ming took out a top-grade Blood Demon Crystal and began to meditate again.

For five months, he had spent this entire time fighting.

He had to regularly suffer the soul-tearing pain of having his will body ruined. This sort of excruciating pain was even more insufferable than physical bodily pain, much less that he had endured it for five months so far.

“These past days, I still haven’t been able to form my own battle spirit, but because I’ve been using so many top-grade Blood Demon Crystals, my cultivation has risen to a half-step Revolving Core.”

Because Lin Ming’s foundation was completely solid, he almost wouldn’t have a bottleneck from the Xiantian realm to Revolving Core realm. Moreover, top-grade Blood Demon Crystals were originally excellent for making breakthroughs through bottlenecks, so his cultivation had constantly been rising throughout this time.

As for his battle spirit, he still hadn’t formed one, but Lin Ming could feel a dim and hazy mist gathering above his spiritual sea. This was pure willpower. Every time his willpower increased through battle, this mist would become richer and thicker.

After another 40-some days passed, Lin Ming had already been in the Road of Emperor for an entire 200 days.

During these 200 days, the pressure of the Prime Emperor force field constantly grew heavier, but the growth of Lin Ming’s willpower was even quicker. This allowed him to adapt to the massive pressure within the world of will.

The mist within his spiritual sea became increasingly thick, to the point that it nearly turned into droplets.

Cha!

A beaming bolt of lightning cut through the world of will, completely crushing an Emperor Will and turning it into the pure power of soul.

“Finally, I’ve defeated the will body of a three-star Emperor level powerhouse…”

Lin Ming fell to his knees, using the Purple Comet Spear to prop himself up. From his head to his toes, there wasn’t a single place that wasn’t a mess. His left shoulder was nearly completely ruined, his chest was stained red, blood gushing out of it, and his organs were in chaos.

If this was the real world, in this situation he would have long ago lost any and all combat strength.

Lin Ming had been fighting this three-star Emperor level powerhouse’s will body for a full 10 days, and today, he had finally defeated it.

A pure energy flowed into Lin Ming’s body, quickly repairing his broken body. This sort of restoration brought along a wonderful feeling with it. The pure power of soul was like a quiet drizzle of rain falling down on him, making him feel happy and comfortable.

Lin Ming immersed himself in this comfortable and wonderful feeling for an unknown time. Suddenly, there was a pain between his eyebrows, as if all the strength of his body was rushing to that single point, able to erupt at any moment!

“Mm… this is…”

Lin Ming’s eyes flashed open. He was surprised to find that the thick mist that hovered over his spiritual sea had suddenly contracted in upon itself!

“Could this be…” Lin Ming suddenly thought of a possibility, a faint sense of incredulity filling his heart.

“Hahaha! Boy, congratulations! You’ve succeeded!” Demonshine’s jazzy voice sounded out in Lin Ming’s mind.

“Battle spirit? Is this really a battle spirit?” Lin Ming was ecstatic with happiness. He stared with wide eye as amazing changes began happening to the thick fog within his spiritual sea. Among these changes, a faint pain of will spread through Lin Ming’s mind. However, this sort of pain only made him feel inexplicably excited.

Nothing was impossible to those that were willing to try hard enough. Lin Ming had spent almost an entire seven months, suffering massive pain to his soul to constantly temper his will and mold his battle spirit. And today, he was finally successful!

To do this, he had sacrificed his cultivation speed and didn’t hesitate to give up perceiving the Emperor stone tablets. Now, at this moment when his battle spirit formed before his eyes, Lin Ming felt that all of this sacrifice and pain was well worth it!

Part of the reason why Lin Ming could form his own battle spirit was his effort, but the majority of it was all because of his incomparably firm will and mindset.

Lin Ming’s heart of martial arts was originally extremely tough and impervious. In addition to repeatedly swallowing soul fragments from the Magic Cube and also cultivating the ‘Overbearing Soul Tactic’, not only had his willpower strengthened, but after obtaining the Samsara martial intent, this had caused a qualitative increase in Lin Ming’s willpower.

In terms of the force of his will, there was no martial artist at Lin Ming’s realm that could compare with him. Similarly, soul attacks were nothing more than a joke in front of him.

If it wasn’t for Lin Ming originally having such talent of will, then tempering his will would have been useless to begin with. In fact, constantly overdrawing the power of his will would have done nothing but damage his mind.

“This is… a battle spirit?”

As Lin Ming looked at the skies over his spiritual sea, he could see that the mist there seemed much more pale, and in the center of that swirling mist seemed to be a vague, tiny azure spear; it seemed unreal, obscure, and illusory.

This spear was as thin as a chopstick and only half a foot long. The spearhead was the size of a knuckle, and the entire shaft was azure, shining with a cold light.

“This is my battle spirit?”

This was the first time that Lin Ming had seen a battle spirit. The memories he had absorbed were very vague concerning battle spirits. As for what they looked like, he didn’t know.

Demonshine chuckled, “Hehe, that’s right. Every battle spirit has a different shape. Some people have battle spirits that are shaped like weapons they often use, for instance, spears, sabers, and swords. There are also some people who have battle spirits that are like the elements they specialize in, such as flames, ice crystals, thunder bolts, and others. There are even some specialized battle spirits, ones that look like beasts, plants, furnaces, and so on. Take good care of your battle spirit and raise it well! Your battle spirit is just like a baby right now, but even so, it is still extremely terrifying!

“You are truly an abnormal freak! You formed your own battle spirit and you haven’t even reached the Revolving Core realm yet. I have no idea just how terrifying you will be when this battle spirit grows up!”

Chapter 634 – Forming the Revolving Core

Normally, the ones that die in a squad were the weaklings. Duanmu Qun didn’t think that Lin Ming would fall here. Even if he heard this news from Lan Xin’s own mouth, he found it hard to believe.

“Hehe, it’s not that the chances of him dying were high, but his death was basically determined.” Not too far away from Lan Xin, a Fey youth smirked.

If this was just after a disaster and everyone had scattered, then it could be said that Lin Ming had gone missing. But, the situation was different. They had arranged to meet after an hour but Lin Ming still hadn’t returned. If he hadn’t died then just what could it be?

“What really happened?” Duanmu Qun asked.

The Fey youth vividly recounted the process of Lin Ming’s death, highlighting repeatedly that he had loudly discouraged him from returning, but Lin Ming had only insisted on being foolish. Finally, he had chosen the wrong method to tackle his problem and ended up never returning.

After the Fey youth spoke, Duanmu Qun frowned. A lost spatial ring? This reason seemed a bit far-fetched, but still passable. If Lin Ming had really fallen here because of this reason, then that was too great of a pity. To not be able to find a rival in his life… it was like Duanmu Qun had lost a goal in life.

Standing alone on a peak, if one didn’t see a higher peak, then it would be easy for their vision to be limited, resulting in them wasting their potential.

As they were speaking, another squad arrived. This squad only had eight people remaining. In this group were two heaven-step Asura Emperor level talents. One was Feng Shen, and the other was the Great Ax Tower’s Blackstone.

As soon as Feng Shen arrived his eyes locked onto Sada’s squad. He clearly remembered that Lin Ming was in this squad. He was curious as to just what lucky chances Lin Ming had obtained.

However, as he didn’t find Lin Ming, a bit of confusion clouded his eyes.

“There’s no need to look, Lin Ming’s gone missing!”

Duanmu Qun’s voice sounded out near Feng Shen’s ear.

The peak Emperor level talents of the Skysplit Towers were often Fey. Feng Shen also came from a Holy Land and was old acquaintances with Duanmu Qun.

“He’s missing?” Feng Shen asked, startled.

“Mm… the chances of him dying are very high…” Duanmu Qun shook his head, thinking it was too great a pity.

“Lin Ming died?” Blackstone arrived with Feng Shen, and after hearing this news, was initially surprised. But he immediately smiled with disdain. Seeing was far better than believing. These top Emperor level talents were never convinced by word of mouth unless they could see with their own eyes. Blackstone had long heard rumors about Lin Ming’s talent and genius, but he had naturally played these all down in his heart.

Blackstone originally didn’t believe Lin Ming was so great. Now that he died in the 8500 mile journey here, he had an expected and satisfied expression on his face.

He laughed and said, “I heard that Lin Ming was the greatest number one talent of the Holy Demon Continent for the least 10,000 years. But, it seems this fame was a bit cheap. To die here, heh, how mediocre!”

Feng Shen frowned as he heard this. He scowled as he said, “The facts are still unknown. According to common sense, Lin Ming should have died. However, there are always incredible and unbelievable miracles occurring  around Lin Ming!”

“Hehe, Feng Shen, I think you’ve been unnerved by Lin Ming in your heart and already have thoughts taken root in your mind  that you are inferior to Lin Ming! Once you have such thoughts, you will never surpass that person in your life!” Blackstone looked at Feng Shen with derision. When a talent loses their proud and lofty nature, their potential for growth greatly suffers.

Feng Shen didn’t speak anymore. His natural disposition was disinclined to argue with others to begin with. All he thought that was when Lin Ming entered the King’s Cage for 108 days, everyone had thought he had died, but, he had emerged at the last moment, not only alive, but with strength  that had soared shockingly, instantly proceeding to kill High Lord Heian.

This was the same as that time… could Lin Ming have really died?

Seeing Feng Shen’s silence, Duanmu Qun walked over and patted Feng Shen’s shoulder in consolation, saying, “Although Blackstone’s  words are crude, he does still have a point. The thought of being inferior to Lin Ming had truly taken root in your heart !”

Feng Shen shook his head and calmly said, “If I am inferior then I am inferior, it’s as simple as that. I never thought of surpassing Lin Ming. As long as I can keep up with his footsteps, then that is enough for me to be a leading hero of the future world.”

With nothing else to say, he went to sit on a boulder and meditate. Out of all the young geniuses present, he was the only one who had come from the same Skysplit Tower as Lin Ming.

He was the only one who had seen Lin Ming’s terrifying talent with his own eyes, his jaw-dropping speed of growth and his heaven defying strength!

When Feng Shen had seen all of this with his own eyes, he had only been able to sigh with envy and admiration!

News of Lin Ming’s disappearance quickly spread around. After all, these people hadn’t come from the same Skysplit Tower as Lin Ming so they were naturally suspicious about his rumors to begin with . After hearing that Lin Ming most likely died here, they also began to believe that this was as expected. Surely, Lin Ming was overrated.

Regardless of whether Lin Ming had truly been strong, his luck was simply too bad, or, perhaps the rumors were also exaggerated. In short, a genius that died was no longer a genius.

An Emperor sat on a throne of a million bones. No matter how brilliant or majestic Lin Ming had been before his death, after dying, he had simply become one of the countless bleached bones paving the road for others to become Emperors!

The topic of Lin Ming’s disappearance or death aroused several hours of discussion. Then, it began to die down. There were too many geniuses that died. With the passing of time, such people were destined to be forgotten in the sands of time.

The people  waited like this  for three days. Slowly, they discovered that something was wrong. At the time they first set out, besides some lone Chief High Lords, there were a total of nine squads. But now, they were one squad short! There were only eight squads left, and in these three days, there had been no sign of them.

It had to be known that the guides had special methods to communicate with each other. But now these communication methods were like stones dropped into the ocean, without the slightest response.

Had they been annihilated!?

Realizing this, everyone felt chills creep up their backs.

An entire squad of 10 people, including even an experienced guide and powerful High Lords, was actually completely annihilated. Just what sort of terrifying situation had they come across?

Was it the legendary evil spirit  from the Eternal Demon Abyss?

Thinking of this, every martial artist felt a surging cold in the air. If their squad had encountered the same things, then their fate might not have been much better!

At this point, Sada quietly stood up and said, “It’s time, we will not wait here any longer. We will return. You can consider returning with one of us eight guides back along the old route we took. But, all the resources that are found on the return trip will not be shared with you. Or, you may now enter the 1500 radius of the Eternal Demon Abyss’ edge. There, the dangers are doubled or even tripled. Even we do not dare to rashly enter, so carefully consider your choice!

After Sada finished, he glanced over the crowd. A great number of martial artists had hesitation in their eyes. After learning that an entire squad had been annihilated, this news left a lingering fear within their minds. If they entered deep within the 1500 mile radius periphery of the Eternal Demon Abyss, their team might break up. Then, not only would they need to resist the threats of those evil spirits, but they also had to defend against their own companions murdering them for their wealth. The risks could be imagined!

Thinking of this, those talents that had originally been full of confidence and wanted to rush into the 1200 mile radius of the Eternal Demon Abyss began to show signs of retreat.

They looked at each other with dread. In the face of such great lucky chances as well as such significant dangers, everyone hesitated…

……………

As all the martial artists were gathered at the meeting point 1500 miles from the Eternal Demon Abyss, Lin Ming was in the middle-late stages of breaking through to Revolving Core!

All of the energy within Lin Ming’s meridians had been poured into his dantian. True essence was constantly forming into tiny grains, slowly spinning into a true essence cyclone there. The more it spun, the closer they approached the center, finally settling at the center of the cyclone and condensing into a spinning crystal core.

This was… the Revolving Core.

The reason that the Revolving Core was called ‘revolving’ core, was because the core was always spinning.

When a martial artist was at the Houtian realm, their dantian had just opened and their true essence was in chaos. With no regulations at all, the efficiency of this true essence was naturally low. When a martial artist reached the Xiantian realm, the true essence would form a stable true essence cyclone in their dantian, increasing the efficiency by another level. However, the total amount of true essence wouldn’t increase by too much. Finally, when a martial artist arrived at the Revolving Core realm, the true essence cyclone in their dantian would condense into a revolving true essence crystal core, with their total amounts of true essence increasing by a large margin!

The spinning true essence turning into a crystal core was just like some celestial bodies of the universe turning into a rotating form.

This was the so-called similarities of the Great Dao. The human body became a miniature universe.

As another day passed, the Revolving Core in Lin Ming’s dantian was now the size of a pigeon’s egg.

Demonshine watched from the side. These days, this sleep-loving old dog had been finding it hard to stay awake as it was always carefully guarding the surroundings. As a result, it witnessed the entire process of Lin Ming attacking the Revolving Core realm.

A pigeon’s egg sized Revolving Core was a tad larger than a normal martial artists Revolving Core. Demonshine wasn’t surprised by this. In general, the more true essence a martial artist had, the larger their Revolving Core would be.

If the Revolving Core that Lin Ming formed wasn’t much larger than other martial artists, then Demonshine would have thought that something was wrong.

Another day later, Lin Ming’s Revolving Core grew yet again, this time turning into a more normal looking sphere. Now, it was around the size of a walnut. This Revolving Core was about 25% larger than a normal martial artist’s Revolving Core.

Demonshine rubbed his chins with his paws, nodding in praise.

Another day passed. The Revolving Core grew once more to the size of a wild hen’s egg. Now, Demonshine was finding it hard to remain calm. This size had exceeded his expectations!

But this wasn’t Lin Ming’s limit. After another day, the Revolving Core became the size of a chicken’s egg. Demonshine began to gulp. This was already twice the size of a normal martial artist’s Revolving Core!

“This boy, just what degree will he grow to?” Demonshine sucked in his long doggy tongue, his eyes staring unblinkingly at the true essence crystal core condensing in Lin Ming’s Dantian.

Then, the fifth day followed. The Revolving Core did not increase in size. But after that, Demonshine’s astonishment did not stop, rather, it increased.

The Revolving Core in Lin Ming’s dantian hadn’t changed in size, but the inherent true essence began to grow more concentrated. As more true essence grains fused with the Revolving Core, the energy within became increasingly rich!

On the sixth day, the Revolving Core shrunk, going back to the size of a wild hen’s egg. But, not only did the total amount of true essence not decrease, but it instead increased by another level!

At this point, Demonshine was already a bit numb.

This boy was simply a monstrous freak, an abnormally monstrous freak!

On the seventh day, the Revolving Core shrunk once again, returning to the size of a walnut. This Revolving Core wasn’t much larger than an ordinary martial artist’s, but the total true essence quantity within was many times greater than that of an ordinary martial artist’s!

Chapter 635 – The Revolving Core Changes

On the eighth day of forming the core, Lin Ming’s Revolving Core was the exact same size as an ordinary martial artist’s, except that the energy within was several times greater.

Compared to an ordinary martial artist’s Revolving Core, the Revolving Core within Lin Ming’s dantian was a much darker hue, and also spun several times faster.

Normally, the faster a Revolving Core spun, the more volatile and active the energy was within, meaning that when it erupted all at once, it would be much more terrifying.

With such a solid energy and fast spinning speed united, Lin Ming’s potential strength could be imagined!

“This boy is a damn farm animal, just what fodder was he fed growing up…” Demonshine mumbled to himself. Lin Ming’s talent was something even he was jealous of. Only by insulting Lin Ming a bit could Demonshine feel a bit better about himself.

At this time, the Revolving Core in Lin Ming’s dantian reached the finale of its condensation process. The Revolving Core no longer changed in size, instead beginning to take its final form. The surrounding energy within the dantian completely gathered onto the Revolving Core, continuously streaming onto this crystalline core.

The Revolving Core became increasingly round. When it was around 99% formed, the energy within the dantian began to suddenly accelerate!

At this time, the true essence crystal core became the incarnation of a voracious monster, completely and recklessly swallowing all of the true essence in Lin Ming’s dantian, leaving it empty of energy. This caused every single bit of true essence in Lin Ming’s body to converge into his dantian like an ocean falling into a sinkhole.

Lin Ming’s dantian became a powerful bottomless pit of suction. It set off a massive whirlpool of true essence, sweeping in all of Lin Ming’s energies.

In a mere few breaths of time,all the energy in Lin Ming’s meridians was sucked dry!

Then, this suction force spread through Lin Ming’s body. Heaven and earth origin energy was also sucked in by this powerful force, continuously gathering into Lin Ming’s dantian!

At the moment a martial artist completed their Revolving Core, it would result in a qualitative change. It would become solid, round, and filled with a deep gravitational force!

It was just like when a star of the universe collapsed into a white dwarf star or neutron star. Once it collapsed, the mass would stay the same and the size would decrease but the gravity would experience a massive leap upwards!

When the cyclone within a martial artist condensed into a Revolving Core it was also a similar process of collapsing. The instant that a Revolving Core formed, because of the intense suction, it would completely condense all energies into the dantian. Within the void of the dantian, the newly condensed crystal core would cause a massive whirlpool, sucking in all the surrounding energy and leading the total true essence amount to have a massive leap.

This sort of leap would bring doubled or even quadrupled strength. Not just that, but after the Revolving Core formed, this sort of true essence crystal core would continuously maintain this attractive force. This was the reason that a Revolving Core martial artist far surpassed a Xiantian martial artist in condensing energy towards their dantian. Whether it was cultivation speed, endurance, regenerative ability, everything would rise.

With these several reasons added together, this was the reason that a martial artist would experience a massive leap in strength from Xiantian to Revolving Core!

Thus, this was why even a Saint level talent like Mu Qianyu, when at half-step Revolving Core, still found it only barely possible to fight a true Revolving Core martial artist.

The attractive pull of Lin Ming’s true essence crystal core was far more terrifying than that of an ordinary martial artist. The true essence whirlpool increasingly intensified without any signs of stopping. It formed a massive cloud of purple heaven and earth origin energy above Lin Ming’s head. At the center of these vast clouds, a funnel-shaped tornado extended downwards, enveloping Lin Ming at the very end and steadily streaming into his dantian.

Seeing such a situation, Demonshine couldn’t even sit still anymore.

Oh heavens, this momentum was so great, it would be visible from several hundreds of miles out!!!

If Lin Ming had closed up within a place of absolute safety then no matter how great the momentum, none of it mattered. Even if he had primed heavenly tribulation to come down on his head, it would still have been fine! But, this place was different. This was the Eternal Demon Abyss, where every step was filled with killing intent and fatal dangers!

Seeing this abnormal situation last for another quarter of an hour without ending, Demonshine’s forehead began to become wet with a nervous sweat.

“Oh good friend Lin Ming, how come you haven’t finished yet? Just when the f*ck is this going to end!?”

At this time, Demonshine was on the same sinking boat as Lin Ming. Without Lin Ming, his damaged soul wouldn’t even a chance to possess or do anything at all!

Demonshine had been counting on Lin Ming ascending into great achievements in the future and being able to profit from this. If Lin Ming died here, then all his efforts would be wasted!

Anxiously, with great fear, another incense stick of time passed. Finally, Demonshine’s complexion changed.

As he expected, the worst turn of events had occurred.

Just a few thousand feet away, seven or eight evil spirits had gathered together, avariciously eyeing the direction Lin Ming was at.

………….

At this time, several hundred miles away, under a cliff, two Giant Demon martial artists and a Goliath martial artist were grouped together. The Goliath martial artist was standing guard while the two Giant Demon martial artists were sitting down in meditation. The injuries on their bodies weren’t too serious, but these injuries would have still been fatal for a common mortal. Just two hours ago, these two Giant Demon martial artist had swallowed pills and were in the process of recovering from their wounds.

“What f*cking bad luck, I can’t believe we followed an idiot guide here, and to think that the f*cker actually dared to call himself a living map of the Eternal Demon Abyss! F*ck!” After a quarter hour, the Giant Demon martial artists had finally healed their wounds and began to cuss out loud.

These three people were part of the missing ninth squad of the Blood Slaughter Steppes. Their entire squad hadn’t been fully annihilated, but rather, only the three of them had survived. The other seven, including the guide, had been completely wiped out!

“I was almost killed by that idiot! Luckily, our strength is outstanding and our luck is good, otherwise we would’ve already become that evil being’s supper!”

Remembering the experience from just several days ago, the three of them felt a lingering fear cloud their minds. That had simply been a nightmare. They didn’t know where the enemy was and all they could do was watch helplessly as their companions slowly burst into puddles of rotten meat, their blood and organs pooling on the ground.

In all fairness, the guide truly could be considered experienced and his strength was also good. But in the face of such a situation, he had made the wrong judgement. He had everyone stand back to back in a circle and stand guard, causing more and more people to die. Finally, several people couldn’t stand it anymore and separately escaped. As for the guide, he had paid for this wrong judgement with his life.

In the end, only the three of them had managed to run away.

These three were all High Lords and also the strongest three of their squad. In terms of individual strength, they could rank amongst the top five High Lords of Polaris Tower. As for the Goliath martial artist, he could even rank in the top three.

Within the Eternal Demon Abyss, every single step was filled with death and there were danger zones and deathtraps everywhere. Sometimes, a squad would experience a complete disaster and only the strongest would be able to survive.

“Brothers, what should we do now? The three of us came to the Eternal Demon Abyss, but we haven’t even had any lucky chances, instead, we’ve almost lost our lives. Should we return like this?” the Goliath High Lord asked. The two Giant Demon High Lords remained silent. Up until now, they had only found two ordinary Demon God Bones. Once divided, it wasn’t much at all. They truly were loath to return like this. But right now, they didn’t even have a guide. The three of them were like headless flies within the Eternal Demon Abyss, running around randomly was far too dangerous!

The Goliath High Lord saw the other two not speaking, and after some thought, said, “The lucky chances within the Eternal Demon Abyss are hard to find, but once they are found they might possibly be the greatest lucky chance we will ever experience. There are many different grades of Demon God Bones. The two we have are the lowest grade. If we can find an earth-step Demon God Bone or even the legendary heaven-step Demon God Bone, then our future days as Peerless Emperors will be just around the corner!”

Within Skysplit Tower, High Lords were indeed powerful, but, in terms of talent, they were actually inferior to the peak existences within the Heavenly Demon Seven Stars, much less Holy Land descendants like Feng Shen, Duanmu Qun, and Lan Xin.

Without true talent, how could they reach this level? After staying in Skysplit Tower for many years, once a High Lord reached a cultivation similar to Life Destruction, they would naturally need to leave Skysplit Tower. Thus, every few dozen years, there would be a new group of High Lords at the Blood Slaughter Steppes.

But among so many High Lords, it was exceedingly rare for any of them to become Peerless Emperors. This was because they lacked talent and potential.

Without a great lucky chance, these three had almost no hopes of becoming a Peerless Emperor.

A Life Destruction powerhouse and an Emperor level powerhouse were on completely different levels. Whether it was strength or lifespan, they were simply incomparable. The temptation of becoming a Peerless Emperor was far too great!

The two Giant Demon High Lords were also unwilling. One of them was about to speak when he was suddenly startled. Blankly gazing off into the distant sky, he could see faint purple clouds in the heavens. Even the surrounding fog had been pushed away by these purple clouds so that they were much more clear and vivid.

“Look over there? What is that?”

“Mm?” As the other two turned to look, they were also shocked speechless!

This sort of change likely meant that there was a massive lucky chance that had appeared!

Of course, this also meant that there might be a terrifying existence there, a grave and fatal danger.

Or it could even be both. Dangers following a lucky chance… that was the most likely conclusion!

“What should we do? Should we go have a look?” One of the Giant Demon Lord proposed after a moment of hesitation. He looked towards the Goliath High Lord, the strongest of their three man group.

The Goliath High Lord grit his teeth. Without a doubt, this was a gamble. But, on the road of martial arts, how could there be no dangers?

There were many people that looked belittled martial artists who had relied on lucky chances to become Supreme Elders, saying that it was only their luck that was good. But, in truth, this was simply pure envy. There were far too many lucky chances in this future, but they were nearly always accompanied with a corresponding danger. The crux was whether or not one was willing to grasp this chance, and whether or not they had the strength to take it!

If one was always timid, hesitating and waffling over every single lucky chance, that was no different than resigning oneself to a life of mediocrity! They might not even be able to reach a high stage of Life Destruction, much less become a Peerless Emperor!

“We’ll go. The three of us will go together and restrain our auras as much as possible. We will take a look at the situation, and if there’s no hope for us to deal with it, then the three of us will immediately flee. If there is even a glimmer of hope, then we’ll bet everything on this to pave our own road of Emperor!”

“Good, I’m also of the same idea!” The High Lords quickly reached a consensus. With such a lucky chance in front of them, if they didn’t even take a look then they would regret it for the rest of their lives.

These three High Lords suppressed their auras as much as possible. With a lucky chance in front of them, they wouldn’t be demure. But, they still had to be cautious as they advanced forwards at high speed!

They quickly rushed through the twisting python terrain. The swirling currents of infernal energy were broken through by them.

Within this twisting python terrain, there were a number of low-level evil spirits. To these three High Lords, as long as they weren’t evil spirits that had rushed out from the depths of the Eternal Demon Abyss after breeding for tens of thousands or even hundreds of thousands of years, then they could deal with one or two.

Like this, they slowly approached the area where Lin Ming was closed up, breaking through to Revolving Core.

But at this time, Demonshine was actually battling with several evil spirits. This battle had already been going on for a long time…

Chapter 637 – Power of the Revolving Core Realm

A battle spirit was the manifestation of a martial artist’s will. A battle spirit was invisible and without form, but it could actually be attached to anything, turning it into an incomparably sharp killing weapon. A withered leaf, with a battle spirit attached, could even cut apart a treasure. This meant that when one’s battle spirit was attached to a withered leaf, the degree of its hardness had surpassed that of a treasure.

Using the same logic, if a battle spirit could be attached to a treasure armor, then it would make that treasure armor even more solid.

But, speaking was easier than doing. After a martial artist just formed their elementary battle spirit, it was still impossible for them to freely manipulate it.

A battle spirit could easily be used for attack. This was because a battle spirit only needed to be concentrated onto certain points.

But using a battle spirit for defense was much more difficult. This was because one had to spread the battle spirit evenly over a surface.

In the moment that Lin Ming was just attacked, his battle spirit vanished from his spiritual sea, evenly spreading out over his body and merging with his skin. This caused Lin Ming’s skin to instantly become as tough as a high-grade earth-step armor. With the addition of Tempering Marrow, which made his ribs a nearly impassable fortress, both of these factors combined were able to abruptly block the Giant Demon High Lord’s hammer!

As Demonshine realized all this, he paused. Did the battle spirit in Lin Ming’s body spontaneously protect him? Or had it been under his control?

If it was under his control, did that mean that Lin Ming had awoken?

As Demonshine was rapidly thinking, the three High Lords that had sneak attacked Lin Ming all had gloomy expressions. To use the flesh and blood body to resist the attack a treasure weapon… how was this possible?

“Is there some kind of special energy on his body?” The hammer-wielding martial artist muttered. He didn’t believe that someone could use just their body to resist his attack.

“What nonsense. Watch this!”

The other Giant Demon High Lord shouted out and stepped forwards.

“Mountain Shattering Strike!”

In order to ensure a killing blow, the Giant Demon High Lord used a martial skill. If he didn’t take advantage of this time to kill Lin Ming, then once Lin Ming completed his Revolving Core, matters would become troublesome.

With an explosive banging sound, the ground underneath Lin Ming was chopped apart and the earth ruptured. But, in this turbulent flow of demon essence, Lin Ming’s body was sent flying up again, all of his clothing torn and as he dripped with blood all over!

“He didn’t die?”

The saber-wielding Giant Demon High Lord was bewildered. He had used a martial skill just now but had only managed to wound Lin Ming.

Just what in the world was this?

Lastly, as the Goliath High Lord saw this, his eyes flashed with a sharp light. His body began to emit explosive ‘ka ka ka’ sounds.

Sky Piercing Devil Arts!

This was a secret arcane skill of the Goliath race used to detonate all of the power within their body. Although this move damaged his body, with it, the Goliath High Lord could put his everything into this attack!

After the second attack had failed to kill Lin Ming, a dark and foreboding premonition filled his heart. He thought that if Lin Ming awakened now, the results would be extremely bad for all of them!

Lin Ming’s current condition was far too weird!

Demon essence was drawn from all over his body and began to flow into the Goliath High Lord’s staff. He would take this staff and directly smash it into Lin Ming’s skull!

The skull was a vital point of the human body. The Goliath High Lord didn’t believe that Lin Ming could have such a strange and mystical protection on both his chest and head. He would smash apart Lin Ming’s head like a sweet watermelon!

Wind howled. The staff contained a massive energy, twisting the space around it. With a shout, the staff came crashing down!

But in this instant, all the surrounding heaven and earth origin energy went wild. The demonic clouds of infernal energy in the sky madly funneled towards Lin Ming’s dantian. Energy flowed out like a vast and surging stormy sea, rocking the earth.

At this moment, Lin Ming’s eyes suddenly shot open, his vision like bolts of lightning shooting out!

As the Goliath High Lord saw Lin Ming’s eyes open, he was incomparably shocked. At this time, it was impossible for him to stop. With an earth-shaking bellow, all of the demon essence was revolved to the point where his meridians were about to break apart, all in order to display the highest power of this staff strike. He estimated that since Lin Ming just woke up, he wouldn’t have the time to dodge this attack.

The staff whistled as it came crashing down. By the time Lin Ming’s eyes had fully opened, the staff was a mere two feet from his forehead.

Bang!

A golden light erupted and energy surged up in massive waves. The Goliath High Lord only felt his hands shake as the arch of his palm cracked. The staff in his hand seemed to suddenly be stuck in stone, unable to move a single inch.

Looking down, he saw that the end of his staff had been firmly grasped by Lin Ming. And, underneath Lin Ming, a massive web of cracks extended out in the earth, reaching out to over a thousand feet, deep fissures in the ground.

This web of cracks was obviously created from a great impact force. But, Lin Ming had withstood this crushing shock without his arm even bending.

“This… this…!”

The Goliath High Lord looked at the end of his staff that was held in Lin Ming’s right hand, his lips shaking. His strike that had contained his complete strength was actually received by the unarmed Lin Ming?

This staff strike was enough to shatter apart a great mountain!

“Lin Ming… you… ” The Goliath martial artist’s voice shook. The power of the Lin Ming in front of him had exceeded his scope of understanding.

At this time, a thick killing intent spread out from Lin Ming’s body. Naturally, the Asura force field had also expanded. With the Goliath High Lord’s strength, facing this force field, even he felt as if resistance was impossible!

Run!

The Goliath High Lord didn’t know what sort of lucky chance Lin Ming had come across, but, without a doubt, the truth was that he had no ability to resist the Lin Ming presently in front of him!

Without a single word more, he turned around and fled. He didn’t bother trying to take back the treasure staff. He knew with absolute clarity that it was impossible for him to take back this staff from Lin Ming’s hand!

The other two High Lords were not stupid. Seeing the Goliath High Lord run, they also turned around to escape. Not just that, but they both chose different directions.

Lin Ming sneered. He reached out his hand to grasp the void.

Cage of Space and Time!

The three High Lords felt as if they had suddenly slowed down, the space around them becoming incomparably thick. It was like they had fallen into a thick bog; there was simply no way to escape.

Lin Ming’s cage of space and time was far inferior to that within the King’s Cage. It couldn’t truly lock in someone; it could only slow down their movements. But, this was enough!

Lin Ming’s feet moved and his body exploded forwards. He didn’t take out the Purple Comet Spear, only using the staff in his hand. Using this staff as a spear, he thrust it towards the Goliath High Lord!

“Ahhhh!”

The Goliath High Lord howled like a crazed mad man. He took out another staff from his spatial ring and pounded it towards Lin Ming.

This was a strike that was completely offensive without the least bit of defense. The Goliath High Lord was well aware that he was not Lin Ming’s match. Before he died, he would either grievously wound Lin Ming or force him to defend.

However, his plan was destined to fail.

In the moment that the Goliath High Lord attacked, he felt the time around him suddenly slow to a ridiculous rate. As his staff was only half way out, Lin Ming’s staff had already stabbed to his chest.

With the battle spirit fused with the staff, there was only a light piercing sound like a chopstick poking into paper. That staff, without any impediment, pierced through the Goliath High Lord’s protective demon essence, continuing to pass straight through his body as if he were made of tofu.

The Goliath High Lord only felt a cold feeling in his chest and an emptiness in his soul. As he looked in front of him, Lin Ming had already disappeared. Turning his head down, all he saw was an arm-thick hole gouging directly through him!

Because the speed was too quick, blood hadn’t begun to gush out yet…

To instantly kill the Goliath High Lord, this was simply nothing to the current Lin Ming!

Lin Ming suddenly changed directions. The space under his feet seemed to shrink, and with just a few steps, he had caught up to one of the Giant Demon High Lords.

The Giant Demon High Lord was already horrified, panic etched all over his face As he saw Lin Ming suddenly appear before him, his complexion completely paled. He simply couldn’t organize a decent counterattack. In truth, it would have been futile regardless. His attack speed was simply pathetic.

With a flash of black light, Lin Ming’s staff had already pierced through the Giant Demon martial artist’s throat. Because the speed was too quick, the Giant Demon martial artist’s neck had been severed at the same time, his head falling off!

As Lin Ming withdrew his staff, the head flew into the air!

Next, as the last High Lord saw his companion miserably die without even being able to put up an iota of resistance, despair filled his heart. When Lin Ming rushed towards him, he died without any surprise.

As the staff was thrust into that martial artist’s back, in that instant, his spine and organs were all twisted to pulp!

From the time that Lin Ming had intercepted the staff, it had only taken him three breaths of time to kill three High Lords!

To Lin Ming, as he was now, a martial artist on the level of a High Lord simply had no ability to resist him. It was as easy as chopping a chicken!

Initially, when Lin Ming had been in the Road of Emperor, he hadn’t made a breakthrough in his cultivation. But, he had comprehended a battle spirit. Because of this, in truth, his strength had actually surpassed that of a High Lord. It was just that he was still inferior to the Tower Master.

Now that Lin Ming had broken through to Revolving Core, his strength had enhanced several times over. Now, killing a High Lord level martial artist only needed a brief moment.

After he killed three High Lords, Lin Ming felt the thick killing intent in his body begin to gradually fade away.

At this moment, a thick infernal energy dispersed outwards above the corpses of the three High Lords, forming into a ten-winged Heavenly Demon that clawed at him.

To the current Lin Ming, these kinds of Heavenly Demons formed from infernal energy were just a joke.

With a flick of three fingers, he attached a wisp of battle spirit to the air, instantly defeating the three Heavenly Demons.

After the Heavenly Demons exploded, they turned into pure infernal energy, quickly gathering into Lin Ming’s body and helping to form his Heavenly Demon Tattoo.

The fifth pair of wings became increasingly clear. Lin Ming had originally been an early ten-winged Heavenly demon, but now after killing three High Lords, two of which were early ten-winged Heavenly Demons and one a middle ten-winged Heavenly Demon, his own Heavenly Demon Tattoo had grown, stepping into the middle ten-winged Heavenly Demon stage.

As Lin Ming saw his Heavenly Demon Tattoo grow once more, his eyes sparkled. “I’m getting closer and closer to a twelve-winged Heavenly Demon, If it’s possible, I should try to condense my twelve-winged Heavenly Demon Tattoo here in the Eternal Demon Abyss. This will be my best chance to do so!”

The Heavenly Demon martial intent consisted of three different force fields – Asura, Death God, and Prime Emperor. As for the Prime Emperor force field, Lin Ming didn’t think much of that. With his current strength, it was basically impossible for him to fully cross the Road of Emperor.

As for the Asura force field, Lin Ming had already obtained it.

Now, the only force field he could comprehend was the Death God force field. After forming a full twelve-winged Heavenly Demon Tattoo, it would be his!

Quietly, he picked up the three High Lords’ spatial rings. As he was about to probe them, he heard Demonshine’s voice in his head.

“Lin Ming, you are simply a vicious beast in human form. You’ve left me speechless!”

Chapter 639 – Living Sacrifice

The seven man squad had already been searching through this blood-red land for an hour. High Lord Sandlight seemed to be very patient, but some of the newcomers were intolerably impatient. With such a great lucky chance in front of them, they were all excited.

“Mm? What’s that?”

A Giant Demon martial artist saw that not too far away there was a bump of dirt in the ground, as if there was a grave mound there. Normally, this sort of mound wasn’t anything strange, but the Giant Demon martial artist could feel a rich and sleepless energy moving about there.

This energy caused the Giant Demon martial artist to pause. What was under that mound? Could it be the earth-step Demon God Bone that High Lord Sandlight mentioned?

After thinking of this, the Giant Demon martial artist’s heart began to race within his chest. Looking all around, he determined that no one was paying attention to him and he began to slowly tiptoe over to the mound.

This blood-red island was several dozen miles wide. The squad had split up to each seek their own lucky chances. If one of them found the treasure alone, then they certainly wouldn’t share it.

The Giant Demon martial artist also had this idea. He raised his guard as he slowly approached the mound. As he closed in, he could feel the energy becoming increasingly rich.

“There really is something buried here.”

He thought for a moment about how to dig out this mound. Using his hands would be a bit improper, so he brought out a halberd from his spatial ring; using this halberd to dig would be much safer. But at the moment he extracted the halberd, his body suddenly shook. His eyes burst open and all the flesh of his body was instantly charred black, his body turning to ash in the next moment. All of his blood vitality had turned into a deep red wisp of light that shot into the mound!

A gentle breeze blew past and the ashes of the Giant Demon martial artist scattered into the wind. From beginning to end, the Giant Demon martial artist hadn’t even said a word.

The squad continued to search. Another hour later, some people began to discover that something was strange.

A few people had vanished into thin air!

“Stop, stop everything!” A martial artist cried out. He didn’t dare to shout loudly but used a true essence sound transmission instead. “I feel that… there are a lot less people!”

After the martial artists of the squad heard this, they gathered together. As they met up, they sucked in a breath of cold air. Three of them had disappeared and they hadn’t even noticed!

“Where did they go?”

The martial artists present fell a bone freezing cold in the air. They didn’t believe that these three had quietly left the squad. The greatest probably was that all three of them had been killed!

The three of them were all strong High Lords, but they had been killed so quietly. There hadn’t even been a sound! This was far too horrifying!

“We must leave immediately!”

A High Lord from the Great Ax Tower said, his face paling. Although a lucky chance was tempting, they still hadn’t found anything for such a long time and three people had already died, quietly and without their notice. If this continued, then just how many more of them would die?

Moreover, they hadn’t even been able to see this enemy. Those that died must have instantly died. The difference in strength was too great!

Even with a lucky chance in front of them, continuing to struggle for it when they didn’t even have the strength to obtain it was just the actions of a fool.

“Let’s get out of here.”

A Heavenly Demon Seven Star from White Stone Tower concurred.

“You want to retreat? We’re about to find it soon, so why would we retreat? If we leave now, then all of our efforts would be wasted.” High Lord Sandlight shook his head as he spoke.

“I agree. There are already some clues appearing. As people that entered the Eternal Demon Abyss, we should already be prepared to die. How can there not be dangers on the road of martial arts?”

A High Lord echoed. His name was High Lord Sky Eye. Like High Lord Sandlight, he too came from Five Color Tower.

After hearing that High Lord Sandlight and High Lord Sky Eye wanted to stay, the two previously speaking martial artists glared at them as if they were crazy.

“If you want to stay so badly then I won’t stop you. Let’s go!” The High Lord from Great Ax Tower said, raising his foot to leave.

High Lord Sandlight shook his head, “How unfortunate. If you stayed, then we might have been able to find it in another hour. Now, it seems that…”

As High Lord Sandlight spoke to here, his eyes suddenly flashed with a thick killing intent. Demon essence erupted from his body!

“Die!”

He drew out a saber from his spatial ring and slashed down at the leaving High Lord’s back!

A sharp saber light cut through space; wind howled!

This High Lord from Great Ax Tower was not some common martial artist. Although he was slightly worse than High Lord Sandlight, it wasn’t by much. Within the Eternal Demon Abyss, he had kept absolute vigilance of his surroundings, not even relaxing if his so-called squad was guarding him. Towards those cruel individuals that walked the killing road, having someone aim at their back was a completely normal matter!

The Great Ax Tower High Lord’s eyes flashed with an angry light. He suddenly swiveled around, and a sword jumped into his hand as if it were alive, cutting out!

Bang!

Demon essence violently collided. The Great Ax Tower High Lord gave a stuffy cough and drew back. After all, he had to quickly counterattack and his strength was also weaker. With this sword strike, he had suffered a loss. But, it was only a loss – he hadn’t been injured.

As he retreated several dozen few, the Great Ax Tower High Lord’s eyes were blood red as he said, “Sandlight, do you want to die!?”

“Hehe…” High Lord Sandlight sneered. Then, he actually put away his saber, as if he didn’t want to continue fighting.

“You…” The Great Ax Tower wasn’t willing to forgive this insult. With anger rising in his heart, he was about to take a step forwards and attack again, when at this moment, he quietly groaned and his body shook. Under everyone’s eyes, his entire body disintegrated into nothing, all of the blood in his body evaporating into a mist even as the rest of him turned into flying ash. All of his blood vitality was turned into a wisp of red light that flowed into a mound on the ground.

This sudden change stunned the youth from the White Stone Tower. A chill crept up his back. However, he didn’t have time to figure out how the Great Ax Tower High Lord had instantly died. All he was thinking was that he was in grave danger. Whether it was the two High Lords from Five Color Tower or this danger zone, everything here was a deathtrap waiting to kill him!

Without saying anything further, the youth from White Stone Tower turned around and fled!

“Where do you think you’re going?”

Beside the youth, the other martial artist from Five Color Tower, High Lord Sky Eye, was already attacking!

A spear thrust forth, straight towards the youth’s back!

At the same time, High Lord Sandlight also attacked. His saber cut off the White Stone Tower youth’s escape routes!

In terms of strength, this youth from White Stone Tower was only a Heavenly Demon Seven; he simply wasn’t a match for any High Lord, much less a pincer attack!

Only able to face one, the White Stone Tower youth blocked High Lord Sky Eye’s attack, but the burst of demon essence from High Lord Sandlight swept over him, causing him to vomit blood, severely wounded.

“Hehe, be relieved that you will be honored as my living sacrifice!”

High Lord Sandlight cut down with his saber, combining his attack with High Lord Sky Eye. In an instant, the White Stone Tower youth’s bodily true essence protection shattered and an arm was bloodily chopped off.

The White Stone Tower youth miserably shrieked. High Lord Sandlight chuckled, stepped towards the White Stone Tower youth and slammed his palm forwards.

Bang!

The youth was easily struck by High Lord Sandlight, sent flying into that mound.

Then, without even a moan, all of the youth’s blood dried up, turning into a stream of light that submerged into the mound.

“Shit… just missing a bit more!”

High Lord Sandlight shook his head regretfully, but High Lord Sky Eye only laughed and said, “It doesn’t matter. Although we’re missing some blood essence… some other prey just delivered themselves to our door. Hahaha, this fool, instead of walking the path to heaven he chose to break into hell!”

High Lord Sky Eye turned his head towards a direction in the void and perniciously said, “This friend, you’ve already been watching for so long, come out so we can see you!”

Without any response from the empty void, High Lord Sky Eye sneered and said, “Don’t think I’m just bluffing. I am called High Lord Sky Eye because my eyes can see through the nothingness like the eyes of heaven! In front of me, any illusion of camouflage you try is useless! Be a good boy and come out to die, or I’ll attack you all the same!”

As High Lord Sky Eye spoke, he lifted his spear and pointed it towards a direction in the void.

At this moment, space warped, as if it were being torn apart. A blue-clothed youth stepped out. His hands were empty, his eyes were calm, and he looked as if he were taking a brisk walk in the spring.

This youth was Lin Ming.

In the moment that space twisted, High Lord Sky Eye’s complexion changed. It was true that his eyes were special and he could sense fluctuations of life in his surroundings. To say that he had the eyes of heaven was an exaggeration. He could find Lin Ming’s hidden position, but he didn’t know just how Lin Ming had hidden.

Originally, he had thought that Lin Ming was using some strange stealth symbol or miniature array, but he never guessed that Lin Ming would hide in the distortions of space.

To use space to hide, the method of highest skill was to rip apart space and hide in the space crack, isolating all energy and atmosphere away. But, within the Sky Spill Continent, this was a nearly legendary skill. Even the Eightfall War Emperor might not have the ability to do this.

The method that Lin Ming used was to warp the space around him, making the light curve around his body, smoothly passing over him thus hiding himself. This was an extremely skillful stealth technique. It also required a very high comprehension into the Concept of Space.

High Lord Sky Eye immediately realized that he might have run into a troublesome fellow.

But, when Lin Ming stepped out of the distorted space and High Lord Sky Eye saw just who he was, his complexion completely changed. “You are… Lin Ming!?”

High Lord Sandlight was also greatly shocked, “Lin Ming, you are still alive!?”

When the squads had all gathered at the meeting area 1500 miles from the edge of the Eternal Demon Abyss, news had already spread that Lin Ming had gone missing. No one knew just where he went, but, according to the analysis of the events, the greatest probability was that he had perished!

High Lord Sandlight would never have imagined that he would encounter Lin Ming here!

He had gone missing for a full half month and then, by himself, had crossed thousands of miles towards the Eternal Demon Abyss and had finally reached the very edge of the fatal forbidden death zone. How had he done this? What had he experienced during this time?

As High Lord Sandlight was thinking about all this, he was suddenly bewildered, “You… you broke through to the Revolving Core realm!”

High Lord Sandlight had just noticed Lin Ming’s cultivation. He was at the early Revolving Core realm!

Before entering the Eternal Demon Abyss, Lin Ming had only been at a half-step Revolving Core. According to all common sense, he would need at least another half year to make a breakthrough. But, Lin Ming had actually only used a single month to make his breakthrough, and in the Eternal Demon Abyss of all places!

Combined with the news that Lin Ming had gone missing, there was only one possibility. That was… Lin Ming had stumbled across a lucky chance, and it was also a massive lucky chance!

Chapter 646 – The Yellow Springs River

If Lin Ming wanted to research and understand the situation about the enclosed space force field, he would have to walk around and slowly find out what the governing rules were.

But, there was a prerequisite. This was that he needed to be able to leave marks along the way!

When Lin Ming had placed down marks before this, they had only lasted for two incense sticks of time before being cleanly erased. That definitely wouldn’t work. After thinking for a while, Lin Ming thought of placing a trace of his battle spirit in the marks.

A martial artist’s battle spirit was a substantialized manifestation of their will. For martial artists that had strong wills, their will might last tens or even hundreds of thousands of years in perpetuity. When Lin Ming had encountered the will lights in the Road of Emperor, this was the reason they had existed until then. Even within the Eternal Demon Abyss, there might be heavenly treasures or demon bones that contained an Emperor will lasting for tens or hundreds of thousands of years.

“The first array symbol…” Lin Ming walked over to a flat area of ground and flicked his finger, shooting out a golden array symbol and condensing it into a small mark. As the mark formed, Lin Ming left a faint trace of azure energy within; this was a wisp of battle spirit.

After leaving down the mark with the battle spirit, Lin Ming didn’t leave. Instead, he say down near the array symbol and waited to see just how fast the energy would pass from it.

The other martial artists were unclear as to what was happening. Thus, a martial artist couldn’t help but ask, “Young Hero Lin, what are you doing?”

“You worthless idiot! What use is there in you asking? You wouldn’t even understand Young Hero Lin’s explanation.” Blackstone suddenly said. The truth was that he also wanted to know what Lin Ming was doing, but he feared that he would disturb Lin Ming’s thought process at this time.

Lin Ming kept total silence and quietly watched the energy leave the array symbol.

Time slowly passed, soon, it had been a quarter of an hour. The closed force field had wearing away the energy within the array symbol, but as for that azure wisp that Lin Ming had left within, it dissipated very slowly.

Lin Ming’s azure will originally had an endlessly growing quality to it. Added to the fact that his will was firm to begin with, it held together well. After a quarter of an hour passed, the energy hadn’t even been reduced by 5%.

Calculating the total time, that mark with a wisp of battle spirit should be able to support itself for around six hours.

Six hours was more than enough time.

“Boy, you’re quite smart! You strengthened that mark with your battle spirit, nice!” Demonshine’s voice echoed in Lin Ming’s mind.

“Alright, let’s continue!”

Lin Ming stood up and the other martial artists began preparing to set out. At this time, Lin Ming was in the lead.

As the group advanced forwards, he would leave behind a mark every 500 feet. The path he took was very strange. Sometime he would go forwards, sometimes he would go to the side, and sometimes he would even go backwards.

However, no matter where he walked, he never seemed to be able to leave the Eternal Demon Abyss. In front of everyone, the Eternal Demon Abyss became increasingly close, and that monstrous flame became more and more clear. It was as if they could already feel the terrible heat waves rolling off of it.

The pitch black Eternal Demon Abyss crossed through the end of the world, endless, limitless, like the maw of an ancient beast, swallowing all!

“Young… Young Hero Lin, is there really no problem?”

A martial artist couldn’t help but ask. He actually wasn’t feeling reassured at all. As he followed Lin Ming, he noticed that they were actually closing in on the Eternal Demon Abyss!

“If you have the ability then you can lead the way.” Duanmu Qun coldly said, causing the martial artist to shut up.

After walking for another several dozen miles, the Eternal Demon Abyss seemed as if it wasn’t even 200 miles away. The group could already clearly see the horrifying fog rising up from the endless gaping maw. What rose was not flames, but a flow of surging black energy. This energy was like a silent fountain, directly impacting hundreds of thousands of feet into the sky.

Lin Ming was silent for a moment, then he said, “Let’s return to our old route.”

He hadn’t been able to discover just what the strange Space Laws were yet, but he was far too close to the Eternal Demon Abyss for comfort. He didn’t dare to continue forwards anymore.

Returning to the original route wasn’t easy either. On the way here, they only needed to walk one mile forwards to go two miles towards the Eternal Demon Abyss. But, in returning, they actually had to curve left and right, taking all sorts of crazy paths just to go back a single mile.

Fortunately, Lin Ming’s battle spirit didn’t fail him. As they returned several miles back, there were still remnants of his battle spirit – they didn’t completely vanish.

As they reached the last several battle spirit marks, the will energy of the battle spirit had nearly depleted itself. This caused Lin Ming to sigh in emotion. Even with his own understandings of the power of space, in addition to Demonshine, and even his battle spirit, all three of these factors together weren’t enough to allow him to figure out just how to leave the 1000 mile forbidden zone. If he could not even find a single clue, then the difficulty that other martial artists would have could be imagined. Not to mention a Titled Asura or Tower Master, but even a high level Life Destruction powerhouse that didn’t have a good grasp of the Concept of Space might perish here!

“We’re back!”

“We really came back! Young Hero Lin truly knows the way!”

The martial artists could see the Eternal Demon Abyss blur as they walked backwards. Finally, in a single go, Lin Ming proved his skills and led them to return all the way to the 550 mile zone from the Eternal Demon Abyss where they had started.

But at this time, everyone’s hearts suddenly chilled. They didn’t know when, but the air had filled with an enchanting aroma.

If this was a nice spring day in the forests, then this fragrance would have been refreshing. But, here in the darkness of the Eternal Demon Abyss, this fragrance caused everyone’s hairs to stand on end!

As everyone abruptly looked up, they saw that the sky was raining down flower petals.

These beautiful and vivid flower petals were like angels flying in the heavens. They were completely out of place in this dreary, dark gray world.

As Lin Ming saw this, he felt a chill crawl up his back. “Demonshine, what is this?”

The jade slip that the Polaris Tower Master had given Lin Ming had very few records about what was inside the 1000 mile forbidden zone. Lin Ming had no idea just what was occurring around him.

Demonshine’s complexion suddenly changed, “This is bad! Those are brain devouring tapirs, hurry up and run away!”

A sharp light flashed in Lin Ming’s eye. He didn’t bother asking what a brain devouring tapir was, instead instantly launching his movement technique and drawing backwards, “Retreat! Don’t be touched by those petals!”

As Lin Ming spoke, a flower petal silently fell onto the head of a martial artist. The martial artist’s body shook, and with a cracking noise, blood shot out from his head!

Those weren’t flower petals! Those were thumb-sized blood-red fleshly insects! They had sharp teeth like steel thorns. With a single bite, they directly pierced through the skull!

Woosh!

The red fleshy insect drilled into the martial artist’s head like a bolt of lightning!

“Ahhhhh!!!!”

The martial artist clutched his head as he fell to his knees. Blood poured out from his head and eyes. The agonizing pain caused him to smash his head constantly into the ground. Every time he did so, thick liquid blood would gush out of the hole in his skull!

Everyone could even clearly hear the sounds of his brain being chewed upon in his skull.

Seeing this ghoulish scene, the other martial artists didn’t hesitate at all. They instantly launched their movement techniques and rushed out with Lin Ming!

At this time, the martial artists discovered that the fragrance they smelled just now had the effect of debilitating their true essence flow. With their true essence circulation hindered, their movements naturally became slower.

“Ahh!”

Another martial artist gave a miserable cry as a brain-devouring tapir started eating away at him.

The miserable cries that filled the air caused the martial artists to panic with fear. They fiercely bit down on their tongues, using the pain to wake themselves up and desperately flee this area!

Lin Ming no longer had time to lay down marks. In a single breath, he brought everyone out several dozen miles. But, at this time, he suddenly stopped in his steps. Right in front of him was a great river. This river was a dirty yellow-brown color and was over 1000 feet wide.

This wide and smoky river seemed as if it originated from the nothingness of ancient times, flowing towards unknown lands.

In the waters of the river, one could see bones floating. Of these bones, the majority of them weren’t human, but rather different races. Some had wings, some had long horns, and others had even more peculiar features.

Just by looking at this river, one could feel an inexplicable sense of bereavement and anguish fill their hearts, causing all of them to be comparably desolate.

“Yellow… the Yellow Springs River!”

At that moment, Lin Ming’s heart stopped in his chest. All of his hairs rose, and without any further words, he immediately swiveled around and ran away!

There was no need for Demonshine to tell him what the Yellow Springs River was. When he inherited the memories of the Demon Emperor’s soul fragment, it had contained a memory of this Yellow Springs River.

It was probably because the Yellow Springs River was too terrifying, thus it left a deep impression on the Demon Emperor, which was then inherited by Lin Ming.

When the Demon Emperor had come to the bank of the Yellow Springs River, he had almost died, becoming more of the countless bones of the river!

Duanmu Qun, Blackstone, High Lord Cloud Demon and the rest were all following behind Lin Ming. As they saw Lin Ming’s sudden frightened expression and hasty retreat, they followed him without a word.

However, because they were slower, the last two martial artists that caught up didn’t notice Lin Ming’s expression suddenly change. In that instant, a trace of confusion and hesitation filled their faces.

And after this slight confusion, they seemed to lose their souls. Their eyes glazed over, their limbs stiffened, and their steps became heavy.

Like zombies, they took several dazed steps forwards and then changed direction, walking towards the Yellow Springs River…

At this time, Lin Ming had already brought the remaining people several dozen miles away. As for those two martial artists that had started shambling towards the Yellow Springs Rover, they had walked into the river, going deeper and deeper within. The river water flowed over their legs, waist, belly, chest, and finally their heads.

A faint trace of blood leaked out from their bodies, mixing with the river for a moment before immediately being swallowed up. The river remained that same dirty yellow color without the least bit of red.

Under the surface of the water, the two martial artists’ bodies had already completely disappeared. There was nothing left of them but bones, as if their bodies had rotted away for endless eons.

After the two martial artists sank into the river, there wasn’t even a stir from where they were. Several breaths later, two skeletons floated upwards, adding onto the endless bones of the river and gradually drifting away…

As everyone saw this, they shivered in fear, a cold sweat streaming down their backs. Of these martial artists, which one of them wasn’t a brave and peerless heroic youths of their generation? Otherwise, there was no way they would have dared to enter Skysplit Tower. Although they didn’t fear death, that didn’t mean they couldn’t withstand such a creepy way of dying. This truly cracked the courage of even the most daring heroes!

“Brother Lin, just what is that river?” Even Duanmu Qun’s voice was shaking at this moment.

“That was the Yellow Springs River…” Lin Ming sighed. The situation was deteriorating more and more. Now, he didn’t even have full faith he could find out how to leave this 1000 mile forbidden zone…

The Yellow Springs River?

The martial artists present were petrified. This river that was depicted in the ancient legends of the Holy Demon Continent… it actually existed?

Chapter 648 – Corpse Devil

“You’ve figured out a way to leave the Eternal Demon Abyss?” Demonshine asked, startled.

“Just a general feel… I don’t know if it’s possible yet…” Lin Ming quietly said. He was continuously playing out scenarios in his mind.

Demonshine was shocked. He was very familiar with Lin Ming’s personality now. If Lin Ming said he could, then he must have around a 70 to 80% assurance that his plan would work.

The 1000 mile forbidden zone was known as a land of no return that not even birds could cross. Even a high stage Life Destruction or weak Emperor level powerhouse might die here.

But, Lin Ming was able to discover the method to leave this land…

When they had captured the demon bone together, that had mostly been relying on Demonshine’s help. But after they entered the 1000 mile forbidden zone, the truth was that Demonshine hadn’t played too great a role. Most of it had been due to Lin Ming’s own hard work and effort!

‘This boy…’

Demonshine sighed with emotion. Perhaps it wouldn’t be too long before a broken remnant soul like him would no longer be able to help Lin Ming.

After a quarter of an hour, Lin Ming had finished deducing the scenarios in his mind. He stood up and said to the group, “Follow me.”

With Lin Ming’s words, everyone quickly stood up. Although they had placed all their hopes on Lin Ming, they still didn’t have much confidence they would be able to make it out of here.

This entire time, they had always been going deeper and deeper into the Eternal Demon Abyss. The closer they got to the center, the faster they were sucked in. It was like there was some invisible gravitational force that was constantly sucking them in.

Demonshine had said that the Eternal Demon Abyss was like a black hole. The closer one was, the greater the attractive force was and the more distorted space became. Wanting to come back out was extremely difficult.

But, Lin Ming had found that he had been caught in a trap of his own misunderstanding. He had thought that to come out of this twisted space maze, he would have to look for an exit.

However, this space maze was extremely complex with countless twist and turns. There were even some crisscrossing paths that were 100 to 200 miles away from the Eternal Demon Abyss. If he had to pass through these then he would have to approach to 100 miles away from the Eternal Demon Abyss, which was undoubtedly very dangerous.

Moreover, there were innumerable danger zones in this 1000 mile forbidden zone. If they encountered some danger and were forced to run away, then all their efforts would have been for naught.

In this sort of situation, Lin Ming felt as if he had walked into a dead end. But then, that great ancient beast had suddenly appeared, giving Lin Ming a groundbreaking inspiration.

When that great ancient beast had let out a deep roar into the skies, the powerful shockwave had surged outwards and destroyed the surrounding space maze!

Then, when the great ancient beast had unfolded its vast wings, the following terrifying storm that swept out had again shattered the space maze, directly blowing them out 1000 feet. This 1000 foot distance was towards the outside of the Eternal Demon Abyss!

In other words, they were blown 1000 feet away from the Eternal Demon Abyss.

As this happened, it was like a light lit up in Lin Ming’s mind. The distorted space here could change the walking direction of the weak, but it could not change that violent and tyrannical shockwave and energy storm from the great ancient beast. The reason for this was because they were far too strong!

If he could be like the great ancient beast and destroy the surrounding space maze, then leaving this place would be much simpler.

Shattering the space here was a madman’s idea. If it were several months ago, Lin Ming wouldn’t have believed he could accomplish this. But now that he had broken through to Revolving Core and his battle spirit had also reached the bronze stage, his striking power was incomparable to how it used to be.

A battle spirit had a colossal effect on striking power. In just this aspect alone, Lin Ming had already surpassed a second stage Life Destruction powerhouse.

Initially, Xuan Wuji and others had cut open a space channel in a broken world. Now, he too should have this ability. Well, at least he should be able to change the curved space at a weak point of this space maze.

Now, the reason that Lin Ming was walking was to look for this weak point in space.

Blackstone closely followed behind Lin Ming. Uneasily, he asked, “Young Hero Lin, how come you didn’t place down an array symbol mark this time?”

Without a mark, how would they return? Blackstone simply didn’t have any sense of security here at all.

Duanmu Qun and the others didn’t understand either. But what they knew was that Lin Ming had his reasons for doing this. They didn’t understand the strange and mysterious principles of this 1000 mile forbidden zone, so there was no reason to ask.

“There’s no need to.”

Lin Ming responded simply without explaining. In fact, leaving battle spirit marks meant that he would have to lose some willpower. One mark was not much, but hundreds of them added together would exhaust him. Right now, Lin Ming had to ensure that his striking power and battle spirit would be at their strongest state.

Blackstone noticed Lin Ming’s silence and tactfully didn’t ask any further. All he could do was follow Lin Ming, his heart anxious the entire time.

After walking for a quarter of an hour, Lin Ming finally found the first weak point in space.

As long as he could destroy this distorted space in front of him, he would be able to leave this level of the space maze and go into the next. It would save him a great amount of time and effort.

Lin Ming closed his eyes.

The Heretical God Force opened.

He revolved the true essence within his body to the limit.

Penetrating Rainbow!

With the battle spirit fused to his Purple Comet Spear, Lin Ming thrust out!

The sudden attack took the other five by surprise. They thought that an enemy had arrived and all began to take out their weapons, preparing themselves for the final showdown. However, as they waited, they discovered that nothing happened. Lin Ming had simply stabbed at empty air just then.

‘Is that fellow too nervous and attacked empty space?’ Blackstone maliciously thought. Before this, he didn’t have any confidence that he would be able to defeat Lin Ming. But, seeing him mess up in public, he couldn’t help but start thinking to himself, ‘So even you’ll have times you’re embarrassed.’

“Let’s go!”

Lin Ming said succinctly and lifted his feet to walk. His thoughts had been correct. With the bronze battle spirit fused into his attack and added to the fact that his cultivation had reached Revolving Core, he really was able to change the distortion in space here!

As everyone saw Lin Ming calmly walk forwards, the rest followed him with no questions.

Following this, a set pattern began to appear. Every now and then, Lin Ming would suddenly attack the empty air.

Everyone was confused; just what was this?

To be honest, attacking empty air looked sort of silly.

If this were another martial artist, they would have assumed that they had a mental sickness. But Lin Ming was different. If Lin Ming did it, then no matter how absurd or ridiculous it looked, there must been some unexplainable mystical function behind it. This could be called the weighty stature of a master.

Attack after attack, everyone was startled at first, but after that they became accustomed to it. No one asked why Lin Ming did what he did – they knew that asking was useless anyways.

Blackstone was disquieted. Were Lin Ming’s silly-looking attacks really effective?

Casually, Blackstone turned back to look at the Eternal Demon Abyss. As he saw it, he was immediately startled.

“Everyone, look!”

The rest of the group turned around to see that the far off Eternal Demon Abyss seemed blurrier now. That billowing flow of energy had sunk back into the thick fog, looking ethereal and dreamlike.

From being clear to faint, this proved that they were walking further from the Eternal Demon Abyss! Moreover, they had gone at least several dozen or a hundred miles!

Realizing this, everyone grew excited.

They didn’t know how Lin Ming had done this, but now no one dared to disturb his thoughts.

As for Lin Ming, every time that he attacked space, the strike of the Purple Comet Spear would completely sink into the invisible surface of space and be camouflaged by it, so that no one could see just how much energy was behind each of these attacks. Everyone assumed that they were just ordinary attacks, but the truth was that every single strike used 80 to 90% of Lin Ming’s strength.

For these short interval and high intensity attacks, even though Lin Ming had the support from the Gate of Healing, he still found it hard to continue.

He had no choice but to take out some pills and restore his strength.

Within the Eternal Demon Abyss, Lin Ming had to constantly make sure he was at this peak state. Otherwise, if a catastrophic danger were to happen, no one would come to his rescue.

“Young Hero Lin, what is so mysterious about your attack? Can we help out?” As Blackstone saw that Lin Ming had already rested for half an hour, he couldn’t help but ask this question. He was too worried right now. Every second longer that they were in this 1000 mile forbidden zone meant that there was that much more danger.

Lin Ming didn’t even have time to respond before High Lord Cloud Demon coldly coughed and shouted, “Blackstone, sit down!”

Blackstone dejectedly returned to his spot.

“You not bothering Brother Lin is already the greatest help!” Duanmu Qun said. He had also been carefully observing Lin Ming’s attacks. Those seemingly random attacks actually came in at very particular angles and speeds; wanting to replace Lin Ming’s attack with their own was easier said than done.

Three quarters of an hour later, Lin Ming was completely restored. At this moment when Lin Ming’s eyes flashed open, he was immediately shocked. He could see a dim green shadow behind Lan Xin. As he took a closer look, a creepy feeling instantly shot up his back. “Lan Xin, behind you!”

“What!?”

Lan Xin was greatly shocked. She suddenly turned around, a cold sweat already dripping down her back. Behind her, a long green-haired corpse woman was silently floating in the air, her crimson lips open as she continuously sucked wisps of essence energy from Lan Xin’s body into her mouth!

“Ahh!”

Lan Xin cried out in alarm, her beautiful face turning pale!

“It’s sucking in your life force!” Lin Ming said, shocked. This kind of green corpse was called a corpse devil. After a martial artist’s corpse was possessed by an evil spirit, it absorbed the infernal energy from the world and slowly became this sort of ghostly monster.

“Die!”

Duanmu Qun’s face flashed with a merciless light. He took out his long sword and stabbed at the corpse devil. Once a corpse devil absorbed one’s essence energy, it would greatly shorten their life. It was unknown just how much of Lan Xin’s essence energy had been swallowed, but if they didn’t kill this green-haired corpse devil then that essence energy would never return.

Facing Duanmu Qun’s violent sword strike, the corpse devil didn’t even try to dodge. It let that sharp sword cut down on its body.

Deng!

The sound of metal striking metal rang out. Duanmu Qun’s sword cut open the ragged clothes of the corpse devil, but it didn’t even manage to scratch the skin.

What!?

Duanmu Qun’s complexion paled. Although that attack just now was rushed and he wasn’t able to use his full strength, it was at least 60 to 70% of his peak power. Yet he wasn’t even to scratch the skin of this monster! If this was so, then even if he attacked with all of his strength he might only be able to give it a minor wound!

The other martial artists also grimaced. Duanmu Qun’s strength ranked amongst the top in their group. If he couldn’t even injure the corpse devil then there was no need to mention the others.

Run!

This was the idea that simultaneously appeared in the minds of several people. However, just as they thought this, it was like they were suddenly thrown into an icehouse. In front of them, around 70 to 80 feet away, were three more corpse devils. They had gathered in a formation and had them surrounded!

Chapter 651 – Heaven-step Demon God Bone

“Special body transformation treasures? What sort of resources would that be?” Lin Ming’s interest was piqued and he couldn’t help but ask. As someone who was a dual body and law cultivator, he was certainly interested.

“Hehe, just open up those sarcophaguses and take a look inside.” Demonshine excitedly said as he licked his doggy tongue. This old dog was easily roused by things like valuable resources.

There were a total of four sarcophaguses. These sarcophaguses seemed carved from obsidian and there were also strange and simple patterns carved onto them; they appeared to have passed through an immeasurably long time.

Lin Ming stood in front of the sarcophaguses. After not finding any array formations, he asked Demonshine, “Is this something from tens of thousands of years ago?”

“Hey, it might be more than several tens of thousands of years. These sarcophaguses should have been used to bury some important people and this cave was most likely their grave. But, it was just far too long ago, and now that so much time passed, who knows what this place was originally like. In short, this tomb was later captured by those four corpse devils and these sarcophaguses also became their lair.”

“Oh? Those four corpse devils weren’t formed by the bodies left behind here?”

“Ha! How is that possible? Even if it were a top level martial artist like the Eightfall War Emperor, their corpse wouldn’t last for so many tens of thousands of years. Their bones should have decayed or, most likely, condensed into Demon God Bones now. Perhaps the reason that those four corpse devils were attracted to this tomb and decided to settle here was because they were attracted by the energy of those Demon God Bones. Lin Ming, go and open the sarcophaguses.”

“Alright!” Lin Ming agreed. He put away the Purple Comet Spear and bent over, carefully pushing open the first sarcophagus.

With a rumbling sound, an incomparably thick infernal energy spilled out from the sarcophagus. Feng Shen, Duanmu Qun, and Lan Xin’s eyes lit up. Behind them, Blackstone and High Lord Cloud Demon were also startled, their eyes revealing disbelief and excitement.

At this time, everyone realized that this was a massive treasure trove!

Everyone craned over to see that the sarcophagus was filled with fist-sized black glass balls, over ten in total. They were all high quality Demon God Bones!

Demon God Bones… so many!!!!

Blackstone gulped, nearly drooling as his eyes flashing with greed and desire.

High Lord Cloud Demon licked his lips. It had to be known that an ordinary pigeon egg-sized Demon God Bone was already considered very precious. One as large as a chicken’s egg was even rarer. There were very few that were as large as a fist, not to mention that looking at the quality of the energy from these Demon God Bones, they were likely all earth-step Demon God Bones!

More than 10 fist-sized earth-step Demon God Bones, their value could be imagined!

All of the Demon God Bones that High Lord Cloud Demon had ever possessed in his life, even when added together, couldn’t compare to even half of a single one of these Demon God Bones!

It was said that the Eternal Demon Abyss was chock full of lucky chances. This was a truly well-deserved reputation! Moreover, this was within the 1000 mile forbidden zone!

“Boy, this is a pretty good sign. Just this first sarcophagus and there are more than 10 low-grade earth-step Demon God Bones. I guess there should be around 30 jins total. But the better stuff is still awaiting us!”

“Mm.”

Lin Ming nodded and continued to open the second sarcophagus.

Rumble rumble rumble!

The second sarcophagus was much heavier than the first one. After opening it, a blazing golden light flooded out, illuminating the entire stone cave.

Lin Ming peered into the sarcophagus. Within it, he was surprised to find something that looked like a palm-sized golden plate. He felt that it must be the fruit of some plant; the fragrance was overwhelming.

“This is…”

Lin Ming was stunned. This fruit contained an incomparably extraordinary energy. Just smelling the scent it emitted made him feel relaxed and breezy, as if every cell of his body was being energized.

Behind Lin Ming, everyone else’s eyes had gone perfectly round. Even a fool could see that this golden disc was much more precious than the previous earth-step Demon God Bones.

“Hey! Wow, this is incredible! That’s a profound gold divine fruit! It is a top quality heavenly treasure that is useful for tempering the body! This is even this Saint’s first time seeing such a thing! Boy, your luck is ridiculous. This profound gold divine fruit is a very mystical type of plant. It’s similar to the mushroom from the mortal world. Those mushrooms can grow on dead wood, but this profound gold divine fruit specifically grows on a Demon God Bone. In other words, it is the mushroom formed from a Demon God Bone. It needs 10,000 years to germinate, 10,000 years to flower, and 10,000 years to produce a fruit. Once the fruit is born, all of the essence within the plant is condensed into that single fruit, becoming the profound gold divine fruit. After picking it, it won’t spoil for even 10,000 years afterwards!”

“It’s a mushroom that grows from a Demon God Bone?” Lin Ming was shocked. This world was truly vast, all sorts of strange things were possible. As it was said, dead wood could not be carved, but the essence of dead wood could be used to breed ginseng, black tiger palm mushrooms, spiritual bamboo, and all sorts of other precious materials and herbs. If there was a lucky set of coincidences, then dead wood could even breed 1000 year old lingzhi, an amazing medicinal material.

Then… what if that dead wood was replaced with a Demon God Bone?

Compared to dead wood, the essence of a Demon God Bone was trillions upon trillions of times superior in both quality and quantity. If this was used to breed a heavenly treasure, the value of this treasure could be imagined!

Demonshine said, “This profound gold divine fruit cannot be bred from just an ordinary Demon God Bone. It would require at least a high-grade earth-step Demon God Bone, and only with divine providence would the profound gold divine fruit tree be born. The tree would only be a foot high and would need to absorb all of the Demon God Bone’s essence in order to germinate. Then, it would have to absorb other Demon God Bones as nutrition, growing for another 30,000 years before its fruit would be born. You can imagine just how difficult this is! Compared to this profound gold divine fruit, even the Nirvana Dragon Root can’t be considered much…”

Hearing Demonshine give such a high evaluation, Lin Ming took a deep breath. But then, he thought of something. He asked, a bit puzzled, “If this profound gold divine fruit is so precious, then how come those four corpse devils didn’t swallow it yet?”

“They probably wished to, but as they say, extremes give birth to extremes. This profound gold divine fruit is bred within a very thick yin aura of the infernal energy and death energy here, and the Demon God Bone is also an extreme yin treasure, however… the profound gold divine fruit is actually an extreme yang and extreme light attributed body transformation treasure. With the cultivation of these four corpse devils, they would probably explode from within if they tried to eat this fruit. If they wanted to eat it, they would still need several tens of thousands of years of further cultivation before they could think of attempting it. Still, just by defending the profound gold divine fruit and absorbing the essence energy that it releases, their harvests would still be tremendous! If I’m correct, then the root of this profound gold divine fruit has already been eaten by those four corpse devils, otherwise, how could they have bodies with durability comparable to a heaven-step treasure?”

“I see! So that’s how it is…” Lin Ming suddenly realized. After the profound gold divine fruit was born, the energy within the roots would naturally be much weaker. If the corpse devils ate the root instead, that was still at the level where they could withstand it.

“What a pity!”

Lin Ming regretfully shook his head. For such a miraculous body transformation medicine like this, even the root was a priceless treasure. Yet, it was eaten up by those four corpse devils.

His thoughts flashed and he asked, “If I had those corpse devils’ bodies, could I refine the medicine efficacy of the profound gold divine fruit’s root from them?”

Lin Ming was only thoughtlessly asking but Demonshine had a scandalized expression after hearing it, “Boy, you’re quite the funny one. The medicinal efficacy has already fused into those corpse devils’ bodies, so even if you refine them there won’t be much left over. Not just that, but it would take a high level alchemist to do so. Do you really think that all those piddling losers of the Holy Demon Continent and Sky Spill Continent have the ability to do this?!”

“Mm…” Lin Ming nodded, bit embarrassed. He was only casually asking anyways, if it didn’t work then that was fine too. He let out a deep breath and then moved towards the third sarcophagus.

As the other five people saw this they couldn’t help but gulp. Today, all the sights they had seen were just too impactful on them.

Even if it were a Holy Land descendant like Feng Shen and Lan Xin, the total amount of resources they had used from birth until now only added up to a single Demon God Bone from the first sarcophagus!

The third sarcophagus’ cover rumbled opened and a thick burst of infernal energy burst out, no less than that of the second sarcophagus. As for Duanmu Qun and the rest who were standing behind Lin Ming, even though they could feel this extremely potent energy, they were too numbed to be fazed by any of this. Even if some monster jumped out they still wouldn’t be surprised.

However, after the third sarcophagus fully opened, all of their eyes still went as wide as full moons. In the massive third sarcophagus, there was only a pigeon egg-sized green glass bead. Although it was small, the energy inherent within it was more than all of the Demon God Bones of the first sarcophagus added up together!

At this time, Duanmu Qun and the rest, who had never seen this object before, could already deduce what it was.

This was… a heaven-step Demon God Bone!

This was a legendary treasure! According to rumors, not even a generation ruler of the Blood Slaughter Steppes had ever obtained a heaven-step Demon God Bone!

“Boy, I have to say your luck is just too good! This is a low-grade heaven-step Demon God Bone!”

“Of this low-grade heaven-step Demon God Bone and the profound gold divine fruit, which one is more valuable?” Lin Ming asked.

“The profound gold divine fruit. As long as you are strong enough, you will be able to find a low-grade heaven-step Demon God Bone here if you put in the time and effort. In fact, you can even find many of them But as for a profound gold divine fruit, that is a treasure born from the stars aligning just right. Without a great lucky chance you would never be able to find something like this.”

Lin Ming nodded. Although the profound gold divine fruit was more precious, to the martial artists of the Holy Demon Continent, they would probably value the heaven-step Demon God Bone more. The legends said that a heaven-step Demon Cloud Bone was an absolute stepping stone to entering the Emperor boundary, and the truth was probably not far off. Especially to someone like High Lord Cloud Demon whose future talent hovered at the precipice of becoming an Emperor level powerhouse. If he could obtain a heaven-step Demon God Bone, the chances of him becoming an Emperor level powerhouse would rise astronomically.

As Lin Ming thought this, he glanced over at High Lord Cloud Demon. And, indeed, he saw naked greed and thirst clouding his eyes!

With his lucky chance to becoming an Emperor level powerhouse right in front of him, how could he not be tempted! If he missed out on this then he would probably never become an Emperor level powerhouse!

Lin Ming didn’t bother with High Lord Cloud Demon, he continued moving onto the fourth sarcophagus!

“I wonder just what is in this fourth sarcophagus…” Lin Ming thought out loud.

“Haha, maybe there’s a medium-grade heaven-step Demon God Bone inside!” Demonshine happily teased. He was in very high spirits right now. Although these were mostly body transformation and essence gathering system treasures that he couldn’t use, it would still allow Lin Ming to increase his own strength. If Lin Ming became stronger, then his chances of helping Demonshine restore his divine soul were that much higher.

Lin Ming bent over and pushed hard against the cover of the fourth sarcophagus, opening it.

With a rumbling sound the fourth sarcophagus opened. However, as he looked inside, he was completely stunned.

Chapter 653 – Murder

When Blackstone had been wallowing in despair, he had indeed said that if he could make it out of this land alive, he would give all of his wealth to Lin Ming. But at that time, Blackstone had been desperate to survive, so it wasn’t strange that he would make such a promise in that situation.

Now he saw just how powerful Lin Ming really was. Not only had Lin Ming managed to find the method to leave this 1000 mile forbidden zone but his strength was indomitable. By himself, he had defeated the four corpse devils, making it seem that their chances of leaving here were much higher.

Under the constantly hanging threat of death, when a person was doing everything they could to survive, as long as they were tossed a rope they would be willing to give up all their wealth. But when that threat was gone, their heart would change and their greed would return. This was the debased nature of man. Moreover, with such a lucky chance in front of him, something so precious that could only be found through a stroke of fate, how could Blackstone not be moved?

After being rebutted by Lin Ming’s words, Blackstone’s bleak expression became even uglier. “Lin Ming… it’s true that I said those words, it’s just that… we entered the 1000 mile forbidden zone together and I risked my life this entire time. Although I wasn’t the one to kill the enemies, I still managed to serve as a shield for you. At least, consider that I lost my arm…”

Blackstone hadn’t even finished speaking when he was interrupted by Lin Ming. “You risked your life for me? Was I the one that pushed you into the 1000 mile forbidden zone? Was I the one who forced you to ‘bring up the rear’ and have your arm cut off?”

This series of rhetorical questions left Blackstone dumbfounded. Initially, the reason he had lost an arm was because he was too scared to rush towards the corpse devil.

At this time High Lord Cloud Demon butted in, “Young Hero Lin… I know that without you, none of us would be alive right now, let alone have a chance to obtain resources. It’s just that… someone as majestic as you will inevitably become a Peerless Emperor in the future and have countless more resources. In fact, aren’t all these resources not too effective for you? I don’t think you’d be able to use everything. If this fist sized earth-step Demon God Bone would have a base value of one, then that heaven-step Demon God Bone would probably have a value of 40 to 50. I don’t know what the golden fruit is, but it shouldn’t be any worse than the heaven-step Demon God Bone, making it also worth 40 to 50. In addition with the 16 earth-step Demon God Bones, that is around a total of 100. You only gave the five of us eight earth-step Demon God Bones, so that is only 8% divided amongst the rest of us…”

“The truth is that I don’t need that much. As long as I can have 1/3… no, ¼ of the heaven-step Demon God Bone then that will be enough for me to break through the Emperor level bottleneck. I can make an oath right here that as long as I become an Emperor level powerhouse, I will remember this kindness for my entire life. When that time comes, if Young Hero Lin has any needs, I will work like a horse for you!”

High Lord Cloud Demon solemnly vowed, making swearing gestures with his hands.

Lin Ming was simply unmoved by this nonsense. His face was expressionless as he said, “It’s true that I have a great number of lucky chances, and I could even say that this heaven-step Demon God Bone isn’t too tempting to me. But, I have friends and family who also need to use them. The decisions I make, I will not change. Me willing to save you isn’t because you are special or anything. Me leading you to leave this 1000 mile forbidden zone is already me being benevolent to you. As for lucky chances, why should I divide any of them with you?”

The reason that he helped rescue everyone was mainly because of Feng Shen and partly because of Lan Xin. Lin Ming regarded Feng Shen as a friend, and Lan Xin had also been a teammate of his, both of them having risked their lives in a squad. When Lin Ming had gone back to capture the demon bone, Lan Xin had sincerely advised him not to go for his own safety, showing true consideration for Lin Ming’s welfare.

Although this was only a very light and simple friendship, Lin Ming placed a great deal of importance and emphasis in these relationships he had, no matter how faint they were. Before, the reason he had been willing to stop and wait for these people and even dividing them less than 10% of these resources, was all because he appreciated Feng Shen and Lan Xin and was willing to give them some face.

As for Blackstone and High Lord Cloud Demon, he was already being merciful by not instantly killing them. And they still wanted to take part of his lucky chance? Dream on!

In fact, if it wasn’t for the fact that Lin Ming was planning on returning to the South Horizon Region right after this tour of the Eternal Demon Abyss, he would have already killed Blackstone and High Lord Cloud Demon right here and right now. Whether it was the profound gold divine fruit or the heaven-step Demon God Bone, both of these treasures were enough to make him a target of powerful forces once the news spread out.

“Young Hero Lin…” High Lord Cloud Demon wanted to say something, but as he saw Lin Ming’s icy cold eyes glaring at him, he could only shut up and remain silent. He felt that once Lin Ming made a decision, he would not easily change it. He simply didn’t have the power to bargain at all. He could only choose to accept this or have nothing at all.

As the weaker man, there was nothing he could do. He didn’t doubt that if Lin Ming wanted to, he could kill all five of them.

High Lord Cloud Demon finally relinquished his desire towards the heaven-step Demon God Bone, and was planning on getting two earth-step Demon God Bones for himself before going back. At least something was better than nothing.

But, at this moment, a voice suddenly resounded in his mind.

“Don’t you want to obtain a heaven-step Demon God Bone? Don’t you want to break through the Emperor level bottleneck?”

Who?

The sudden voice startled High Lord Cloud Demon. This voice appeared in his mind, and after hearing it, it didn’t sound like it came from any of the other five people here.

Could this be…

High Lord Cloud Demon’s eyes turned over to the fourth sarcophagus, his face paling. It couldn’t be her!

As this idea grew in his heart, a chill rose from the soles of his feet and traveled up his spine, shooting straight into the skies. He did want a heaven-step Demon God Bone, but he absolutely didn’t want to come into contact with this kind of ghostly being.

At this time, High Lord Cloud Demon also noticed Blackstone’s situation. Before, Blackstone had a very ugly complexion, but now he looked confused, his pupils losing focus as if he were in a trance.

“He also heard the voice?” High Lord Cloud Demon was shocked. Also, it appeared that Blackstone had already fallen into this trap!

At this moment, High Lord Cloud Demon suddenly discovered that it wasn’t just Blackstone that heard this voice, but also Feng Shen, Lan Xin, and Duanmu Qun. All of their complexions had changed. Among them, Duanmu Qun and Feng Shen still appeared lucid, but a trace of turmoil had appeared in Lan Xin’s eyes!

‘This is bad!’ High Lord Cloud Demon’s heart surged with a strong sense of unease. At this time, he remembered Lin Ming and quickly turned to look at him, but then, his field of vision suddenly turned into an endless white field. In the dim light, he could see a peerless powerhouse wearing armor, holding a divine weapon as he looked upon the world with contempt!

And this powerhouse’s appearance was exactly the same as High Lord Cloud Demon’s!

This was his appearance several hundred years from now after he became a Peerless Emperor!

“Peerless Emperor? My Peerless Emperor!?” This thought reverberated in High Lord Cloud Demon’s mind. Then, he lost himself in illusion, forgetting what was happening now.

Many martial artists had a mental weakness. Once they suffered a soul attack or tried to make a breakthrough, this weakness would become their heart demon, struggling to swallow their spiritual sea.

High Lord Cloud Demon’s heart demon was his obsessive desire to become an Emperor level powerhouse!

At this time, besides Lin Ming, the only one able to maintain their sanity was Duanmu Qun. But, his forehead was seeping with sweat and he had an extremely grim expression.

Feng Shen was second to Duanmu Qun. Although his strength was weaker, his heart was firm and he was able to maintain his consciousness. As for Lan Xin, High Lord Cloud Demon, and Blackstone, all three of them were completely entranced.

“Who is this?” Lin Ming’s mind went cold. He grasped the Purple Comet Spear and maintained full alert. He own will was as firm as iron and he also had the battle spirit and Samsara martial intent; he was able to completely ignore this sort of soul attack.

He didn’t even blink to destroy that illusion in his soul.

There weren’t any signs of evil spirits around… could it be…

Lin Ming suddenly turned to look at the fourth sarcophagus!

Was it her!?

If it truly was her, then the consequences would be calamitous!

She had been an unbelievable existence. Even if she had died 100,000 years ago, her residual will was not something that Lin Ming could contend with.

But at this moment, Demonshine’s voice sounded in his mind, “Lin Ming, do not panic. It is not that woman, no, it is the heaven-step Demon God Bone! I was negligent! A heaven-step Demon God Bone must have a mind of its own. How could it willingly be caught and eaten up by others?”

Demonshine’s voice suddenly woke up Lin Ming! Demonshine had once said that a heaven-step Demon God Bone must have a consciousness and would be much more difficult to capture. In fact, even a top earth-step Demon God Bone would be intelligent. For instance when Lin Ming had caught the Blood Demon Bone from before, that demon bone was intelligent, and could tempt martial artists close to absorb their blood vitality.

So this was it!

Lin Ming let out a deep breath. If it was just the heaven-step Demon God Bone, then there wasn’t a reason to dread it at all.

He took a step forwards, wanting to seal up the heaven-step Demon God Bone that was causing all this trouble. But at this moment, Blackstone let out a bellowing roar as he rushed towards Lin Ming!

The heavy sword in his hand swept out straight towards Lin Ming’s neck!

Blackstone had been thoroughly controlled.

It was apparent that the heaven-step Demon God Bone feared Lin Ming so it had controlled Blackstone and made him attack.

Seeing this scene, Lin Ming coldly snorted, “Since it’s like this, don’t blame me!”

Towards someone like Blackstone, Lin Ming wouldn’t stay his hand for fear of harming him, or do something so stupid as withstanding Blackstone’s attacks while trying to suppress the heaven-step Demon God Bone.

If he was controlled because his mind was weak, who was to blame?

Grasping the Purple Comet Spear, the Heretical God Force opened. Lin Ming’s spear swept out!

Bang!

The heavy sword was struck away. Blackstone’s arm shook and his palm ruptured

In terms of striking power, he was no different from a baby in front of Lin Ming.

However, after the heavy sword was sent flying away, Blackstone still rushed towards Lin Ming, wanting to strangle him. His eyes were already a deep blood red.

Seeing this, Lin Ming sneered. His attack just now had contained his battle spirit. A battle spirit was invisible and intangible. It could crush all, including the divine soul, negative emotions, life force, heart demons, and everything else that was insubstantial.

Lin Ming had wanted to help Blackstone by destroying the heart demon that had invaded his spiritual sea, but his spear strike simply had no effect, Blackstone was still desperately trying to kill him at all cost. So, it seemed Blackstone really did hate him from the depths of his soul. This heart demon had galvanized the hatred in his heart and made him desperate to kill Lin Ming.

“You are hopeless!”

Lin Ming was expressionless as he thrust out the Purple Comet Spear!

This spear strike was infused with his battle spirit as well as the full power of the Heretical God Force.

Puff!

With the added sharpness from the battle spirit, Blackstone’s protective demon essence and neck were both torn apart by Lin Ming’s spear like paper, blood shooting out!

Chapter 661 – Glory of the Battle Spirit

The Polaris Tower Master was forced back?

In that collision between Lin Ming and the Polaris Tower Master, it was the Polaris Tower Master who was actually forced back!

All of the martial artists present were stunned. It was true that Lin Ming’s aura was no weaker than the Polaris Tower Master’s, but aura didn’t represent a martial artist’s complete strength, and there was also something strange and tricky about Lin Ming’s aura. Moreover, the Polaris Tower Master’s accumulated fame and strength were too great; it was hard for anyone to imagine that a heroic youth could be stronger than him.

But now, in a single exchange of blows, Lin Ming had only been a little shaken, but the Polaris Tower Master was actually forced back 10 whole steps. Although the Polaris Tower Master wasn’t injured, his blood still tumbled and he had eaten no small loss.

At this point, the Polaris Tower Master’s complexion was extremely ugly. He thought that Lin Ming was only using some sort of special force field to suppress his aura, but his strength wasn’t too special.

He didn’t use his sword for his first attack because with his status as a Tower Master, having to go all out to deal with a junior was a bit shameful. Even if he won in the end, people would still criticize him.

In fact, although the Polaris Tower Master’s weapon of choice was a great sword, his fist skills were still extremely powerful. The reason he fought with his fist was because he wanted to use Lin Ming to demonstrate his power and authority. But he never that that if he didn’t use his sword, Lin Ming also wouldn’t use his spear and would fight with fists instead!

Fist against fist, the Polaris Tower Master was confident that he could break Lin Ming’s arm. But, after their fists collided, the Polaris Tower Master discovered that what he hit clearly wasn’t a fist but an iron hammer instead! Not only was Lin Ming’s fist terrifyingly adamantine, but there was also a strange power of vibration within it, nearly causing his own arm to be broken.

This boy, was he really human?

Although he guessed that Lin Ming must have practiced some sort of body transformation technique, it was impossible for the human body to be tempered to this degree. This was a durability that was comparable to a treasure! Not even the Giant Demons or Goliaths, races well known for their formidable bodies, would be able to hold a candle to him!

Just where had this abnormally monstrous freak come from!?

The Polaris Tower Master was enraged. He suddenly pulled out a heavy sword from his spatial ring and pointed it straight at Lin Ming!

Huuu –

A blazing black flame ignited atop the Polaris Tower Master’s great sword, the aura overwhelming!

“Medium-grade heaven-step treasure!?”

All of the surrounding martial artists cried out in alarm. For heaven-step treasures, there were enormous differences between every rank. Within Skysplit Tower, because the High Lords overflowed with far too much wealth, it was common to see them with heaven-step treasures. But, these were mostly the lowest of heaven-step treasures. As for medium-grade heaven-step treasures, only very few people had seen them before.

“No, that’s not a medium-grade heaven-step treasure but a peak low-grade heaven-step treasure; it’s only a step away from becoming a medium-grade heaven-step treasure.”

Everyone looked at Lin Ming. Lin Ming thought for a moment, and then took out the Purple Comet Spear from his spatial ring.

The Purple Comet Spear was originally crafted from top materials. But, those were considered top materials only relative to a fourth-grade sect like Divine Phoenix Island. Moreover, the one who forged the Purple Comet Spear was Ancestor Chi Yan who was only a middle Revolving Core powerhouse.

Thus, the Purple Comet Spear within Lin Ming’s hand was only a peak high-grade earth-step treasure.

“Lin Ming’s spear is only a high-grade earth-step treasure?”

As everyone saw Lin Ming’s spear, they were surprised before shaking their heads in disappointment.

In fact, as an early Revolving Core powerhouse, it was already excellent that he had a high-grade earth-step treasure weapon. But, placed within the Blood Slaughter Steppes where resources were immeasurably plentiful, and also placed within this group of High Lords and Holy Land descendants, this high-grade earth-step treasure appeared rather shabby instead.

When compared to the Polaris Tower Master’s great sword, it especially paled. There was a difference of a large boundary between the two. With a mere high-grade earth-step treasure to resist a medium-grade heaven-step treasure, how could he even defend against it?

“The difference is too great! Even if Lin Ming is strong, he will suffer too much because of the difference in their treasures. There is no way he’ll be able to fight!”

The use of a treasure did not lie mainly in its ability to increase a martial artist’s combat strength, but rather the degree of its own hardness!

If an inferior treasure were to hit a top ranked treasure, it was possible for the lesser one to break in half!

Even Duanmu Qun, Lan Xin, and Feng Shen were feeling nervous for Lin Ming.

“Haha! Lin Ming, you want to use that trash spear to face my Heaven Opening Sword, you are really asking to die!” The Polaris Tower Master wickedly grinned as he looked at the Purple Comet Spear in Lin Ming’s hand, his voice filled with contempt and ridicule.

At the start, the Polaris Tower master had wanted to win in a beautiful and awesome manner so that he could establish his authority in front of everyone. But now, after that brief period of fighting, he had changed his mind. Lin Ming’s power had already exceeded his every expectation. As long as he could win then he would be satisfied!

“Who lives and who dies, we will know after this battle!” After speaking, Lin Ming’s aura began to rise. Underneath his feet, the land began to rupture from his increasingly sharp aura.

“Humph! Your end is imminent and yet you remain such a flippant piece of garbage. Lin Ming, you dared to slander me, you dared to slander the Blood Slaughter Steppes, and for this, I shall take your dog life now!”

The Polaris Tower Master gave a loud shot and stepped forwards, the land breaking beneath his feet!

His body turned into a stream of light that shot towards Lin Ming, the great sword in his hand cutting down like the peak of a mountain!

This sword was actually aimed towards Lin Ming’s Purple Comet Spear! He wanted to cut apart Lin Ming’s Purple Comet Spear. As long as he succeeded, it was the same as chopping off a tiger’s fangs. Lin Ming’s combat strength would drop to the floor!

As the surrounding martial artists saw this, they all thought in their heart that the Polaris Tower Master’s methods weren’t honorable. But, in a struggle of life and death, the winner was king and the loser was the villain. As for what method was used, none of that was important.

Lin Ming’s eyes flashed with a cold light. The Heretical God Force opened to the extreme, the Eight Inner Hidden Gates erupted, and the complete battle spirit was fused into the Purple Comet Spear.

A battle spirit was invisible and intangible, but it could be attached to any treasure, turning it into an incomparably sharp killing weapon. A trivial withered leaf with a battle spirit attached to it could cut apart a treasure!

Lin Ming poured his battle spirit into the Purple Comet Spear, and thus, the originally insufficient quality Purple Comet Spear began to shine with a shimmering greenish yellow light; this was the glory of a bronze battle spirit!

Clang!

The Polaris Tower Master’s heavy sword smashed into the Purple Comet Spear, pressing down on it like a great mountain. The earth underneath Lin Ming’s feet exploded and the Purple Comet Spear fiercely bent, but this strike was actually abruptly kept off by Lin Ming!

“What!?”

The Polaris Tower Master was shocked. He never thought that his all-out strike, combined with a peak low-grade heaven-step Heaven Opening Sword would actually not be able to break apart a high-grade earth-step treasure spear!

The Polaris Tower Master was naturally a greatly experienced genius of his generation. An idea suddenly rose in his heart… could this greenish gray light be… a battle spirit?

Impossible! This was impossible!

Not only was the Polaris Tower Master shocked, but all the surrounding martial artists were dumbfounded as they saw that the Purple Comet Spear didn’t break. However, in that split-second, no one had time to think about what just happened.

There was only a whistling sound, and then because of the heavy pressure, the curved Purple Comet Spear suddenly snapped back like a whip, shooting straight towards the cheek of the Polaris Tower Master.

The Polaris Tower Master could no longer afford to think about just what that greenish gray light was on the spear. He pulled back his Heaven Opening Sword and quickly drew away. But even so, the power of thunder still snuck into his body like the strike of a viper

Chi chi chi!

The Polaris Tower Master felt half of his body instantly paralyzed. That power of thunder also had Lin Ming’s battle spirit attached to it!

Just that tiny wisp of battle spirit caused the originally insufficiently ranked Thunder Soul to become incomparably dangerous!

The Polaris Tower Master wretchedly coughed. But at this moment, Lin Ming had already taken a step forwards. His feet stepped upon Golden Roc Shattering the void and all space seemed to lose meaning underneath his steps. It was as if Lin Ming had directly teleported in front of the Polaris Tower Master, the spear in his hand already thrusting down!

“Ahhh!”

The Polaris Tower Master fiercely bit down on his tongue, forcefully awakening himself with pain. He raised the Heaven Opening Sword in his hand and slashed towards Lin Ming.

He was trying to use a purely offensive strike to force Lin Ming to retreat.

But in this moment, the flow of time seemed to slow down around the Polaris Tower Master. His sword seemed stuck in a bog even as Lin Ming’s spear shot out like a blazing meteor, its speed reaching the extreme!

Concept of Time!?

The Polaris Tower Master’s eyes turned bloodshot. Under the threat of death, he erupted with 120% of his potential, emitting a terrifying energy and using it to directly burst out of the time cage. At the moment that Lin Ming’s spear thrust down, he moved completely contrary to the laws of physics, forcing that spear that would have struck his heart to stab into his left shoulder instead!

With the infusion of battle spirit, Lin Ming’s spear cut through the Polaris Tower Master’s protective demon essence like it was tofu, stabbing his shoulder and penetrating straight through!

Blood shot out; Lin Ming’s spear had broken the Polaris Tower Master’s clavicle!

“Ah!”

The Polaris Tower Master’s eyes flashed with the light of insanity. He used his muscles to firmly clamp down on the Purple Comet Spear and then slashed his sword towards Lin Ming’s neck! He wanted to use this opportunity with the Purple Comet Spear stuck in his body to cut off Lin Ming’s head!

Lin Ming only coldly sneered. True essence erupted from the Purple Comet Spear. Each wisp of true essence had a touch of battle spirit fused with it, shooting out like a pack of steel needles. The Polaris Tower Master’s meridians and muscles in his left shoulder had become a twisted mess!

As a result, the strength of the muscles imprisoning his spear no longer existed.

Lin Ming’s figure dodged backwards, easily escaping the Polaris Tower Master’s sword and leaving a massive gaping wound in the Polaris Tower Master’s left shoulder!

Blood flowed like a river, the meat there ground into a blur.

This was the terror of a battle spirit. Its name as the strongest attack wasn’t just from its unmatched sharpness, but also its terrifying destructive power!

The Polaris Tower Master fell down, staggering backwards several steps as he used his great sword to support himself, only then being able to come to a standstill.

As the martial artists present saw this, all of them were shocked speechless. They had thought that Lin Ming’s strength might be above that of the Polaris Tower Master, but the quality of his treasure weapon was simply too inferior. Overall, he was at a disadvantage. They never imagined that after several exchanges of moves, the Polaris Tower Master would be the one who was severely wounded!

Lin Ming had simply used an overwhelming strength to completely suppress the Polaris Tower Master without giving him the chance to resist.

At this time, Zhuan Yu’s lips were shivering. He realized now that the difference between him and Lin Ming was a great boundary, like a Xiantian martial artist compared to a Revolving Core martial artist, or a Revolving Core martial artist compared to a Life Destruction master.

How ridiculous that he had challenged Lin Ming to a battle a year from now; he really didn’t know what it meant to die!

“Great Ax, help me!”

The Polaris Tower Master clutched his shoulder and pleaded to the Great Ax Tower Master for help.

The Great Ax Tower Master gulped, his heart bitter. He certainly knew the true identity of the Polaris Tower Master. If he watched on helplessly as the Polaris Tower Master died in front of him, then the ruler of the Blood Slaughter Steppes would never forgive him.

Chapter 665 – Achieving 12 Wings

After becoming a twelve-winged Heavenly Demon, a person would obtain Heavenly Demon martial intent and become the ultimate taboo existence within the Blood Slaughter Steppes. The Blood Slaughter Steppes’ true fear was not the Holy Land Alliance, but an Emperor level powerhouse like the Eightfall War Emperor who had also managed to obtain a twelve-winged Heavenly Demon Tattoo.

There didn’t need to be many of such individuals. As long as three or four such existences simultaneously attacked the Blood Slaughter Steppes, the Steppes Master would suffer defeat!

“All High Lords heed my order! Everyone attack Lin Ming together! Although he is strong, he cannot stand a barrage of your martial skills!”

Elder Xiao crazily shouted. It was true that Lin Ming was strong, but this had mainly manifested in his striking power. In just the aspect of striking power, Lin Ming even surpassed an ordinary second stage Life Destruction powerhouse. Any defense would be pierced and pulverized!

But in terms of defensive power, no matter how fierce Lin Ming was, it was impossible for him to stand there and take attacks from a High Lord powerhouse, much less a barrage of them!

All of the surrounding High Lords began to move, taking out their weapons and attacking Lin Ming.

But, how could they possibly compare to Lin Ming in speed?

Cha cha cha!

The heaven-step treasure spear was like a pure white dragon swimming through the vast sea. Wherever it went, blood would follow!

Lin Ming indeed couldn’t block a volley of attacks from the High Lords. Even if just five or six martial artists attacked him at the same time, he probably wouldn’t be able to block that either. But, by depending on Golden Roc Shattering the Void, his movement skill that allowed him to weave through the battlefield like ghosts and gods, how could anyone think of successfully hitting him?

As he flitted between the 20 some High Lords, Lin Ming’s attacks were like vorpal death sentences!

The white spear was fused with billowing flames and arcs of electricity. Each and every attack had the power of a bronze level battle spirit poured into it!

“Ahhh!”

Seeing Lin Ming rush towards him, a High Lord swung his heavy sword at Lin Ming, wanting to fend off this attack. But Lin Ming completely ignored his attack and continued thrusting his spear.

In that instant, Lin Ming’s spear passed through the High Lord’s sword light and then struck the heavy sword with a metallic ring. Then, an inconceivable scene occurred that made everyone tremble. The great sword, which was also a heaven-step treasure, actually had its thick blade pierced through by Lin Ming’s spear!

The long spear penetrated through the heavy sword and stabbed into the High Lord’s throat, taking his life with a single spear strike!

Such a sharp spear light caused all of the martial artists present to pale, sweat dripping down their backs. Everyone knew that the white spear was a low-grade heaven-step treasure. But, in Lin Ming’s hand, this spear had reached a degree of sharpness that no one could block!

Facing this sort of demon, just who would dare to fight him?

The dozen some remaining High Lords were pale as they turned around to run. However, Lin Ming did not intend to let a single one of them escape. The space underneath his feet suddenly shrank as he seemed to teleport directly behind a High Lord’s back, his spear thrusting into his body!

“Don’t kill me! I surrender! I’ll leave–”

The High Lord frantically shouted. However, his voice died in his throat. The white spear penetrated through his back and straight out of his front, a bloody light shooting out!

Leave?

Lin Ming’s lips curved in a devilish grin. At the moment that they decided to kill Duanmu Qun, everyone had already forfeited their lives in this gamble!

Seeing that they couldn’t kill the one in front of them, but then seeing that they themselves would die and even wanting to retreat; just where in the world would you find such a good deal?

“Damnit!”

Seeing six or seven ordinary High Lords cut down by Lin Ming as if they were vegetables, Elder Xiao’s eyes turned red, “This old man will kill you!”

Pouring true essence into his lance, Elder Xiao struck out at Lin Ming.

“Humph! You really think that I’m afraid to fight you?”

Lin Ming’s eyes sparked with a cold light. He grasped his spear, thrusting it up. He would welcome anyone anytime!

Before, he hadn’t dared to directly fight because Elder Xiao and the Great Ax Tower Master were attacking him together, and the treasure in Lin Ming’s hand was lacking. But now, seeing Elder Xiao rushed towards him alone, this was what Lin Ming had wished for. A spear thrust out, fires burning to the heavens!

A vast Concept of Fire burnt Elder Xiao’s cloud of demon essence to cinders. Spear and lance collided!

Bang!

Elder Xiao’s body shook. After receiving such a heavy blow, he was blown backwards like a broken kite, blood leaking out from his mouth.

After Lin Ming had switched to a heaven-step treasure spear, he had been able to completely free the power of his battle spirit. Now, his striking power was not something that Elder Xiao could hope to compare with. For this old man to think of meeting him in a head-on attack with, he had simply been seeking death!

“Great Ax! What the hell are you doing? Do you think he will let you go!?”

Elder Xiao crazily shouted, his voice full thick with anger and killing intent.

Great Ax grit his teeth and stepped forwards. At this time he had truly stepped onto the road of no return. His only path of redemption was to kill Lin Ming!

Elder Xiao forcefully revolved his demon essence and suppressed in internal injuries, swallowing down the blood that was filling his mouth.

One on the left, one on the right, both of them attacked Lin Ming!

Facing these two simultaneous attacks, although Lin Ming was confident in himself, he didn’t lower his guard. Suffering even a minor injury here would be disastrous.

However, he had never intended to meet both of their attacks.

Seeing billowing clouds of demonic energy roiling towards him, Lin Ming’s lips curved in a cruel smile.

Golden Roc Shattering the Void!

Hoo-!

Lin Ming’s figure instantly vanished again. In the next moment, he had already moved several hundred feet away, appearing right in front of the Polaris Tower Master!

At the same time that Great Ax and Elder Xiao attacked him, he had decide to kill the Polaris Tower Master!

“Ahh!”

The Polaris Tower Master’s eyes widened as he saw Lin Ming suddenly flicker in front of him, scared so badly that his soul nearly left his body. In his life, he had killed countless lives, and now this was the first time that he had truly faced death.

The fear of dying gripped his mind. His eyes widened, his heartbeat stopping!

He didn’t want to die! He was the son of the Steppes Master! He enjoyed countless resources, countless beauties, limitless fame! In the future, he would become a twelve-winged Heavenly Demon and inevitably step into the Emperor level realm!

He would live for six or seven thousand years, with endless wealth and an exalted status. He would have peerless authority, wielding the fates of a trillion lives in his hands with absolute power! He would have a harem with countless proud and heavenly women of every race…

And now, all of this, all of his dreams, would disappear with this single spear strike!

“Lin Ming, don’t–!!!”

“Young Master!!” Several hundred feet away, Elder Xiao also shouted out. However, no one was able to stop Lin Ming.

Without a hint of hesitation, his spear came plummeting down, directly passing through the Polaris Tower Master’s throat like a bolt of lightning!

Puff!

Blood sputtered out. The Polaris Tower Master opened his mouth as if he were trying to say something, but his vocal cords had already been torn to pieces so he was unable to utter a single word.

Lin Ming was inscrutable as he pulled his hand back and received his spear. As he drew back the spear, blood gushed out, spraying into the air. In this final strike that killed the Polaris Tower Master, he hadn’t even infused his spear with his battle spirit, ending his life no differently than he would butcher a chicken of pig.

A powerful and ambition genius of his era, who had planted slave seals in the spiritual seas of several generations of proud sons of heavens, who had become the Polaris Tower Master that had controlled Polaris Tower for dozens of years, had died today, killed no differently than the lowest of beasts!

“Young Master!”

Elder Xiao’s eyes were blood red. His heart raged with an inferno of hatred, a thick burning intent sizzling in his mind. In the end, all he could do was look on helplessly as the Polaris Tower Master died right in front of him!

This wasn’t because of any mistake Elder Xiao had made. In that situation just now, he could no longer stop Lin Ming. If he didn’t attack Lin Ming, then that was no different from freely allowing him to becoming a twelve-winged Heavenly Demon. Yet, if he wanted to attack Lin Ming, he would need to join forces with Great Ax. And now, the result of this was… he had given Lin Ming the chance to directly slaughter the Polaris Tower Master.

His movement speed was inferior and his striking power was inferior. From the point that Lin Ming obtained the white spear, the initiative had gone to Lin Ming’s hand, remaining there forever!

As the Polaris Tower master died, an incomparably rich infernal energy leaked out from him. This mass of infernal energy was several times purer and richer than any other mass of infernal energy that Lin Ming had ever seen!

At this moment, the bass growl of a demon filled the air. The fierce Heavenly Demon phantom that hid within Lin Ming’s arm tattoo appeared, rushing towards the mass of infernal energy and swallowing it all!

With the additional six or seven High Lords that Lin Ming had killed just before, all of this infernal energy combined together, completely absorbed by the Heavenly Demon phantom!

Roar!!

The Heavenly Demon phantom stretched out its sharp claws and unfolded its towering wings. It faced the heavens and gave off a loud cry. Its five pairs of wings were already extremely clear, and now, under the effects of that rich infernal energy, the final sixth pair was also slowly expanding!

A twelve-winged Heavenly Demon!

After Lin Ming killed the Polaris Tower Master, he finally became a twelve-winged Heavenly Demon!

With the influx of infernal energy, the Heavenly Demon phantom began to rapidly grow, finally reaching a monumental 40 to 50 feet. It was like an Asura that crawled out from the endless abyss. Thunder and fire raged underneath its feet, and its entire body was wrapped with thick, bulging muscles. As it released its 12 wings, they nearly covered the skies!

All of the surrounding martial artists were dumbfounded.

This was the first time they had witnessed the birth of a twelve-winged Heavenly Demon!

“Mad… he’s a madman…” Zhuan Yu’s lips trembled. At this moment, he didn’t even have the courage to face Lin Ming, let alone fight him.

As for Elder Xiao, a trace of fear flashed in his eyes. He had a deep foreboding feeling that if he couldn’t kill Lin Ming today, then one day, Lin Ming would become the gravedigger for all 12 Skysplit Towers!

He was absolutely a terrifying threat! In fact, he was far more horrible and dreadful than even the Eightfall War Emperor! He had the personal reasons and also the ability to personally bury the entire Blood Slaughter Steppes under his feet, drowning the land in a sea of blood!

“Hurry and take advantage of this time while he’s concentrating the Heavenly Demon phantom to kill him!”

Elder Xiao leapt forwards. The Great Ax Tower Master also hesitated for a moment before throwing himself forwards too. At this time, there was no way he could retreat unless he turned and ran into the Eternal Demon Abyss. But, this was the only nearby exit from the Eternal Demon Abyss and it would soon close. Running away would be no different from suicide!

One on the left, one on the right, Elder Xiao and the Great Ax Tower Master attacked together!

At this time, the Heavenly Demon phantom released a deafening, earth-shaking roar. A terrifying force field fell over everyone like the end of times!

In that instant, Elder Xiao and the Great Ax Tower Master felt a deep fear in their hearts. This was a killing intent directed at their very souls, causing everyone to tremble where they stood!

This was…

The Death God force field of the Heavenly Demon martial intent!

Under the cover of this infernal energy that was so thick it manifested into essence, Elder Xiao and the Great Ax Tower Master’s striking power had instantly and unexpectedly weakened by 30%. At the same time, the Heavenly Demon phantom behind Lin Ming suddenly shrunk, instantly minimizing from 40-50 feet to half a foot, turning into a complete twelve-winged Heavenly Demon Tattoo that landed on Lin Ming’s arm.

After condensing the complete Heavenly Demon Tattoo, Lin Ming felt his body filled with an explosive power. Facing the attacks of Elder Xiao and the Great Ax Tower Master, Lin Ming poured all of this destructive energy into his spear, thrusting it out!

Penetrating Rainbow!

Bang!

A terrifying blast wave combusted, appearing like a massive red and purple lotus blooming in the world. All of the space in the area began to twist together. After being struck by such a terrifying strike, Elder Xiao and the Great Ax Tower Master were flung away like leaves in a storm. The previously injured Elder Xiao spat out another mouthful of blood. As for the Great Ax Tower Master, although he didn’t vomit blood, the palm of his hand directly cracked apart!

With a ‘ka ka ka’ sound, a massive crack had appeared in the double-headed ax in his hand!

Chapter 680 – Subdue

“Let’s attack together!”

An Elder loudly shouted as he faced the Giant Leviathan’s tentacles, extracting a ruler from his spatial ring at the same time.

The other Elder took out a heavy sword. The two of them began revolving their true essence to the limit, using their ultimate abilities!

Two storms of black true essence erupted. Under the minute control of the two Elders, the two attacks fused as one, heavily smashing into the net of tentacles.

Bang!

Flames exploded. Several shining tentacles that bore the brunt of the attack dimmed down, rapidly shrinking back. However, more and more tentacles rushed forth to take their place, leaving no room for the two Elders to run as before.

“This is bad!”

Seeing the tentacles that were filled with energy rush towards them, the two great Elders’ eyes turned blood red. With their insignificant first stage Life Destruction strength, resisting this net made of the Giant Leviathan’s tentacles was impossible.

“I’ll use up my life!”

The two Elders thought of this idea at the same time. However, something happened that shocked them. As the great tentacles rushed towards them, they actually began to slow down, wrapping around them without even the slightest intent of piercing through their bodies.

Ka ka ka!

The two Elders felt as if their bodies were being constricted by several large pythons. Their organs ached with an agonizing pain, and their bones almost broke.

“This damn beast!”

The two great Elders dripped with sweat from the pain. They had lost any and all strength to resist.

At the same time as their hearts filled with grief and despair, they also realized something. This Giant Leviathan must have been controlled by someone, otherwise it would have killed them and  not surrounded them like this.

As for the one who could control the Giant Leviathan, they could only think of one person.

That was… Lin Ming!

The two Elders could scarcely believe this. When Xuan Wuji had laid down his control onto the Giant Leviathan, he had made a massive array formation, used a secret skill to stimulate his soul potential, and had even gathered countless masters to support him. Even then, he had just barely managed to succeed.

But Lin Ming, with just his strength alone, how was he able to simultaneously fend off and counter the attack of four Elders, forcefully wipe off the soul mark that Xuan Wuji had left behind, and then even plant his own soul mark in such a short time?

Thinking of this, the two Elders began to have a deep sense of fear swell from within them. They no longer regarded Lin Ming as a 20 year old youth. To them he was now a monstrous genius, a terrifying and mysterious existence beyond their comprehension.

Woosh!

The two Elders felt their bodies tighten. The Giant Leviathan’s tentacles rapidly returned as the beast opened its great maw and swallowed both Elders. The two Elders saw pitch black for a brief moment, and in the next instant they had arrived in a light red dimension.

…..

10 miles away, as Feng Shen, Duanmu Qun, and Lan Xin saw this, they were all shocked speechless.

After Lin Ming had drilled his way into the Giant Leviathan’s body, he had used some unknown method to cause the Giant Leviathan to roar out in pain for an entire quarter of an hour. Then, something surprising happened. All of the South Sea Demon Region Elders began to escape separately. The two in front were fortunately able to escape safely, but the two behind them were far too slow. They had been caught by the Giant Leviathan!

What was going on?

“It’s like… this Giant Leviathan has been subdued by Lin Ming?” Feng Shen couldn’t believe his own words as they came out of his mouth, but this was the only plausible explanation.

Duanmu Qun also praised, “Incredible. Although this Giant Leviathan is not too great in one-on-one combat, it can display a massive destructive force in a large-scale battlefield. This is a great war beast that even a Holy Land would be jealous of. I have no idea what Lin Ming did; his every action is a riddle to us.”

Duanmu Qun sighed. At this time he no longer thought about competing with Lin Ming. As long as he could remain on good terms with Lin Ming, then that would allow the future of his Divine Wood Holy Land to see a broader and higher road.

At this time, in the Giant Leviathan’s inner dimension Lin Ming wore black clothes as he stood tall, his hands crossed behind his back. He was calmly staring at the two Elders. Although his gaze was peaceful, there was also a faint edge to it that caused one’s heartbeat to skip a beat.

“Lin Ming…”

An Elder gulped. When a bounty was placed on Lin Ming throughout the entire South Sea, he had seen Lin Ming’s portrait. This youth in front of him seemed similar, but there was a very great difference in his temperament. The Lin Ming in the portraits was a handsome and delicate youth, but the Lin Ming in front of them was like a king that commanded life and death!

“You… just who are you?”

An Elder couldn’t help but ask. He couldn’t imagine that this terrifying existence in front of him was just a 20 year old youth.

When this Elder was young, he too had been a Saint level talent. When he was 20 years old, he had been a late Houtian martial artist. Because of his superb talent, he was just able to fight the worst of Xiantian level masters. This was already a very stunning achievement. But compared to Lin Ming, even describing this difference as cloud and mud wasn’t enough to do it justice.

“I am who I am. As for my Lin Ming’s name, I think that you already know!” Lin Ming indifferently flourished his white spear and pointed it towards the two Elders. “I will now give you a choice. Surrender to me and allow me to freely plant a slave seal in you for 50 years. After 50 years, I shall free you! Otherwise, your only other choice is death!”

Lin Ming had originally wanted to kill these two Elders, but after deliberating upon it some more, a first stage Life Destruction master did have a very good combat strength. It had to be known that Mu Fengxian herself was also a first stage Life Destruction master.

Waging war against a sect was not a matter of a single person, much less when Lin Ming’s own individual strength wasn’t actually that strong.

Facing the powerful Xuan Wuji, Lin Ming had to grab as many advantages as he could. Xuan Wuji would soon exit his seclusion. At that time, even if Lin Ming was weaker than Xuan Wuji, he still had to have the qualifications to content with him.

“Humph, I would rather die than have a slave seal planted in me!” An Elder spat out between clenched teeth. To a proud martial artist, a slave seal was simply the highest form of insult. Once a slave seal was planted he would be nothing but a mindless slave; he would never be able to have his own thoughts.

“Then let me help you!” Lin Ming said without hesitation. He lifted his spear, about to kill them, when at this moment the other Elder shouted out, “Wait!”

Lin Ming’s hand stopped. He asked, “What else do you have to say?”

The other Elder’s mind raced. He grit his teeth and said, “You said that this slave seal will only be for 50 years, why should I believe you?”

After a slave seal was planted, the slave would have to obey every single order from their master, unable to even commit suicide. If Lin Ming didn’t release this slave seal 50 years from now, then that was truly a life worse than death.

Lin Ming sneered, “I can control at most 10 people with my slave seals. Thus, you two simply do not have the qualifications to be my servants for 50 years. Does this explanation satisfy you?”

Lin Ming’s words could be described as excessively arrogant and unrestrained. After the Elder heard this, he was greatly uncomfortable in his heart. But even so, he still couldn’t help but acknowledge that Lin Ming had the capital to speak his words. 50 years later, Lin Ming would have already become a Peerless Emperor, possibly even standing at the pinnacle of all Emperor level powerhouses. How could he possibly waste two slots of his slave seals to raise up two first stage Life Destruction slaves?

The Elder bit out, “Alright, I agree!”

“Elder Sun, you…” The Elder that said he would rather die than submit saw this other Elder compromise and began to panic. “You would rather throw away your dignity and ruin your heart of martial arts just so you can live on in such dishonor? Do you know that after being controlled, Lin Ming will make us kill our own descendants!”

“Elder Zhou, you’re still thinking about that at a time like this?” Elder Sun gloomily lifted his eyes, listlessly looking at the other old man. “Us demonic path martial artists have always cared about ourselves first and foremost, taking ourselves as the center of all decisions. So who cares if we’re forced to betray and kill those from the South Sea Demon Region? As for my heart of martial arts, who cares? Our cultivations have reached reached the limit that we can attain. In our lives, there is no hope for us to ever reach the second stage of Life Destruction, so why would I care if my heart of martial arts is ruined? If you want to die then I won’t stop you, but I don’t want to die, I haven’t lived my life yet. In the first half of my life I desperately struggled for all lucky chances like a madman, closing up to practice, and now after great difficulty I can finally enjoy the fruits of my labors. I also want to enjoy my next several hundred years of life. I do not want to die here!”

Some martial artists, such as Lin Ming, practiced martial artists to reach the pinnacle of martial arts.

Some martial artists who practiced martial artists did so in order to gain more power, have a higher status, and enjoy all the beauties and mortal sins of the world.

Elder Sun was one of these latter martial artists. He was too nostalgic and reluctant to part with his life, he simply hadn’t enjoyed it enough. If a Life Destruction powerhouse didn’t participate in the wars of a sect and didn’t try to find lucky chances to break through to higher realms, then they could casually go to any smaller land and enjoy life like a living god.

Hearing Elder Sun say this, Elder Zhou also hesitated.

If one could live, who would want to die?

……………

1,000,000 miles away, Profound Province –

The southernmost side of the Sky Spill Continent had a total of ten domains and nine provinces. Among these, a ‘province’ was slightly smaller than a domain. For instance, the surrounding territory of Divine Phoenix Island was considered the Divine Phoenix Province.

The Divine Phoenix Province was subordinate to another greater domain, but there were also some provinces that were independent. For instance, the Profound Province was like this.

The Profound Province was located in between the Five Element Region and the Judge Mountain Province. It was one million miles away from the South Horizon Region.

The number one sect of Profound Province was the Yin Yang Profound Palace, a newly promoted fifth-grade sect.

Yin Yang Profound Palace’s cultivation methods focused particularly on double cultivating as a complementary ability. Here, double cultivation benefited both man and woman. It was different from the violent sucking of energy style that the South Sea Demon Region practiced. Thus, the Yin Yang Profound Palace could be barely considered an orthodox sect.

Because of the special characteristics of this cultivation method, many disciples of the Yin Yang Profound Palace were married couples that cultivated together.

Even the Palace Masters of Yin Yang Profound Palace were a couple. The man was named Xing Ji and the woman was named Xing Can; they were renowned as the double Yin and Yang stars.

The Xing couple’s cultivations were both at the extreme second stage Life Destruction. Because of their Yin Yang cultivation method, they were especially well suited to combining their attacks. If the two of them joined forces, they were actually just able to deal with a third stage Life Destruction powerhouse.

The Xing couple had one son. His name was Xing Yang and he was an Emperor level talent.

As long as an Emperor level talent didn’t die, they would have a slim chance of becoming a true Emperor level powerhouse.

The Xing couple had placed very high expectations on Xing Yang. They hoped that he could become an Emperor level powerhouse in the future and lead their Yin Yang Profound Palace to become a true Holy Land.

At this time, within an elegant courtyard at the eastern section of Yin Yang Profound Palace…

A great millennium old tree stretched out its lush leaves and branches, covering the entire courtyard. Underneath this great tree, there was a simple stone table, and on this stone table was a tea set. Sitting around this stone table were three people.

The one in charge at this table was an elderly woman wearing a robe. Her silver hair was nobly coiffed upwards, bound with an exquisite phoenix hairpin.

This person was the Highest Elder of Divine Phoenix Island, Mu Fengxian!

Chapter 690 – Kiss

Ever since Lin Ming left and Divine Phoenix Island had encountered disaster after disaster, Mu Qianyu had imagined countless times in her mind just what her reunion with Lin Ming would be like.

In her most ideal dreams, it was nothing more than Lin Ming returning back stronger. He would return to her, help her hold up the skies, shelter her from wind and rain, and do his best to turn the tide.

However, this was nothing but her wishes.

When Lin Ming left, he had only been at the Xiantian realm. As for Xuan Wuji, he would soon reach the fourth stage of Life Destruction. If just a short 10 years, even if Lin Ming’s talent far surpassed everyone else within the Sky Spill Continent, a genius that had never been seen since ancient times, it would still be impossible to reach such a formidable degree.

10 years was simply too short a time for the growth of a top master. Moreover, there was the possibility that Lin Ming’s potential would be exhausted. After all, there were many variables in the growth of a genius. Just because they were rising stars in their youth didn’t mean they would absolutely become top masters in the future.

What Mu Qianyu cared about was not what degree of strength Lin Ming could obtain, but whether or not he would be able to return safe and sound. With Lin Ming’s personality, she knew that he wasn’t someone that would resign himself to mediocrity.

On this journey that he traveled alone, he would undoubtedly enter into all sorts of mystic realms and danger zones. The risks and perils he would encounter could be imagined.

Mu Qianyu feared that if Lin Ming left, she would never hear from him again.

In that case, she would really perish from her suffocating sadness.

She was looking forward to meeting after this 10 year promise, but at the same time she was also scared. She was scared that 10 years from now, she would go to Thundercrash Mountain to wait for something that was only a dream!

She never imagined that in just a short two and a half years of time, Lin Ming would actually appear in front of her, well and safe. Compared to when he left, his appearance hadn’t changed much. It was just that the temperament and aura revealed between his brows was different from before. He had lived through many great changes, and the air around him seemed much sharper and fiercer than before.

Although his temperament was different, he still gave off an incomparably familiar feeling that absolutely proved it was him beyond a shadow of any doubt.

Mu Qianyu’s soul trembled.

This time, she no longer cared about what he had experienced or how strong he had become. A single thought echoed out again and again in her mind…

He returned! He had safely returned!

Mu Qianyu covered her mouth. She didn’t know why, but at the moment she saw Lin Ming, all the grievances and pained she had suffered for this past two and a half years, all of that pressure she had to bear, all of it seemed to be washed away from her heart.

As she saw Lin Ming, her heart and mind filled with an overwhelming joy, so great that she couldn’t help but burst into tears.

Was this a dream?

Lin Ming stopped a few dozen feet in front of Mu Qianyu, neither of them speaking.

When Lin Ming first saw Mu Qianyu, it was like their souls connected, blending together, allowing him to experience everything she was feeling.

He could feel her helplessness and her fragileness. He could feel that the walls she had set up to support herself had come tumbling down, all of her emotions pouring out from her.

Lin Ming felt fortunate. He was glad that he had come back early. Otherwise, if seven and a half years of time passed again, he couldn’t imagine just what would have happened.

He subconsciously opened his arms, wanting to hold her. But, he actually stopped halfway, stiffening a bit.

His love towards Mu Qianyu was intermingled with respect, a sense that came from Mu Qianyu’s otherworldly temperament that seemed to defy being defiled or blasphemed by anyone.

This was also the reason that Lin Ming referred to Mu Qianyu as Miss Mu and Senior-apprentice Sister.

However, Lin Ming hadn’t thought that just as he opened his arms, he would see a flash of red in front of him, and suddenly a warm and fragrant body came rushing into his embrace.

Smooth arms were like snakes that wrapped around Lin Ming’s back and neck. Mu Qianyu seemed to exhaust all of her strength as she hugged Lin Ming without reservation, as if she wanted to meld her body into his.

Lin Ming could even feel a slight ache from his back from the force of those two arms.

“Hold me…”

Mu Qianyu whispered into Lin Ming’s ear, as if she was afraid he would disappear once she let go.

Lin Ming hugged Mu Qianyu. As he ran his hands down her back, he could feel her smooth and tender body through the silk fabric of her clothes. As they held onto each other with no space between them, he could feel the touch of a beautiful woman’s breasts against his own chest.

The light fragrance of a woman filled his senses. He could hear Mu Qianyu’s heartbeat and feel her breath.

This sort of wonderful feeling held an incomparably charming and tender warmth. Ever since those three sweet days at Thundercrash Mountain, Lin Ming hadn’t had such intimate contact with Mu Qianyu.

In this moment, in the entire world it was as if only the two of them existed. In the silence of the mountains, as the stars brightly shimmered in the night sky, their two lonely hearts seemed to support each other.

Mu Qianyu quietly fell into Lin Ming’s arms. From when she was born until now, she had never felt as fragile or happy as she did today. She wanted to hug Lin Ming and place everything she had with him.

In this brief instant, all she felt was him. Any sort of rain or wind or disaster, nothing mattered anymore.

The two of them hugged for an entire quarter of an hour. When Mu Qianyu’s tears finally stopped flowing, she said in a quiet voice, “I’ve missed you…”

These simple words, without an embellishment, actually contained all of her true feelings for these last two and a half years.

“I know.” Lin Ming gently said. As he looked down, he could see Mu Qianyu looking up at him. A crystal clear tear still shined at the corner of her eyes, sparkling like radiant silver underneath the moonlight, like bright pearls blooming in the deep sea.

In this cold moonlight, with this beautiful woman looking at him, everything seemed hazy as if it were a perfect dream.

Lin Ming felt his heart throb.

He cradled Mu Qianyu’s face in his hands, he paused for several breaths of time.

Then, he kissed her.

Mu Qianyu’s body trembled. The world faded away. Her arms instantly tightened around his body and her entire body seemed to soften into his. She closed her eyes as her long lashes gently trembled, lost in this deep abyss of this kiss.

This was Lin Ming’s first kiss, and it was also Mu Qianyu’s first kiss.

He greedily nibbled on her cherry-red lips, sucking on the tip of her wet tongue until Mu Qianyu’s entire being shivered. Only then did the two of them reluctantly break away from each other.

“Everything will be fine now.” Lin Ming whispered in Mu Qianyu’s ear. These words were not empty words of comfort. This was a vow. A vow he made from the confidence in his own strength.

As long as he was here, everything would be fine!

However, Mu Qianyu could no longer tell the difference between these words now. She gave a soft cry of pleasure as her face flushed red with blood. Her cheeks seemed like a ripe peach right now, wet enough that they would drip water with just a little pinch.

She softly poured herself into Lin Ming’s chest, allowing her entire body to weigh down on Lin Ming’s shoulder. Her breath caught in her chest and she exhaled. Ever since Mu Qianyu was young, she had rarely come into contact with men at Divine Phoenix Island. Thus, she was unfamiliar with the relations between men and women. Within Thundercrash Mountain, although it was an ambiguous time, that was only a chance meeting that Mu Qianyu had with Lin Ming; it was impossible for her heart to be affected. That sort of ambiguous encounter had allowed left her shy and embarrassed, charmed by Lin Ming. It wasn’t like now, where her heart throbbed and she was unable to stop her actions.

“Senior-apprentice Sister, how are Xingxuan and my parents?” Lin Ming suddenly asked. Besides Mu Qianyu, his greatest worries were Qin Xingxuan and his parents.

Mu Qianyu said, “When Divine Phoenix Island was destroyed, the sect was in a very precarious situation. Honorable Sect Master asked the disciples of Divine Phoenix Island whether or not they were willing to go to Ying Yang Profound Palace. Many of the lower level disciples left because of this… and as for Xingxuan… she originally wanted to come with us, but I was worried that she might have an accident if she stayed with us. I arranged for her to secretly go to a mortal country in the Five Element Region where your parents are also staying.

For a martial artist’s cultivation, they needed spiritual lands, resources, practice arrays, and so forth. Normally, a martial artist wouldn’t go to a mortal country. But, Mu Qianyu believed that what Qin Xingxuan needed the most was not cultivation, but to go on living in peace and safety. If Qin Xingxuan went to a mortal country, then with her Houtian realm strength, that was enough to guarantee her and Lin Ming’s parents’ safety.  As for the South Sea Demon Region, it was impossible for them to chase down a single unknown Houtian realm martial artist over a million miles away.

“I see…” Hearing that Qin Xingxuan and his parents were safe, Lin Ming let out a sigh of relief. As long as they were safe and alive then it was great. As for everything else that was lost, it could be taken back.

At this time, Mu Qianyu finally discovered Lin Ming’s cultivation. Her eyes widened as she said with disbelief, “Lin Ming… you… you’ve broken through to Revolving Core?”

“Yes. Just several days ago I made a lucky breakthrough.”

“This…”

Mu Qianyu covered her mouth, shocked speechless. Two and a half years ago, Lin Ming was at the early Xiantian realm. After leaving for such a short time, he actually managed to break through to Revolving Core!

And looking at Lin Ming’s dantian, the energy was collected, the origin energy was dense, and a faint vortex could be vaguely seen. This was not an ordinary Revolving Core!

Although Mu Qianyu was also at the Revolving Core realm, this was far too different compared to Lin Ming!

“How could… this be so fast…”

With Mu Qianyu’s talent, she broke through to the Xiantian realm when she was 22 years old and then to Revolving Core when she was 30. This had taken a full eight years. But, Lin Ming had only used two and a half years, and he wasn’t even 21 years old yet!

When Mu Qianyu was Lin Ming’s age, she was only at the peak Houtian realm!

This was simply the difference between the heavens and earth.

This was no longer something that could be described as just an Emperor level talent.

“Lin Ming… how strong are you now?” Mu Qianyu asked with wide eyes. When Lin Ming had left, he was at the early Xiantian realm and Mu Qianyu was at the extreme Xiantian realm. The difference between their strength hadn’t been too great.

Now Lin Ming had jumped an entire boundary. By all reasoning he should have strength at least equal to a late Revolving Core master. Or perhaps he could even compare with the weakest of Life Destruction powerhouses.

Lin Ming naturally didn’t need to hide anything from Mu Qianyu. “I’m not too sure what the limits of my strength are. It’s only a rough estimate, but I can kill a first stage Life Destruction master. As for Xuan Yuqie and other second stage Life Destruction powerhouses, I’m probably not their match yet.”

“You can kill a first stage Life Destruction powerhouse?” Mu Qianyu’s heart jumped. Lin Ming’s strength was far more terrifying than what she had imagined.

In truth, Life Destruction was equal to the extreme Revolving Core. It was a very special stage within the Revolving Core realm. For Life Destruction martial artists, their true essence was also located in their dantian’s Revolving Core. It was only because they experienced a remolding and transformation of their bodies and dantian that a Life Destruction martial artist’s strength far surpassed that of a Revolving Core martial artist.

If Lin Ming could kill a first stage Life Destruction martial artist, what would happen once he reached Life Destruction?

As Mu Qianyu thought of this, she was suddenly startled. She seemed to think of something. If Lin Ming could kill a first stage Life Destruction martial artist…

She looked towards Lin Ming, an expression of disbelief on her face as she asked, “Lin Ming… 10 days ago, the one who pillaged and razed the South Sea Demon Region… that couldn’t have been you right…”

Chapter 691 – A Night Of Tender Warmth

In the rumors that Mu Qianyu had heard, the so-called Divine Kingdom Crown Prince had the strength to kill a first stage Life Destruction martial artist.

By himself, he stirred up the South Sea Demon Region, upheaving their world. He killed over a thousand disciples of the South Sea Demon Region and forced Xuan Yuqie into a miserable state where she couldn’t even fight back.

And now she asked Lin Ming because their two strengths seemed similar. Such a coincidence would certainly have Mu Qianyu associate them.

Hearing Mu Qianyu’s question, Lin Ming was a bit surprised. He never tried to deliberately hide his identity; he assumed that the people of Divine Phoenix Island would have already known about him. But now it seemed that the South Sea Demon Region had set up a blockade of all news, afraid that Great Zen Temple, Black Flood Dragon, or some other fifth-grade sect would try and partake in the share of Lin Ming.

Thinking about this, Lin Ming only sneered. The South Sea Demon Region had thought he was a lamb to be butchered, but they never imagined they would already be ruined before they could taste the meat.

Lin Ming said to Mu Qianyu, “Senior-apprentice Sister, I returned to the South Horizon Region one month ago yet I couldn’t find you. I learned that Divine Phoenix Island had been destroyed, and in sadness, I went to Divine Phoenix Island to search for clues. There, I discovered that the South Sea Demon Region had set up a branch. At the time, I didn’t know where you went, so I killed the branch Elder there to search his soul. The result was that I didn’t even obtain any news of you and instead brought Xuan Yuqie and the Giant Leviathan to come knocking on my door. As for the matters after that, I’m sure that you’re well aware.”

Lin Ming’s words seemed understated, but Mu Qianyu was already completely bewildered.

The death god of Divine Phoenix Island that had killed three Life Destruction Elders, stolen away the Giant Leviathan and even killed his way into the South Sea Demon Region…

All of these unbelievable events had come from Lin Ming’s hands!?

Venturing a guess was one matter, but hearing Lin Ming confirm her suspicions was a completely different matter.

“Lin Ming… you…”

Mu Qianyu didn’t know what to say.

Before this, Mu Yuhuang and everyone else was hoping that Lin Ming would be able to return in ten years and hold up the heavens for their Divine Phoenix Island. To Mu Qianyu, this already seemed like a very exaggerated possibility. After all, 10 years from now, Lin Ming would be around 27 or 28 years old; it would still be difficult for someone so young to face a fifth-grade sect by himself.

But, she never imagined that in just a short two and a half years, Lin Ming would not only return, but completely flip over the entire South Sea Demon Region!

Just what had Lin Ming experienced in these two and a half years? His talent was far more terrifying than when he left through the transmission array!

At that time, if a Divine Kingdom Crown Prince or some other favored son of heaven could compare with Lin Ming, then to the current Lin Ming, such a Crown Prince or Holy Son wouldn’t even be able to touch the hem of his pants!

It had to be known that the Divine Kingdom Crown Prince was reported to by nearly 30 years old. For a 30 year old youth to be able to change the entire South Sea war with just his own strength was already extremely shocking.

And Lin Ming was only 20 years old!

That was an entire 10 years young! This was a difference of 10 years in talent and this was even when compared to a Divine Kingdom Crown Prince!

Mu Qianyu didn’t know what to say to Lin Ming. After being stunned for a long time she mumbled, “Lin Ming, what have you been through these past two and a half years?”

Thinking of his experience through these past two and a half years, Lin Ming was also filled with emotion. For this entire time, nearly every day was filled with thoughts of death and battle.

“It’s a long story. Let’s go somewhere else and I’ll slowly tell you.” Lin Ming didn’t plan on hiding anything from Mu Qianyu. He wanted to tell Mu Qianyu about everything he had experienced in the Holy Demon Continent.

No matter how tough and stable Lin Ming’s will was, if he fought on the edge of danger for too long, he would still accumulate too much tension in his nerves and mind. What he wanted was some time to relax, and to be able to confide in someone who understood him that he had absolute trust in.

“Mm, let’s go to my cabin. It’s just underneath the mountain cliffs.” As Mu Qianyu spoke to here, her beautiful face flashed with a red blush like the glow of a setting sun.

Little Swallow Mountain didn’t have any buildings on it to begin with. The cabins were temporary residences set up for the Divine Phoenix Island disciples. Besides the courtyard for meetings and other official business, there were no other large scale constructions. Mu Qianyu didn’t want to bring Lin Ming to the meeting hall. Thus, the best place was naturally her own cabin.

To invite Lin Ming to her own bedroom in the dead of night was truly a bit… suspect. But, thinking about the relationship between them, this wasn’t anything strange. A martial artist who always acted according to their own heart and objectives simply didn’t care about the gossip from others.

Thinking like this, Mu Qianyu also calmed down, becoming much more confident in herself. Without waiting for Lin Ming’s reply she immediately jumped down the cliff.

The wind blowing down the mountain caused Mu Qianyu’s silk clothes to flap in the wind. Lin Ming was startled for a moment before he followed her, a strange sense of happiness surging in his heart.

If Mu Qianyu hadn’t felt that he belonged to her, she would never have made such an invitation.

The cliff was only a few hundred feet high; they arrived at the bottom of the cliff in an instant.

In the night of Little Swallow Mountain, the skies were black like ink and the stars dazzled against the vast vault of heaven. At the bottom of the cliff, the mountain winds washed over the grassy land like undulating waves. The sounds of insects were everywhere and the air was clear and fresh.

Walking on such a mountain, one’s mood would be especially tranquil.

Stepping through the soft grass, Mu Qianyu and Lin Ming soon came to a group of cabins. This area was one of the places with the richest heaven and earth origin energy on the entirety of Little Swallow Mountain. Not only was Mu Qianyu’s cabin here, but also Mu Bingyun, Mu Yuhuang, and Mu Fengxian’s.

A martial artist’s perception was very sensitive. As Lin Ming and Mu Qianyu walked near with no intention of hiding themselves, everyone naturally sensed the two. However, they all had a mature and tacit understanding of the situation and thus no one came out to greet them.

Quietly looking at this group of cabins, Mu Qianyu suddenly felt extremely embarrassed. Originally she didn’t think this was a big deal, but now that she was in this situation, Mu Qianyu began to have a guilty conscience as if she were doing something naughty.

“Mm… there isn’t an extra cabin, so you’ll have to stay here with me tonight.” Mu Qianyu awkwardly said as she opened the cabin door.

Naturally, Lin Ming would never say something ridiculous at this moment like that Duanmu Qun and the others were staying in the spirit boat, and there was actually plenty of room there. Wouldn’t that just be spoiling the fun too much?

After he calmed his mood, he stepped foot in Mu Qianyu’s room.

The layout of Mu Qianyu’s cabin was very simple. The wood furniture was newly carved and it hadn’t even been baked through with fire. It retained a great deal of its moisture, filling the entire cabin with a light scent of bark.

The cabin was comprised of one bedroom and one living room. There was a simple bookshelf in the living room, and on this bookshelf were several types of jade slips and dozens of ancient-looking books.

In her bedroom was a large wooden bed. On the bedside was a small set of drawers, and on this set of drawers was a small jade bottle with a Vermillion Bird Flower blooming within.

In truth, all of a martial artist’s belongings could be placed into their spatial rings. Anything that was placed out in this room was there for decoration.

“Is… is it too simple?” Mu Qianyu hesitantly asked. This was the first time that a man had ever entered her room. Even when they both stayed at Divine Phoenix Island, Lin Ming had never entered her room before.

This nervous feeling was a bit strange.

“It’s great.” Lin Ming lightly said, feeling the awkward atmosphere.

“Tell me about what you’ve been through these past two and a half years. I want to hear it.” Mu Qianyu pulled Lin Ming’s hand and they sat on her bed together. She lifted her chin, her bright eyes staring at Lin Ming just like a young girl that was eager to listen to bedtime stories.

“Okay.”

Thus, Lin Ming began his story from when he left the Demon God Imperial Palace. He recounted from the point he took the transmission array to the Holy Demon Continent. He recounted to her everything he knew about the races, customs, and influences of the Holy Demon Continent. He spoke of when he was severely wounded in the Bewitching Cloud Prairie and forced into slavery because he lost his strength. Then, he traveled to the Blood Slaughter Steppes and climbed up Polar Skysplit Tower. From there, he fought Xing Tian in a fatal battle on the second floor, stepping onto the third floor and then entering the King’s Cage where he faced the plotting of High Lord Heian.

Afterwards, he continuously defeated three great masters of the Heavenly Demon Seven Stars, and then killed High Lord Heian with his own hands. With his fame having sharply risen, through so many twists and turns, he then had to suffer the Polaris Tower Master planting a slave seal within him.

By tricking the Polaris Tower Master, he had managed to enter the Road of Emperor and comprehend his own battle spirit. Finally, he ventured into the Eternal Demon Abyss, capturing the demon bone and then being forced to stray into the 1000 mile forbidden zone. There, he picked up a profound gold divine fruit, discovered the corpse of a 100,000 year old goddess, and then, having broken through to Revolving Core, he then killed the Polaris Tower Master…

Besides matters related to Demonshine and the Magic Cube, Lin Ming didn’t conceal anything else. He truthfully told her everything.

Although Mu Qianyu knew that Lin Ming would experience many trials and tribulations through these two and a half years, she never imagined that he would wade through so many life and death dangers. Even with Lin Ming sitting safe and sound right beside her, as Mu Qianyu listened to him explain all of the perilous situations and dead ends he had run into, she felt her heart tightly clench in her chest. But as she listened to how he saved the day, turning danger into safety and reversing the situation, she also felt happy for him, a joy that came from the depths of her heart.

After Lin Ming finished speaking, because Mu Qianyu’s emotions had risen up and down several times, her face was blushing red. She gradually fell into Lin Ming’s arms.

The two of them supported each other as they kissed. Each of them felt the warm temperature of the other, gently stroke and caressing each other’s skin.

Whether it was Lin Ming who had experienced constant death and fighting for the last two and a half years, being worried most of the time, or whether it was Mu Qianyu, who had suffered through the great pressure of her position and watching everything around her fall apart to the wind and rain of life, both of them needed comfort, both of them needed warmth.

With a warm and fragrant body pressed into his chest, Lin Ming’s entire senses were filled with a delicate scent. Lin Ming felt as if he had embraced the entire world. This intoxicating feeling that set off butterflies in his stomach made his mind throb, even as a surge of lust and desire ignited in his heart, quietly simmering…

After so many years of martial arts practice, Lin Ming was no longer that newbie who had entered the Seven Profound Martial House, nearly losing his mind in the pass of passion on that sea jade platform.

Instead, he was a master who was capable of controlling his own emotions.

His thoughts stirred, and a light flashed in his eyes. He wanted to use his battle spirit to cut this rising desire. But then, he thought about it some more.

The fires of his desire were in truth the development of his own consciousness, a natural progression of his growth as a man. Why would he want to cut it?

From when he first encountered her at Thundercrash Mountain to when she welcomed him to Divine Phoenix Island, Mu Qianyu had truly cared for Lin Ming every step of the way.

When he entered the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm, it had seemed that Lin Ming was a star that fell from the heavens, and Mu Qianyu had fallen into sadness and despair for him.

In the Demon God Imperial Palace, Lin Ming had to face being hunted by Lei Jingtian. He had given her the Escape Symbol and the two of them had made a life and death vow. Finally, before he left through the ancient transmission array, they had promised each other a meeting ten years from now.

Every condition had been successful.

Then he would naturally allow this pass of passion to take its course.

Lin Ming slightly suppressed the desire in his heart and softly said, “Yu’er, how have you been for these past two and a half years?”

As Mu Qianyu heard Lin Ming refer to her as Yu’er, her heart throbbed. She didn’t know, but this small change in her name was in truth a decision from Lin Ming…

As she thought of these two and a half years, Mu Qianyu felt a bit sad. She hesitated for a moment and then truthfully spilled out her story. Now that Lin Ming had grown up, there was no need to hide anything from him anymore.

From the time that she and Lin Ming separated, she spoke of Xuan Wuji recklessly searching the entire South Sea for him. Then, she replayed the demise of the Wartime Alliance, the destruction of Divine Phoenix Island, then being forced to take refuge in Yin Yang Profound Palace, and then having to have their two Vermillion Birds taken away as well as having to suffer all sorts of harsh conditions.

Hearing this, Lin Ming frowned. “Little Flame and Fireshine were taken by Yin Yang Profound Palace?”

Chapter 697 – Hall of Flowing Blood

How…how could this be?

Xing Zizan covered his right chest, the blood thickly flowing through the cracks of his fingers. As he looked at his blood-soaked hands, his eyes filled with panic and disbelief.

Xing Zizan had instantly been defeated!

Behind Xing Zizan, Xing Yang was shocked speechless. He couldn’t bother to figure out how Lin Ming had done this. He just knew that chills were crawling down his back. With Lin Ming’s strength, killing him would only take an instant.

And before now, Lin Ming had already revealed a thick killing intent against him.

This was also natural. If Xing Yang was in Lin Ming’s position and someone had thoughts to take his woman, then he too would kill or castrate his enemy.

Moreover, Lin Ming, Duanmu Qun, Feng Shen, and Lan Xin all had heaven-step weapons and likely originated from a Holy Land. In front of a Holy Land descendant, he was the same as a beggar in front of a rich young lord. For these types of people, killing commoners over things like jealousy or disputes was nothing unusual!

It could said that even if Lin Ming killed him, with the absolute suppressive strength from a Holy Land, there was nothing his parents would be able to do.

Thinking of this, Xing Yang was extremely horrified. That impact of energy just now was so amazingly intense that it should have been sensed from the main peak. But could he persist until his parents arrived?

If he died because of something like jealousy, then he really would die in an unjustified manner.

‘Capture Mu Qianyu first!’

This thought suddenly flashed through Xing Yang’s mind. He was close to Mu Qianyu, and after Lin Ming used that Chasing Thunder spear skill to severely wound Xing Zizan just now, he was now several hundred feet away.

Xing Yang grit his teeth, a fierce light suddenly bursting out from his eyes. Mu Qianyu’s cultivation was only at the early Revolving Core realm and Xing Yang was at the late Revolving Core realm. In terms of talent, Xing Yang was above Mu Qianyu, and in terms of strength, he far exceeded her.

Quietly, with the slightest movement, he took a step backwards. He sent a true essence sound transmission to the eight Revolving Core Protectors, then he suddenly launched forwards!

Mu Qianyu was Lin Ming’s lover. Naturally, he would especially care for her safety. As long as he could capture Mu Qianyu then he wouldn’t need to fear being randomly harmed or killed, and he would be able to last until his parents came.

Xing Yang was not weak. He was an Emperor-level talent with a late Revolving Core cultivation. He could be said to be a powerhouse that had reached the limits of power beneath the Life Destruction realm!

Xing Yang’s sudden attack surpassed everyone’s expectations. Lin Ming, Mu Yuhuang, and everyone else were very far from Mu Qianyu now. Since Xing Yang was the first to move, he naturally held an advantage in speed.

“Yu’er, be careful!”

Mu Fengxian cried out in alarm. At this time, Mu Fengxian was the closest to Mu Bingyun. Because her life source had been damaged, she had stood far back from the battlefield with Mu Qianyu and Mu Bingyun. Now that she saw Xing Yang suddenly rush towards Mu Qianyu she had no other choice but to block him!

In terms of strength, Mu Fengxian was no longer Xing Yang’s match. But if she could delay him for even just a single breath of time that was enough for Lin Ming to catch up!

However, just as Mu Fengxian made her move, Xing Yang’s eight Revolving Core Protector guards also made theirs!

Just now they had received Xing Yang’s true essence sound transmission and were already prepared. The eight of them had trained together for a very long time and had incomparably tacit understandings with each other. As soon as one moved, all of them moved in unison.

These eight guards all had a cultivation at the mid or late Revolving Core. If they were able to set down a formation on the battlefield, then they could use this to delay even a first-stage Life Destruction master for at least ten breaths of time.

Eight saber lights fused into one, cutting towards Mu Fengxian. Right now, Mu Fengxian was only equal to an ordinary late Revolving Core martial artist. There was no way she would be able to withstand this attack!

As Mu Yuhuang saw this she became full of anxiety. “Honorable Master!”

Mu Yuhuang was still 70-80 feet away from Mu Fengxian. As a first-stage Life Destruction master, she could quickly cross this distance in a brief moment. However, no matter how fast Mu Yuhuang’s steps were, it was still impossible for her to respond in time to that saber light!

As Mu Yuhuang’s feet began to move, the eight Revolving Core Protector’s saber lights had shot in front of Mu Fengxian. At the same time, Xing Yang had also appeared in front of Mu Qianyu, his hands reaching out for her soft, jade-white neck!

Mu Qianyu had experienced battles both great and small; she did not panic in the least. She revolved all of her true essence to the limit and flew out towards Lin Ming. But the difference in strength was too great and Xing Yang also had the advantage of surprise. In that instant, Xing Yang was only a foot away from Mu Qianyu.

Xing Yang’s eyes flashed with brutal light. In order to ensure the absolute success of grabbing her, this hold contained enough strength such that it was certain injure her.

“You want to die!?” Lin Ming’s eyes widened as an unparalleled, pure killing intent flashed in them. His feet pushed off and then unbelievable scene occurred. He was hundreds of feet away, but distance seemed to lose all meaning beneath Lin Ming’s movements. He flash stepped right to Xing Yang’s side, the spear in his hand already slamming down into Xing Yang’s wrist.

The heaven-step treasure struck Xing Yang’s flesh and blood body.

Puff!

With a light sound, Xing Yang’s wrist was crushed broken!

“Ahhhhh!”

With severe pain streaking throughout his body, Xing Yang grasped his wrist with a miserable scream as he tumbled away. Lin Ming didn’t even bother caring about him. Because behind him, not too far away, Mu Fengxian’s sword was about to collide with the saber light of those eight Revolving Core Protectors.

As for Lin Ming, not only was he far away from Mu Fengxian but he had just used his momentum now to stop Xing Yang. In this case, no matter how skilled Lin Ming was in the Concept of Space, he still wouldn’t have enough time to make it.

If Mu Fengxian bore the brunt of this attack, at most she would be injured; it wouldn’t endanger her life. But Mu Fengxian was already old and had damaged her life source. Even a minor wound now was not a trivial matter.

Lin Ming fiercely clenched his teeth and condensed his true essence. With the support of his battle spirit, the Asura force field erupted!

A force field was a special existence. In a vacuum without resistance, it traveled at the speed of light. To this force field, a 70-80 foot distance held no significance!

Bang!

Under the fires of Lin Ming’s anger, the force field’s energy spread out like an unstoppable tsunami.

Within the Asura force field, all power was suppressed. This included organs, muscles, bones, true essence, and even the soul!

The eight Revolving Core protectors were swallowed up by the surging waves of this Asura force field. Immediately, all of them felt as if they had smashed into an invisible brick wall.

Lin Ming’s strength was in-between the first and second stage of Life Destruction. Now, with the increased power of his battle spirit, his Asura force field was comparable to the original force field within the King’s Cage. If a weak martial artist were trapped within this force field they would simply perish on the spot!

Although the eight Revolving Core Protectors had formed a battle array, this battle array’s function was only to combine their saber light attacks together. As for this overwhelming force field that came instantly crashing down on them, they had no defense against it at all!

“Ahh!”

Several middle Revolving Core martial artists couldn’t withstand such an immense pressure suddenly weighing down on them. They fell over, gurgling blood!

This was just like an ordinary person suddenly appearing on one of the Sky Spill Continent’s stars where gravity was dozens or even hundreds of times stronger. Their organs, skeleton, dantian, spiritual sea, everything that comprised them would instantly come under a massive wave of pressure several dozen times greater than normal!

Peng!

A mid Revolving Core martial artist’s Revolving Core suddenly shattered, all of the true essence in his body suddenly vanishing. At his side, another mid Revolving Core martial artist’s heart stopped beating because of the heavy pressure. All of the blood vessels in his body burst apart and blood gushed out of his head!

Soon after, for all those Revolving Core martial artists, whether it was their dantian, heart, or spiritual sea, underneath the immense pressure of the Asura force field, everything began collapsing, instantly killing them all. Even the guard captain was bleeding from his ears. His face was paler than death and his body was limp as he almost fell to the ground.

After being devoured into that Asura force field, the battle formation of those eight Revolving Core Protectors naturally broke. As for that attack that was aimed towards Mu Fengxian, it no longer held any real threat and was easily countered by her.

“You…”

That late Revolving Core guard captain kneeled on the ground, barely supporting himself with his saber. He bit his lips as he looked at Lin Ming, his eyes full of fear and horror.

An uncaring expression remained in Lin Ming’s face. A blood-red light flashed in his eyes.

The Death God force field erupted!

The Death God force field superimposed onto the Asura force field. Although this was simply stacking them together, it was still enough to multiply their strength.

The guard captain only felt as if he had fallen into a blood pond from hell, drowning in its bloody waters, the manifested killing intent so thick and pure that it was swallowing him alive.

This so-called killing intent was in truth the will and desire of a martial artist to utterly extinguish the life of an enemy.

When martial artists desired to kill someone, they would first produce this will within their hearts, thus sending out a thick killing intent. When this killing intent coalesced into material essence, one could directly cut off the life of another without even moving a step!

The Asura force field could be said to be a crushing suppression of a martial artist’s body, true essence, dantian, energy, and spiritual sea.

As for the Death God force field, that was the will to snuff out a martial artist’s source of life. If one’s will wasn’t firm or their cultivation was insufficient, then once enveloped by this Death God force field, they would immediately be killed where they stood.

As the guard captain was simultaneously covered by the Death God force field and Asura force field, he vomited a mouthful of blood and his eyes turned white. He crumpled onto the ground, his fate unknown.

As Mu Yuhuang and Mu Fengxian saw this, both of them were shocked speechless.

Just how was this possible?

How had Lin Ming done this? Mu Bingyun also looked at Lin Ming, her indifferent eyes now filling with awe, horror, and complete disbelief.

When Lin Ming had sent a late Revolving Core Elder flying back with just a flick of his finger, that was still a movement, and he might have possibly even used his spear energy to wound him. Although it was truly the ability of a monstrous genius, it was still understandable.

But just now, Lin Ming had only turned around with death in his eyes, and that entire group of guards had suddenly and inexplicably died!

That was a battle array that could withstand a first-stage Life Destruction powerhouse for a period of time!

This had completely surpassed their understanding.

“Lin Ming, you…” After seeing this terrifying strength, Mu Fengxian looked at Lin Ming as if she didn’t recognize him anymore. This young man had surpassed all reckoning. In just two and a half years, Lin Ming had actually protected her, whereas she should be protecting him as he was her junior!

Not too far away, Duanmu Qun sucked in a deep breath, secretly admiring Lin Ming. Lin Ming’s Heavenly Demon force field had already gained a standard of proficiency at which he could freely use it and control it to a minute degree. In that moment when the force field had erupted like a devastating tsunami, it had instantly killed several Revolving Core Protectors. But as for himself, who had been standing just a few dozen feet away, all he felt was a light breeze without even a hint of suppression.

Lin Ming’s absolute control of his force field was bewildering!

Without a doubt, this was all because of Lin Ming’s powerful soul force and also because of his battle spirit.

Because he had formed his own battle spirit, Lin Ming’s will was exceedingly powerful. The will was in itself a kind of force field, and the battle spirit was a manifestation of that energy. Thus, a battle spirit could easily be fused into the Heavenly Demon force field, drastically increasing its strength.

At this time, the broken-handed Xing Yang was still rolling on the ground, crying in pain. Lin Ming sneered, angled his long spear, and slowly walked towards Xing Yang….

Chapter 702 – Xing Ji Arrives

The youth that stood  atop the Giant Leviathan didn’t have too high a cultivation but when the black-clothed Elder looked at the monster that was beneath his feet, he couldn’t conjure the least bit of resistance.

Moreover, based on the circumstances, the black-clothed Elder highly suspected that this youth in front of him was the Divine Kingdom Crown Prince that had been making such an uproar for nearly the entire last month.

Or at least a subordinate of the Divine Kingdom Crown Prince.

“Isn’t that Mu Qianyu and Mu Yuhuang?”

The black-clothed Elder saw the two red dressed women beside Lin Ming and gulped. He could feel a strange nagging sensation at the back of his mind. How could Divine Phoenix Island possibly be together with the Divine Kingdom Crown Prince? And from their appearance, they were obviously close to each other.

Upon seeing the massive amount of energy condensing within the Giant Leviathan’s body, the black-clothed Elder quickly said, “Great expert, mercy!”

Then he quickly turned to the two middle Revolving Core Protectors at his side and roared out,

“What are you two doing? Hurry up!”

To the Giant Leviathan, the Yin Yang Profound Palace’s great protective array was no different from paper. If they opened the array too late, then the entire thing would be completed broken by the Giant Leviathan. That would require an unthinkable amount of resources to restore.

The two middle Revolving Core Protectors froze for a moment before quickly flying out, shooting forwards like arrows.

In a short time, the entire array formation began to tremble. The barrier shield around the Yin Yang Profound palace slowly faded away. Standing atop the Giant Leviathan, Lin Ming calmly entered within.

The black-clothed Elder’s face was bitter as he saw this. He didn’t know what they had done or when Yin Yang Profound Palace had managed to offend such an evil star.

“Lin Ming, I can feel Little Flame’s energy from the southeast section of Yin Yang Profound Palace.” Mu Qianyu said from behind Lin Ming.

“Okay.”

Lin Ming ordered the Giant Leviathan to turn. The several dozens of miles long Giant Leviathan was nearly able to cover the entire Yin Yang Profound Palace.

Seeing this massive monster block out the heavens, all the martial artists within Yin Yang Profound Palace stopped what they were doing and looked towards the skies with bewildered expressions. They were shocked speechless. Just what the hell was that thing?

The South Sea Demon Region was over a million miles away from Yin Yang Profound Palace. Although the Giant Leviathan had become infamous even this far out, the martial artists of Yin Yang Profound Palace had never seen it before, thus they couldn’t recognize it.

They all came out of their residences and training areas, flabbergasted as they stared at the massive titan floating in the sky with absolute dismay.

The Giant Leviathan’s terrifying aspect laid in its great size. Its thick and oily skin was more than thousands of feet thick. Let alone how tough this skin was, even ordinary rock that thick would have been difficult to break open. Thus, the Giant Leviathan’s defense was nearly impenetrable by any martial artist below the Divine Sea realm.

As for its striking power, there was no need to elaborate on it. The massive figure didn’t even need to use its energy attack. As long as it was allowed to free fall, it would be able to flatten the entire Yin Yang Profound Palace.

“It’s that building over there!”

Mu Qianyu rapidly spoke as she pointed at a red tower 30 miles away. She could feel Little Flame’s energy coming from over there.

……..

In that great hall within that red tower, Little Flame and Fireshine were cowering, their neck and feet locked by red chains. During these past months, the two Vermillion Birds had constantly suffered from having blood drawn out from them, and now they were weakly crawling on the ground, their large red eyes bleak and filled with utter sadness.

The Vermillion Birds were intelligent creatures; they clearly knew what destiny awaited them.

Beside the Vermillion Birds, two old red-robed alchemists had squat down near the Vermillion Birds feet. They used a small silver dagger to cut open the legs of the Vermillion Birds, allowing the thick red blood to flow out, capturing the blood in small jade bottles. What they took was blood, not blood essence. A Vermillion Bird had a limited amount of blood essence; naturally, they couldn’t randomly take it. But, even if it was blood, taking it every single day still slowly consumed the Vermillion Bird’s vitality and essence energy.

However, the two Vermillion Birds seemed to understand that resistance was meaningless. They let the two red-robed old men draw their blood, lying there motionlessly as if they had already died.

In order for the alchemists to use the blood for research, they needed to have Vermillion Bird blood that was brimming with blood vitality. Thus, Yin Yang Profound Palace had force fed the Vermillion Birds blood poison pills to stimulate their bloodline potential. This sort of blood poison pill would certainly reduce the fires of the Vermillion Bird’s lives, shortening their life spans even further.

Of course, these alchemists never took these effects into consideration.

The red-robed alchemists chuckled as fresh blood streamed into the jade bottles… Just when they were about to put away the bottles, the half-dead Little Flame suddenly shook its head as if it were shocked by something. The two Vermillion Birds raised their heads, their bright and innocent eyes filled with a glimmer of hesitant hope and excitement.

“What are they doing?”

The red-robed alchemist frowned, not understanding the situation. Little Flame suddenly beat its wings as it tried to stand up. As it flapped its wings about, it directly caused the jade bottle of blood in the alchemist’s hands to fall down.

“F*ck!”

The red-robed alchemist was furious. He took out a thick whip from his waist and struck Little Flame with it. With a loud snapping sound, Little Flame’s body fiercely trembled. After several months of torture, the Vermillion Bird was weakened to the point where it could not withstand such a cruel beating.

A blood wound appeared and several red feathers were whipped off. But, Little Flame bit its beak together, not making a single sound. Its eyes were full of wondrous hope as it looked outside of the hall. It could feel Mu Qianyu’s energy approaching. This caused Little Flame’s breathing to quicken, its big red eyes glowing with tears.

At that moment, a voice echoed in its mind.

“Don’t move! Little Flame, I’ll save you!”

Pa~

Another whip slashed against Little Flame’s body, opening its skin even more. “Get on the floor! Didn’t you hear me!?”

The red-robed alchemist angrily said. In order to draw out Little Flame’s blood, he needed the bird to lie on the ground.

However, Little Flame only trembled but it still struggled to stand with all its energy. It raised its head, waiting to greet its master.

Little Flame didn’t want to see Mu Qianyu in a distressed state where it seemed half-dead.

“You stupid bird! Are you dumb or something!” The red-robed alchemist’s whip came striking down again. Vermillion Birds could understand his words. But, even under this constant pain and intimidation, Little Flame simply didn’t listen to him.

“Lin Ming, please, faster, Little Flame is under attack…” Mu Qianyu covered her mouth, tears running down her eyes. She and Little Flame were connected to each other; she could feel everything that was happening to it.

“Understood.”

Lin Ming’s voice was ice-cold as his eyes filled with rage. 30 miles was only one thirds of the length of the Giant Leviathan.

“Lift up that tower!”

Lin Ming ruthlessly ordered.

Woosh woosh woosh!

Five thick tentacles shot out towards the red tower. As they approached, a barrier of light appeared around the tower. This was the tower’s defensive array formation.

Seeing this light, Lin Ming wasn’t surprised. He ordered, “Rip it open!”

Bang!

Underneath the forceful impact of five tentacles, the defensive array was torn apart and the tower shook.

Just as the alchemist was about to strike out with his whip again, he paused. Mm? What happened? He looked up with a dazed expression, and then a horrifying scene occurred.

The red tower’s roof suddenly split apart. It wasn’t just the roof, but the walls, floor, load-bearing beams, everything was being torn apart. Several large black tentacles crashed inside as the entire tower was torn in half.

“What is that!?”

The two red-robed alchemists paled. Their cultivations were at the early Revolving Core and extreme Xiantian. Underneath these massive tentacles, they were no different from little rats in front of a giant snake. They had no ability to resist.

“Run!”

The two red-robed alchemists reacted fairly fast. But, just as they turned to run away, tentacles already ripped through the floor and smashed into them.

“Ahh!”

“Ahh!”

With two miserable cries, the two red-robed alchemist’s chest were directly crushed flat, all of their organs turning to goo.

Against these two people, Lin Ming didn’t show the slightest bit of mercy. Since he had already killed eight people here, he didn’t mind killing another two.

“Little Flame!”

As soon as the tentacles ripped open the roof, Mu Qianyu was able to see Little Flame’s injured appearance. Little Flame’s entire body was covered with scars and blood, and the fires of its life were only one third of what they were at its peak. Mu Qianyu felt weak, like someone had twisted a knife in her heart.

Without waiting for the tentacles to wrap around Little Flame, Mu Qianyu rushed towards it. She clung to Little Flame’s neck, her tears soaking its faded feathers.

“Squawk squawk…”

Little Flame cried out in a soft voice. Its large red eyes were wet and its body shook as it gently covered Mu Qianyu with its wing. This was how Little Flame expressed its love and joy at seeing Mu Qianyu at last, all of the pent up emotions that had suddenly come swelling up.

Lin Ming and Mu Yuhuang also fell down at this time. As Mu Yuhuang saw Fireshine’s appearance, her eyes reddened with tears. However, she was much more composed and restrained than Mu Qianyu was. She walked forwards and gently touched Fireshine’s head.

“Let’s go up. I will settle Little Flame’s debt with Yin Yang Profound Palace.”

As Lin Ming spoke, several tentacles formed a lotus-like throne in front of them. By stepping onto this, they could quickly enter the dimension within the Giant Leviathan.

“Yu’er, Sect Master, please enter into the Giant Leviathan’s dimension first. I have a matter I must finish first.”

“Mm? What do you plan on doing?” Mu Yuhuang asked.

“Collect interest from Yin Yang Profound Palace.” Lin Ming’s eyes flashed with a cold light as he spoke. This caused Mu Yuhuang’s eyes to jump up. She wanted to give a few words of advice and tell him not to go too far. But after thinking about it some more, she didn’t say anything. For these past years, Lin Ming had always handled affairs accordingly and with absolute confidence. Even if it seemed impossible, he still managed to accomplish it somehow.

Thus, there was no need to say anything more. She only told him to be careful of Yin Yang Profound Palace’s Palace Masters and then stepped into the Giant Leviathan’s dimension with Mu Qianyu and the two Vermillion Birds.

Lin Ming stood on the Giant Leviathan’s fin and ordered it to fly towards Yin Yang Profound Palace’s medicine garden.

“Hehe, little boy, you want to rob Yin Yang Profound Palace’s medicine garden? I like this! Huhuhahaha!” Demonshine’s maliciously playful voice sounded out in Lin Ming’s mind.

“Mm…” Lin Ming nodded. In fact, he had an idea. Since the heaven and earth origin energy was so rich within the Giant Leviathan, then why didn’t he simply build up his own medicine garden within the Giant Leviathan? He could raise some spirit plants and spirit grass to pave his way to becoming an alchemist later.

As Lin Ming thought of this idea, his eyes suddenly widened. He discovered that several dozen miles away, a streak of light was racing across the horizon at an extremely high speed. Although this light was very far away, Lin Ming could determine that this incoming master was a second stage Life Destruction powerhouse.

Yin Yang Profound palace only had two second stage Life Destruction powerhouses: Xing Ji and Xing Can.

Xing Can was still at Little Swallow Mountain. Thus, this streak of light that was approaching from the opposite direction could only be the other Palace Master of Yin Yang Profound Palace, and also Xing Yang’s father… Xing Ji.

Chapter 706 – Reaching Black Hole Revolving Core

“Xingxuan, what is it?”

“Ah, nothing’s wrong… ” Qin Xingxuan quickly shook her head. But, this action of hers seemed as if she hoped to hide something.

Lin Ming’s mind stirred. He wanted to say something but he eventually didn’t.

Qin Xingxuan carefully took the jade box and placed it in her spatial ring. With these treasures, in addition to her current talent, it wouldn’t be any problem at all for her to reach Life Destruction in the future.

Lin Ming said, “Xingxuan, it’s getting late; I’ll return to my room first.”

“Mm, alright.” Qin Xingxuan nodded and then escorted Lin Ming out.

A night passed without words. The next morning, Lin Ming took his parents, little sister, along with Qin Xingxuan and Mu Qianyu to return to the Giant Leviathan’s dimension. The 90 mile long Giant Leviathan flew high in the sky, soaring towards the South Sea Demon Region.

Lin Ming’s plan was to go to the South Sea Demon Region and dig up their medicine garden. The last time he went there he had simply plundered away all the medicinal herbs, but he hadn’t taken away the spiritual earth. Lin Ming intended to go back and finish the job.

After the South Sea Demon Region had suffered such a catastrophe they had already learned from their mistakes. They created a formation of surrounding scouts, and when Lin Ming reached the 5000 mile border of the South Sea Demon Region, the scouts discovered him and relayed the news.

When Xuan Yuqie received this true essence sound transmission her face turned green with hate. She never thought that just after half a month, Lin Ming would ride the Giant Leviathan back here and attack the South Sea Demon Region again!

If this could be tolerated, what else could be too?

Bang!

The chair Xuan Yuqie was sitting on burst into pieces from her anger. She was so mad that she could feel her stomach twisting into queasy knots. But this time, besides escaping, there was nothing else she could do.

Grinding her shiny teeth together, Xuan Yuqie calmly issued out an order. “All South Sea Demon Region martial artists heed my orders. Cease all training and immediately leave the three Demon Region islands and gather at the Abyssal Islands 1600 miles away!”

“Ah?” The Elder in charge of relaying orders was stunned. He was about to ask what had happened when Xuan Yuqie angrily shouted out, “What are you doing, hurry up!”

The Elder quickly relayed the orders, frightened.

After the only person left over was Xuan Yuqie, she felt nauseous from the anger raging in her heart. “Lin Ming, you have gone too far! You and I are irreconcilable enemies!”

……………

By the time Lin Ming arrived at the South Sea Demon Region, all of the martial artists had already left. This surprised Lin Ming somewhat. He slowly ordered the Giant Leviathan to fly towards the South Sea Demon Region’s medicine garden and discovered that there weren’t many medicinal herbs left over. It seemed that almost everything had already been carried off by the South Sea Demon Region martial artists in their hasty retreat.

Lin Ming faintly smiled, not caring much. He didn’t come for those trash herbs to begin with. What he came for was the spiritual earth here.

The South Sea Demon Region’s medicine garden was already larger than the one in Yin Yang Profound palace; it was a full two square miles. Lin Ming sent out 400 to 500 tentacles, digging out the entire garden by the roots, and then took away as much as the Giant Leviathan could.

1600 miles away on a deserted island, Xuan Yuqie was watching all of this take place through the phantom shadows of an array disc. Her lungs nearly exploded with rage on the spot. Before she left, she had everyone pack up all their belongings and everything else valuable. It was only the medicine garden’s spiritual earth that she hadn’t thought to bring away, as it was impossible to do so to begin with. Now, even that was looted by Lin Ming.

He was simply a locust!

Wherever he went, everything was destroyed!

Her full milky white breasts fiercely heaved up and down. Xuan Yuqie roared out, “Lin Ming, I hope you f*cking die!”

……………..

Lin Ming commanded the Giant Leviathan to head tens of thousands of miles deep into the South Sea. There, the great beast began to slowly submerge downwards. The Giant Leviathan was a Saint Beast of the vast sea to begin with; it could dive hundreds of thousands of feet deep.

At such a depth, the water pressure was terrifying. Even if it were a first stage Life Destruction powerhouse, they would be greatly weakened if they had to fight in such an environment.

However, the Giant Leviathan was able to regulate the pressure within and outside of its body, freely moving in the deep sea.

At this time, in the dimension between the Giant Leviathan’s eyes, Lin Ming was sitting there, his eyes shut. In front of him were two high-grade earth-step Demon God Bones.

“Boy, are you planning to make a breakthrough in your boundary?” Demonshine’s voice asked in Lin Ming’s mind.

Lin Ming had broken into Revolving Core when he had first entered the Eternal Demon Abyss. Now, over half a year had already passed. In the ancient tomb of the goddess in the 1000 mile forbidden zone, Lin Ming had closed up and trained there for one month. He had reached the large success of the early Revolving Core realm. Afterwards, he had formed his 12-winged Heavenly Demon Tattoo and his cultivation had reached the peak of early Revolving Core. Now, with the support of these high-grade earth-step Demon God Bones, it wouldn’t be any problem for him to breakthrough to the middle Revolving Core realm, thus Demonshine had asked this question.

However, Lin Ming actually shook his head and said, “No, I plan on forming a Black Hole Revolving Core first, then I will consider making a breakthrough. Every day I don’t form a Black Hole Revolving Core, will be another day that I don’t make a breakthrough.

The so-called Black Hole Revolving Core was when one’s foundation reached the pinnacle. All of the true essence pellets and other energies within the dantian would completely condense onto the crystal core without anything escaping. This would form the most perfect Revolving Core. This sort of Revolving Core was like a black hole; there was only entry and the attraction force was also much greater.

For a martial artist that reached Black Hole Revolving Core, not only was the total true essence in their dantian far greater than normal, but the speed they absorbed heaven and earth origin energy was that much faster than other martial artists. There was simply no comparison between the two.

“Heh! Well said! If your foundation is not solid then it will become easy to encounter bottlenecks in your future cultivation. The most important thing to you is not making a break through, but building up your foundation! I estimate that Xuan Wuji still has several months before he can leave his seclusion. That should be enough for you to reach Black Hole Revolving Core.“

Demonshine said with appreciation. These past years, although Demonshine was not able to help too much in the material world, he was still able to guide and direct Lin Ming so that he had to take fewer detours in his roads of martial arts.

Lin Ming sat down cross-legged and took out a high-grade earth-step Demon God Bone. Then, he began to absorb the incomparably pure energy contained within.

With the support of this energy, the scattered true essence crystals that freely floated in the gaseous energy around the Revolving Core began to slowly condense together, falling onto the surface of the Revolving Core.

This was an extremely arduous and time consuming process. This was because the true essence crystal pellets were like stars in the sky. Not only that, but once these crystal pellets fell onto the Revolving Core’s surface they could also fall off again, forcing Lin Ming to redo the process.

In order to overcome these difficulties, he had to continuously reinforce the compression process.

And in order to do all this, it required a massive amount of time and energy. If he didn’t have these high-grade earth-step Demon God Bones supporting him, then Lin Ming might have needed one to two years before he was successful.

Thus, no matter how much of a monstrous talent one was, it was impossible to continue without the support of resources. One would only waste their potential before completely vanishing.

Training was a boring and lonesome process. Day after day passed. Because Lin Ming entered the ethereal martial intent state, he was able to rid himself of outside distractions and completely concentrate his thoughts on consolidating his foundation. Because he had taken some fasting pills before this, Lin Ming didn’t even need to eat or drink. In fact, he didn’t even need to move.

Ten days…

One month…

Two months…

Lin Ming seemed to have turned into a statue. If it weren’t for the fact that there was no dust in the Giant Leviathan’s dimension, he would have already become covered with a thick layer of it.

Finally, after two and a half months, the last several true essence crystals, underneath the energy compression of the Demon God Bone, cleanly settled onto the Revolving Core.

In that instant, there was a sudden change!

That Revolving Core that was uniformly spinning suddenly seemed as if it couldn’t withstand its own attractive force and it began emitting crackling ‘ka ka ka’ sounds. Lin Ming’s Revolving Core had begun to break!

However, this breakage was not merely the appearance of cracks, but rather the entire crystal core collapsing!

In the moment that the Revolving Core began to collapse, Lin Ming gave a stuffy cough and his body shook. He felt as if his heart had been grasped by a demonic claw and was being squeezed to a pulp!

Because he had lost control of all the energy within his body. It furiously and violently raced through his meridians as if it wanted to break out. His hands, feet, muscles, everything seemed as if it would explode. In that instant, Lin Ming even thought he would die here.

“Lin Ming, don’t worry! This is because your Revolving Core broke apart and temporarily lost its function. Once it reforms, you will be able to control your energy again.” Demonshine’s voice sounded out in Lin Ming’s mind. After a martial artist reached the Houtian realm, true essence would fully fuse into their body. But, the area where true essence gathered and condensed, the dantian, would become a martial artist’s greatest weakness. Once the dantian broke apart then a martial artist would immediately die.

Lin Ming was now almost in this situation.

Soon, Lin Ming couldn’t even breathe. His heart stopped beating and all the blood froze in him. Lin Ming was distressed to the extreme. However, he couldn’t even form a painful expression because he had lost control of the muscles in his face.

This state continued for a full 10 breaths of time. When his perception began to fade away, the shattered Revolving Core in his body suddenly burst out with a blazing black light. From its original walnut size, it shrunk to the size of a quail egg. The speed it was spinning increased by several times, and it turned from a dark gray to an absolute black without even the least bit of shine.

After the new Revolving Core formed, the lost control flushed back into Lin Ming like a surging tide. The true essence within his meridians started circulating again and his blood flow returned to normal. His entire body trembled and he fell to the floor, panting and breathing in great gulps of air. That feeling just now was really the same as dying.

“Boy, you’ve really done it this time! When the Demon Emperor was still on this planet, even he hadn’t reached this level!” Demonshine’s tone was somewhat sour. He couldn’t help but be a bit jealous of Lin Ming’s talent and ridiculously solid foundation. In the future, Lin Ming’s achievements would truly be limitless.

Lin Ming sat on the ground for a while as he caught his breath. As he examined his dantian, he found the new Revolving Core there. It was pitch black without a single bit of sheen to it, as if it were a portal that led to another time and space.

A Revolving Core was similar to a star. If the total mass was the same and the radius was smaller, then the gravitational force would be comparatively stronger.

At this time, Lin Ming’s Revolving Core was now able to attract surrounding heaven and earth origin energy several times faster than before. Lin Ming could faintly feel the origin energy within the Giant Leviathan constantly gathering around him. Even if Lin Ming didn’t take the initiative to absorb it, this energy would still be swallowed up by the Black Hole Revolving Core, quietly settling on the surface and becoming a part of his cultivation.

This is the self-cultivation of the Black Hole Revolving Core?” Lin Ming was shocked. When a martial artist formed a Black Hole Revolving Core, because of its greater ability to attract energy, it could automatically train itself. In just this aspect alone, it completely left all other ordinary Revolving Core martial artists in the dust.

Chapter 709 – Opening the Eight Inner Hidden Gates Again

Demonshine controlled the Giant Leviathan and rose from 350,000 feet to 30,000 feet. At this depth, the water pressure was still terrifying.

Xuan Wuji was standing guard at the seabed 100,000 feet deep. If the Giant Leviathan rose again then they would most likely meet Xuan Wuji’s attacks.

“Lin Ming, what do you plan on doing?” Demonshine asked. Although Lin Ming’s strength had suddenly shot up, he was still far from being able to compare to Xuan Wuji. Facing Xuan Wuji head on was no different from walking into the jaws of death.

Lin Ming said, “They can guard here as much as they want. I’ll go to their headquarters and see just how long they can stay. If they don’t go back, then they can watch as their entire lair is destroyed and everyone killed.”

Lin Ming had already formed his Black Hole Revolving Core and broken through to the middle Revolving Core realm. His strength had risen to yet another level. He estimated that with his current abilities, he should just barely be able to defeat a second-stage Life Destruction martial artist. But as for his true combat strength, he would need to fight with a second-stage Life Destruction martial artist to find out. Just from this, ruining their headquarters yet again wouldn’t be too difficult.

“Massacre their headquarters?” Demonshine’s eyes brightened. “Hahaha, I like! Boy, your tastes suit this Saint perfectly! Don’t worry. With this Saint managing this Giant Leviathan, it shouldn’t be difficult to stay here for half a year. Let go of your limits and destroy everything around you! I can’t wait to see just what expression those damn brats will have! Hahahaha!”

The more Lin Ming thought about it, the happier he was with this idea. This would place those bastards in a dilemma. If they continued to stay here and guard this area, then Lin Ming would ruin their entire headquarters. But, if they left, then he could calmly order the Giant Leviathan to return to sea level and restore itself to its best condition. This was truly a good move.

Lin Ming said, “Don’t worry. I’m going to temper my body first.”

As he spoke, he took out a gold fruit from his spatial ring. This was the profound gold divine fruit!

The profound gold divine fruit was similar to a mushroom of the mortal world. But, while a mushroom grew atop old wood, this profound gold divine fruit had grown atop a Demon God Bone.

It was known that a millennium-old Lingzhi that grew from old wood was considered a wondrous medicine. Then, having absorbed the essence of the Demon God Bone, the value of the  profound gold divine fruit could be imagined.

When Lin Ming had gone into the 1000-mile forbidden zone within the Eternal Demon Abyss, he had encountered four corpse devils. The corpse devils had bodies as durable as a heaven-step treasure. This had made it so Duanmu Qun’s and the others’ attacks couldn’t even scratch them.

If it weren’t for Lin Ming’s battle spirit, which he was able to pour into the Purple Comet Spear and substantially increase his striking power, then even he wouldn’t have been able to do anything to those four corpse devils.

When Lin Ming had chased a corpse devil back to its den, he had gone into that tomb and discovered the secrets within.

The reason they had such a terrifying defense was all because of this profound gold divine fruit.

The profound gold divine fruit was an extreme Yang and extreme light-attribute body transformation treasure. With those four corpse devil’s cultivations, they naturally couldn’t swallow it. But they absorbed the root of the profound gold divine fruit. When the profound gold divine fruit grew, it would absorb the essence within the root of the Demon God Bone. Thus, the energy within the root was naturally much weaker. The four corpse devils were just about able to absorb this with their cultivation.

“Lin Ming, you want to swallow this?” Demonshine was startled. The profound gold divine fruit could be classified as a Lingzhi grown using a Demon God Bone as nourishment. The inherent energy within was extraordinary. Demonshine wasn’t absolutely sure that Lin Ming would be able to withstand its effects. Not just that, but a profound gold divine fruit was a top-grade material of materials. If it was directly eaten then the effects would be quite lacking in comparison.

“Lin Ming, don’t you intend on becoming a top alchemist in the future and refining this profound gold divine fruit? If you do, then the effects will be several times better.”

Lin Ming shook his head, saying, “If I become a top alchemist, I fear it will take several years to do so. At that time I’ll already have new lucky chances. It’s not worth it to save this profound gold divine fruit and waste my own potential. For me, there is no heavenly treasure that is as valuable as time.”

“Hehe, well said, boy. You really don’t need to care about something like a mere profound gold divine fruit. This is a top-grade body transformation medicine. After eating it, it will greatly enhance your body’s defensive powers. Perhaps you might even become as durable as a top earth-step treasure or a heave-step treasure!”

A human’s body couldn’t be compared to a corpse devil’s. Even having the durability of a top earth-step treasure was freakish.

At this time, Lin Ming was not just tempering his body and increasing his defensive power, but he was also trying to take advantage of this opportunity to open the second of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates—the Gate of Limit.

At this time, a long time had already passed since Lin Ming opened the Gate of Healing. His body transformation foundation had become very solid since then. With a quality body transformation medicine like this profound gold divine fruit, then it shouldn’t be too difficult to breakthrough to the Gate of Limit.

“Black Hole Revolving Core, middle Revolving Core Realm, and the Gate of Limit opened too. Just what degree will my combat strength reach?”

Lin Ming clenched his fists together, a thick fighting spirit rising inside him. He was thoroughly anticipating fighting a second-stage Life Destruction powerhouse. In fact, he even wanted to go out right now and test out his abilities.

Taking the profound gold divine fruit in hand, Lin Ming could clearly feel the terrifying energy contained within. There was no need to mention eating it, just smelling its rich fragrance made him feel refreshed, as if all the cells in his body were being revitalized.

Lin Ming no longer hesitated. He swallowed the profound gold divine fruit down his throat. As soon as it entered his mouth, it turned into a surge of heat that melted into his body.

After several quiet breaths of time, the energy began to boil up like hot water, recklessly entering into Lin Ming’s blood vessels, running rampant everywhere!

Lin Ming’s blood vessels and body had already been tempered many times; it was as tough as a treasure. Even so, with such a terrifying influx of energy rushing into his body, it was still a bit difficult to withstand.

This sort of situation was well within Lin Ming’s expectations. All this time, Lin Ming had undergone similar scenarios many times. He bore the deep pain and calmly revolved the “True Primal Chaos Formula,” manipulating the energy of the profound gold divine fruit such that it smashed into the Gate of Limit at his spine.

The spine was also called the dragon bone. It was central axis and main pillar of the human body. It supported all other bones, including the head, chest, abdomen, and all limbs. Everything depended on their connection to the spine. When a person used any strength, this first had to pass through the spine.

The spine was like a bow. The more taut a bow, the tougher it was. The more flexible a spine was, the stronger a person was. However, the truth was that a martial artist’s spine often became one of their weaknesses.

This was because the spinal nerves were also located within the spine. The body of nerves was extremely complex and fragile. If these nerves were struck and cut off, then a martial artist would in essence become a cripple unless they had cultivated to an ever-living boundary. Otherwise, even with top heavenly treasures it would still be difficult to restore the contorted spinal nerves.

These characteristics of the spine made it so it was difficult to train it. A martial artist could train their muscles, organs, and bones, but it was difficult to train the nerves and marrow.

Lin Ming had completed to perfection Marrow Tempering and had also completed an initial tempering of his spinal cord. This was enough to fight those at Revolving Core and below, but when facing those at the Life Destruction realm and higher, it was still lacking.

Within the Eight Inner Hidden Gates, the Gate of Limit was used to train the supplementation of marrow.

The Gate of Limit gathered energy to enhance the defensive strength of the spine. Then, taking the spine as the center, it would guide a martial artist’s entire body, allowing their strength to multiply severalfold. Besides strength, a martial artist’s explosive force, bearing capacity, balance, and defensive power would all significantly increase.

Pa pa pa!

Lin Ming’s back cracked and crackled. An invisible stream of origin energy rapidly twisted around Lin Ming’s body, forming small storms. During this fierce collision of energy, Lin Ming’s clothing was not able to withstand the impact and quietly disintegrated into dust, revealing his solid and fit back, like that of a graceful leopard.

At this time, the skin and muscles of Lin Ming’s back had become a strange, translucent, jade-like color. Lin Ming’s entire spine was highlighted through this. The vertebra and the blood vessels were clearly visible and every single nerve could be made out. Starting at the bottom, from the base of the spine, a bright surge of crimson light crawled up. This bloody light gathered together, forming a bean-sized pearl of blood.

This was where the Gate of Limit was located!

Lin Ming was now heavily sweating. His breath was labored, and many of his meridians and blood vessels had burst apart, unable to withstand the tyrannical pressure and energy that ran recklessly through him. But he was completely unaware of this. He grit his teeth, gathering all the energy in his body and thrusting it towards where the energy of the profound gold divine fruit was, ramming both energies into the Gate of Limit.

Failure occurred again and again. Sweat streamed down Lin Ming like rain.

Two hours…

Four hours…

Slowly, Lin Ming’s sweat began to mix with rivulets of blood. If it weren’t for the strong regenerative powers of the Gate of Healing, then there would have simply been no way he could have supported himself for such a long time.

Even so, his face became incomparably pallid and his lips were deep purple. Because of the severe pain and twitching in his hands, the stone bed beneath his hands had been crushed to bits.

Even Demonshine was alarmed by this terrifying scene. Lin Ming was someone who cultivated with body and energy. At only a young 21 years of age, he had swallowed a profound gold divine fruit, constantly pushing the limits of his body. This resulted in him frequently having to bear enormous pain in the name of progress.

Another two hours passed. Lin Ming’s lips were torn from his biting and both his eyes were bloodshot.

“Break for me!”

Bang!

In that instant, all of the energy and blood vitality within Lin Ming’s body rushed into that spot at the base of his spine. Then, it was like something exploded there. Following that, blood shot out from that spinal area, blasting out hundreds of feet away like a crimson arrow.

After this blood shot out from him, Lin Ming collapsed. He fell onto the broken stone bed, covered with sweat, without even an ounce of strength left.

On his back, that strange jade-like sheen slowly disappeared and his skin became solid again, his muscles going back into hiding. After breaking through the Gate of Limit, he had used up too much strength.

“Lin Ming, I have to say I’m quite jealous of you and yet, strangely, I want you to succeed. You’ve reached the middle Revolving Core at only 21 years of age and you’ve also opened the second of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates. Even the Demon Emperor of the past is far inferior to you!”

Lin Ming didn’t even have the strength to answer. He was only able to crawl up and sit straight. His arms trembled as he took out a pill from his spatial ring and swallowed it, meditating afterwards.

Meanwhile, the Revolving Core in Lin Ming’s dantian crazily sucked in heaven and earth origin energy, helping to restore Lin Ming’s physical strength.

Two hours later, Lin Ming opened his eyes. Those dark eyes seemed to contain all the thunder of heaven and earth, making those who saw them tremble with fear.

“Let’s go.” Lin Ming stood up. His vision was like a keen sword as it shined with an icy killing intent.

Chapter 718 – A Shocking Trial Ground

“I’ve finally passed.” Lin Ming let out a breath of relief. That test had not been easy at all. When Lin Ming had passed the general level smelting trial, he had been young, thus the enemies he faced were correspondingly weaker. Even so, it had cost Lin Ming a massive amount of time to pass it, and if he hadn’t brought enough Vermillion Bird blood essence with him, then it might have been nearly impossible to pass the smelting trial in any reasonable period of time.

But now, Lin Ming’s age and cultivation had risen. Facing the king level smelting trial qualifier, it hadn’t been as difficult to pass. This proved that the rate Lin Ming grew had exceeded the Ancient Phoenix Great Temple’s expectations of someone from the royal line.

“Sir Temple Spirit, I have a question I would like to ask you. Those several successors and princes I fought, just how old were they?”

This was the question that Lin Ming most wanted to ask. He desired to know how his talent compared to those geniuses of the Ancient Phoenix Clan and just what degree the disparity between them was.

The Temple Spirit said, “Trial Challenger, your skeletal age is at 21 years. The difficult of your corresponding test should also be at the 21st rank. However, because your bloodline density is lacking, the true difficulty of your test was somewhat higher. Your matches were all 24 or 25 years old. They were all outstanding heroic elites of the Ancient Phoenix Clan’s Royal Family. However, when their phantoms faced you, their energy and cultivation were also under heavy suppression; they were in no way at their peak condition. Thus, it is impossible to assess your talent in comparison to theirs.

“I understand.”

Lin Ming wasn’t too surprised by this. In the Ancient Phoenix Clan, their resources and talents were far from what the Sky Spill Continent could compare with. For instance, the Nirvana Dragon Root was a rare and precious heavenly treasure that all Life Destruction masters of the Sky Spill Continent would go stark mad for. However, thinking about it some more, that Nirvana Dragon Root was in truth some unwanted medicinal herb kept in the Demon God Imperial Palace’s medicine garden by the Demon Emperor before he ascended into the Realm of the Gods. Although it’s value had surged because of the tens of thousands of years that had passed, when it was truly contrasted to the great sects within the Realm of the Gods with incomparably vast legacies, it wasn’t even worth mentioning.

There might be some half God Beast bloodline genius out there, using medicines and pills daily with a value that far surpassed the Nirvana Dragon Root. What they trained in were high-level Realm of the God’s cultivation methods that were in no way inferior to Lin Ming’s, and they would even have the guidance of old beings from the Realm of the Gods whose cultivation far surpassed that of the Divine Sea’s. Lin Ming didn’t find it strange that there would be many such individuals whose own comprehensive talent even exceeded his own.

Destiny was also a part of one’s talent. For a martial artist to be born in a great sect of the Realm of the Gods, or perhaps even a Holy Land, that too was a part of their destiny.

But for Lin Ming, although he originated from the lowliest of mortal backgrounds in one of the three thousand boundless worlds, simply one of a trillion trillion ants scurrying about, he still didn’t believe that his destiny was any less than that of an outstanding young elite from a Realm of the Gods Holy Land.

This was because…he had the Magic Cube.

Although the current Lin Ming hadn’t been able to perceive the secrets of the Magic Cube, he had a faint feeling that the Magic Cube might be one of the greatest treasures within the entire universe. As he grew stronger in the future, he would be able to unlock more and more of the Magic Cube’s powers, bringing him that much closer to the peak of all martial arts.

“Trial Challenger, we are here…” As the Temple Spirit spoke, the space around Lin Ming began to suddenly twist. A slight dizzying vertigo overcame him, and in the next moment he was sent up to a broad platform.

This platform was shaped like a massive circle, at least 10 miles in diameter. On its surface, there were a variety of mysterious, ancient runes engraved within; these were clearly array symbols.

However, what surprised Lin Ming was that he hadn’t seen a good number of these array symbols before. Lin Ming believed that he was skilled in understanding ancient array formations, but facing the patterns and marks on this platform, nearly everything here was completely unknown, making him feel a bit helpless.

Was this an array formation laid down by the Ancient Phoenix Clan?

“Sir Temple Spirit, are these the grounds for the king level smelting trial?” Lin Ming looked at the entire round platform. This platform emitted a simple, vast energy; it was startling. In addition to these mysterious, ancient runes, Lin Ming wouldn’t be surprised if it was something similar to the Seven Profound Valleys’ Ten Thousand Killing Array.

Of course, this Ancient Phoenix Great Temple’s array formation was like the difference between heaven and earth compared to that of the Seven Profound Valleys.

However, the Temple Spirit shook its head and said, “This is not the site of the king level smelting trial. Rather, it is the transmission altar that leads to the king level smelting trial….”

The Temple Spirit’s words were unhurried without any hint of emotion behind them. But as Lin Ming heard them, he was completely shocked!

What!?

This was only a transmission array!?

A ten-mile-wide transmission array covered in countless mystic runes!

Heavens! Where would such a transmission array lead to!?

In the broken world of the Demon God Imperial Palace, Lin Ming had seen a massive, ancient transmission array that was hundreds of feet high with 108 grooves for true essence stones. With all sorts of array symbols covering it, it had been a large-scale array formation.

That was the greatest transmission array Lin Ming had seen to date. But now, compared to this transmission array around him. It was absolutely overshadowed like an ant to an elephant.

This array formation was ten wiles wide! Spreading out his perception, Lin Ming discovered dozens of fist-sized grooves around him. As for the transmission altar itself, that was a thousand feet high!

The entire altar seemed carved from burning red jade. Lin Ming had never seen this jade-like material but he could feel the vibrant energy rolling off from it.

This sort of transmission array…

Lin Ming glanced at the Temple Spirit. If the Demon God Imperial Palace’s transmission array could send someone billions of miles away, then this transmission array could send someone trillions or even tens or hundreds of trillions of miles afar!

“Sir Temple Spirit, just where does this transmission array go to? If I can’t complete the smelting trial in half a year, I would rather not enter,” Lin Ming uneasily asked. If he went so far away, returning probably wouldn’t be easy.

“Trial Challenger, I cannot guarantee when you will complete the smelting trial. The king level smelting trial is considered one of the core cultivation resources of the Ancient Phoenix Clan, and is divided into several stages. You can only continue to the later stages if you complete the first stage of the smelting trial. Once you finish the first stage of the smelting trial, you may also return. But, as for how long it will take you, I cannot tell.”

“What’s the fastest time that a martial artist of the Ancient Phoenix Clan completed the trial?” Lin Ming quickly asked.

“The fastest was…72 days!”

As the Temple Spirit spoke this number, even though its nature was that of indifference, there was still a trace of respect and reverence in its tone. 72 days was a terrifying number.

“72 days…I understand.” Since there were people that could complete the trial in 72 days, then Lin Ming was confident that even if he couldn’t match that number, three months also wouldn’t be a problem.

The Temple Spirit shook its head and said, “Trial Challenger, 72 days for completion of the trial is not an Ancient Phoenix Clan Prince from my Nuyan Family. That individual had a perfect Phoenix Clan bloodline. That is, half of his bloodline came from humanity and the other half came from a Phoenix. His perception, talent, none of that can be measured with common sense. Perhaps you might not even have the qualifications to pass the very first stage of the smelting trial in 72 days.”

Perfect Phoenix Clan bloodline?

Lin Ming sucked in a deep breath. From the very first time he had stepped onto the road of martial arts, taking each step by step until he reached where he presently was, he was now finally able to approach those peak talents from the Realm of the Gods.

Now, he would finally traverse the same path that the heroic young elites of the Realm of the Gods once tread, climbing towards the true peak of martial arts!

Everything had to restart from zero. The road was now underneath his feet!

Lin Ming’s entire body burned with a brilliant fighting spirit. If he didn’t come into contact with the Realm of the Gods, then he would never see where the peak of all martial arts lay!

“I don’t need to finish in 72 days. As long as I can pass within half a year—that’s more than enough! Beam me up!”

“Good! It shall be as you wish.”

As the Temple Spirit finished speaking, from above the skies of the massive altar, hundreds of fist-sized crystals slowly fell down, fitting themselves into the grooves of the altar.

Lin Ming had never seen these red energy stones before. But from the energy fluctuations, he could sense that these crystals were incomparable to true essence stones or Blood Demon Crystals.

This was also within reason. In order to mobilize such a terrifyingly large transmission array, how could ordinary energy stones possibly be enough?

These red crystals were absolutely priceless. If just the consumption to transmit a young elite was so high, then the training resources they received could be imagined.

No wonder the Ancient Phoenix Clan held such strict requirements to qualify for the king level smelting trial. In order to train a single member of the Royal Family, this required a massive amount of resources. Even with Lin Ming’s talent, he still hadn’t obtained the qualifications easily.

Bang!

The red crystals erupted with energy. The entire transmission altar suddenly shook as all of the array symbols upon it lit up in dazzling succession!

A beam of fiery-red light shot out from the altar, straight into the skies. As Lin Ming stood on the transmission array, he felt an endless and terrifying pressure fall over him with overwhelming force, suppressing him to a nearly unbearable degree.

Heavenly Demon force field—open!

Lin Ming simultaneously released the Death God and Asura force fields. With their support, Lin Ming was just barely able to withstand this immense pressure.

This secretly shocked Lin Ming. “This transmission is truly extraordinary. If a normal Xiantian martial artist were to stand here, they would explode from the pressure!’

Bang!

The transmission array suddenly trembled. More and more red energy surged forth, covering the entire altar.

In the next moment, Lin Ming felt his body suddenly accelerate in a dizzying motion as the world spun around him. This acceleration was so sudden and fast that Lin Ming felt as though he would barf out his organs. Rays of red light wrapped around Lin Ming, the void shattered, and he was tossed into this incomparably chaotic space flow!

Having experienced this scene previously, Lin Ming’s eyes lit up. This was also an opportune time for him to further hone his Concepts of Space and Time!

The chaotic space flow that Lin Ming faced this time were even more violent and terrifying than before. But Lin Ming’s strength had greatly increased from the past, and his understanding of the Concept of Space had reached a very deep degree. Even if he couldn’t directly withstand the violent space flows, he still had ways to avoid it, ensuring that he would be safe.

After soaring through this space flow for an unknown period of time, even someone with Lin Ming’s endurance consumed 70-80% of his true essence. Finally, he felt his body shake as he was kicked out from the space channel!

Then, Lin Ming was able to clearly gaze at the scene before him. This was the true king level smelting trial!

Lin Ming was thoroughly shocked. Prior to this, he had imagined many times just what the king level smelting trial would be like. Perhaps it was similar to the Ten Thousand Killing Array, or the King’s Cage, or maybe even the Road of Emperor, but he never thought it would be like this…..

This was actually a city! A city filled with people!

Chapter 719 – Timeworn Phoenix City

Right in front of Lin Ming was an incomparably vast and deep valley. Lin Ming stood right on the top of a cliff hundreds of thousands of feet high. The cliff walls were smooth like polished mirrors. If one didn’t have the ability to fly, then perhaps even a Revolving Core martial artist would be unable to climb this.

Looking down from the top of the cliff, he saw an endless mist of hazy clouds, extending off into the distant horizon for thousands of miles. But, within this fog, he could make out several mountains that were hundreds of thousands of feet high, towering into the heavens as if they were pillars supporting the vault of the world.

A magnificent, crimson castle city was nestled within these mountains. Its walls were several hundred feet high, grand and majestic, and above the city massive flaming birds shuttled back and forth. On top of these flaming birds rode riders wearing scarlet sets of armor with lances in their hands.

Besides these fiery birds, there was a massive spirit boat being ferried forwards by ten Golden Crows, their bodies wreathed in flames. Each of these Golden Crows were much larger than the Vermillion Birds of Divine Phoenix Island, their twin wings each extended 200 feet out and their backs wide enough to fit 10 people standing side by side.

At this time, this massive spirit boat headed forwards into that giant, crimson castle city. As Lin Ming stood 100 miles outside, he could clearly hear the resounding cry of phoenixes, a melodious and valiant song that echoed endlessly between the heavens and earth.

“What a great divine city!”

Lin Ming sucked in a deep breath. Although he already knew that outside of the Sky Spill Continent there was the three thousand boundless worlds as well as the even greater and more illusory, unattainable Realm of the Gods, knowing was one matter; seeing with his own eyes was another altogether.

This scene was simply staggeringly breathtaking; it was only inferior to the phantom of the God Beast he had seen in the Eternal Demon Abyss.

As Lin Ming turned around, he saw that the Temple Spirit was following behind him, its form rippling like a water mark. “Trial Challenger, this is Timeworn Phoenix City. It is my Nuyan Family’s king level smelting trial site. You may enter.”

“Timeworn Phoenix City….Nuyan Family…”

Lin Ming’s eyebrows arched upwards. He asked the Temple Spirit, “Sir Temple Spirit, the Nuyan Family is only part of the Ancient Phoenix Clan. So would that mean that the other trial challengers of other clans and families are also converged within Timeworn Phoenix City?”

The Temple Spirit replied, “Yes.”

So it was true…. Lin Ming sucked in a deep breath of cold air. If he wasn’t wrong, then the Sky Spill Continent’s Ancient Phoenix Clan only comprised the Nuyan Family branch. But, within the Realm of the Gods, there was the much greater true Ancient Phoenix Clan. There was even a possibility that the Ancient Phoenix Clan was a Holy Land-rank influence within the Realm of the Gods!

“Come, I shall lead you into the city,” the Temple Spirit said. Then, a blurry light wrapped around Lin Ming and they flew together towards that colossal city.

After half an incense stick of time, Lin Ming arrived at the great castle city. As he reached the city gates, he saw that they were 1000 feet high, and at the very top there were three massive golden words emblazoned on a huge signboard: Timeworn Phoenix City!

These three words emanated an unbelievably inexhaustible and vigorous aura; just looking at it made his mind blur. Even though Lin Ming was confident in the firmness of his own willpower and mind, he still didn’t dare stare for too long.

“This sign…”

The Temple Spirit said, “The above words on that signboard were personally written by the Third Patriarch of the Ancient Phoenix Clan; within it is contained the root Laws of all fire-attribute energies. Normally,  if a martial artist looks at it they will feel dazed. Even those who have formed a battle spirit are no exception.”

“I see….” Lin Ming was startled. It wasn’t said which family clan this Ancient Phoenix Clan Third Patriarch came from. It was possible that he was the Third Patriarch of the Ancient Phoenix Clan from the Realm of the Gods. It was hard to imagine just what boundary such a person would have reached.

“Come, let us enter,” the Temple Spirit said before slowly floating forward.

The great road leading to Timeworn Phoenix City was over a mile wide. Along the way, there were a number of martial artists sporadically scattered about, all of them wearing red. In his black clothes, Lin Ming stuck out like a sore thumb.

As Lin Ming sensed the cultivation of those young heroic elites he saw along the way, he was secretly surprised. Nearly all of them were at Revolving Core or even at Life Destruction. There were several who were at the Xiantian realm, but they were obviously under 20 years of age. They didn’t break through to the Xiantian realm any later than Lin Ming.

As Lin Ming arrived at the entrance to Timeworn Phoenix City, a soldier dressed in fiery armor stopped him. “Identify yourselves! Name and origin!”

At this time, the Temple Spirit fluttered down beside Lin Ming. It said without feeling, “Ancient Phoenix Clan, Nuyan Family Protector from Sky Spill Continent. The trial challenger’s name is Nuyan Ming.”

Nuyan Ming?

Lin Ming was startled before relaxing. He was a disciple of Divine Phoenix Island and he had also obtained the inheritance of a single blood drop of the Ancient Phoenix from the Ancient Phoenix Great Temple. He could at least be considered an honorary Nuyan Family member.

“Nuyan Family?” The city gate guardsman showed a thoughtful expression. He took out a jade slip, glanced at it, and then said with some surprise and consternation, “The Nuyan Family has not sent any fellow clansmen to the Royal Family smelting trial for 150,000 years!”

“Yes!” the Temple Spirit replied. Then, a simple token emerged out of thin air in front of it. The front of the token had the design of a phoenix in nirvana, and the back of the token and a single word written in the Realm of the God’s language—Nuyan.

The city gate guardsman looked at Lin Ming strangely. He then took the token and nodded, “You truly are of the Nuyan Family line. You may enter.”

Lin Ming stepped into Timeworn Phoenix City with the Temple Spirit. As Lin Ming formally entered the city, he felt a great vague pressure come pressing down on him. This caused all of the true essence within his body to immediately weaken by at least 20%.

Looking up in the sky, he could see countless red clouds surging in the heavens, constantly forming a variety of mystical patterns that seemed as if they contained the endless profound principles of the universe.

“The fire origin energy here is…too rich, too pure!” Lin Ming gasped. He felt that what he breathed in was not air but the purest and most primal of fire origin energies!

This fire origin energy perhaps shouldn’t be described with the word “rich.” Rather, it was power that was closest to the Law of Fire!

“If I train here, it can’t even be described as twice the result with half the effort….” Lin Ming sighed with emotion. The great sects and Holy Lands of the Realm of the Gods were truly flush with resources, but as to what degree it was, it was hard to consider with just his imagination. Now, seeing it with his own eyes, he could only sigh for the disparity that existed between the mortal world and the Realm of the Gods!

In Timeworn Phoenix City, even if one didn’t train, one would always be undergoing a baptism of fire energy, making the energy within their dantian even purer! If one supplemented this with cultivation, the ease of perceiving the Law of Fire could be imagined.

Especially for the people here; they all had a formidable bloodline power. Their own compatibilities with the Law of Fire were extremely high to begin with!

“Follow me, I shall bring you to the Timeworn Phoenix City Protector. He will guide you to the first stage of the Royal Family smelting trial.”

Lin Ming followed the Temple Spirit to the Temple of Protectors. Along the way, they passed by many red-clothed young men and women. If any one of these people were placed in the Sky Spill Continent, then they would be existences that Duanmu Qun, Feng Shen, and Lan Xin wouldn’t be able to compare with by far.

“These people all come from the Realm of the Gods?” Lin Ming asked.

“No….” The Temple Spirit shook its head. “Most of these people come from similar mortal worlds like the Sky Spill Continent. Only a small portion of them come from the Realm of the Gods.

“The Realm of the Gods is an incomparably broad land. But there are even more people within it. When someone decides to practice martial arts, their lifespan will become longer, and the number of descendants they leave behind will swell in number. After a long time, even the near unlimited resources of the Realm of the Gods would find it hard to support such a great number of people. At times, there will be some branch families of certain sects and clans that will pass through space cracks, entering into the lower mortal realm where they settle down. The Ancient Phoenix Clan within the Sky Spill Continent was in this situation.”

As the Temple Spirit spoke, Lin Ming was suddenly enlightened. So that’s how it was!

Humanity’s ability to multiple was truly terrifying. If a martial artist lived for 10,000 years, they could have dozens or even hundreds of children. These children would have their own children, and then the rate of population would increase exponentially. Quickly, a sect’s spiritual land would not be able to bear this. At that point, it would be a wise choice for a branch of that sect to settle down in the world of mortals.

“So, the Sky Spill Continent Ancient Phoenix Clan’s Nuyan Family was also the same?” Lin Ming had never understood why various ancient ruins from the Realm of the Gods had appeared within the Sky Spill Continent. For instance, the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm, Road of Emperor, Eternal Demon Abyss, or even the various array formations of the Demon God Imperial palace, all of them came from the Realm of the Gods.

“Yes! Once upon a time, the Sky Spill Continent also had a brilliant and storied past. Although it was not comparable to the Realm of the Gods, it still had its moments of magnificence….” As the Temple Spirit spoke to here, it seemed reluctant to keep talking. Lin Ming also didn’t want to push the subject. He had a faint feeling that 100,000 years ago, a time at which the history of the Sky Spill Continent had been wiped out, it also had something to do with the fall from brilliance that the Temple Spirit had implied in its words.

Lin Ming had long thought something was strange. Although ancient texts could last thousands of years at most, the large sects should have methods to preserve their history. For instance, specially crafted jade slips. It shouldn’t have been possible for everything that happened 100,000 years ago to suddenly vanish.

‘I wonder what the matter with the Eternal Demon Abyss is. There are obviously life forms from the Realm of the Gods that reside there. Above the Eternal Demon Abyss there are also the Road of Emperor, King’s Cage, and the 12 Skysplit Towers; all of that should have been built by those existences within the Eternal Demon Abyss. But why did they do that and why had they retreated to the Eternal Demon Abyss and never left? Is this related to the fall from glory that happened 100,000 years ago?’

Lin Ming remembered that tens of thousands of years ago, there was a massive, beastly claw that emerged from the Eternal Demon Abyss, instantly killing 12 Emperor-level powerhouses. He also remembered that ancient great beast he had seen in the 1000-mile forbidden zone; its body had spanned for thousands of miles. And there was even that goddess in her tomb sleeping, unblemished and undisturbed for all those years. Without a doubt, these were not mysteries that should exist in the Sky Spill Continent or Holy Demon Continent.

What kind of secret was there in the Eternal Demon Abyss? Lin Ming felt that he had just glimpsed the very tip of the iceberg. Well, at least he now knew generally how the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm and Eternal Demon Abyss had come about.

“We’re here. This is the Hall of Protectors. Trial Challenger, I shall wait for you here until you have completed the first stage of the trial or are eliminated. Perhaps you might even die….” The Temple Spirit finally stopped at a red-domed building that was hundreds of feet high. On the very top of the dome, there was a massive statue of a phoenix, its wings spread out in flight as if it were living creature trapped there in time.

“You may enter.”

“Thank you, Sir Temple Spirit.” Lin Ming took a deep breath and walked into the flame-hued Hall of Protectors. In the deserted corridors, his footsteps echoed loudly.

Chapter 726 – God Transforming Mirror

With the help of a guide, Lin Ming arrived at the assigned dwelling.

“Sir Nuyan, this is your basic equipment.” The guide passed Lin Ming a spatial ring.

As Lin Ming sunk his consciousness within, he saw a simple 10-foot-long wooden case, a set of red clothes, and red boots.

This wooden case was…

Lin Ming’s eyes brightened. He had been using a spear for so many years that he didn’t even need to open the box to tell that there was a spear within this case!

It was purely intuition.

Lin Ming enthusiastically opened the case and a long fiery-red spear appeared under Lin Ming’s eyes. The spear edge was a foot long and it shone brightly, with a chilling cold. The spear shaft was made from an unknown metal; it was exceedingly tough, yet flexible at the same time.

All sorts of runes and lines were engraved on the barrel of the spear. These patterns undoubtedly contained the power of Fire Laws.

This was… a medium-grade heaven-step treasure?

Or was this a high-grade heaven-step treasure?

Lin Ming’s eyes shone. He had been using a heaven-step white spear acquired from a High Lord of Skysplit Tower; he didn’t even know what its name was. Beside its toughness, there was no benefit to wielding that white spear. It wasn’t like the Purple Comet Spear, able to increase the power of his thunderfire abilities. It was extremely inconvenient for him.

But now, this red spear in front of him was obviously useful for enhancing the power of fire. Moreover, it was a treasure ranked even higher!

“What rank is this treasure?” Lin Ming asked.

Up until now he only had a few rare encounters with anything above low-grade heaven-step treasures, so he didn’t have much of an understanding toward this.

The guide said, “Sir, this is a medium-grade heaven-step treasure. But in mere terms of toughness, it’s on equal standing with a high-grade heaven-step treasure. It is a standard service weapon that my Timeworn Phoenix City issues to new talents. If you don’t use the spear, then you may apply for a replacement weapon.”

Within the Ancient Phoenix Clan, because there were many people who rode Vermillion Birds in battle, long pole-type weapons were the most commonly used. This was different from the inheritance of Divine Phoenix Island. When Lin Ming was going through the qualification test for the king-level smelting trial, many of the phantom matches was facing were also using spears.

“This spear is actually only a standard service weapon…”

Lin Ming was speechless. This was a spear that every trial challenger who was participating in the king-level smelting trial would receive. It seemed that within the Realm of the Gods, heaven-step treasures were only considered common garbage.

This was also reasonable. Within the Sky Spill Continent, even a Life Destruction martial artist like Xuan Wuji was able to acquire a heaven-step treasure, much less a Divine Sea master. There was no need to even mention the Realm of the Gods. Here, powerhouses were most likely using Saint artifacts, or even higher quality weapons.

Lin Ming took the red spear in his hand and casually shook it. The spear shaft trembled with a terrifying contained strength.

“What a great spear! In terms of resources, martial artists from the lower realms are just like little babies from the slums; they are simply unable to compare with martial artists from the Realm of the Gods.”

Besides the long spear, the standard issued clothes were also top quality goods. Once worn, they felt as airy as silk. Having been woven from divine fire silk, they were actually immune to fire and water and were also extremely resistant. Even with a normal treasure one would find it difficult to slice through them. In Timeworn Phoenix City, it was light and practical – perfect for talents to use in training.

“Sir, if you please. Your room is right ahead.” The guide bowed.

Lin Ming looked up. In front of him was a door leading to a separate miniature dimension.

In Timeworn Phoenix City, every young elite’s residence was their own dimension. The advantage of this was that once the door was closed, the room would then become an absolute isolated space, so that the martial artist inside would not be interrupted during their training time.

After settling into this dimension, Lin Ming saw a bookshelf filled with all sorts of jade slips, both large and small. He casually picked one up and swept his perception through it. These were actually fire-attribute law cultivation methods, advisory letters, and ancient texts. These jade slips were mostly  high-grade cultivation method manuals collected by powerhouses of the Ancient Phoenix Clan from various regions. They were given to trial challengers, mainly for them to use as a reference in their own training.

Lin Ming looked through a few jade slips. Then, he sat down and immersed himself in perceiving insights into the Laws and Concepts he had gained earlier.

The totem symbol atop Heretical God Seed was as small as a grain of rice. However, Lin Ming could actually make out every single line and change in texture on its surface. These traces were all enlarged tens of thousands of times within Lin Ming’s vision, each and every simple mysterious pattern appearing defined in his eyes.

Meditating on the totem engraving on the Heretical God Seed was much more beneficial and much easier than meditating on the Burning Heaven Totem Stone.

Lin Ming could already faintly feel that the affinity the Heretical God Seed held towards the Concept of Fire had exceeded that of the Concept of Thunder.

Amongst the various major Concepts, ones like the Concepts of Space and Time, the Concept of Eternity, the Concept of Annihilation, and other such Concepts were much more abstract and elusive, and were somewhat more formidable than others. However, the truth was that once one thoroughly comprehended the source of a Concept, and reached the pinnacle of comprehension with it, then even with one like the Concept of Fire one could still achieve heaven-shaking results and become a king of their generation.

Hu – !

Lin Ming stretched out his palm and a fiery flame-spear appeared in his hand, its energy quickly solidifying. In the next moment, the flame spear completely condensed into a solid spear. The spear point and shaft both gleamed with a metallic luster, just as if they had been cast from red metal.

“After inscribing the flame totem, the Heretical God Seed within me has also evolved.” Lin Ming felt his heart shining with a brilliant fighting spirit. He wanted to test his strength in battle and see just how much progress his Concept of Fire had made.

At that moment, a strict voice suddenly rang out in the dimension. “Ten days have passed. Everyone gather at the Southern City Temple. The test will now begin!”

“The test is finally starting.” Lin Ming’s eyes flashed with a sharp light. The king-level smelting trial tests were extremely severe. The first test would eliminate 30-40% of the martial artists. In the future, tests would only become more and more difficult. Ultimately, only a tiny number of people would make it through the trials.

Lin Ming walked towards the Southern City Temple. Here, the red-robed Elder responsible for directing the test was already waiting.

“Come with me.”

After everyone had gathered, the red-robed Elder led everyone to a separate chamber. Here, there was a massive crystal mirror. The mirror was over 100 feet high and was hundreds of feet wide. It spread across an entire wall.

“This is the God Transforming Mirror. It is an illusory magic array used for tests. You only need to stand in front of the God Transforming Mirror and touch it in order to start the test. Within the God Transforming Mirror there are nine different shifting realms. With your current strength, lasting in the first shifting phase for a quarter of an hour will qualify as passing, and lasting for half an hour will be considered outstanding. Those who fail will need to take the transmission array and leave the smelting trial site,” the red-robed Elder indifferently said.

Hearing this, the heroic young elites became somewhat nervous. If they had a poor performance then there was the fear of being eliminated. If they had a good performance then they could only hope to make progress for even better results. For instance, Huo Wenlong, Huo Yu and the others all carried a great pressure on their backs. Their goal was not only to pass the smelting trial, but also to compete with Lin Ming and overshadow him.

“We shall start from the trial challengers of the Mortal Corridor. I will call your name to step forward and start the test. Sheng Gonglu, Chi Hu….”

The red-robed Elder continuously called out the names of four people. As these four people stood in front of the God Transforming Mirror, all of them were lurching with unease.

They followed the red-robed Elder’s instructors and reached out their hands to touch the God Transforming Mirror. In the next moment, all of them fell into a strange trance-like state, as if they were completely isolated from the outside world….

Chapter 736 – Leaving Seclusion

“Oh? Nuyan Ming has left seclusion?”

In Timeworn Phoenix City, the other martial artists had already heard this news. There were even some martial artists that had returned to Timeworn Phoenix City a second time for the smelting trial that were piqued by Lin Ming’s situation.

“I wonder if Nuyan Ming will go directly to the God Transforming Mirror…” A martial artist said, his voice tinged with envy and worship.

“He should go close up for another period of time. There are many martial artists that will have numerous new comprehensions after enlightening themselves with the totem stones. They need to thoroughly digest everything they’ve learned so that their grasp of it is greater.”

“How long will Nuyan Ming last this time? Can he break through the second world?”

“Break through the second world? Don’t be silly, how simple do you think the second world is. The God Transforming Mirror has a total of nine different worlds. If you can break through the sixth and seventh, then your power is equivalent to a Holy Lord. If you break through the ninth then you are the incarnation of a fire god. If you want to break through the second world, you would need strength at least equal to a Divine Sea powerhouse from the mortal worlds. Nuyan Ming is talented, but his cultivation is only at the Revolving Core realm; how can he possibly break through the second world already? If he can last for a few breaths more of time then that’s believable, but anything beyond that would be too freakish.”

“Power to contend with a Divine Sea powerhouse from the mortal worlds?” The martial artists present were startled as they heard this. Although the mortal worlds were nothing compared to the Realm of the Gods, a Divine Sea powerhouse was still a top level existence within those lower realms and they were still at a level that these young martial artists couldn’t match yet.

As everyone was discussing Lin Ming, they actually received the news that he had gone straight to the God Transforming Mirror!

He didn’t go back into seclusion but instead rushed directly there!

“This Nuyan Ming fellow is too confident in himself!

“I wonder what he managed to comprehend these past 11 days. I really envy him!”

Besides masters like Lin Ming and Huo Wenlong, most martial artists here didn’t have the chance to close up for such a long period of time. In fact, they had very few chances to enlighten themselves with the totem stones. When they could no longer perceive the Laws through meditation, they could only come out from their dimensions and watch the revolution of energy Laws of Timeworn Phoenix City, obtaining some minor understandings from experience.

………

At the entrance to the God Transforming Mirror’s hall, old man Jun smiled as he looked at Lin Ming and said, “You came straight here instead of closing up for some more?”

Lin Ming replied, “These past days, this disciple has a few things that he wishes to try. I can’t wait any longer.”

In these past 11 days, Lin Ming had achieved an extremely high degree of understanding towards the Concept of Burning Heat and had even seen through the next level to the Concept of Annihilation. With so many new comprehensions, he wanted to determine whether these were true or not and could only do so by testing them in the world of the God Transforming Mirror.

Although Lin Ming was well aware that his progress would be even better if he closed up some more, to Lin Ming, this sort of progress wasn’t important. What was important was enhancing his understandings of Laws and Concepts.

“The God Transforming Mirror is in use. It will be ready in less than an hour.”

In Timeworn Phoenix City, there was only a single God Transforming Mirror and all the martial artists needed to use the God Transforming Mirror in their smelting trial. Although the time for each use was very short, one would often encounter a situation in which the God Transforming Mirror was being occupied by others.

After calmly waiting for an hour, old man Jun lit up a sound transmitting talisman to Fairy Feng, informing her that Lin Ming had come to the God Transforming Mirror.

This was the first smelting trial test after Lin Ming came out of seclusion. Thus, he naturally attracted the attention of a massive number of martial artists.

However, Huo Wenlong and Huo Yu hadn’t come. After all, looking at someone else bathe in glory wasn’t too comfortable for them, not to mention that Huo Wenlong was also in seclusion perceiving the Laws too.

With a hand touching the God Transforming Mirror, Lin Ming instantly entered into a trance.

“First world, break!”

In the God Transforming Mirror, Lin Ming grasped his red long spear and immediately used Bury the Heavens. By consuming just 40% of his strength the first world directly collapsed around him!

In just six breaths of time, he had broken through the first world!

Old man Jun’s eyes brightened. This was a result that defied the will of the heavens!

At the location where Lin Ming’s palm touched the God Transforming Mirror, a small crack appeared. This crack was even larger than the last one; it was nearly a full foot long.

Six breaths to break through the first world, creating a crack in the mirror a foot long…

The martial artists who witnessed this were dumbfounded. Lin Ming’s progress was simply too quick. None of them could think of catching up to him so they simply didn’t bother comparing with him.

“The second world!”

Lin Ming stood at the bank of roiling rivers of lava. As he looked to the sky, the vast expanse of the heavens was covered in a chain of red stars. Giant meteors were born from this chain of stars, howling as they came crashing down!

This world held the Annihilation Concept of Fire. The power of space in this world was nearly indestructible. With Lin Ming’s strength, he couldn’t even shake it, much less tear it apart. If he wanted to destroy this world then he could only rely on the Law of Annihilation to reverse the chain of stars, breaking the balance between those glowing red lights and cause the world’s power of annihilation to implode in on itself, eventually collapsing.

But Lin Ming’s understanding towards the Concept of Fire hadn’t reached such heights yet, his understandings of the Laws weren’t even close. Not just that, but his strength was insufficient to reverse the chain of stars to begin with, so breaking the second world was simply a dream.

The reason he came to this second world was to substantiate the comprehensions he had made.

Woosh!

The first meteor came howling down, dragging a long tail of flames behind it. Lin Ming had no intention of dodging it. This rain of meteors was simply too dense. No matter where he tried to hide, he would still be caught up in the shockwaves of the explosions.

Lin Ming flourished his long spear, the image of the falling meteor reflecting in his ink black eyes.

Bang!

The meteor crashed into the ground. The earth was torn apart and massive amounts of lava sprayed into the air, raising giant waves thousands of feet high!

As the shockwaves recklessly burst out, the images of the dancing flames of the Burning Heaven Totem Stone appeared in Lin Ming’s mind. Burning Heaven Totem Stone, annihilation of the heavens, the most exquisite Law contained within it was the Concept of Annihilation!

“Break for me!!”

Lin Ming gave a loud shout. The long spear in his hands was like a red flood dragon as it pierced forth. An azure spear light followed behind it, directly impacting into violent waves of lava!

A flash like a birthing sun shined out. In that instant, the waves of flames were split apart by Lin Ming!

In terms of strength, these meteors that were hundreds of feet wide and had power comparable to that of a Supreme Elder from the Realm of the Gods. Even the shockwaves were not something that Lin Ming could withstand.

However, what happened was that Lin Ming had torn apart these shock waves, opening a haven of safety for himself within the raging energy.

This was the cleverness of Laws. If Lin Ming could thoroughly realize the Annihilation Laws of the second world then he could rise from weakness here and find a path to live.

After breaking apart the first waves of turbulent lava, Lin Ming’s face flushed red with blood. Without even time to catch his breath, there was another deafening explosion as the second meteor impacted the ground!

Lin Ming summoned his true essence, raising his spear.

Chasing Sun!

With a spear thrust, he flew ten miles across the skies. The surging seas of lava were once again pierced through by Lin Ming.

Then, the third meteor!

This meteor was far larger than the last two meteors; it was nearly half a mile wide. When it crashed into the ground the entire earth shook and countless shattered stones and even the core of the world itself seemed as if it would be destroyed. Lava shot up, reaching into the heavens. As Lin Ming faced these turbulent waves of flames, he released the Heretical God Force to its limit. The Heretical God Seed howled as compressed true essence poured out!

Bury the Heavens!

A spear thrust out. Lin Ming reversed the power of space, and with his understanding of the Concept of Fire, this nearly 1000 foot wall of lava was torn apart by him!

In these three penetrating attacks, Lin Ming had consumed a great deal of energy. But, his ability to restore himself was similarly astounding. Lin Ming thrust forth his spear the fourth time – Penetrating Rainbow!

Bang bang bang!

Meteors continued to howl as they came roaring down. The earth was torn apart, hundreds of massive pits appearing in the ground. All of the rock islands had long been crushed to bits. Lava rained down on everything, covering the world!

Strike after strike came piercing out. Lin Ming was like a flood dragon swimming in a sea of lava. Chasing Sun, Chasing Thunder, Penetrating Rainbow, Bury the Heavens, all of these moves were used repeatedly again and again!

And this entire scene fell into Fairy Feng and Guru Blueflame’s eyes.

“This boy, he’s using the meteor shower in the God Transforming Mirror’s second world as a place to gain experience.” Guru Blueflame smiled, his tone filled with appreciation.

Out of Lin Ming’s various moves, the truth was that Chasing Sun was the most suitable for breaking through the Concept of Fire. Chasing Sun was itself a move purely based off the Concept of Fire and its strength was decent too.

As for Bury the Heavens and Penetrating Rainbow, while these moves were stronger, the use of energy was also that much greater. In an extended battle, Lin Ming should have used Chasing Sun in order to minimize the amount of energy used and make the greatest progress.

But Lin Ming didn’t do this. From Chasing Sun to Bury the Heavens, he used different moves every time. He even used Chasing Thunder which didn’t have a matching Concept during the weaker shockwaves.

This was because only when one used different moves in different situations would one have a more profound comprehension of the Annihilation Laws. He did this all in order to verify the truths he had comprehended in the Sky Corridor.

Doing this would certainly cause a far greater consumption of energy and affect his final results to a certain degree. If Lin Ming was a vain person who only desired fame, then he wouldn’t have done as such.

Guru Blueflame and Fairy Feng were both characters that had lived for over 10,000 years. With their vision, they naturally saw what Lin Ming was attempting. Thus, this was why Guru Blueflame appreciated Lin Ming’s decision.

“20 breaths of time. Nuyan Ming’s endurance is far better than what I imagined.” Fairy Feng generously praised.

“Mm… his endurance comes from his body transformation achievements. A dual cultivation of body and essence.. there aren’t many heroic young elites in the Realm of the Gods that would attempt this. To reach this step at such a tender age, he must have experienced a great deal of pain but also a great deal of lucky chances. I think that he shouldn’t be able to last much longer. Perhaps up to 30 breaths of time.”

As Guru Blueflame and Fairy Feng spoke, several more breaths of time passed. Lin Ming had already consumed 60% of his true essence. His forehead was dripping with large beads of sweat and the Ancient Phoenix flame mark between his eyebrows was dark red like blood.

Bang!

Another meteor half a mile wide smashed into the ground. Lin Ming’s body was tossed up like a leaf. As he drew back he thrust out his spear several times, demolishing the shockwaves of flames. However, the aftershocks still rushed into his meridians, minorly wounding him.

25 breaths of time, 26 breaths of time, 27 breaths of time… 30 breaths of time!

The meteor shower became increasingly dense. Lin Ming’s pupils were filled with the phantom of flames. The red long spear in his hand was scorched deep red, and even though Lin Ming was proficient in the Laws of Fire, there were still multiple burn wounds on his body.

31 breaths of time, 32 breaths of time…

Lin Ming’s inner true essence rapidly depleted!

When one had 100% of their physical strength remaining, it was possible to easily defeat an opponent. However, when one only had 20-30% of their strength remaining, even if they gave it their all they still might not be able to wound their opponent, and they would even consume more strength at a faster rate.

At 33 breaths of time, a massive meteor nearly a mile wide came crashing down. For a time, it was like the sea of lava completely flipped upside down. The sky turned completely red and the lava nearly reached the chain of stars hanging in the heavens.

Lin Ming could no longer withstand this. His vision went black and he instantly passed out.

Final result – 33 breaths of time!

Chapter 744 – The Bloodstained Deep Sea

A great mystic fairyland enchantment was originally difficult to break. Moreover, the Giant Leviathan’s intelligence was low to begin with; it simply wasn’t able to differentiate between fantasy and reality.

If the array had a boundary, then the Giant Leviathan could directly break through it. But, this Mystic Thousand Sea Sealing Array had no boundaries. If the Giant Leviathan attacked, its strike would simply fade outwards, causing no damage to the array itself.

On a side of the deep sea trench, the strange octopus was laying down the array formation with Bai Guanyun.

The deep sea trench was very long. The entire array formation had to cover a radius of 10 miles. While the octopus creature crawled onto the walls of the ocean trench its body wriggled as it drew deep sea origin energy through its arms and into its body.

“Brother Fish, that Lin Ming boy has many secrets on his body, right?” Bai Guanyun asked in a seemingly casual manner. In his opinion, there was no way that Xuan Wuji would be willing to pay any price to just kill this Lin Ming for revenge.

The strange octopus looked at Bai Guanyun, its entire body bulging and pulsating like the waves of the sea. “I do not know…”

Its voice was forced and hard to understand as if it had to use some arcane ability to stiffly change its normal language into something understandable.

Bai Guanyun pondered for a moment. He didn’t know what sort of secrets Lin Ming had on him, but he very much wanted a portion of the spoils. However, he simply didn’t have the ability to contend against Xuan Wuji. His only chance was if he found several more allies or if he found some opportune turning point.

“I heard this Lin Ming is less than 25 years old… to be at the middle Revolving Core at such a young age, there definitely must be some sort of extraordinary secret on his body.”

Bai Guanyun didn’t play around with the strange octopus. He directly told him his thoughts, hoping to arouse its interest. “If we can capture Lin Ming ahead of time and use a soul searching technique on him, then perhaps we might be able to glean something. Of course, the premise of this all relies on whether or not Brother Fish can fix the array formation so that we can hide this from Xuan Wuji. As for the matter of capturing Lin Ming, you can leave that to me. I can guarantee you that there won’t be any problems.”

Bai Guanyun’s tone was very casual. He was a man of ambition. Although he knew that there was a risk of enraging Xuan Wuji, he still couldn’t resist the desires of his heart. As for dealing with Lin Ming, this didn’t seem like a problem to him to begin with.

To change the array formation to hide all this from Xuan Wuji and then capturing Lin Ming?

The octopuses mind stirred. It’s hand movements slowed a bit, and its body oscillated. It was unknown just what this strange creature was thinking about.

Without a doubt, Lin Ming was definitely a delicious delicacy. But, to move against Lin Ming was the same as stealing food from the jaws of a tiger. They would have to risk arousing Xuan Wuji’s wrath.

There was still several days until this array formation would be finished. If it could use this time to plan its moves…

While the strange octopus was thinking, it suddenly became aware of a very unusual feeling. As a deep sea life form, it was extremely sensitive to any changes in the water. At this moment, it could feel a faint murderous intent rushing through the sea.

“Mm? Dodge!”

The strange octopus frantically screamed out. Its body suddenly accelerated to the side. Bai Guanyun was shocked, immediately following it. As for the spot they had just been floating at, the current of water there had twisted into the point of a blade, crazily spinning and slicing its way through!

“What is this!?”

The strange octopus was shocked. That strange spinning water blade didn’t contain any energy, but with just the driving force of will itself, it seemed as if it could cut everything to pieces!

“Who is it!?” The strange octopus and Bai Guanyun spun around, both of them looking in the same direction. There, they could see a blue-clothed youth that wielded a red long spear. In the deep darkness of the sea, he was like a god of death that slowly approached them. His entire body seemed to meld into the surrounding seawater, making that red spear in his hands seem particularly dazzling.

Since it was hundreds of thousands of feet deep under the sea, there was no sunlight. One could only count on their own perception to sense things. But, that red spear seemed as if it was emitting its own crimson light like a flame burning in the darkness.

“You are…” Bai Guanyun’s pupils contracted. This youth’s face wasn’t unfamiliar to him. Before coming here, he had already investigated the situation in the South Horizon Region. He knew that this boy was Lin Ming!

“You are Lin Ming? Haha, truly I can search far and wide, only to find you so easily here! Since you’ve come visit me, then you might as well stay behind!”

Bai Guanyun’s words seemed rampant to the extreme but he remained highly alert in his heart. He revolved the energy in his body to the limit. According to his intelligence, Lin Ming’s strength was inferior to that of a third stage Life Destruction master, so why would he take the initiative to attack them? There were the two of them and even Xuan Wuji was nearby. Did he have a death wish?

At this time, Lin Ming gave off an aura similar to a vicious deep sea beast from the depths of the divine sea. It was like he was completely enveloped in killing intent, making anyone who looked at him feel repressed, unable to revolt.

Bai Guanyun immediately extracted a peak high-grade earth-step treasure sword from his spatial ring. At this time, he finally noticed that Lin Ming’s cultivation was actually at the late Revolving Core realm!

Late Revolving Core realm! That was inconsistent with the information he received…

Bai Guanyun didn’t even have time to ponder the meaning of this. In the blink of an eye, Lin Ming’s spear had already thrust straight towards him!

Brilliant flames roiled, heating up the seawater until it bubbled. The spear shot thousands of feet forwards in an instant as if it were a blazing meteor in the deep night sky.

“Humph!” Bai Guanyun coldly coughed. Although he was somewhat ambivalent towards Lin Ming, this didn’t mean that he feared him. “Merely at the late Revolving Core realm and you suddenly think you’re undefeatable in the world? This old man will let you know just how strong a third stage Life Destruction master is! Heaven Shattering Sword!’

Facing this unfathomable Lin Ming, Bai Guanyun didn’t dare to hold his hand. With a loud cry, he used 100% of his strength to launch a counterattack. This Heaven Shattering Sword strike was one of his great master moves!

Meanwhile, the strange octopus waved its tentacles, ready to go all out. But in this moment, a bright crimson light suddenly shined out from between Lin Ming’s eyebrows. The spear in his hand suddenly soared in speed!

Concept of Fire Annihilation – Chasing Sun!

The might of this spear was like a falling meteor from the God Transforming Mirror’s second world. With a loud explosive sound, the sword in Bai Guanyun’s hands broke apart!

What!?

When Bai Guanyun saw his own sword shatter like a pane of glass, he was immediately horrified. At this critical moment, he drew back in a panic. However, Lin Ming’s long spear homed in towards him. As the Law of Annihilation bloomed in front of Bai Guanyuan, all of the sea water around him began to instantly deconstruct. With a miserable scream, the right half of Bai Guanyun’s body was covered in blood!

Not dead yet?

Lin Ming’s eyebrows pricked up. With absolute silence, his spear swept out!

Bai Guanyun was so scared that he felt as if his soul had fled from his body. “Brother Fish, save me!”

At this time of crisis, the strange octopus had also discovered just how terrifying Lin Ming was. Although it didn’t know just what had happened in these past four months, without a doubt, Lin Ming’s strength had risen dramatically. At this time, it was impossible for the strange octopus to contend with him!

As for saving Bai Guanyun, that was simply just a joke. Instead, it hoped that Bai Guanyun could delay Lin Ming for some time so that it could safely escape. Since things had devolved to this point, it no longer had any intention of laying down any sort of sealing array formation. If it couldn’t kill Lin Ming, then the consequences would be dire indeed.

The strange octopus flung out several tentacles, quickly fleeing into the deep sea.

Bai Guanyun cursed in his heart. At the doors of death, he fiercely bit down on his tongue and spat out a mouthful of blood essence, forcefully revolving true essence in his body, causing his body to suddenly shoot up 10 feet. This caused Lin Ming’s spear strike to miss its target and sliced through his leg instead of cutting him in half.

Puff!

His leg bones ruptured and blood oozed into the water. Bai Guanyun screamed as his heart filled with a manic despair.

Lin Ming no longer cared about chasing after Bai Guanyun anymore. He swiveled around and the Asura force field and the Death God force field erupted together. At the same time, he flicked his finger and a mass of purple flames shot out from his hand.

As these flames appeared, the surrounding sea water instantly vaporized. A massive spherical hole was burned through the center of the deep sea.

This fire was the Burning Star Flame.

Pouring his battle spirit into the flames, Lin Ming sprung out his five fingers and the Burning Star Flame shot out like a hail of arrows!

“Ohh!”

The strange octopus that had fled not too far away suddenly screamed. Because it was suddenly covered by these dual force fields, its speed instantly plummeted. It felt as if a sun was suddenly born in the sea, and the high water content of its body quickly withered away in the face of this purple sunlight!

The strange octopus was from a deep sea race and was a water-attribute life form. Fire was its natural nemesis.

Roarr!

The strange octopus let out a strange cry. It spat out a black ball from its body, shooting it straight towards the Burning Star Flame.

Monster’s core?

Lin Ming’s eyes brightened. If he wasn’t wrong, then this was the strange octopus’s monster core. The deep sea races were less like humans and more like highly intelligent monsters and beasts. A monster core was something that only a high level monster could cultivate. It was similar to a human’s Revolving Core crystal nucleus. Additionally, the most important thing was that it would only use this monster core to fight its enemies when it encountered a highly dangerous situation.

The monster core was extremely fast as it collided with the Burning Star Flame. With a loud bang, a terrifying detonation occurred in the deep sea. The explosive shockwaves surged out in all directions, pushing Bai Guanyun away. As for the strange octopus, because its monster core was damaged, it let out a miserably cough and flew backwards as it emitted a huge jet of inky black fluid.

Lin Ming grasped his red long spear and stepped forwards. After becoming accustomed to the explosive shockwaves from the meteors of the God Transforming Mirror’s second world, these shockwaves were now no different from a cool spring breeze to Lin Ming. It simply wasn’t even worth mentioning.

He easily broke past the shockwaves. As his feet stepped forwards, he displayed Golden Roc Shattering the Void, instantly appearing in front of the strange octopus!

At that moment, the strange octopus’s face distorted with horror. Its monster core hadn’t yet returned to its body but Lin Ming had already arrived in front of it. The severity of the situation could be imagined!

“Die.”

Lin Ming expressionlessly thrust out his spear. The spear held the Concept of Burning Heat within it. The crimson spear edge burned red like it just came from the center of a blazing sun. As it shot forwards, a massive amount of water evaporated around it. The octopus screamed out as Lin Ming’s spear pierced right into its soft head.

“Ahhhh!”

The strange octopus emitted a completely inhuman scream. It’s originally milky white face became covered wish rosy colors, as if paints were being mixed on its skin.

Chi chi chi!

The strange octopus’s body rapidly withered away as all the water in its body evaporated. As for that spinning black monster core that was returning, Lin Ming snatched it in his hands.

The monster core of a third-stage Life Destruction monster could be considered a great fortune. If a martial artist directly swallowed it up, it would be useful for one’s cultivation. In addition, it could also be used to refine pills. Since Lin Ming had decided to step onto the path of becoming an alchemist, he naturally wouldn’t miss out on rare water-attribute materials like this.

Chapter 745 – Fighting Xuan Wuji

From the time Lin Ming had appeared to when the strange octopus died, it seemed like a long while, but the truth was that only five to six breaths of time had passed.

Bai Guanyun stared on helplessly as Lin Ming used this tiny bit of time to slaughter the strange octopus whose strength was similar to his as if it were a chicken or dog. In his heart, there was nothing but an inexplicably rising fear.

Both of his legs had been cut off; it was impossible to escape.

How could things turn out like this?

Bai Guanyun felt as if he had gone crazy. Four months ago, Lin Ming only had the strength to barely kill a second stage Life Destruction master. How could his strength progress so quickly!

Normally, for a martial artist to advance a single stage of Life Destruction every few dozen years was already an incredible speed. But Lin Ming had only taken four months to enhance his strength by at least a boundary. This caused Bai Guanyun to fall into a hopeless despair.

But at this time, a billowing whirlpool suddenly appeared in the deep sea. A formidable aura surged forth like an endless tide. Bai Guanyun was suddenly overjoyed. He turned his head to see that not too far away, Xuan Wuji had grasped a jet black lance and was rushing his way over.

“Brother Xuan, save me!”

Bai Guanyun loudly called out for help. But as his voice left him, a burning hot spear appeared like a ghost right in front of his throat.

Ca!

With a faint sound, blood spurted out. Bai Guanyun stared at Lin Ming with wide eyes, unwillingness and disbelief coloring his face. However, as his perception had already faded away, he was no longer able to see anything in the water before him. The only thing that filled his vision was darkness.

Peng!

Bai Guanyun’s true essence protection shattered and sea water came pouring in, crushing Bai Guanyun’s body to nothingness. This was a depth of hundreds of thousands of feet; the pressure was extremely terrifying. Bai Guanyun was not from the deep sea races. Once his human body lost its true essence protection, his eyeballs instantly burst apart, his eardrums perforated, and sea water fluxed into his body, squishing his organs, meridians, muscles, bones, and everything to mush.

Lin Ming calmly took back his spear. With a wave of his hand, he retrieved Bai Guanyun’s spatial ring.

“Lin Ming!”

A voice touched with the tiredness from the endless trials of life echoed outwards. As Lin Ming turned around, he could see that just a thousand feet away in the jet black sea water, Xuan Wuji was floating, pointing a lance straight at Lin Ming.

Lin Ming indifferently waved his spear, meeting Xuan Wuji in return.

On one side was a cold, dark light, and on the other side was a blazing red dawn!

After so many years, Lin Ming had finally gained the capital to stand in front of Xuan Wuji and fight with him!

That young, ordinary youth that had just entered the Seven Profound Martial House now had the ability to declare war on the number one master within the entire South Sea!

As Xuan Wuji looked at Lin Ming, various feelings and emotions filled his heart.

“It should have been nearly five years since my great grandson Xuan Ji was killed by you… no, in less than five years, you’ve risen up from the peak of Pulse Condensation to the late Revolving Core realm. I have investigated your past. When you were 15 years old you were only ordinary, not special at all. Now at just 21 years of age, a bit more than six years’ time, you’ve grown from a mere common mortal to a top master that can instantly kill a third stage Life Destruction powerhouse. Within the Sky Spill Continent, your speed of cultivation is unprecedented from ancient times until now. I am truly curious; just what secret do you have with you?”

As Xuan Wuji spoke, Lin Ming didn’t respond. However, the Turquoise-Eyed Ape Clan Patriarch that was following behind Xuan Wuji actually blanched. In less than five years he had gone from the peak of Pulse Condensation to the late Revolving Core realm!?

The Turquoise-Eyed Ape Clan Patriarch only knew that Lin Ming’s talent was monstrous. But, he had never been too sure as to what Lin Ming’s history was. But now, listening to Xuan Wuji speak, this was the first time that he discovered that Lin Ming was an absolutely heaven-defying monstrous freak of nature!

In five years, to go from the peak of Pulse Condensation to the late Revolving Core, with such a terrifying cultivation speed, only a fool would believe that Lin Ming didn’t have some heaven-shattering lucky chance with him!

No wonder Xuan Wuji had been willing to pay any price to capture Lin Ming.

“This is… truly unbelievable, ah…” Xuan Wuji deeply sighed, his eyes flashing with a strange, otherworldly look. “At Revered Master Tianguang’s birthday banquet, you fought with Xuan Ji. Although Xuan Ji was only at the Houtian realm, his talent was still extraordinary and he had cultivated the Ancient Devil Arts. With his complete strength he was even able to match a Xiantian master. However, he was still defeated by you, a mere boy with a trivial Pulse Condensation cultivation!

“At that time, your talent was astonishing, but there were talents like you all over the four Divine Kingdoms, and there were even many young elites that surpassed you. At that time, I was startled by you, but I did not fear you. The reason I wanted to kill you was only because I wanted to avenge Xuan Ji’s death, not because I thought that you had any amazing secret on your body. I never imagined that in such a short time, you will develop to the point where you could threaten me!”

“Afterwards… you entered the Demon God Imperial Palace, and with your little Houtian realm cultivation, you played with us old fellows in the palm of your hand. You stole away the Nirvana Dragon Root and the Cosmic Melting Furnace! The meticulous plans that I laid down for over ten years was actually made into a gift for a little child! How laughable is that! Even now, I still don’t understand. Just how were you so skilled in ancient array formations? How did you obtain all those treasures and then make a grand escape to freedom? You snatched away the Nirvana Dragon Root and Cosmic Melting Furnace and then left for two whole years. Now you’ve returned, and you’ve returned as a complete monster. The reason I was so anxious to flush you out of hiding was because I truly feared you from the very bottom of my heart. I feared you so much that I even imagined days when I would take a nap, and the second I woke up you would have obtained the strength to kill me and would have already come rushing to my door!”

Xuan Wuji said in a single breath. After knowing of Lin Ming’s existence for such a long time, there had been too many questions pressing down on his mind. The pressure on his heart had increased every day.

“Secret?” Lin Ming faintly smiled. “Xuan Wuji, don’t you know about the existence of the Realm of the Gods? You fear how fast I grow but that is only because you are nothing more than a frog in a well. In the three thousand boundless worlds, there are countless extraordinary young elites just like me. One day, perhaps you will find that everything you’ve chased after in your life is nothing in the eyes of others, nothing but leftover garbage for them to step over.”

“Hahaha!” Xuan Wuji laughed, “What you said is true. There are no limits in this universe; there is always a higher peak, a stronger man. I am truly nothing but a little frog in a well, but I am unwilling to remain so. I am unwilling to chase after things that are nothing but trash in the eyes of others. Thus, I want to leave this world. And you, Lin Ming, you will be my springboard to do so. Perhaps your secret is only garbage to the powerhouses in the Realm of the Gods, but in my eyes, it is the most precious treasure. It is my only hope to break past my limits! Let’s do this! Lin Ming, show me just where the limits of your strength lie!”

As Xuan Wuji spoke, he flourished the lance in his hands and thrust it straight at Lin Ming.

“Take my lance – Sunder the Profound Heavens!”

Bang!

Xuan Wuji’s true essence exploded out, forming a massive amount of pressure in the sea. The seawater around Lin Ming suddenly became as hard as iron as it began to envelop him.

Although this pressure wasn’t able to harm Lin Ming, it was still able to form a cage around him, sealing the directions where he could escape.

But, the truth was that Lin Ming had no intention of dodging to begin with. A frontal melee was what he desired above all!

True essence revolved in his body as the Heretical God Force was released to its limit. Lin Ming held the red spear, pouring his battle spirit into the spear point. For a time, the entire spear radiated a glorious flaming red light!

Chasing Sun!

The seawater was evaporated by the burning hot energy. Lin Ming’s spear stuck Xuan Wuji’s lance point!

Bang bang bang!

Two amazing energies collided. The sea water crazily spun around, mixing up from the forces. As the Turquoise-Eyed Ape Clan Patriarch saw the situation devolving, he had already long retreated.

“Mm… this is!?!”

In the instant that Xuan Wuji exchanged moves with Lin Ming, he felt an incomparably sharp strength rush into his lance. It was like his heaven-step lance was unable to resist this force, issuing out a keening tremble!

This caused Xuan Wuji to be extremely alarmed!

“Burst!”

Xuan Wuji loudly shouted, detonated the true essence on the lance point. He was driven far back from the energy backlash. As he looked down at the black spear in his hands, he could see that it was still shaking. If this continued, then he couldn’t guarantee that his lance wouldn’t break!

This was a heaven-step treasure! If it were a high-grade earth-step treasure, it would have absolutely broken apart just now!

Xuan Wuji’s vision focused on the red spear in Lin Ming’s hands. That spear seemed to be a heaven-step treasure, but there was something strange covering it. Xuan Wuji was completely unable to determine just what rank of treasure it was.

However, even if it were a medium-grade heaven-strep treasure, it was would still be impossible to create such a terrifying pressure on his heaven-step lance. As Xuan Wuji recalled that incomparably keen strength just now, his heart suddenly trembled.

Could that strength be…

A battle spirit?

The South Sea Demon Region had once been a Holy Land. It’s Holy Ruler, the Netherworld Great Emperor, had been a top ranked character within the Sky Spill Continent three thousand years ago. In the ancient texts of their sect, there were certain records of battle spirits.

Xuan Wuji didn’t recognize this battle spirit at the start because this power was far too distant a realm for him. So, he simply never thought of it!

“This brat Lin Ming has actually formed his own battle spirit at the late Revolving Core realm? No, that’s wrong. According to the description in the ancient texts, this sort of battle spirit is not at a low grade. Lin Ming probably formed his battle spirit at an even earlier boundary! He is still young and yet he comprehended his own battle spirit! Moreover, that spear strike just now didn’t contain just a battle spirit. There was also an incomparably mystical Concept of Fire. The profound mystery of this Concept is something that perhaps even Yin Yang Profound Palace Master Xing Ji’s own Concept of Fire could not hold a candle to!

Yin Yang Profound palace was a sect that focused on the water and fire cultivation methods, using Yin and Yang elements to complement each other. Xing Ji trained in the fire-attribute and his cultivation was at the second stage of Life Destruction. Xuan Wuji had also once experienced Xing Ji’s Concept of Fire. But compared to Lin Ming’s own Concept of Fire, it was nothing more than trash.

“A battle spirit comparable to that of a Divine Sea Supreme Elder and a Concept of Fire that surpasses Xing Ji’s own understanding…” As Xuan Wuji held onto the black lance in his hands, rough and violent waves beginning to churning in his heart.

He had always thought that the reason Lin Ming became such a monstrous genius was because his luck was good and he stumbled onto a massive lucky chance. If Xuan Wuji could obtain this lucky chance, then his achievements would be even greater.

But now, whether it was the Concept of Fire or a battle spirit, neither of those can be attained with just a lucky chance. Battle spirit depended on one’s will and the Concept of Fire looked at one’s perception. Could Lin Ming truly be an unprecedented rare talent?

Xuan Wuji’s complexion sank as he turned grim. He lifted his spear and wiped his right hand on the lance point. Fresh scarlet blood poured onto the lance point and shaft. Then, an incredible scene occurred. In that moment, the black lance seemed to become a bloodthirsty vicious beast, completely absorbing Xuan Wuji’s blood and turning from black to a bright red.

“Lin Ming, I didn’t think that with just a single exchange you’ve already pushed me to the point of making a blood sacrifice to my lance. Today, this battle will decide our life and deaths!”

Chapter 747 – The 100,000 Mile Chase

Bang!

With another violent explosion, Xuan Wuji was only able to barely defend against Lin Ming’s Bury the Heavens. Under the shockwaves, he was sent flying back thousands of feet. In the shifting tide of the battle, Xuan Wuji’s minimal advantage against Lin Ming had already disappeared.

As for Lin Ming, after he was forced back several hundred feet, he shook his long spear and stabbed towards Xuan Wuji again.

Penetrating Rainbow!

A blazing spear light pierced through the deep sea. At this time, Xuan Wuji was still exhausted. He hadn’t even managed to conjure up any new strength before Lin Ming’s strike came hurtling towards him once again.

Bang!

Xuan Wuji coughed stuffily as he was sent flying away. The tumbling blood in his body was barely suppressed by his true essence.

The difference in their remaining strength was only growing!

Chasing Sun!

Bury the Heavens!

Law of Annihilation, Chain of Stars!

Lin Ming used move after move, completely overwhelming Xuan Wuji!

How was this possible!?!?

Xuan Wuji felt the blood surging up in his body as wounds accumulated all over him. As he faced Lin Ming’s non-stop barrage of increasingly powerful attacks, fear finally began to bloom in his heart, causing him to draw back. He was truly ambitious, but in this situation where his chances of success were becoming increasingly slim, he wasn’t stupid enough bring himself to death’s door.

Escape?

This thought flashed through Xuan Wuji’s mind. He indeed had some cards left in his hands, but facing this inexhaustible puppet-like Lin Ming, Xuan Wuji already felt a tinge of fear. He feared that even if he used every final card in his hands he still couldn’t kill him. If that happened, then he wouldn’t even have the chance to escape anymore.

With twist of his hand, Xuan Wuji took out an ash gray pill from his spatial ring. This pill was refined from 10,000 year old milk stalactite. After swallowing it, it could rapidly restore 30% of one’s true essence. It could be said to be a miracle medicine capable of reversing any battle.

There was still a vast distance from here to the Sky Spill Continent. Xuan Wuji only had less than 40% of his true essence left. If he didn’t supplement it, then it would be impossible for him to return.

With a flick of his finger, Xuan Wuji grudgingly swallowed down the pill, immediately turning around to escape!

“You want to run away?”

Lin Ming’s eye flashed with a thick killing intent. If he didn’t remove the weed by the roots then there would always be a viper aiming at him from the dark. After suffering a lesson from Ouyang Boyan, Lin Ming would not allow this kind of matter to repeat itself again.

True essence erupted and a battle spirit infused Asura force field spread out at the speed of light. The force field instantly overtook Xuan Wuji, leaving behind an undetectable battle spirit mark on his body.

Lin Ming had used this battle spirit mark once in the Eternal Demon Abyss to search for an exit from the 1000 mile forbidden zone and also once in the South Sea Demon region to chase down the numerous escaping masters there. If one didn’t have a battle spirit like Lin Ming, then it was impossible to detect it, much less remove it.

After leaving behind this battle spirit mark, Lin Ming would be able to find Xuan Wuji even if he fled to the ends of the earth.

“Demonshine, have the Giant Leviathan float back up to the surface to recuperate its wounds. I will chase down Xuan Wuji!”

“Okay!” Demonshine chuckled, “Hunting down and killing others is what this Saint likes the most!”

Lin Ming received his red spear and stepped with Golden Roc Shattering the Void, instantly chasing after Xuan Wuji.

In the deep sea, it moving forwards was very slow. In addition, every step forwards required several times more energy it took than to fly. Xuan Wuji didn’t have much of his original energy remaining to begin with, thus he naturally needed to run out of the sea first.

Bang!

Sea water exploded, forming a massive spray of water hundreds of feet high. Xuan Wuji shot up into the heavens, flying straight towards the north. As he flew, he took out a enchantment bead from his spatial ring and tossed it behind him.

Xuan Wuji had used this kind of enchantment bead once before in the Demon God Imperial Palace to block Abbot Whitebrow and the others from chasing after him. If it hadn’t been for Lin Ming tinkering with the transmission array and changing it, then Xuan Wuji would have had enough time to escape.

Bang!

The bead burst apart at the sea level, forming a blue hued enchantment barrier that sealed up the water surface like a glass wall. As soon Lin Ming ran out his speed dropped as he was caught by this enchantment.

“Break!’

Lin Ming thrust out his spear. With his battle spirit infused into it, he struck the enchantment barrier. This blue barrier that had originally been able to withstand both Nanyun Wang’s attacks and Abbot Whitebrow’s Bright Buddha Palm Seal now had countless cracks appear through it.

“Break again!”

Lin Ming thrust his spear out a second time. This time, the enchanted barrier completely collapsed. He stepped on the void, turning towards Xuan Wuji and chasing after him.

“This brat!”

Xuan Wuji’s mind went cold. Although he knew Lin Ming’s striking power was formidable, he didn’t that that his enchantment bead would only be able to stop Lin Ming for a single breath of time.

“3000 miles to the north is a transmission array of my South Sea Demon Region. As long as I can pass through it first and destroy it from the other side, I can expel Lin Ming from the space channel. With that, I should be safe.”

“Mystic Thunder Wings!”

Xuan Wuji formed a series of seals with his hands. Then, clothes on his back tore apart, revealing a pair of purple wings that stretched out. This was a flight-type treasure that was refined with plumes from several different Saint Beasts. It could improve Xuan Wuji’s speed to a certain degree.

“This boy is too difficult to deal with. Fortunately, this flight treasure that I refined can finally show its use. With it, it shouldn’t be a problem to increase my speed by 20-30%.

Xuan Wuji unfurled his two wings, shooting forwards like an arrow. Wherever he went, a terrifying sonic boom formed, rumbling through the air like a moving thunderstorm. Even the sea surface was split apart from the wind pressure!

In a single go, Xuan Wuji was able to fly out several hundred miles. As he swept his perception behind him, a chill crept up his spine. Lin Ming was still chasing him! Not just that, but he was closing the distance between them!

“How could this be!?”

Xuan Wuji was greatly shocked. Even though he was flying at full speed and had the support of a flight treasure boosting him, he was still slower than Lin Ming!

He discovered that with every single step Lin Ming took he would cross several miles. Space twisted underneath his feet as if it shrunk. With just a several steps the gap closed by several dozen miles!

What kind of movement was this!?

Xuan Wuji grit his teeth, revolving his true essence to the limit. To a character like him, a 3000 mile distance didn’t take long to traverse all. But now that he was being chased down by Lin Ming, this distance actually became a trial of life or death!

The distance between them increasingly shortened. If this continued for another half incense stick of time, then Lin Ming would catch up to him. Once he was embroiled in another battle with Lin Ming, running away again would be far harder.

Xuan Wuji cursed aloud and clenching his teeth, cutting a line across his wrist with his fingernail. This was the third time that he would be using his blood essence. Two drops of blood essence shot out, one to each wing. The Mystic Thunder Wings turned a blood red and his speed rose up once again!

After using his blood essence three times, even though he only used a few drops every time, it would still accumulate. Even Xuan Wuji wouldn’t able to continue like this. In this battle, his life source had already been damaged. If he wanted to restore it, it would take at least several dozen years of time and a massive amount of heavenly treasures.

“This damned boy!”

Xuan Wuji was breathless with anger. The chances of him obtaining the secret on Lin Ming’s body was becoming increasingly slim, not to mention that the South Sea Demon Region was already 90% destroyed by Lin Ming. His losses had been far too great!

“I will no longer care about the South Sea Demon Region. After I leave the South Horizon Region, I will go straight to the four Divine Kingdoms!”

Xuan Wuji and Lin Ming flew after one another, causing massive explosions on the sea’s surface from the high speed sonic booms that they created. After making a blood essence sacrifice to his wings, Xuan Wuji had finally been able to create some additional distance from Lin Ming. Now, the transmission array was directly in front of him!

This was a transmission array established on a desolate island. There were originally South Sea Demon Region disciples protecting it, but now that the South Sea Demon Region was in a state of near dissolution, these disciples had long fled to lands unknown.

Xuan Wuji fell to the ground like a cannon strike. As he hit the floor, a massive crater formed from the impact, shaking the island and causing rock formations all over to collapse.

“The transmission array is still here!’

Xuan Wuji was overjoyed. He ran into the transmission array, and with a flick of his fingers, true essence stones flew into the four corners of the transmission array.

The array formation was activated!

After seeing the blazing comet that was Lin Ming closing in from a distance, Xuan Wuji’s eyes flashed with hatred. “One day, this old man will have you pay the price for today!”

In the next moment, Xuan Wuji’s hideous expression completely disappeared in the transmission array.

“Mm? He ran through a transmission array?”

Lin Ming fell down to the island and swept his perception around. He instantly understood the principles behind this transmission array. This was the most ordinary of transmission arrays; it would at most send someone 100-200,000 miles away.

“Xuan Wuji will definitely destroy the exit of this transmission array when I’m inside, forcing me out of the space channel.”

For a small transmission array like this, if there was a problem in the transmission process, it would be life-threatening for a martial artist with a weaker cultivation. But, for someone like Lin Ming, this was not a problem. At most he would pop out halfway through.

Lin Ming jumped onto the transmission array and launched the array formation. Space twist, and in the next moment, Lin Ming entered the space channel.

A transmission channel of several tens of thousands of miles could last from a dozen to several dozen breaths of time. As soon as ten breaths of time passed, the space channel suddenly shook and the power of space began to chaotically distort. Massive cracks began appearing in the space channel. It was obvious that the exit was being destroyed by Xuan Wuji!

Hu hu hu!

From the cracks in the space channel, a massive overflow of turbulent space began to flood inside, forming a black storm that swept towards Lin Ming. If a martial artist with insufficient cultivation were swept up by this storm, they would be shredded apart and die. Even for a martial artist that was strong enough, they would still be thrust out of the space channel, terminating the transmission process.

Facing this sort of situation, Lin Ming didn’t panic at all. He flicked all 10 of his fingers, forming a number of true essence air flows that shot out. After the menacing space storm was struck by the true essence air, it actually began to rapidly fade away, and soon subsided after several breaths of time.

Compared to the super long-distance array formation that Lin Ming had experienced before, violent space turbulence of this degree was nothing at all. With Lin Ming’s comprehension towards the Concept of Space, he could actually break apart the turbulent power of space and forcefully complete the transmission.

“Set for me!”

Lin Ming thrust out his spear, stabbing it into the space barrier around him. The space channel that was about to break apart was actually forcefully stabilized by Lin Ming.

“The exit coordinates are around 70-80,000 miles from here!”

With the exit destroyed, the transmission coordinates would blur. Lin Ming wasn’t a god. Although he could rely on his understanding of Space Laws to forcefully complete the transmission, he still lacked the exact coordinates of the exit point.

However, with the battle spirit mark that Lin Ming had left on Xuan Wuji, he could use that to approximate the location of it.

“There is still around 30,000 miles.”

Lin Ming confirmed the position once again.

“20,000 miles… 10,000 miles… it’s nearby!”

Shatter!

Lin Ming stabbed his spear into the space channel barriers. In the next moment, space collapsed and Lin Ming was flushed out from the space channel.

Chapter 756 – Duel of Battle Spirits

The wisp of air pierced through the small jade dish and still had ample force left over to shoot towards Wang Yichan. Wang Yichan took his sword out to block it, but the strike still caused his low-grade heaven-step treasure sword to tremble. From this alone, the difference in the two battle spirits could be imagined!

“This Lin Ming, if I’m guessing correctly then I fear that battle spirit has nearly reached large success of the bronze level!” Li Yifeng sucked in a breath of cold air. Even the young maid standing beside him had widened eyes. As someone who also came from the four Divine Kingdoms, she naturally understood what it meant to have a bronze level battle spirit at large success.

Every level of a battle spirit was divided into four ranks: elementary, small success, large success, and perfection. It wasn’t wrong that Wang Yichan was talented, but he had still just formed his battle spirit several years ago and its rank had slowly reached the elementary rank. As for Lin Ming, his battle spirit was already at the peak of small success; there were even many Divine Sea powerhouses that hadn’t been able to achieve this degree yet!

A difference of a little more than a boundary wasn’t much at all, however, Wang Yichan’s cultivation was at the second stage of Life Destruction and Lin Ming was only at the late Revolving Core. If Lin Ming were to step into the second stage of Life Destruction then it was possible for his battle spirit to reach bronze level perfection, and perhaps he could even obtain a silver battle spirit before he reached the Divine Sea!

A silver battle spirit was a legendary existence. Thus, the gap between the two could be seen from just this.

‘With a mere late Revolving Core cultivation his battle spirit has already reached the peak of small success. Then, when did Lin Ming form his battle spirit? The early Revolving Core realm?

‘…Or even extreme Xiantian?’

As Li Yifeng thought this, he felt a chill crawl up his spine. Even that young maid who didn’t think too much of Lin Ming was also shocked speechless. In terms of will, Lin Ming’s talent in that category had exceeded her understanding.

Perhaps… he really did kill Xuan Wuji by himself.

As this thought echoed in the young maid’s heart, she closed her dropped jaw.

If Li Yifeng could think of this then Wang Yichan was even clearer on what was happening. As for Great Zen Temple’s Abbot Konghe, although he didn’t understand the different ranks of battle spirits, he was still able to determine that Lin Ming’s battle spirit was far more formidable than Wang Yichan’s.

In that moment, Abbot Konghe felt that the world of juniors had reached a level that was nearly impossible to catch up to. Maybe in a few decades, or even less, these juniors would reach heights that he couldn’t even comprehend.

“Lin Ming, I never thought that you would also have a battle spirit.” Wang Yichan’s lips twitched. His battle spirit was his ultimate killer move. He had intended to use it to shock and awe the entire audience, but he never imagined that Lin Ming would turn it around to shame him instead.

His heart sank as he thought to himself, ‘My battle spirit has a demonic path attribute to it. I was too careless just now and didn’t use the special attribute. If I go all out, then a difference of a small boundary shouldn’t matter too much.’

Wang Yichan couldn’t stand that he had been defeated in what he excelled at the most. This was a major blow to his self confidence.

“Slaughter path attribute, battle spirit assault!”

A black light suddenly erupted in Wang Yichan’s eyes, turning into a substantiated sword of will that thrust straight at Lin Ming!

Wang Yichan had comprehended a battle spirit when he was crossing through Life Destruction. Moreover, what he comprehended was a rare specialized battle spirit. This battle spirit had a slaughter path attribute; it was able to display the strongest destructive power in battle, even able to directly extinguish the life force of an opponent!

A duel of battle spirits?

Lin Ming’s mind stirred. Before this, he had heard Demonshine say that martial artists with battle spirits could battle in the world of will through their battle spirits.

Wang Yichan was the first martial artist Lin Ming met who had a battle spirit. Before this, although he had never truly fought with a martial artist in the world of will, he had done something similar during his stay at the Road of Emperor. There, when Lin Ming faced the road of will lights, in order to pass every light he would have to enter the will world and engage the residual will of the past Emperors in battle.

Lin Ming was not a stranger to battles within the world of will. In fact, it was quite familiar to him.

Lin Ming’s thoughts focused and the battle spirit floating in his spiritual sea transformed into a long spear that roared forth!

An azure ray of pure will shot forth from between Lin Ming’s eyebrows, meeting Wang Yichang’s sword of black will.

Peng!

As both battle spirits collided, Lin Ming and Wang Yichan both arrived at the world of will.

Without further ado, Wang Yichan flicked his finger and a massive black python appeared out of thin air, rushing towards Lin Ming. This was a python formed from Wang Yichan’s thoughts. In a battle within the world of will, victory didn’t depend on cultivation methods of martial skills; even cultivation didn’t have that great of an influence. Rather, it purely depended on whose will was stronger.

Compared to the road of will lights Lin Ming had once faced, Wang Yichan’s battle spirit was far inferior. An azure long spear shot forth like a meteor, drilling right through the black python.

A great deal of black blood rained to the ground. Wang Yichan devilishly grinned and then loudly shouted, “Slaughter energy, swallow all!”

At that moment, the thick black fog burst out from the python’s body, swallowing up that azure long spear.

With a ‘chi chi chi’ sound, the black mist melded into the spear shaft as if it were trying to assimilate with it.

Wang Yichan laughed, “Lin Ming, my battle spirit has a slaughter path attribute! I can extinguish your life and swallow your will!”

Battle spirits could also have different attributes?

Lin Ming’s mind stirred. He hadn’t heard Demonshine mention this point before.

Lin Ming wasn’t unfamiliar with slaughter path attribute abilities. When he completed his twelve-winged Heavenly Demon Tattoo he had obtained the slaughter path attribute Death God force field. But, this was a battle in the world of will. He couldn’t use the Death God force field here unless he reproduced it using his own will. In the end, a battle in the world of will depended entirely on whose will was stronger.

But he didn’t need the Death God force field to begin with. If a battle spirit could have an attribute then Lin Ming’s azure will also had an attribute. That was – endlessness!

“Break!”

Lin Ming gave a deep shout and an azure light suddenly radiated outwards. With a resounding dragon roar, an Azure Dragon impacted the heavens, thrusting its claws out and directly ripping apart the black python’s body to pieces.

Lin Ming had obtained only a single drop of reverse scale blood, but the truth was that its quality was far higher than the blood of the Ancient Phoenix.

The blood of the Ancient Phoenix was only ordinary phoenix blood. In the legends, a Phoenix God Beast preyed upon Giant Leviathans. Its size was no less than that of a Golden-Winged Roc, and when it spread out its two wings it was able to hide the endless blue skies. It was difficult to say just how much blood such a creature had!

As for that drop of reverse scale blood Lin Ming had obtained in the Sorcerer Pagoda, that came from an Azure True Dragon’s reverse scale. For dragons that had a reverse scale, to touch it meant death. The blood from the reverse scale was only inferior to blood essence. Naturally, the quality was much higher than a phoenix’s ordinary blood.

Bang bang bang!

The black fog was completely scattered by the azure energy. After exterminating the black python, the azure dragon rushed forth with unstoppable force, firing right into Wang Yichan.

“Damnit!”

Wang Yichan angrily cried out as he produced a long sword, cutting it towards that azure dragon.

Peng!

The long sword broke apart and Wang Yichan’s body was torn in half by the azure dragon’s claws. With a miserable scream he was thrust out of the world of will, his eyes opening even as his body dripped with a cold sweat and his face became pallid.

In the world of will where the battle had only lasted for three breaths of time, Wang Yichan had been defeated!

Lin Ming opened his eyes looking calm as usual. As his cultivation constantly rose, his battle spirit became increasingly close to breaking through to large success of the bronze level. Within the Sky Spill Continent, a Divine Sea powerhouse with a large success bronze level battle spirit could be considered extraordinary.

“Lin Ming!”

Wang Yichan’s mouth twitched as he gasped for breath in great gulps of air. In this fight of battle spirits, his main body hadn’t been damaged but his will had been injured. It would be several days before he was restored to his peak condition.

He was unwilling to accept that defeat just now and wanted to fight Lin Ming again in the real world. However, after having lost just now, fighting again would not leave any good impressions on those present and even winning would mean he lost face. Moreover, Wang Yichan had been frightened in that exchange just now; he wasn’t too confident that he could defeat Lin Ming, even in the real world.

“Wang Yichan, if I’m not wrong then that so-called concubine of yours was captured from somewhere and then had a spell placed on her. Although I won’t call myself some sort of honorable gentleman, I wouldn’t do anything recklessly shameful. If you two truly loved each other then I would have no objections, but now, taking her from your hands is well within reason!”

Lin Ming’s words were much more reasonable, and now that he had won that battle against Wang Yichan just now, all of the initiative had fallen into his hands.

“Lin Ming, do you truly wish to become enemies with my Northwest Great Desert? Have you clearly thought about just what the consequences will be like!?” Wang Yichan said out loud before continuing with a true essence sound transmission, “I will trade a fifth grade spirit vein source for that white jade key!”

Wang Yichan had no choice but to lay down the threat of sect extermination. But at this moment, Li Yifeng laughed and stood up, “Brother Wang, you’ve already lost what there is to lose, can’t you afford what you lost?”

Wang Yichan followed the direction of the voice. As he saw Li Yifeng casually standing at the corner of the main hall, his heart jumped. This was definitely another extraordinary young elite! This person must come from some great power. “You are…”

“I am Li Yifeng!”

“Li Yifeng! Prince of the Seven Star Divine Kingdom! To think that such a solemn and dignified Divine Kingdom Prince would actually come to Lin Ming’s wedding celebrations. Could it be that your Seven Star Divine Kingdom is trying to recruit Lin Ming?”

Wang Yichan felt his heart go cold as he saw Li Yifeng. This Li Yifeng’s comprehension of the Law of Wind had reached an extremely high level and his foundation was incomparably solid too. He had at least twice the amount of total true essence that a normal Revolving Core martial artist would have, and the power of the stars was sealed in his right hand, greatly strengthening him.

Of course, Wang Yichan wouldn’t care about these things at all. After all, Li Yifeng’s cultivation wasn’t that high. But what Li Yifeng represented actually caused Wang Yichan to feel a pang of fear.

Li Yifeng represented one of the four Divine Kingdoms, the Seven Star Divine Kingdom!

Compared to the four Divine Kingdoms, the Northwest Great Desert was far lacking in all aspects.

The Seven Star Divine Kingdom wanted to win Lin Ming over to their side?

Wang Yichan couldn’t help but think this. If this were so, then what grounds did his Northwest Great Desert have to threaten Divine Phoenix Island?

“The jade key and the Life Destruction Pill!”

Wang Yichan spat out these words in a livid rage. He did care about the Life Destruction Pill, but what was most important here was that mystic realm key. In truth, this key contained some of Xuan Wuji’s works inside, otherwise it would never have been placed with him to begin with. If every key wasn’t collected then they would be unable to open the mystic realm left behind by that demonic path Holy Lord.

Lin Ming waved his hand and two jade boxes flew towards Wang Yichan. After Wang Yichan received them he swept his perception through them quickly and then coldly humphed, “We’re leaving!”

Wang Yichan brought his two underlings and left in great strides, leaving behind that woman with gray pupils to stand quietly in the main hall. Slowly, everyone’s visions turned towards her.

Chapter 760 – Wood Spirit Jade

“Xingxuan, Yu’er.”

In Mu Qianyu’s bridal chamber, Lin Ming had called in Qin Xingxuan and Mu Qianyu. As the two young women sat shoulder to shoulder on the bed, their figures complimenting the red silk sheets was far too beautiful to behold.

Several months had passed since Lin Ming killed Xuan Wuji. Lin Ming had momentarily suspended his cultivating, spending a good period of his time meditating on the alchemy techniques left behind by the Realm of the Gods alchemist, as well as spending time with his parents and family. After his marriage with Mu Qianyu, Lin Ming’s thoughts had become bedeviled by the relations between men and women, and he had shared in these sensual pleasures with her every night.

“This is for you.” Lin Ming took out two square crystals from his spatial ring. Every crystal block had two drops of red liquid sealed within. These red drops looked thick and viscous, as if they were crimson pearls.

“What is that?” As Mu Qianyu saw these four drops of red liquid she felt her heart jump. She could clearly feel that there was something extraordinary about these red drops of liquid.

“This is the blood of the Ancient Phoenix.” Lin Ming said.

Hearing these words, Qin Xingxuan was already surprised to the point of  being spellbound. As for Mu Qianyu, her eyes were completely wide, a look of astonishment and disbelief coloring her face.

“Blood of the Ancient Phoenix? As in the Phoenix God Beast!?”

“Yes.”

When he was still at Timeworn Phoenix City, he had obtained a total of 110 drops of Ancient Phoenix blood. Of these, the first 100 were given to Lin Ming first and then directly absorbed by him.

The next 10 drops were only delivered to Lin Ming several days later. However, he didn’t use them because the effects wouldn’t be obvious for him anymore.

Thus, it was better for him to give Mu Qianyu and Qin Xingxuan two drops each so that this could greatly improve their physiques.

As for the remaining six drops, he intended to save those for emergencies. For instance, when Qin Xingxuan had exhausted her blood essence at Blood Demon Island, if it wasn’t for Lin Ming coincidently having Vermillion Bird blood essence with him, then Qin Xingxuan would have already perished.

“Lin Ming, where did you get this blood of the Ancient Phoenix?” Mu Qianyu asked, short of breath. She had only read of this blood of the Ancient Phoenix in the ancient texts of Divine Phoenix Island. Still, she had always thought that these were legends. She never imagined that this sort of treasure actually existed in the Sky Spill Continent!

“At the king level smelting trial.”

“You participated in the king level smelting trial?” Mu Qianyu’s large eyes widened even further. When Lin Ming had told her about the smelting trial rules of the Divine Phoenix Mystic Realm, the king level smelting trial had been the highest level possible. And yet Lin Ming had actually completed it!

“Yes, this Ancient Phoenix blood is the reward of the smelting trial.”

“Then you should absorb it!” Qin Xingxuan suddenly said. Mu Qianyu also nodded. The effects of the blood would show their true potential under Lin Ming.

“I’ve already absorbed far too much; a few more drops won’t have much effect.” Lin Ming pointed at the flame mark between his eyebrows, “Don’t you feel it?”

Since Lin Ming first absorbed the blood of the Ancient Phoenix, a faint pressure had always emitted from his body, especially on those martial artists with the Vermillion Bird bloodline. However, Lin Ming normally suppressed this pressure and since his strength was already so formidable to begin with, everyone that was around him often enough became accustomed to it. Thus, Mu Qianyu hadn’t asked any questions.

As Mu Qianyu heard Lin Ming’s words, she wasn’t sure just what expression she should have. That blood of the Ancient Phoenix that was only depicted in the ancient texts of Divine Phoenix Island… Lin Ming had actually said that a few more drops wouldn’t have any effects!?

As Lin Ming saw Mu Qianyu’s thoughts written all over her face, he laughed and said, “Yu’er, in the Realm of the Gods a Phoenix might have a body that spans thousands of miles long. Who knows just how large it is. If all of its blood were taken out then it might be enough to drown a city. What I have here is only four drops, and it is also the most ordinary Phoenix blood; it’s not as if it’s blood essence or something like that. It’s not as exaggerated as you think.”

Hearing Lin Ming speak, Mu Qianyu didn’t know whether to laugh or to cry. “This might not be much to you but it’s a great lucky chance for me. My talent is at the peak of the Saint level and these two drops of Ancient Phoenix blood will be enough for me to enter the Emperor level.

“Don’t speak of this Ancient Phoenix blood. In Divine Phoenix Island, even Vermillion Bird blood essence is enough to make others go crazy. They couldn’t even imagine the blood of the Ancient Phoenix! With these two drops of Ancient Phoenix blood, that is enough for an ordinary talent to become a Saint level talent.”

In terms of talent, it was easier to raise the more mundane one was. For an ordinary talent to become a Saint level talent, all they would need was a single great lucky chance. For instance, two drops of Ancient Phoenix blood.

As for a Saint level talent rising to an Emperor level talent, that would require the accumulation of several lucky chances. In addition, a martial artist would also need to have extraordinary natural talent to begin with.

And above an Emperor level talent, if one wanted to rise to the ranks of Huo Wenlong and Huo Yu, that was even more difficult. At that time, something that might be a great lucky chance to a Saint level talent might only be standard treasure for someone like Huo Wenlong.

For instance, this Ancient Phoenix blood. To a talent like Huo Wenlong, this basically wasn’t a great lucky chance because Huo Wenlong already had an extremely rich Ancient Phoenix bloodline to begin with. Thus, this was something that was basic for him and that he should naturally have. Conversely, it would be a disadvantage if he didn’t.

So even if Lin Ming absorbed another 100 drops of Ancient Phoenix blood, this would only allow him to become a bit stronger. It wouldn’t increase his talent to another level.

Lin Ming’s comprehension of Fire Laws should have been something a genius of his talent level could accomplish. Otherwise, they were lacking to begin with.

“Yu’er, Xingxuan, I’ve already made an appointment with Li Yifeng to go to the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom. I leave one month from now. During this journey, I might be gone for several years.”

Of the four Divine Kingdoms, the strongest was the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom. They were also famed for their alchemy techniques. Since Lin Ming wished to study alchemy, it was naturally the best choice for him to go to the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom.

Alchemy was an extremely complex skill. In order to refine pills within a furnace it required more than just a variety of spiritual herbs and treasures. There were special materials needed to direct the mixture and also to form the medicinal base.

If he wanted to create high level pills, there was one material he absolutely couldn’t do without. That was – wood spirit jade.

Wood spirit jade and Demon God Bones were similar items.

Demon God Bones were formed when the leftover energy field of powerhouses or Saint Beasts was sealed underground, slowly condensing over a period of tens of thousands of years.

As for wood spirit jade, those originated from spiritual woods and herbs that remained unpicked by others and eventually died a natural death. Then, their rich energy and fruits would be buried in the ground for tens or even hundreds of thousands of years before finally condensing into a wood spirit jade.

The former was an animal and the latter was a plant.

Both were formed through similar principles, but there was actually a big difference between the two.

Since Lin Ming wished to study alchemy he needed a massive amount of wood spirit jade. However, this sort of material was extremely difficult to find in the South Horizon Region. Although there was a great amount of wood spirit jade in the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom, it was collected by others as a rare resource. With Lin Ming’s current finances, buying a small amount to use was no problem. But, if he wished to use a great amount, especially high quality wood spirit jade multiple times, then this was something that even Lin Ming’s wealth couldn’t support. Not to mention that he didn’t have the wealth to support continued use, but the main problem was that wood spirit jade was a material that couldn’t necessarily be bought.

Lin Ming had taken inventory of all his belongings. Up until now, the strongest powerhouse he killed was the fourth stage Life Destruction Xuan Wuji. As for the rest of his wealth, the next two with the most resources had been the two helpers of Xuan Wuji that had helped him lay down the great array formation in the deep sea as well as the South Sea Demon Region’s Elders. All of these people added together had a wealth equal to that of Xuan Wuji.

In other words, Lin Ming was currently quite wealthy amongst high level Life Destruction powerhouses. However, he was far from being able to compare with a Divine Sea powerhouse.

Of course, this was assuming that Lin Ming didn’t sell the heaven-step Demon God Bone or the blood of the Ancient Phoenix. These two treasures were naturally not something that Lin Ming would casually use.

If Lin Ming wanted to go to the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom to find wood spirit jade, it would be impossible for him to purchase it with his wealth. And he couldn’t purchase it to begin with since there was no place to do so.

So, Lin Ming could only rely on the rich knowledge inherited from that Realm of the Gods alchemist to seek wood spirit jade and excavate it on his own.

It wasn’t an exaggeration to say that every alchemist could also be called a skilled geologist and explorer. In order to look for wood spirit jade, and especially high quality wood spirit jade, one would often have to search hundreds or even thousands of feet underground. A martial artist’s perception had problems penetrating underground to begin with, much less the fact that the regions where wood spirit jade existed often had special geological features that interfered with perception.

With these factors combined, an alchemist could only rely on their experience and knowledge to search for wood spirit jade.

For the remaining month, Lin Ming closed up to thoroughly research alchemy techniques. Although the memories of that Realm of the Gods alchemist had been completely etched into his mind, integrating and mastering this information was still a very long and arduous process.

During his research of alchemy techniques, when his mind was fatigued, Lin Ming would take out a Demon God Bone and continue training. After some time, Lin Ming had already gone from the early Revolving Core realm to stabilizing himself firmly in the center.

However, he still had a very long road until he reached the Life Destruction realm.

From Revolving Core to Life Destruction could be considered a large boundary. To a human martial artist, this was the process of their body being transformed and reborn into something new.

Before Life Destruction, that was a mortal body.

After Life Destruction, that was a spirit body.

This sort of transformative process was completely different from the body transformation process of washing the marrow and tempering the body.

Once body transformation was brought to the point of 100% Tempering Marrow with the Eight Inner Hidden Gates opened and the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace afterwards, then a martial artist would have a body comparable to a Saint artifact, indestructible and invincible. They could raise their hand to sink the stars and shatter the moon and their roar could kill weaker martial artists.

A spirit body was different. Even though it was a spirit body, the defensive power was still frail and without the protection of true essence it would easily be pierced through by weapons.

The role of the spirit body was to converge the origin energy of the heavens and earth. A Revolving Core realm martial artist could only store true essence in their dantian and meridians. It was also impossible for them to directly absorb heaven and earth origin energy with their bodies. Rather, they had to rely on their many acupoints.

But after Life Destruction, that mortal body would reform from scratch, expelling all impurities and activating every cell so that they could actively absorb heaven and earth origin energy.

Thus, a martial artist with a spirit body completely didn’t need acupoints and could use their bodies to absorb heaven and earth origin energy. This meant that a Life Destruction martial artist would have a total true essence quantity several times that of a Revolving Core martial artist. Even their resilience and endurance would greatly increase.

This was also the reason why a Life Destruction martial artist’s strength leapt upwards.

If Lin Ming could reach Life Destruction, then not only would he have a spirit body, but he would also be tempered with the Eight Inner Hidden Gates and have a bodily durability equal to that of a treasure. To have both of these benefits was the advantage of dual cultivating in body and essence.

Without noticing, until up the day that Lin Ming and Li Yifeng’s agreed appointment was, Lin Ming still didn’t have an understanding of the four Divine Kingdoms. In fact, he didn’t even know all of the four Divine Kingdoms’ names. To have a guide was wonderful. Not to mention anything else, but there was a trip of millions upon millions of miles to go from Divine Phoenix Island to the four Divine Kingdoms, and there were hundreds of large and small transmission arrays that had to be passed through. Without Li Yifeng’s help, passing through these transmission arrays wouldn’t be easy.

Chapter 762 – White Dragon Jade Row

“Thanks. What is the price on this ore? I’ll give you the equivalent market price amount.” Although Lin Ming had planned on searching for wood spirit jade, the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom was still an extremely vast region. Moreover, many wood spirit jade-rich locales had been locked up by the authority of the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom. If he wanted to search for his own wood spirit jade then he would need a massive amount of time. If so, then it was best for him to buy as much as he could with his current wealth.

“Brother Lin couldn’t be planning on studying alchemical techniques, right?” Li Yifeng saw that Lin Ming wasn’t a wood-attribute martial artist, then the more likely reason he would want wood spirit jade like this would be to practice alchemy techniques. Normally, once a martial artist reached a certain boundary, it was common for them to study several auxiliary skills in order to help temper their soul. For instance, Li Yifeng himself studied array formations.

“That is my intention.”

Li Yifeng whistled, “Whew, Brother Lin, you just started studying alchemy techniques and you already want to use wood spirit jade?”

Lin Ming laughed out loud, not explaining further.

He understood what Li Yifeng was trying to say. After all, he was only 21 years old so he couldn’t possibly have studied alchemy techniques for too long. And, something like alchemy required the accumulation of experience and repeated failures. A newcomer to alchemy would have a very low chance of success, and wanting to practice creating high level medicines was simply a pipedream. And with wood spirit jade being so rare and valuable, using it to train up one’s skill was simply far too luxurious.

How could Li Yifeng have known that Lin Ming had inherited the complete memories of a Realm of the Gods alchemist? These memories included alchemy skills, experiences, and all sorts of recipes. Lin Ming had already thoroughly integrated most of this knowledge together, and now his success rate for creating low level medicines was already very high.

But in that Realm of the Gods Supreme Elder’s memories, there were far too few recipes that didn’t require wood spirit jade.

“Brother Lin, if you wish to try, then I can gift you a piece.” There were pieces of wood spirit jade ore. Although they weren’t low in value, Li Yifeng was still able to give out a piece of two.

“We’ll go with the market price.” Lin Ming didn’t want to owe favors to anyone.

The two of them pushed back and forth for a bit, and finally, Li Yifeng listed the price for the four pieces of wood spirit jade. As Lin Ming heard this, he was actually shocked. Altogether, these four pieces of wood spirit jade were 600 spirit essence stones.

A low-grade spirit essence stone’s value was equivalent to a top grade true essence stone’s, which was the same as over a million low-grade true essence stones.

600 spirit essence stones were worth more than 600,000,000 low-grade true essence stones. When Lin Ming had dug up the buried treasure of the third-grade Moon Seizing Sect, besides some pills and 12 Shattered Heart Demon Crystals, there were also around 7000 to 8000 medium-grade true essence stones. If those were all traded in, that wasn’t even enough for one million true essence stones.

The entire buried treasure deposit of a third-grade sect wouldn’t even be enough to buy a small lump of wood spirit jade. Lin Ming also estimated that Li Yifeng was quoting him a price on the lower end. To a character like Li Yifeng, not to mention a low-grade spirit essence stone, but perhaps even a medium-grade spirit essence stone didn’t mean much to him.

Like this, 600 top grade true essence stones disappeared. Not accounting for the treasures that Lin Ming hadn’t exchanged for spirit essence stones yet, Xuan Wuji’s wealth had shrunk by 10%.

If things continued at this pace, then Lin Ming would be broke in no time.

‘Do I really have to sell that heaven-step Demon God Bone?’

As Lin Ming thought about this, he walked into his own room and began to start his first alchemical recipe using wood spirit jade.

The memories of that Realm of the Gods alchemist had been extremely complete without many holes. His skill, technique, and experience in alchemy had been incomparably profound and complex, far more complex than the inscription techniques Lin Ming had learnt before. If it wasn’t for the fact that Lin Ming’s cultivation had rapidly risen since then, wanting to study these alchemy techniques would have been nothing but a dream within a dream.

It required a massive amount of resources to raise an alchemist. The reason that nearly all of the alchemists in the entire  Sky Spill Continent were concentrated in the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom was that they had adequate resources.

In other words, they were filthy, disgustingly, sickeningly rich.

And putting aside the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdoms, the other three Divine Kingdoms probably couldn’t produce a top class alchemist. This was because the consumption of resources was too high; the gains weren’t equal to the losses. Also, their alchemy technique inheritance was far too lacking.

But for Lin Ming the alchemy techniques he studied were on an unbelievably higher level than what any alchemist grandmaster of the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom could ever hope to reach.

If it were said that the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom needed to use 100 jin of wood spirit jade to train an alchemist grandmaster, then for Lin Ming to study alchemy by himself might require several thousand jin of wood spirit jade.

This estimate already included the fact that Lin Ming had inherited the foundation of Realm of the Gods’ alchemical techniques as well as an immeasurable amount of experience.

What he wished to refine was miracle medicines capable of opening the Eight Inner Hidden Gates and the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace. The lowest level materials for these types of medicines would be ingredients like the profound gold divine fruit and other such heavenly materials. As for the requirements of wood spirit jade, not only did he need quantity but he also needed quality. In the memories of the Realm of the Gods Supreme Elder, top medicines frequently required top quality wood spirit jade that was aged for several million years, or even tens of millions of years.

This had already surpassed the understanding of any alchemist within the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom.

…………….

A month later, Lin Ming and the group made their way through countless large and small transmission arrays, finally arriving at the central region of the Sky Spill Continent. As Lin Ming looked down from his spirit boat, he saw that right beneath him was actually a vast and desolate desert.

“Are we close to the four Divine Kingdoms?” Lin Ming asked, a bit stunned. In his imagination, the four Divine Kingdoms were incomparably lively lands with grand Holy Lands everywhere. But currently, they had been flying through a seemingly endless desert for days now. And before this desert there had been nothing but more deserts upon deserts.

“Haha, we are indeed, we’re almost at the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom.” Li Yifeng had already guessed what Lin Ming was thinking. He continued, “Don’t look down on this desert below us. This area is called the Thatch Region. West of here is the Northwest Great Desert, which is also Wang Yichan’s domain. The Thatch Region is a place where good and bad exist, with bandits and desert pirates everywhere. The reason for this is because there is wood spirit jade produced here, and this area also isn’t under the jurisdiction of the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom.”

“I see!” Lin Ming was suddenly enlightened. Hundreds of thousands of years ago, or perhaps even millions of years ago, this desert beneath them had once been a great and lush forest with incomparably rich origin energy and all sorts of heavenly materials growing within. However, because of various geological changes, the spirit veins had withered away and the forest had eventually turned into a desert. The spirit trees and spirit plants had also been buried underground over the passage of time, slowly becoming a land filled with buried wood spirit jade.

Li Yifeng sighed as he reminisced over the past, “For this desert, there have been countless wars fought with rivers of endless blood flowing over the land. Ultimately, no one was able to take sole control of this land and thus it became a free land where all the major powers entrenched themselves. There are also a great number of wood spirit jade transaction sites here with all sorts of wood spirit jade carvings and accessories. These items change hands all the time; that is, this place is a sinkhole for a massive amount of spirit essence stones!”

Wood spirit carvings and accessories had to have a history of several thousand years as well as stemming from the hands of a famous craftsman in order to earn the recognition of being called an ancient jade treasure by someone like Li Yifeng.

The Realm of the Gods alchemist had several memories related to these things. In fact, that alchemist had actually been a wood spirit jade carving grandmaster. Carving wood spirit jade was also a method for alchemists to exercise their focus and precision, helping them in a small way to temper and perfect their own soul.

That Realm of the Gods alchemist had also collected a massive amount of ancient carvings and accessories. Of course, these treasures had a history of at least 60,000 to 70,000 years, with some being hundreds of thousands or even millions of years old. It was far from anything that the Sky Spill Continent could compare with.

“Brother Lin, I’ll take you to a place today. This is a good place, with far too many good things inside! I will take you to open your eyes!” As Li Yifeng spoke of that place his eyes began to fill with excitement.

“Okay.” What Lin Ming needed the most now was wood spirit jade. He certainly wouldn’t refuse going to such a place.

“That’s right, don’t tell that Murong about this, it will just be us two brothers going. That Murong is really about to pester me to death.” Li Yifeng’s words held a very familiar tone to them. Martial artists would generally refer to each other as ‘brothers’ as a sign of politeness, but this Li Yifeng seemed to treat Lin Ming as if they were really brothers.

A day later, Li Yifeng’s spirit boat stopped at a small city in the desert. After no resting well for an entire month, he decided to have a good night’s rest here and also search for a chance to throw off that annoying Murong. Li Yifeng brought Lin Ming and Qing’er to make seven or eight circles around the entire city before finally coming upon a humble and common-looking stone building.

From the outside, this stone building didn’t have a single sign. There were only four words written above the building door – White Dragon Jade Row.

After entering the stone house, Lin Ming finally realized that there was something peculiar going on here. The interior space was much larger than he had imagined, and the furnishings were a bit… crude. Everything seemed to be formed from the rough rocks of the desert. The stone tables and stone chairs seemed to be hewn apart by a saber without even being polished down.

At the side of the room was a stone table with some tea set aside for guests. And on the other side of the room were rows upon rows of wooden shelves. Every shelf had a variety of jade carvings and accessories placed upon it, ranging from as high as a foot to as small as a ring. The collection of items was dazzling and diverse.

In front of these shelves was a middle-aged man wearing a leather hat. The man had a sturdy build and there was a thick scar on his face. It was unknown just what sort of beast skin his clothes were made from, but his collar was opened wide and his sleeves were far shorter than his arms. His clothes had heavy-looking metal buttons on them, each of them as large as a baby’s fist.

This sort of clothing had a very rugged and barbaric flavor to it; it matched very well to the desert around them.

As the scarred man saw Li Yifeng approach, he immediately smiled in welcome, “Sir Li! No wonder I heard that lucky magpie call from the gates earlier; it seems that I have honored guests visiting today.” The scarred man looked rough and cumbersome but his mouth was thick with honey – it was obvious he was skilled at kissing ass. Then he took on a tone of business and asked, “Is Sir Li here to buy something today? We have just unearthed a pair of ancient bracelets, would Sir Li like to take a look at them?”

Hearing the scarred man’s attentive introduction, Li Yifeng’s eyes brightened. His interest had really been stirred up. “Good, let’s take a look.”

Just as Li Yifeng’s voice fell, another group of people walked in from outside. The man in the lead wore a yellow embroidered dragon robe and he had a pair of green balls in his hands that he was constantly rubbing together.

These balls were actually made from wood spirit jade.

“Isn’t that the great Sir Li? Hahaha, I never thought that I would stumble into you here at the White Dragon Jade Row. This is truly serendipity. Are Sir Li’s hands itchy and wanting to buy some little souvenirs from here?” The yellow dragon-robed man faintly smiled. From the tone of his voice he obviously came from some great and influential power.

Li Yifeng frowned as he saw this man arrive. It was obvious that he and this man were not on friendly terms.

Chapter 771 – Heavencraft Trading Company

When Demonshine saw the mass of blood, his shifty little eyes immediately brightened. “I want that blood!”

Lin Ming swept his mind over the blood. The blood was similar to the blood from the first level of the Cosmic Melting Furnace; both of them exuded an ancient energy. Thus, the should be blood of the Ancient Giant Demons. In terms of quality, it was far from being comparable to Ancient Phoenix Blood, but it was still extremely precious.

“Alright.”

Lin Ming wasn’t stingy. To Demonshine, who only had his soul form left, the power of this blood essence was the only way for him to recover. During the past years, Demonshine had helped him a great deal, and had even saved his life several times.

Demonshine hurriedly leapt out from Lin Ming’s spiritual sea, turned into a small red curly-haired dog, and plunged towards the mass of Ancient Giant Demon blood. He immediately swallowed it whole.

With a contented sigh, Demonshine’s dog-like face revealed an extremely satisfied expression.

After swallowing the blood, Demonshine’s entire body flushed red. Afterwards, his originally vague and distorted body became much more solid.

This continued for half an incense sticks worth of time. After it stopped, Demonshine used his paws to pat his belly, and burped loudly. “Awesome, so awesome! 10 more jin of this stuff would be great!”

Lin Ming faintly smiled, shaking his head. It was already quite good to have two taels of this blood, but this damned dog actually wanted 10 jin.

He pointed at the black demon armor floating in the air and asked, “Demonshine, can you tell me what this demon armor is?”

Lin Ming’s inherited memories from the Demon Emperor were mostly incomplete; he had no memories about this demon armor.

Demonshine licked his lips and replied, “That’s the demon armor that Master personally forged when he was still on the Sky Spill Continent. Tens of thousands of years ago, there was an epoch were countless rivals and heroes rose up in unison, with new legends being created daily. Master’s strength was unparalleled in that world, however, there were still opponents that could threaten him. For instance…the deep sea races!”

Lin Ming nodded in understanding. On this world, the boundless sea’s size was far greater than the land mass. There were an immeasurable amount of things that lived inside of the deep sea, including many diverse and interesting races. There were even races from the ancient desolate era, who had bloodline legacies far surpassing that of humanity.

In this situation, the number of deep sea race powerhouses that existed far surpassed that of humanity. If it weren’t for the fact that the deep sea races were more suited for living deep underwater, and couldn’t survive long on land, then they probably would’ve probably engaged in a never-ending war with humanity.

Demonshine continued, “Master fought with his deep sea race opponents for a long time, before eventually even this demon armor was pierced through, with Master barely managing to defeat his enemy in the face of countless dangers. Because the demon armor had been pierced, Master decided to keep the demon armor inside of the Cosmic Melting Furnace and repair it. However, the time required to repair the demon armor was extremely long. By the time that Master left this world, the demon armor still hadn’t been fully repaired. However, tens of thousands of years have passed now, and this demon armor has finally repaired itself inside of the Cosmic Melting Furnace. Not only has it been fixed, its grade is now even higher than it was in the past. That Giant Demon blood I just absorbed should’ve been left behind by master in order to help repair the demon armor; it’s simply that the demon armor didn’t use all of it up.”

“So that’s how it is…”

Lin Ming reached out his hand and grasped hold of the demon armor. Then, he discovered that there was a circular gap missing in the left chest region of the demon armor.

Such a uniform gap was clearly not caused by a weapon piercing through it. This area should’ve been where the heartguard mirror was placed.

“The heartguard mirror is missing?”

“Looks like it.” Demonshine shook his head, a bit regretful. “If it were the complete demon armor, then it’s value would be no less than the Cosmic Melting Furnace. After all, there aren’t many defensive treasures on its level out there.”

Lin Ming bluntly put on the armor. For a time, he felt a demonic energy wrap around his body, fusing with his bodily protective true essence, causing it to be even firmer and more tenacious than it was before.

“Oh? It had this sort of effect?”

“Of course. Good armor isn’t just tough, it also has a top class ability to reduce injuries. If one’s armor isn’t able to weaken an enemy’s attacks, then it’s useless no matter how solid it is!”

Many martial artists’ attacks had penetrative properties. Simply defending against the physical strike of their weapons wasn’t enough; one also needed to defend against the hidden energy behind it.

“What do you plan on doing with the Five Color Fruit and the Void Tempered Root?” Demonshine asked.

“The Five Color Fruit and Void Tempered Root are both high level heavenly materials. I plan to use them for the base of a pill I’ll make soon. I’ll also add a 200,000 year wood spirit jade, dragonspine grass, and finally skyflower stones to act as the catalyst, to concoct a Fivefade Void Pill. That should be enough for me to open the third of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates.”

“Hehe, if you reach the large success realm of your alchemy technique, then not only will it enhance your soul, but your body’s transformation progress rise will at an astronomical rate. Who wouldn’t be jealous of this? However, the Fivefade Void Pill is a pretty high ranking recipe; do you have the confidence to successfully refine it?”

“Not at the moment, but I can slowly practice until I can. I’m not in too much of a hurry. Practicing alchemy is also a way to temper the soul.”

Lin Ming’s inherited memories from the Realm of the Gods alchemist were relatively complete, including even the precious experiences and skills that he’d studied. However, just this alone wasn’t enough. While Lin Ming’s knowledge was sufficient, he still lacked coordination between his body, soul, energy, and mind.

This was akin to a zither master that had never played a zither song before. Even if they knew the music by heart, and knew perfectly well how to play the music, they still wouldn’t be able to perfectly interpret the song on their first try. This was simply because their fingers wouldn’t be able to keep up with their mind.

What Lin Ming had to do right now was constantly practice, so that his body could memorize the use of alchemical skills. Every time he touched the energy, his control of the flame… all of it had to become a conditioned reflex. He had to be able to put on a perfect performance without thinking. This was the only way for him to achieve the highest chance of successfully refining a pill.

“Where do you plan on finding dragonspine grass or skyflower stones?” Demonshine asked.

“I’ll look for Li Yifeng.” Lin Ming had already thought of this.

Li Yifeng was a Prince of the Seven Star Divine Kingdom who usually loved to make new friends; he should know all sorts of people. In addition, he had connections to many of the four Divine Kingdom’s domestic intelligence networks, so asking him for information would be both the fastest and most efficient way.

And Li Yifeng did not disappoint him. Just ten days later, he returned with news.

Ho-!

The flames of a sound transmitting talisman flashed in front of Lin Ming, causing him to immediately stop working on the pill he was currently refining. The only thing inside of the pill furnace was a pile of black ash.

He ruefully smiled. The Cosmic Melting Furnace’s heat was just too intense. Trying to practice with low level medicinal herbs that couldn’t stand up to these sort of burning hot temperatures was truly a great challenge.

During the past few days, he’d spent a third of the spirit essence stones he’d gained from the White Dragon Jade Row, all to buy wood spirit jade.

The medicinal herbs he’d been using for practice came from the medicine gardens of the South Sea Demon Region, and the Yin Yang Profound Palace. At this point, he’d used up 20% of the medicinal herbs, but the amount of successfully refined products were a pitifully low number. Usually, all he did was create pile after pile of black ash.

“If the Xing couple from the Yin Yang Profound Palace learned that their carefully grown medicinal herbs were all being used by me, just for practicing alchemy, I wonder just what sort of faces they’d make.” Lin Ming shook his head, laughing at himself. He’d been rapidly burning through his money these past  days. Although he called these medicinal herbs low leveled, the truth was,  they were enough to make a martial artist go crazy with greed if they were placed in a third-grade sect.

“Lin Ming, what does the sound transmitting talisman say?” Demonshine asked.

“It’s from Li Yifeng. He told me the whereabouts of skyflower stones. Apparently, they can be bought at the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom’s Heavencraft Trading Company. As for dragonspine grass, he still hasn’t found any information.”

“Alright. Then, what do you plan on doing now?”

“We’re going to the Heavencraft Trading Company first!”

…..

The Heavencraft Trading Company was located in Witch Creek City, which was within the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom. It had a 6,000 year old history, an inheritance that surpassed most fourth and fifth-grade sects, and was able to stand on the same level as some Holy Lands.

The Heavencraft Trading Company was one of the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom’s three great trading companies, and had a very deep background.

For the Heavencraft Trading Company to have developed to this level, and in the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom at that, inevitably meant that they were inextricably linked with the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom’s royal family.

When Lin Ming entered Witch Creek City, where the Heavencraft Trading Company Headquarters were located, he didn’t even need to ask around to see the location of the Headquarters building. This was simply because it the building stood out so much.

High in the sky there was a garret that rose hundreds of feet into in the air, and was over a thousand feet wide. It was actually floating there, suspended in midair.  Around the garret were traces of faint purple smoke that shone underneath the bright sunlight; it was obvious that all of this was due to an array formation.

Keeping such a massive garret suspended in the air likely took a massive amount of spirit essence stones every year. From this alone, one could see just how deep the Heavencraft Trading Company’s wealth was.

Lin Ming quietly waved his sleeves and flew upwards. But when he did, he discovered that there were invisible fluctuations that covered the sky. These fluctuations formed a kind of resistance, hindering Lin Ming’s movements as he approached the Heavencraft Trading Company. Lin Ming was slightly miffed. If he could feel this resistance, than others certainly could as well. How did this place even do business? Did they meet with their customers outside?

The higher Lin Ming flew, the more obvious the resistance became. By the time that Lin Ming had finally reached the entrance to the Heavencraft Trading Company, he’d come to an understanding that there were stipulations to enter this trading company. A martial artist with an extreme Xiantian cultivation, or perhaps someone that had just entered the early Revolving Core, or possibly even an early Revolving Core martial artist with an unstable foundation; none of these people would be able to enter the Heavencraft Trading Company.

And, even if they could, they’d have to exhaust all of their strength to do so, thus shaming themselves. There was no way that they’d have any face to enter the trading company afterwards. What kind of store was this, where one had to fight just to enter? If just entering once was like this, it was doubtful that many people would return.

This meant that the Heavencraft Trading Company slammed their doors in front of all martial artists below the Revolving Core realm. This should also be the reason why their trading company’s headquarters was suspended in midair.

To stay suspended in the sky already gave off a lofty and grandiose feeling. Coupled with the fact that they denied to serve all martial artists below the Revolving Core realm… this was enough to establish just how high quality a business the Heavencraft Trading Company was.

As Lin Ming walked up the steps of the Heavencraft Trading Company, he saw a large black sign hung proudly above the 50 feet tall gates. There had been two highly-stylized words written on it with a large, thick brush—’Heavencraft Pavilion’.

These two words held faint traces of Concepts and Laws imbued within them. And on both sides of the high gates, there were also more accompanying words.

These words were simple:

‘Only treasures sold, no common things.’

‘Only powerhouses accepted, no entry for the mediocre. ‘

“How audacious!” Lin Ming was speechless. This Heavencraft Trading Company was really crazy. Did this mean that every single person who couldn’t enter the Heavencraft Pavilion was a mediocre person?

As he walked towards the Heavencraft Pavilion, the gatekeepers had already opened the doors, gesturing invitingly towards Lin Ming.

In the spacious lobby, there weren’t many visitors; it seemed somewhat deserted and lonely. This was also within his expectations. After all, the Heavencraft Trading Company didn’t rely on the volume of its transactions to succeed.

“This Young Hero, may I ask what requests you have?” Every visitor to the Heavencraft Trading Company would be approached by a beautiful young maid, who would then give them one-on-one service. The young girl responsible for assisting Lin Ming seemed to be around 18 or 19 years old. Her slender figure was very tall; she was only a bit shorter than Lin Ming.

“I would like to purchase skyflower stones.” Lin Ming directly stated.

Chapter 772 – Skyflower Stones

“Skyflower stones?” The young maid asked, stunned. These were extremely rare objects. Heavencraft Pavilion had just managed to obtain several skyflower stones recently. Because they were high level alchemy materials, they were very popular in the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom, and their price was also correspondingly sky high.

She never thought that Lin Ming, who seemed so young, who immediately ask for skyflower stones.

The young maid hesitated for a moment, suspecting that Lin Ming was simply messing around and just wanted to see the beautiful skyflower stones. Then, he would just make an excuse and decide not to buy them.

Although she had her doubts she still reported this information over. A moment later, a black-clothed old woman walked down from upstairs.

The black-clothed old woman narrowed her eyes as she sized up Lin Ming. With her experience she could naturally see that Lin Ming’s foundation was exceedingly stable. In addition to his age and cultivation, he should definitely be some extraordinary junior of his generation.

This sort of person truly might be able to afford skyflower stones.

“This little brother, please come along with me.”

The old woman turned around and walked upstairs with Lin Ming following close behind her. As Lin Ming stepped onto the staircase, he discovered that between the floors of Heavencraft Pavilion, there were actually invisible layers of resistance similar to when he was flying up. Except, the resistance from this level to the next was twice as much. Perhaps even a normal early Revolving Core martial artist wouldn’t be able to walk up.

When he turned around to look at the young maid behind him, he saw that she had a shining token on her waist. It was clear that this token let this Houtian level maid freely traverse the Heavencraft Pavilion.

There were even less people on the Heavencraft Pavilion’s second floor. After Lin Ming sat down, two maids set a plate of snacks down in front of him. Not too far away from Lin Ming, there was a red-clothed old man sitting down at another table. This red-clothed old man had a second stage Life Destruction cultivation.

The old man was holding a teacup in one hand while slowly fiddling with a cover in the other. He glanced up at Lin Ming, all smiles.

Lin Ming nodded politely in return. This red-clothed old man should also be a guest of the Heavencraft Pavilion.

At this time, from a side hall of the second floor, a purple-veiled slender woman walked out. “Two guests, you’ve waited for a long time.”

Her melodious voice that was like tinkling bells immediately attracted both Lin Ming and the old man’s attention.

The woman looked to be just over 20 years old, and although she had veil over her face, one could clearly make out that the woman underneath was a simple yet exquisite beauty. Her stature was elegant, and her skin glittered like a translucent crystal. She was a stunning specimen of femininity that was easy for others to be lost in.

The woman opened her mouth and said, “I’ve heard that both honored guests are here to purchase skyflower stones. The truth is, these skyflower stones only arrived at the Heavencraft Pavilion’s Headquarters five days ago, yet 20-30 people have already come to see them. However, no one has been able to purchase them. This is mainly because….”

As the purple-clothed woman spoke up to here, she smiled and continued, “This is mainly because these skyflower stones don’t belong to our Heavencraft Pavilion, but instead have been placed here on commission by another esteemed guest. This guest wishes to use the skyflower stones to trade for some equally rare materials. If you two honored guests are unable to bring out an item that can satisfy that guest, then no amount of spirit essence stones will be enough.”

“Oh, so it’s like that. I was wondering why such valuable alchemical materials had remained within the Heavencraft Pavilion for so long. May I inquire as to which martial cultivator it was? Perhaps this old man might know him!” The red-clothed old man asked as he stroked his beard, smiling. He obviously had the intention of trading for the skyflower stones by directly establishing his relationship with the owner.

The purple-clothed spoke with no intentions of hiding the truth, “It’s Grandmaster Zhuan Bixian.”

“Zhuan Bixian!” The red-clothed old man revealed a look of shock, “So it’s Grandmaster Zhuan Bixian, who’s ranked in the Destiny Decree’s top 150! Then, this is truly out of this old man’s league.”

The red-clothed old man shook his head over and over again.

From the Houtian realm to the Life Destruction realm, the difference was only equal to a single boundary within the Life Destruction realm. This was also the reason that there was such a huge disparity in strength between martial artists of different stages in the Life Destruction realm. The red-clothed old man was at the second stage of Life Destruction; that was an entire four boundaries away from the sixth stage Life Destruction Zhuan Bixian. Not just that, but every boundary within the Life Destruction stage carried with it an enormous risk of death.

This caused the red-clothed old man’s status difference with Zhuan Bixian to be even greater than a Xiantian realm martial artist and Revolving Core martial artist in the South Horizon Region. Especially since this Zhuan Bixian was a master listed on the Destiny Decree.

As the red-clothed old man spoke, a handsome 17 to 18 year old youth stepped down from the stairs. He faintly looked over Lin Ming and the red-clothed old man, then said, “I am Grandmaster Zhuan’s disciple. Grandmaster’s time is precious, so if you have any precious treasures that you’d like to trade with, please bring them out for me too look at.”

This handsome youth was young, but his tone of voice was quite arrogant. His words carried a hint of superiority and impatience. In truth, this was also understandable. During the past days, dozens of guests had come to the Heavencraft Pavilion to personally request the skyflower stones. Every time this happened, this youth would have to come downstairs to meet them. He’d run down here over and over again, yet no one had been able to bring out anything that could attract his attention. How could anyone else not be impatient at this point?

The red-clothed man laughed, thinking little of it. He sent a true essence sound transmission towards the handsome youth. If he dared to come here to buy skyflower stones, then he naturally had to have some valuable possessions to trade with, and was currently listing them out to the youth.

After the handsome youth finished listening to the red-clothed old man, his face changed and he icily said, “I apologize, but my Master already has many of these things, and has no interest in obtaining any more of them. In fact, his are even more precious.”

The red-clothed old man’s smile froze on his face. The handsome youths haughty and indifferent tone obviously brooked no room for negotiation.

Lin Ming watched all of this happen while thinking about it. He’d expected this. After all, a Revolving Core martial artist wouldn’t have any interest in the possessions of a Xiantian martial artist.

“And you?”

The handsome youth glanced over at Lin Ming. When he saw that Lin Ming only had a Revolving Core level of cultivation, he didn’t hold out much hope that Lin Ming would have anything interesting.

Lin Ming was silent for a moment. He’d been thinking about what items he could bring out that would interest Zhuan Bixian. In fact, he did have a great number of incomparably valuable treasures that could interest him. For instance, the heaven-step Demon God’s Bone, the Concept of Fire jade slips from Timeworn Phoenix City, the remaining six drops of Ancient Phoenix Blood, the Void Tempered Root, the Five Color Fruit, and so on.

However, it was naturally impossible for Lin Ming to take these items out. And even if he did, it wasn’t something that just some skyflower stones could possibly trade for.

After deducting these items, Lin Ming’s leftover possessions weren’t very valuable.

Seeing that Lin Ming hadn’t spoken, the handsome youth appeared a bit annoyed. “Do you have anything or not? If you don’t, then please don’t waste my time; I’m very busy.”

As Zhuan Bixian’s direct disciple, the handsome youth had a bit of a sense of superiority. Lin Ming didn’t seem much older than him, and no matter what angle he looked at it from, it was impossible that someone so young could be a true customer of the skyflower stones. This sort of top alchemical material could normally only be purchased by an older, more powerful alchemist.

Lin Ming faintly smiled, finally remembering something. He replied, “I do have something, but I fear that you won’t be able to recognize it, and thus won’t be able to complete the transaction.”

The handsome youth deeply frowned. He glumly said, “I might be young, but I’ve followed Master ever since I was a child. I’ve had to remember a massive number of materials every day. I’ve read countless ancient books detailing heavenly materials from the four Divine Kingdoms. Underneath the heavens and earth, I dare to say that there’s nothing I won’t be able to recognize. If I can’t recognize something, then that item would be something that even a Divine Sea Supreme Elder wouldn’t want to have, and you naturally wouldn’t either. If you have anything then take it out. I fear that whatever you think might be precious and rare, as you’re saying, will just be an ordinary good in my eyes!”

The handsome youth had a good deal of experience and insight, otherwise Zhuan Bixian would never have sent him here to supervise the transaction.

“Alright.” Lin Ming nodded, and calmly took out a jade box from his spatial ring. When he opened the jade box, one could see a red plant with a meat-like consistency. On top of its roots was a distorted face; it looked like a ghost that was being tortured.

Underneath the face was a fist-sized crown of meat that was pulsating like a rapidly beating heart. The entire plant looked like a mouse that had just been born; it’s flesh was a light yellowish-pink, and there were also some light hairs decorating it. It was an atrocious thing that was quite difficult to look at.

Zi zi zi!

When the handsome youth saw this plant he paused, completely stunned. Was this a plant or an animal? How could something grow into such a disgusting, nauseating appearance? And what was this even called? It was simply to bizarre to the extreme.

“This item, would Grandmaster Zhuan need it? I’d like to ask you to appraise it for me.”

Lin Ming pushed the jade box forwards the handsome youth. This plant was the 10,000 Year Old Corpse Grass that Lin Ming had found in the Eternal Demon Abyss.

10,000 Year Old Corpse Grass was similar to caterpillar fungus from the mortal world. It was a parasitic plant that would attach itself to the corpse of an Emperor level powerhouse, and would then use the skeleton as nourishment. As it grew, it would have to constantly devour the vitality of martial artists in order to mature.

When Lin Ming had adventured into the Eternal Demon Abyss, he’d seen Highlord Sandlight and Higbnhlord Sky Eye trick and kill their companions, turning them into flesh and blood sacrifices for the 10,000 Year Corpse Grass. They did so in order to feed the plant until it was satiated, and to let it then enter a deep hibernative state where it would be easier to capture.

Finally, Highlord Sandlight and Highlord Sky Eye had tried to kill Lin Ming, and were in turn turned into nourishment for the 10,000 Year Corpse Grass. Thus, the 10,000 Year Corpse Grass had fallen into Lin Ming’s hands.

This was something that could only grow in the strange environment of the Eternal Demon Abyss. It was the same as extinct within the entire Sky Spill Continent.

Mainly looking at its wonderfully ugly appearance, coupled with the screeching and harsh sounds it emitted, this created an absolutely shocking effect that left the handsome youth speechless.

In fact, not only was the handsome youth dumbfounded, even the purple-veiled woman and the black-clothed old woman were bewildered. They were both high level figures within the Heavencraft Pavilion. They were both well read, and had experiencd with a great number of treasures before.

Still, they’d never seen something like this.

Lin Ming asked, “What does Young Hero think of this?”

The handsome youth didn’t reply for the longest time. He didn’t even know what this thing was called, much less how valuable it was, so how could he possibly reply to Lin Ming.However, what he could determine from this thing, was that he sure was an animal or plant, it had an extraordinary powerful blood vitality! If it were used to refine a medicinal supplement towards one’s life force, it would certainly have miraculous effects.

In the face of Lin Ming’s question, the handsome youth was left embarrassed. He had just spoken so proudly of his skills and with such gusto too, and yet in the blink of an eye he encountered something he couldn’t identify. The loss of his face here had been immense.

The handsome youth grit his teeth and said, “I’ll look for my Master.”

Chapter 778 – First Battle of the Destiny Decree

Although Heavencraft Xiao couldn’t bear to thrust Xiaoxiao into the fiery pit of doom, he was well aware of just what it meant to stand in the Crown Prince’s good grace.

The Crown Prince was very ambitious. It was even possible that he would become the most powerful Divine Emperor in the history of the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom. If he could follow the Crown Prince then he would be able to step onto a larger stage and achieve a greater ideal.

“I’m sorry Xiaoxiao, but a great man must be ruthless. For my descendants, for the future glory of the Heavencraft Trading Company, I can only make you the small sacrifice to achieve the greater good.”

When Corpsemancer saw Heavencraft Xiao nod in agreement, he strangely cackled and said, “A wise man can recognize the situation!”

As he said these words he jumped onto his crow puppet and flew away in a cloud of dust.

Heavencraft Yun was left behind. His face was pallid and his lips trembled. In the end, he merely sighed, not saying anything at all.

………

“Little Jade, bring me a basin of water so I can wash my face.” Heavencraft Xiaoxiao ordered a maid.

“Yes, young lady.” A young girl in an aquamarine dress ran to fetch a basin of water and a white towel.

“Little Jade, my eyelids have been jumping all day. I fear that something bad will occur today.”

“Young lady, everything is fine. Don’t you have Sir Lin?” Little Jade chuckled, giving Xiaoxiao a humorous side eye. Xiaoxiao was at the age where she understood matters of love and also knew of the relations between men and women. She was at a similar age with Lin Ming who was strong, talented, handsome, and brave. It would be easy for any girl to fall for him and imagine a life with him.

However, Xiaoxiao simply didn’t have the energy or time to consider these things. All she felt was that she was tired. Very, very tired…

“Little Jade… go and deliver more spirit essence stones to Sir Lin. Also, make sure that Sir Lin’s three meals are all prepared with the best spirit food materials. Don’t –”

As Xiaoxiao spoke to here she suddenly heard a massive explosive sound originating from the front hall as if a thunderbolt had struck the earth. Her complexion immediately changed as she shot up.

“Young lady! Bad news! There’s a battle happening outside!”

A maid ran over in panic. Xiaoxiao rushed into the front hall and her apricot eyes suddenly shot wide open. In the front hall, a servant was stabbed through the throat with a bone lance. He lay face up on the ground, his eyes staring wide like a dead fish; he hadn’t died in peace.

Beside the dead servant was a skinny, skeletal old man who wore a cruel and sadistic expression. His face was full of pins as if he had been stitched from pieces of human skin. His dark ghostly green eyes were like a rabid wolf, and his entire body emitted a hostile, terrifying energy. Just by approaching him one would feel the fire of one’s life rapidly fading away, as if they would extinguish at any given moment.

“Who are you!?”

Xiaoxiao felt a chill crawl down her spine. Her cultivation was only at the Xiantian realm and she wasn’t able to see through this skeletal man’s cultivation in the slightest. But she had a premonition that this man was a terrifying existence; he was absolutely not some unknown nobody.

“Jejeje, this old man’s nickname is Corpsemancer. And you are that little girl Heavencraft Xiaoxiao… not bad, not bad.” Corpsemancer stretched out a scarlet tongue while his ghostly green eyes were observing Xiaoxiao. Then, he said words that made Xiaoxiao’s heart nearly freeze in her chest, “Using your skin to make a corpse puppet, that will certainly be beautiful indeed.”

“Corpsemancer!” Xiaoxiao’s face whitened to the point where there wasn’t even a touch of red left. Corpsemancer was a character on the Destiny Decree. He was a notorious and infamous individual who had murdered countless innocents. Moreover, his methods of killing were inhumane and grotesque. She didn’t doubt that Corpsemancer would do exactly as he said. If she fell into his hands then that would be a fate a hundred times worse than death. He was simply the devil incarnate.

Sky Spill Continent’s Destiny Decree had a total of 360 individuals ranked upon it. Among there, as long as one was at the sixth stage of Life Destruction then they would be ranked no matter how poor their foundation was. Even if their foundation was bad and they didn’t have too many years remaining they would still rank in the top 200.

As for those at the fifth stage of Life Destruction, most of them were arranged below the top 200.

It was extremely difficult for a fourth stage Life Destruction martial artist to be ranked. The exceptions were if there was something special about their cultivation method or if their talent was unbelievable.

And for Corpsemancer, his cultivation method was exceedingly special. What he cultivated were the corpse puppet techniques and Yin Corpse Laws of the demonic path; he was an incomparably abnormal existence that gave everyone headaches.

Xiaoxiao was the successor of the Heavencraft Trading Company so she naturally knew every single master on the Destiny Decree as well as a great deal of information about them. This was because those individuals were possible customers of the Heavencraft Trading Company.

As she recalled the information of Corpsemancer, she felt as if she had fallen into icy despair. She never imagined that her two uncles would invite a Destiny Decree martial artist.

“There is also someone called Lin Lanjian. Boy, be a good little child and come out to quietly become my experiment subject.” Corpsemancer poured true essence into his voice. His words penetrated through every inch of the Heavencraft Pavilion.

“Corpsemancer, are you looking for me?” Without knowing when, Lin Ming had appeared in a corner of the hall as if he had been standing there all this time. Only Corpsemancer realized that Lin Ming had used some incomparably exquisite movement ability to instantly arrive.

“Hehe, good movement technique, there’s a little bit of meaning to you. You’re so young and yet so strong. You’ll become absolutely great puppet material. This old man really does appreciate you. Thus, I´ll give you a chance to commit suicide so I can take your body. Otherwise, if you fall into my hands, then you won’t even have a chance to beg for death.”

When Corpsemancer chased down martial artists, many of them chose to commit suicide when they lost all hope of escaping any further. Otherwise, if they fell into his hands then they would have to linger at the border of life for several months, staring helplessly as their own skin, eyes, hands, feet, and everything else was slowly cut and stripped off.

This sort of pain and despair could be imagined.

Lin Ming quietly took out his red long spear. Although this guy in front of him was arrogant, that was because he had the qualifications to be arrogant. He was far more powerful than Xuan Wuji!

Lin Ming had no choice but to go all out in this battle. Moreover, he didn’t have complete confidence he could win. This was because he simply didn’t know the true depths of Corpsemancer’s strength.

As Corpsemancer saw Lin Ming pull out his spear, his grotesque smile widened. “It seems you want to refuse my generous charity? Very well, let me see just how tough your life is.”

He then unfolded both his hands. Atop of them were a pair of ghost claws that shined with a cold brilliance. A dim green light flashed intermittently on the edge of the ghost claws; this was corpse poison.

“Sir Lin.” Xiaoxiao bit her lips and said to Lin Ming with a true essence sound transmission, “Sir Lin, I sincerely thank you for everything you have done for me so far. Before, we have already agreed that if you were to run into someone that you couldn’t deal with, then the arrangement between us could be terminated at any time. Corpsemancer is ranked somewhere around 330-340 on the Destiny Decree. I am so sorry for having dragged Sir Lin into this mess. If there is a chance, Sir Lin, please escape.”

With every word she said, her face paled ever further. If it were possible she certainly hoped that Lin Ming would stay. However, if Lin Ming couldn’t deal with Corpsemancer then there was no meaning in him staying here to die.

As she imagined her fate once she was captured by Corpsemancer, she was terror-stricken.

Lin Ming glanced at Xiaoxiao for a brief moment and responded, “To show mercy to your enemies is to be cruel to yourself. If you don’t take advantage of the time when you have absolute superiority to eliminate your enemies then you will inevitably incur the bitter consequences of your own weakness. Remember this and take care!”

After saying this, Lin Ming grasped his red long spear and rushed out of the Heavencraft Pavilion.

Peng!

The great doors that stood several dozen feet high were instantly broken apart by Lin Ming’s spear. He then soared out without glancing back.

Xiaoxiao felt as if she had lost her soul at this moment.

To show mercy to your enemies was to be cruel to yourself…

This was the most simple truth that everyone understood. But to truly implement this required great courage and determination.

She closed her trembled eyes. She knew exactly what Lin Ming was referring to. In a situation where she had absolute advantage, she had allowed Heavencraft Yun to freely leave as he willed.

She didn’t dare to kill Heavencraft Yun because she feared she couldn’t withstand the pressure from the family. She was afraid that Heavencraft Xiao would use this opportunity to punish her, possibly even expel her from the family.

But now, Heavencraft Xiao had taken the advantage to strike the first blow. The only one to suffer would be herself.

“Sir Lin should be escaping… can he escape…?”

As she looked at the broken door and the shattered wood that swayed in the wind, all she felt was incomparable sadness and grief.

Now that Lin Ming had left, she was nothing but a fish on a chopping block; she had no strength to resist.

“Young lady, Corpsemancer is chasing Lin Lanjian. We should take this chance to escape as fast as we can.” The black-clothed old woman nervously said. She then reached out her hand to grab Xiaoxiao.

Xiaoxiao mournfully laughed. She whispered as if she had just lost her very soul, “It’s useless, everything is useless. Corpsemancer has left a mark on my body. I can no longer escape his palm…”

“That Lin Lanjian, he actually runs when we need him the most! Damnit!” The black-clothed old woman angrily said.

“Grandma White, there is no one in this world that should be born to die for us…” Xiaoxiao shook her head. But as her voice fell she suddenly heard a loud thunderous explosion from outside that caused the entire Heavencraft Pavilion to tremble.

Hmm?

Xiaoxiao ran several steps out of the broken door. From here, she could see that several miles away, Lin Ming and Corpsemancer were flying high in the sky, their clothes flapping wildly in the wind.

Beneath them, the bustling and lively Witch Creek City sprawled out to the endless horizon.

The air still reverberated with intense true essence shockwaves. It was obvious that a great battle was brewing.

“Lin Lanjian intends to battle Corpsemancer? The reason he ran out of Heavencraft Pavilion was because he feared their battle affecting the others inside?”

For some time, Xiaoxiao was lost in thought. And beside her, Grandma White was also stunned. Although she had complained about Lin Ming just now, those were only words said under a veil of angry and helpless desperation. She was well aware that what Lin Ming had done was completely reasonable. After all, their agreement had been that their contract would become invalid once Lin Ming met a powerhouse that he couldn’t contend with.

And even if there was no such agreement, Lin Ming escaping was also completely understandable.

If it had been her in Lin Ming’s position, she would also escape at this time. Only a complete fool would die for a stranger.

However, she never imagined that Lin Ming would actually decide to fight Corpsemancer.

At this time within Witch Creek City, whether it was martial artists or common mortals, every single person had raised their heads to see the scene unfolding up in the sky.

Witch Creek City was a medium to large scale city of the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom. In this city there were naturally a vast number of considerably experienced masters. They were all able to instantly distinguish that these two people up in the air were top class powerhouses.

In particular that skinny skeletal fellow who was wrapped in white cloth; he was definitely a master amongst masters!

Who were they? They dared to fight in Witch Creek City?

The powerhouses of Witch Creek City were bewildered.

Of course, most of these martial artists were below Revolving Core; they couldn’t see through Lin Ming and Corpsemancer’s cultivation.

“Those two actually dare to fight in the skies of Witch Creek City! This is far too brazen!”

“That’s right! Fighting is prohibited within Witch Creek City. This is the general rule of every large city. If these two people dare to blatantly ignore the rules in front of everyone then their punishment will be death!”

Chapter 779 – The Great Battle of Witch Creek City

Large cities naturally had the law and order of large cities, otherwise, they simply couldn’t be called a city. There would be no difference between them and the barbaric wilds filled with bandits and strife.

In Witch Creek City, all who took part in public fighting would suffer severe punishment. Anyone who ignored warnings would even be executed.

“The city guards are on their way. Then there will truly be a good show to watch, haha!”

And as everyone expected, they city guards quickly caught up. The captain of them was a man named Rong Lin. Before everyone arrived he shouted out, “Just who the hell do you two think you are!? You dare to fight so openly in my Witch Creek City! How insolent!”

As the captain of the city guards, he was generally a solemn and dignified character. Usually, just a single shout from him was enough to frighten others and solve any problem.

But this time, after he shouted out his warning, he was actually ignored. He stared with eyes wide open, as his vision tightly locked onto that skinny skeleton old man that was flying in the air. Then, his complexion completely paled.

“C-Corpsemancer!?”

He was petrified the spot.

“Captain, those two fellows are far too arrogant, they actually dare to fight in the skies of my Witch Creek City! They are courting death!” Beside Rong Lin, another city guard that had relied on family connections to join suddenly spoke up. He was a young martial artist that served as Rong Lin’s deputy.

“Captain, why don’t you tell them to lay down their weapons so we can quickly capture them?” The young martial artist looked at Rong Lin in puzzlement.

However, Rong Lin remained completely silent while his complexion was becoming increasingly ugly.

Well, if the captain wasn’t going to do it then he would do it for him. The young martial artist felt that shouting out loud and grabbing everyone’s attention would be a very glorious act.

“To those listening above! We are –”

The young man only just started shouting when Rong Lin jumped like a cat and quickly covered the young man’s mouth.

“Do you want to die!?”

Rong Lin’s entire forehead was covered with nervous sweat. In every Divine Kingdom, there were only several dozen Destiny Decree characters and most of them were in long term seclusion. They simply lived like hermits for the majority of their life.

If they were a central ruling figure of a mortal nation, then Rong Lin could only be considered a middle class city guard official. The disparity in status could be imagined.

And most fearful of all was that Corpsemancer was an infamous fellow known for his capricious cruelty. Anyone that fell into his hands would suffer a fate worse than death!

He would rather face a top 200 ranked Destiny Decree character than have to cross paths with Corpsemancer. This was because Corpsemancer could randomly kill someone without even batting an eye!

“Captain?” The young man asked somewhat unhappy.

“Everyone obey my command! Evacuate the crowd and isolate the scene! Without my orders, no one can speak a single word of nonsense and absolutely no one can interfere! All offenders will be brutally punished!”

As Rong Lin spoke to here he suddenly saw that the skeletal man floating in the air shot a glance at him. The skeletal man smiled, revealing a blood red tongue and bone white teeth.

It was just a single look but Rong Lin was filled with fear and terror. It was like an icy bone lance had been thrust into his heart.

Rong Lin trembled with dread. He waved his hand and said, “Everyone, retreat ten miles out!’

“What?”

“F*ck! I told you to retreat, so retreat! That fellow above us is a Destiny Decree master!” Rong Lin originally didn’t want to reveal the status of Corpsemancer, but as he saw that the young martial artist wasn’t convinced, and even had an eager look to butt his way in, he had no choice but to announce a bit of Corpsemancer’s information.

“De-de-de-Destiny Decree!?” The young martial artist was not an idiot. In fact, upon hearing the name of the famous Destiny Decree, everyone was shaken to their cores. They were all well aware just what that implied.

“Is there a mistake? If that skeletal old man is a Destiny Decree master, then what about his opponent? He’s obviously just a 20 some year old youth, and his cultivation… his cultivation is… at the late Revolving Core realm!?”

“Yes, he is only at the late Revolving Core realm and his opponent is Corpsemancer. That young man is insane!” Rong Lin’s eyes blazed as he looked at Lin Ming. As captain of the city guard he naturally had an understanding toward all the top level characters of the four Divine Kingdoms. However, he couldn’t recall the slightest bit of information about Lin Ming.

It wasn’t just the city guard, but all observing martial artists discovered that the difference in cultivation of the two flying in the air was simply too great.

“Is this a life or death battle, or a senior advising a junior?”

“He’s definitely directing him. Don’t make too much of a fuss, that old man might be that youth’s master. He will certainly suppress his strength to a degree.”

Woosh! Woosh!

Two shadows flew to a distant point 10 miles away from the battlefield. These two people were Grandma White and Xiaoxiao.

“Lin Lanjian Isn’t someone from my Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom nor is he someone from the other three Divine Kingdoms. It’s probable that he hasn’t heard the fame of the Destiny Decree yet, thus he rashly acted. Young miss, this is our only chance. If we continue watching the battle from here then it’s the same as waiting to die.” Grandma White anxiously said.

If Lin Ming really were a junior of the four Divine Kingdoms then it would be impossible that someone with a talent as monstrous and unprecedented as his could remain obscure. Thus, she only thought that Lin Ming came from some faraway region and didn’t know just how fierce the ranked masters of the Destiny Decree were.

Let alone Lin Ming, even that senior that knew Xiaoxiao’s father couldn’t be ranked on the Destiny Decree.

“Grandma White, there is a mark planted on my body; escape is no longer possible. I have already accepted my fate. I would rather stay here and watch Young Hero Lin’s battle. Perhaps, there is even a small glimmer of hope that Young Hero Lin can create an opening for us. At that time we’ll attack together, and even if we can’t win, we can still die an honorable death!”

“Alright…” Grandma White shook her head, no longer attempting to convince Xiaoxiao.

At this time, more and more martial artists began filling the skies. All of them felt that something was off about this situation. How come that the usually blustering and swaggering city guards didn’t take this chance to bring these law breakers down?

Meanwhile, up in the skies, Lin Ming and Corpsemancer had already faced each other for over 20 breaths of time.

Lin Ming was the first to make a move.

Bang!

Before his long spear even shot out, double force fields were already erupting outward.

The Asura force field combined with the Death God force field as the dual force fields were released together!

A tide of power rushed out in all directions, setting of a horrifying storm of energy.

The Death God force field, annihilating all life vitality.

The Asura force field, universal suppression of a martial artist’s strength and soul!

The air trembled. Most of those martial artists floating in the air and watching the scene weren’t masters. They hadn’t yet been able to figure out just how Lin Ming’s strength contrasted with Corpsemancer, but now as Lin Ming’s force field enveloped the entire battlefield, all of them became nothing more than leaves in a storm, scattering or collapsing in all directions! The slightly weaker martial artists, even if they were an entire mile away from Lin Ming, still vomited out a mouthful of blood as they were severely injured!

“What is that!?”

All of the martial artists were dumbfounded. Was this the power released by that youth?

“What kind of killing intent is this?” Xiaoxiao forcefully gulped. Lin Ming had never used this power when he fought the Elders of the Heavencraft Family. It was clear now that he didn’t think it was needed at the time.

“This is a force field ability, moreover he has dual force fields!” Grandma White recognized just what sort of skill Lin Ming had used. Force field abilities were exceedingly rare; even a supremely talented junior of the four Divine Kingdoms wouldn’t necessarily have one. It was a highly revered and respected ability.

This was not because a force field was freakishly strong, but because a force field could coexist alongside martial skills. It could invisibly increase a martial artist’s strength or have a number of other effects without affecting the martial artist’s fighting ability at all.

“Hehe, boy, I like you more and more. Once I turn you into a puppet I can keep your force fields. This is far too perfect! Force fields are the ability that puppet masters love the most!” Corpsemancer sinisterly smiled and his ghostly eyes were gleaming.

A powerful puppet master could restore most of the special abilities a martial artist had before death. In fact, a puppet’s power could even be raised through the passage of time with the application of a number of arcane skills.

“You really love dreaming.”

Lin Ming barked out a short laugh and flourished his spear. He poured his battle spirit into it and thrust out. The inherent power of thunderfire broke through the shackles of space, and with a keening cry, a turbulent wave of energy began to rise up from all around.

Bang! Bang! Bang!

Space nearly collapsed. Lin Ming’s spear instantly passed a 1000 feet forward, thrusting straight between Corpsemancer’s eyebrows.

Corpsemancer creepily laughed as his withered claws suddenly grasped forward. A black ghost claw appeared out of thin air and shot out towards Lin Ming.

As the claw shot forward a cold wind swirled up around it, as if countless grieving ghosts formed the black ghost claw that issued mournful wails.

Kacha!

The spear and sharp claw collided together. The ghost claw disintegrated, but Lin Ming’s spear light also melted away like white snow under the scorching sun.

True essence shockwaves rolled up in massive waves. All of the surrounding martial artists quickly retreated as their complexions immediately changed.

It had become crystal clear to everyone here that these two evil stars were simply ancient vicious beasts in human form. If they were caught up in the ensuing storm of energy then there wouldn’t be anything left of them, not even their ashes!

As for Xiaoxiao and Grandma White, they weren’t affected because they were very far away to begin with. But they could still feel that horrifying energy that rampaged about, even from such a distance.

“This should only be a testing move. I have no idea how much strength Lin Lanjian used, but if that is the majority of his strength then there isn’t even a slim chance that he’ll win. Corpsemancer hasn’t even brought out his puppets yet.”

Grandma White’s face was filled with worry. When Lin Ming had unleashed his dual force fields, a faint hope lit up in her heart. She had been slightly optimistic that Lin Ming might be able to create a miracle or even last a period of time against Corpsemancer. In such a massive fight, there would definitely be other masters arriving if it lasted long enough. At that time, there might be a chance for a favorable turn of events.

“How interesting! So interesting!”

Corpsemancer’s skin stitched face became more and more excited. He swiped his special ring and a massive demon puppet rushed out. There were two great wings on its back and its entire body was wreathed in thick, dark blue muscles that were as solid as rock.

Giant Demon?

Lin Ming’s mind went cold. This was actually a Giant Demon puppet! Just where had Corpsemancer managed to obtain the corpse of a Giant Demon?

“That is the puppet technique and also a Giant Demon puppet! That man must be…”

Some of the surrounding martial artists recognized the Giant Demon puppet. Although they didn’t recognize Corpsemancer, they did manage to recognize that puppet. In truth, top masters that wielded puppets were nearly extinct.

Thinking of all of them, there was only a single person that was this famous for their puppet technique.

And then combining that with this sinister and ominous old man’s cultivation, the truth of his identity finally revealed itself.

“The Destiny Decree ranked 330, Corpsemancer!”

“Corpsemancer? Is that really him!?”

“Heavens! No wonder the city guards don’t dare to do anything! That old man is actually Corpsemancer… Then just who is that youth? Did that young man come out of nowhere?”

At this time, no one said anymore that the fight unfolding in the air was a senior directing a junior. Corpsemancer was absolutely not the type to do so, and Lin Ming’s cultivation method was completely different from his.

This was a true life or death battle!

For a late Revolving Core powerhouse to challenge the Destiny Decree ranked 330, Corpsemancer, in a life or death battle…

This was madness!

Chapter 780 – Stepping Onto the Highest Stage

“This is a Giant Demon puppet that I carefully crafted myself. I call it… the Gargoyle. Let me take a good look at just how many of my puppets you can force me to use!”

Giant Demon puppet? So it seemed that the Sky Spill Continent also had a Giant Demon race. Just where had this Giant Demon corpse come from?

The Sky Spill Continent and the Holy Demon Continent were both isolated from each other. The last time that they had contact with each other was likely when the Netherworld Great Emperor traveled to the Sky Spill Continent through the Demon Emperor’s transmission array and then later on founded the Silent Demon Emperor City.

If it was said that there were Giant Demon skeletons from thousands of years ago then Lin Ming wouldn’t be surprised. But, puppet techniques required the use of fresh corpses in order to function properly. This meant that one of the four Divine Kingdoms had members of the Giant Demon race within them.

“Where is your Giant Demon corpse from?” Lin Ming directly asked.

“Hehe, of course it comes from the Asura Divine Kingdom. Is that so strange? This old man has no interest in bantering with the likes of you. Now die!”

Corpsemancer gave a loud shout and the Giant Demon puppet extracted a 15 foot axe before cutting it down towards Lin Ming.

As this axe cut out, roiling black clouds followed behind it. This was obviously the demon essence that the Giant Demon race used. Although it was similar to true essence, they had essential differences between them.

An astounding puppet master could reproduce all the abilities that the deceased had before their death. Demon essence was no exception.

‘The Asura Divine Kingdom actually has the Giant Demon race; that is beyond my expectations.’ Lin Ming shook his long spear, filling it with the Concept of Fire as he smashed it against the Giant Demon’s axe.

But at this time, there was a crackling sound as a two foot section of the axe broke off. A thick chain pulled out from the shaft, causing the entire weapon to turn into something like a bola.

With special devices and traps everywhere, it was nearly impossible to guard against. This was one of the special characteristics of puppets.

Ka ka ka!

Lin Ming’s red long spear was caught in the chain. At the same time, the axehead was pulled by the chain, smashing straight towards Lin Ming’s head.

At such a close distance, for such a change to happen in the axe was truly a sinister combat technique. Moreover, since Lin Ming’s spear was twisted into that chain he was unable to dodge it. Unless he abandoned his spear and retreated, his only option would be to directly block that axe.

But to a martial artist, their weapon was their life. To abandon their weapon in battle was equal to disillusioning their own heart of martial arts.

“Sir Lin!”

Xiaoxiao couldn’t help but cry out in alarm as she watched the battle from a distance.

All of the surrounding martial artists also watched with wide eyes, waiting to see just how this junior would fight against such a top genius.

But at this moment, Lin Ming appeared nothing but serene. He shook he long spear in his hands.

The large success bronze battle spirit erupted!

Kacha!

With a shattering sound, that chain as thick as an arm was directly broken apart by Lin Ming!

Soon after, Lin Ming’s spear thrust forwards, piercing through that half foot thick axe with an unstoppable and sharp spear light that stabbed towards Corpsemancer’s head.

“Mm?”

Corpsemancer was bewildered. This was… a battle spirit!?

With his sight and experience he naturally recognized that this was a battle spirit. Lin Ming only had a mere late Revolving Core cultivation and yet his battle spirit was so keen; how could he not be shocked?

Bang!

Lin Ming’s spear stabbed into a white bone shield. At that moment, in front of Corpsemancer, another puppet appeared. This puppet looked like a giant turtle. What Lin Ming had pierced through was its shell.

As the spear punctured the shell, although the shell didn’t break, cracks still appeared, spreading out like a spider web.

All of the martial artists present could clearly see what happened. A spear had broken apart the axe and simultaneously broke through the first level of armor of another puppet. This striking power was freakishly abnormal!

“So you comprehended a large success battle spirit. It seems I truly underestimated you, no wonder you would dare to fight me.” Corpsemancer’s ghostly green eyes flashed with a blazing light. He licked his lips and coldly said, “I have now decided to sincerely kill you.”

Lin Ming’s talent far surpassed Corpsemancer’s estimations. To have such an enemy, and for him to be so young, Corpsemancer naturally couldn’t allow him to live. Otherwise, his future troubles would be endless.

“Complete body!”

With a loud shout, Corpsemancer’s skinny skeletal body began emitting loud crackling sounds. The white cloth that bound his body like a mummy ripped apart and a pair of blood-red wings unfurled. After the wings stretched out they were more than 10 feet long; they appeared like the wings of a giant bat.

At the same time, scales began to appear all over Corpsemancer’s face. His arms lengthened and his claws became even larger, a chillingly cold light shining from them.

After the initial probing strike, Corpsemancer was now ready to go all-out.

Lin Ming was solemn. After reaching this boundary, no other junior was his opponent. If he wanted to fight he could only challenge those old monsters that had been stranded in the Life Destruction realm for hundreds of years. In front of these existences, Lin Ming was still far too young.

There were several small boundaries within the Life Destruction realm. From the first stage to the seventh stage of Life Destruction, the difference was approximate to the difference between the Houtian realm and the Revolving Core realm.

For the late Revolving Core Lin Ming to challenge a Destiny Decree master, that meant that he had now transcended the struggles of juniors and transitioned into fighting powerhouses of the older generation. At this moment, Lin Ming had truly stepped onto the highest stage of the Sky Spill Continent.

Corpsemancer extracted a massive scythe from his spatial ring. The scythe blade glowed with a cold light and its entire body was deep black. It looked like the scythe of the grim reaper.

As the scythe appeared, a limitless amount of resentment and malice filled the air, as if countless ghosts were weeping and screaming around the scythe.

“What is this sound? It pains the ears!”

“It’s drilling into my brain. The scythe is calling to me!”

All of the surrounding martial artists only felt as if countless demonic spirits were screaming into their ears. This sound seemed to have enormous penetrative power. Even if they covered their ears the sound still passed through, drilling directly into their spiritual sea.

As the martial artists with weaker cultivations heard this sound they felt as if their heads were about to crack open and all of the blood drained out from their faces.

“Hurry up and retreat!”

Some martial artists shook their hands as if they had awakened from a nightmare and began calling out warnings. However, many people were unable to withdraw under the effects of this sonic attack. They lost consciousness and fell down from the skies.

“This is the Evil Hate Scythe that Corpsemancer forged from countless suffering souls and lives. Every strike contains a near-endless amount of grudge and resentment; it can destroy a martial artist’s will!”

“If just hearing the sound of it is so terrifying, then what will happen if it cuts down on you!?”

Lin Ming bore the attack. As he was enveloped in the energy field of resentment from the Evil Hate Scythe, his face remained expressionless.

He could clearly hear this resentment colliding with his own dual force fields. ‘This Corpsemancer, it seems he really transformed his own body into a puppet.’

A high level puppet master’s greatest strength lay in their own bodies. This was because their bodies made the best puppets. Once their skeletons and meridians were modified beyond all recognition, their defensive power would far surpass a general martial artist’s.

To be invulnerable themselves and also be able to coordinate three or four puppets together, a powerful martial artist would have an extreme headache if they bumped into a formidable puppet master.

As Corpsemancer brought out his complete body, his two eyes had already transformed from a ghostly green to a deep blood red. He grabbed the long scythe in both hands and unfolded his wings. Then, he silently slid forwards like ghosts and demons; his speed was shocking!

All of the observing martial artists tarried. All they saw was a flash as Corpsemancer appeared in front of Lin Ming, his black scythe rapidly cutting down! This sort of speed was in no way inferior to Lin Ming’s Golden Roc Shattering the Void!

Too fast!

Lin Ming was already horrified. This wasn’t teleportation, but it was a speed that made it seem as if there were no difference!

“Nether Strike!”

The black scythe seemed to emerge from space. It cut through space, carrying with it endless resentment and howls from mourning ghosts as it slashed towards Lin Ming. This attack hadn’t even arrived and yet its aura was so terrifying!

Lin Ming waved his spear. Facing this all-out Corpsemancer, Lin Ming naturally didn’t dare to hold back.

Law of Annihilation, Chain of Stars!

A spear ran up to meet the enemy. The Concept of Fire and the Concept of Space were poured into the spear, causing all of the heaven and earth origin energy in a 10 mile radius to restlessly move. The fire energy and the power of space fused together, condensed into tiny little fragments that rapidly spun around like a chain of stars, shrouding down towards Corpsemancer.

Ca!

The tiny fragments of fire and space struck with the resentment of the black scythe, creating a harsh keening noise to split the air.

Lin Ming’s spear crossed with the black scythe. A terrifying wave of true essence exploded, causing the atmosphere to vibrate. They were nearly evenly matched!

During the battle, Corpsemancer revealed a diabolical grin. Not only did he have his own attack but he also had puppets!

As Corpsemancer struck out with the Nether Strike attack, the Giant Demon puppet and the great turtle puppet also attacked. The Giant Demon puppet turned the axe shaft in his hands, turning it into a makeshift long spear as he thrust out at Lin Ming’s back. At the same time, the great turtle puppet opened its vast maw and spat out a beam of black energy.

These two attacks joined together. Their combined power just was slightly less than Corpsemancer’s own Nether Strike.

This was an attack from the front and back!

“Sir Lin, be careful!” Xiaixiao shouted out. Her life was now linked together with Lin Ming’s – how could she not be tense? If Lin Ming was defeated, she would suffer a fate worse than death.

At this critical moment, Lin Ming took a sudden step forwards. Space twisted underneath his feet. Although it looked as if he had only taken a casual step forwards, he had actually crossed a mile, causing both of the puppets’ attacks to miss.

Lin Ming stood in the skies. A mile away from Corpsemancer, he pointed his spear point right at him.

“I’m also confident in my speed. Although my long distance speed may not reach the degree of your twin black wings.”

Bang!

Dozens of miles away, the black beam of energy released by the great turtle puppet smashed into a mountainside, causing an entire rock shelf to collapse.

Watching Lin Ming and Corpsemancer fighting in the air, everyone present felt as if they had lost their breath.

This was the showdown of Destiny Decree masters. Although the Sky Spill Continent had over 100 Divine Sea powerhouses, all of these existences were secretive individuals that almost never appeared. Most of them had hidden themselves in seclusion for countless years.

Without the Divine Sea, the Destiny Decree was king!

The Destiny Decree was equivalent to the highest stage of the Sky Spill Continent!

“Space Laws? What a pleasant surprise.” Corpsemancer sinisterly laughed. As Lin Ming had said, that extreme speed of Corpsemancer’s came from the pair of wings on his back. In terms of long distance travel, he was faster than Lin Ming. But, in short distances, he was actually slower than Lin Ming. Lin Ming’s Golden Roc Shattering the Void was able to twist space, with a single step, approaching teleportation. This was the strength of Laws. As for those black wings behind Corpsemancer, they were merely heaven-step flight treasures.

“You are indeed an unrivalled talent. Only killing someone like you can bring me sweet pleasure! Jejejeje!”

Chapter 784 – The Crown Prince’s Invitation

In the past few days, Lin Ming had come to understand what sort of person the Nine Furnace Crown Prince was.

His name was Yang Yun, and his martial talent was extraordinary. It seemed as if he had come across an immense fortuitous encounter when he was young, and had now broken through to Life Destruction at a mere 30 years of age.

Yang Yun was a character that wielded alarming power throughout the entire Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom. He wasn’t on a level that the likes of Li Yifeng could even compare to.

Although Li Yifeng was a Prince, there was a vast difference in their respective influence. Putting aside the disparity between the Seven Star Divine Kingdom’s strength and the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom’s strength, just Yang Yun and Li Yifeng’s respective status in their Divine Kingdoms alone was incomparable.

Li Yifeng could at best be considered a playboy, and had a natural disposition towards laziness and fun. His finances were all controlled, and he had even been punished with confinement before.

As for the Nine Furnace Crown Prince, he had at least five subordinates that were all Destiny Decree masters, and he himself was also ranked on the Destiny Decree. It was just that his ranking had been omitted from the Decree, and there hadn’t been any information dispatched about him for many years. The depths of his strength were a complete mystery to all.

Compared to Yang Yun, Li Yifeng was just a little baby that hadn’t grown up.

It was impossible for Lin Ming to be at ease when facing such a character. Yang Yun was nearly twice his age, and even the power of his subordinates wasn’t something Lin Ming could ever hope to contend with.

For the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom, Yang Yun represented the peak of strength outside of the Divine Sea powerhouses.

Despite the fact that Yang Yun had no enmity or grudge with Lin Ming, and that he shouldn’t even have a reason to harm Lin Ming to begin with, Lin Ming didn’t want to enter a place like the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom. That could truly be described as a dragon’s lake or a tiger’s cave; a truly dangerous zone!

Most of the Destiny Decree masters of the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom were subordinates of the Divine Kingdom. After all, the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom was not just a nation, but a quasi sixth-grade super Holy Land!

The Divine Kingdom’s three great Imperial Scholars, twelve Great Officials, and five Nine Furnace Guard Captains were all Destiny Decree ranked characters, and were also ranked extremely high on the Decree.

In addition to that, the Divine Kingdom had Emperor Uncles and High Princes that had lived for several thousand years and had gone into seclusion. These people were even more terrifying!

They had most likely entered into the Divine Sea. In a sense, the current Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom could compare with the Demon God Imperial Palace to a small degree. The Demon God Imperial Palace had once been a great sect that ruled the world, the most terrifying power in the entire Sky Spill Continent!

In front of these people, Lin Ming simply didn’t have any strength to resist. Once he entered the Divine Palace, he would be at their disposal.

Directly refusing Yang Yun wasn’t a good idea either, however, as it might anger him. This way, Lin Ming could only sidestep this invitation by saying he still hadn’t recovered from his wounds after his fight with Corpsemancer, and needed more time to recuperate.

This was a tactful method of rejection.

After Lin Ming passed out the message, he continued to train and practice alchemy.

Just yesterday, Xiaoxiao had delivered the dragonspine grass that she had promised, and two tufts of them at that.

She had also delivered a considerable amount of spirit essence stone and wood spirit jade to him.

This wasn’t all Xiaoxiao’s doing, but also the gifts that the Heavencraft Trading Company saved up to win over Lin Ming.

Within the entire Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom, including the three great trading companies, two great banks, and Hundred Treasure Auction House, the only business giant that had a Destiny Decree Master serving them was the Hundred Treasure Auction House.

This guest had also only lent his name, and wouldn’t act unless there was a great event occurring.

While this Destiny Decree master was ranked somewhere similar to Lin Ming, he was already over 1500 years old. He was far from comparing to Lin Ming’s potential.

If the Heavencraft Trading Company could be on good terms with Lin Ming, then the future returns would be inestimable.

Who knew what the future held? Perhaps Lin Ming might even break through to the Divine Sea realm. The Divine Sea realm! A Supreme Elder that could awe even an entire Divine Kingdom!

The top 100 ranked masters of the Destiny Decree were already characters that people couldn’t even look up to. Then, what sort of existence would a Divine Sea Supreme Elder be?

Even the Elders of the Heavencraft Trading Company were unable to imagine this.

If they could be on good terms, or even merely know of a Divine Sea Supreme Elder, that would make their family’s status skyrocket. The Heavencraft Trading Company was a great power that didn’t lack wealth; what they lacked was strength to take matters into their own hands. Underneath the absolute suppression of the Divine Kingdom, they were no different from defenseless pigs that were being raised up. They could be taken out of their pens and slaughtered at any time.

Now, because Xiaoxiao was on good terms with Lin Ming, her status in the family had advanced by leaps and bounds. With her two great uncles escaping from the family under the cover of night using the transmission array, there was no longer anyone that was able to threaten her position as Family head. The Council of Elders had already passed a resolution, and after another two months, an auspicious day would be chosen. Heavencraft Xiaoxiao would then complete the grand ceremony of family succession.

Recently, Lin Ming’s alchemical skills had also been constantly increasing. If he wished to refine the Fivefade Void Pill to open the third of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates, though, he was still far from being able to do so.

Lin Ming looked at the Cosmic Melting Furnace alchemy materials that were floating in front of him. There was the Five Color Fruit, Void Tempered Root, dragonspine grass, skyflower stones, as well as three jins of 200,000 year old wood spirit jade.

“This wood spirit jade quality is a bit too poor. If I had million year wood spirit jade, then my chances at successwould be much higher. Unfortunately, wood spirit jade that old is just too rare; even the Heavencraft Trading Company would have difficulty finding it.”

As Lin Ming was murmuring to himself, he suddenly felt a cold air rise up inside his chamber.

Killing intent?

Lin Ming’s mind went cold. His training chamber had protective array formations surrounding it. If one didn’t destroy the array formations, and only had their killing intent seep in, then that proved that this person’s killing intent was unimaginably condensed.

Lin Ming quickly put away the Cosmic Melting Furnace and opened the protective array formation, exiting the training chamber. As he stepped outside, he saw that just 200 feet away from him stood a passive, green masked man, whose ice cold mask gave off a heartlessly indifferent feeling.

“A wood spirit jade carved mask?”

Lin Ming’s mind stirred. With his understanding of wood spirit jade he immediately understood the use of this mask.

Wood spirit jade was able to isolate away all external perception. Because of this, a mask made of wood spirit jade was the most effective and simple method to hide one’s own appearance. Even if a Divine Sea Supreme Elder stood here, they still wouldn’t be able to identify who this person was. As for normal appearance changing techniques, they could only fool with people similar cultivations. Anyone with sharp enough eyes of high enough cultivation would instantly see through that type of disguise.

“I could borrow this method later.” If Lin Ming hadn’t seen this man in front of him, then he would never have thought wood spirit jade would also have this sort of function.

“You are….” As Lin Ming looked at this green masked man’s cultivation, he didn’t know just what sort of arcane ability this man practiced. Since his dantian had also been hidden in a deep fog; it was impossible to see through his cultivation.

But, just from the aura that emitted from his body, Lin Ming could feel his own heart reacting by beating faster. Without a doubt, this person was a master among masters.

He had come to Heavencraft Pavilion, but hadn’t disturbed the guards. That killing intent he released just now also didn’t have any malice behind it; this man had simply used this method to inform Lin Ming of his arrival.

Thus, Lin Ming was able to approximately guess just what sort of status this man had.

“I am the Nine Furnace Guard’s Chief Commander. You may refer to me as Fleeting Dragon.”

The Nine Furnace Guard Chief Commander was under the direct control of the Crown Prince. Lin Ming wasn’t surprised at all.

“When his Highness the Crown Prince invited Sir Lin for an audience, Sir Lin hadn’t yet recovered. Now, a month has passed and his Highness the Crown Prince has specifically sent me here to inquire into Sir Lin’s state and also send a miraculous healing pill. If Sir Lin’s wound is cured, then please follow me back for a visit to the Nine Furnace Divine Palace. If Sir Lin still isn’t feeling too well then I shall wait at Heavencraft Pavilion until Sir Lin’s wounds are healed.

As the Nine Furnace Guard Chief Command said these words, Lin Ming no longer had any reasonable argument he could use to refuse. He could only reluctantly agree.

He didn’t wish to involve himself in the high level battles of the four Divine Kingdoms. However, just seeing the Crown Prince might not be too bad either. For instance, the million year wood spirit jade he needed may be very difficult for the Heavencraft Trading Company to find; however, the Nine Furnace Divine Palace should definitely have it or find it.

………

The Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom was divided into nine provinces. The Nine Furnace Divine Palace was located at the largest and busiest province – the Central Province.

The area of just the Central Province was larger than ten South Horizon Regions combined.

Around the Central Province, the other eight provinces surrounded it. As for the back of the Central Province, that area extended to the edge of the Sea of Miracles.

The Sea of Miracles was the greatest life forbidden zone of the entire Sky Spill Continent. The four Divine Kingdoms surrounded the Sea of Miracles in a giant circle. And, far behind these four Divine Kingdoms was the South Sea, Fog Sea, North Sea, and Crimson Sea. At the very center of everything was the Sea of Miracles. This made the Sky Spill Continent to look like the shape of an irregular donut.

The Sea of Miracles was also known as the Sea of No Return, and also the Ocean of Endless Storms. It was rumored that the entire sea was pitch black and covered with infinite lightning storms. To enter was to walk into certain death. Even a Divine Sea Supreme Elder was no exception.

As for the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom’s Divine Palace, that was only 10,000 miles from the shores of the Sea of Miracles.

As Lin Ming arrived at the foot of the Nine Furnace Divine Palace, he looked up to see a 100,000 foot high snow-capped mountain rage. The Nine Furnace Divine Palace was actually established above these mountains.

This wasn’t strange at all, as most sects were built above mountains or spiritual islands. This was because these types of places often had extremely high quality spirit veins.

The Nine Furnace Divine Palace was also the same.

Just by arriving at the base of the mountains, Lin Ming could feel a rich heaven and origin energy rushing over him like a never ending tide, submerging him within. With every breath he took, he could feel all traces of this energy seep into his own dantian, subtly raising his cultivation.

If just standing at the base of these mountains had such an effect, then the origin energy density at the summit could be imagined.

This was also the reason that so many Destiny Decree masters were willing to join the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom. If they could close up and train in the Nine Furnace Divine Palace, then that would be far better than any other place they could go to.

“These are sixth grade spirit veins, or maybe even higher…”

Lin Ming had never seen a higher spirit vein before, and was thus unable to estimate the level of this land’s spirit veins.

Beside Lin Ming, even the normally silent Fleeting Dragon revealed a trace of pride in his eyes as he saw the Nine Furnace Divine Palace.

He said, “This mountain is named the Nine Furnace Divine Mountain and the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom’s name originates from this mountain. The founding ancestor of the Nine Furnace Sect established his sect on the Nine Furnace Divine Mountain. A it grew from there, it finally becoming the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom. The Nine Furnace Divine Mountain came first, and the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom followed after.

“Sir Lin, Miss Heavencraft, please follow me up the mountain!”

When the Crown Prince invited Lin Ming, he had also conveniently invited Xiaoxiao. This caused Xiaoxiao to be terrified. Just what sort of legendary existence was the Nine Furnace Crown prince? She had no idea why someone like the Crown Prince would invite her. Was it just to accompany Lin Lanjian here?

Chapter 785 – Let Me See Your Armor

The Nine Furnace Divine Mountain reached 100,000 feet high. The summit was covered in pure white snow all year round. Within the endless expanse of snow and the deep blue glaciers, countless towers of jade soared high up into the skies. Every tower was supported by array formations. Ancient snow fell outside, but within the tower, under the effect of these formations, rare flowers from all seasons blossomed in all their splendor, full of life and vitality. It was truly a sight to behold.

While one side was covered in endless snow and ice, the other side was filled with lush green spiritual plants. Such a sharp and clear contrast was like a heavenly paradise on earth.

At the summit of the Nine Furnace Divine Mountain there was a beautiful lake that displayed all four seasons. This lake was named the Nine Flower Lake. This entire lake was covered in a dense fog, and at its center was a pavilion carved from jade.

Within this pavilion was a young man that was lightly playing a zither. The zither’s melody that thrummed in the air was pleasant to the ears. In the Nine Flower Lake, snow lotuses bloomed all around. As this jade-like handsome young man played his zither, he appeared even purer and loftier than a woman, as if he were an immortal that had descended down from the heavens.

As the young man saw Lin Ming and Xiaoxiao arrive, he faintly smiled, “Brother Lin, welcome to the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom as my honored guest.”

The young man’s voice had a strangely pleasant lilt to it; it made one feel very comfortable listening to him.

“Is he the Nine Furnace Crown Prince?”

The Divine Kingdom Crown Prince in front of him was completely different from what he had imagined.

“Lin Lanjian greets his Highness the Crown Prince.”

Lin Ming simply cupped his hands across his chest. As someone who wasn’t from the Divine Kingdom, there was no need for him to be overly courteous.

“Brother Lin is too polite.” Yang Yun similarly cupped his hands across his chest. This was a ritual exchange from those of the same generation; there was no hint of the status of the Nine Furnace Crown Prince behind it. “Fleeting Dragon, guide Brother Lin to the reception hall. I shall head there soon after.”

“Yes,” Fleeting Dragon respectfully said. Lin Ming could feel from this respect that the Nine Furnace Crown Prince was an extraordinary character. Otherwise it would be impossible to sincerely convince a master like Fleeting Dragon.

The Nine Furnace Crown Prince’s dantian was also covered in a thick fog; it was impossible to see his cultivation.

“I heard that Yang Yun crossed into Life Destruction at just 30 years of age. Ten years have passed now. I wonder what stage of Life Destruction he has reached now…”

Lin Ming didn’t doubt that Yang Yun could even jump ranks to fight. If so, then his strength was terrifying.

After arriving at the reception hall, Yang Yun arrived in just half an incense stick of time. At this time, he had changed his clothes and was now wearing a purple gold robe as well as a purple gold crown. The robe he wore was embroidered with the image of a five-clawed golden dragon. Whether consciously or unconsciously, he emitted a noble air around him that made others want to fall to their knees and worship him.

This sort of aura that made one wish to bow before him was called the legendary Breath of the King. This so-called Breath of the King was similar to a force field, the only difference being that it was far weaker in intensity. To a martial artist on the level of Lin Ming, this sort of aura had absolutely no use. But Xiaoxiao was different. She felt a great pressure just from standing in front of Yang Yun.

That previously jade-like handsome, ethereal Yang Yun had now overlapped with the current Yang Yun that released the Breath of the King. It was impossible to distinguish just which one was the real Yang Yun.

Yang Yun realized that Xiaoxiao’s complexion had paled. He gently smiled at her and then purposefully restrained his energy. Xiaoxiao immediately felt the pressure on her lighten and her face flushed red again.

“I apologize Miss Heavencraft. Cuicui, please brew a pot of jade tea for Miss Heavencraft.”

The last few words were spoken to a palace maid. Xiaoxiao gratefully smiled, flattered that someone like Yang Yun would care about such an unimportant person as her. As for the jade tea, as the Young Mistress of the Heavencraft Trading Company, Xiaoxiao was well aware of just what that was. That was an extremely precious Yin-attribute tea. It was said that if a mortal woman drank a cup of it she would become one year younger, and if she drank an entire pot she would become ten years younger.

This was no exaggeration. Only after stepping on the path of cultivation would one’s life potential develop. Hence, as a mortal, it was relatively easier to extend their life..

But for a martial artist, especially Life Destruction martial artists, because they had trained themselves to the limit, they had to completely unearth all of their life’s potential. Thus, wanting to extend their life was far too difficult.

The maid named Cuicui respectfully served tea to everyone. Her appearance was exquisite and with her young age she still had a Xiantian realm cultivation. For such a heavenly gifted girl to be a palace maid, this was obviously proof of the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom’s legacy.

She poured the jade tea in Xiaoxiao tea cup and also served ice lotus tea to Lin Ming and the Nine Furnace Crown Prince. This sort of tea was even more precious than jade tea. It was produced from the dried petals of the ice lotuses that grew around the Nine Flower Lake. As for the ice lotuses of the Nine Flower Lake, they could be called heavenly treasures.

The Nine Furnace Crown Prince smiled and said, “Brother Lin is truly an astounding person. You are just over 20 years of age and yet you’ve managed to step into the pages of the Destiny Decree with just a late Revolving Core cultivation. When I was Brother Lin’s age, the difference was simply far too great!”

The Nine Furnace Crown Prince ruefully smiled. Lin Ming didn’t respond, only waiting for the Nine Furnace Crown Prince to state his intention for inviting him over here.

However, the Nine Furnace Crown Prince had no intention of doing so. Instead, he and Lin Ming talked about the customs and policies of the four Divine Kingdoms, as well as relating to him the various large sects and influences, and all sorts of other strange information.

Yang Yun was an eloquent individual and extremely well spoken. His manner of speaking was charming and light, make him very comfortable and disarming to talk too. Even Xiaoxiao couldn’t help but have a favorable impression of him.

Finally, after an hour of conversation had passed, Lin Ming asked, “May I ask why Your Highness has requested my presence here?”

“Haha, Brother Lin need not worry, I merely like to befriend the heroes of this world. Also, Brother Lin, there’s no need to be so polite. Please, call me Yang Yun.”

Yang Yun’s words were well said and Lin Ming didn’t speak further. The truth was that he knew that the so-called ‘befriending heroes of this world’ and winning over the will of people all meant that he was recruiting others for his own purposes. Yang Yun’s cleverness lay in the fact that he didn’t directly mention this matter. Instead, he first wanted to be friends with Lin Ming. Friends first, leader after. Otherwise, it would be too easy to be turned at the start.

Even though Lin Ming had guessed Yang Yun’s true intentions, he still didn’t refuse him.

“Brother Yang’s skill in fine arts and military expertise is renowned throughout the world. In the future, you’ll likely become an unrivalled Divine Emperor. For Brother Yang to value me so highly is truly flattering.”

“Haha, Brother Lin is too modest. I wonder which force Brother Lin originated from? With Brother Lin’s talent I fear you’ll become the top powerhouse of the Sky Spill Continent in the future. When that time comes, I might need to rely on Brother Lin.”

The two young men complimented each other. Lin Ming smiled, not responding to Yang Yun’s inquiry of his background. In response, Yang Yun tactfully didn’t ask again. “Brother Lin, I happened to have invited some astounding young elites from the Sky Spill Continent here today for a banquet at the Nine Flower Lake. Would Brother Lin like to join me to the lake and share in some wine whilst meeting the heroes of this world?”

To be considered an astounding young elite by Yang Yun, they must have the most extraordinary prides of heaven within the entire Sky Spill Continent. Not only would their strength and talent be extraordinary, but they should also be greatly influential. For instance, the successor of a great sect or perhaps an extremely powerful Divine Kingdom Prince.

Lin Ming hadn’t replied yet when a maid came in to report on some news. “Your Highness, the White Clan Princess has arrived.”

“Oh? Then I shall immediately go to receive her. Brother Lin, how about going with me?”

“Mm, alright.” Lin Ming nodded.

Yang Yun had indeed invited heroic young elites that stood at the very peak of the Sky Spill Continent. These people all ranged from their twenties to their fifties.

For the Xiantian realm, someone 50 years old would be considered middle-aged. But if one could step into the Life Destruction realm in their thirties, then they would appear in their twenties even if they were 50 years of age. In addition, Life Destruction powerhouses lived for thousands of years. Thus, a 50 year old Life Destruction powerhouse could also be considered someone of the younger generation.

The White Clan Princess, the Great Smelting Kingdom Prince, and the Seven Star High Prince Successor, each of them were eminent characters.

For instance, that White Clan Princess. The so-called White Clan was a family clan that lived at the borders of the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom in a hidden world. This Family Clan had a very special bloodline; they had a bloodline seal. A bloodline seal was a special ability inherited through the bloodline of that family clan. This sort of ability could only be inherited by direct descendants.

Two thousand years ago, a Divine Sea Supreme Elder was born in the White Clan, thus they became worthy of being a true Holy Land level power. And now, their current Family Head also had a high chance of breaking through to the Divine Sea. At that time, their White Clan would have two Supreme Elders backing them. Although that was far from being able to match with the four Divine Kingdoms, it was still a focal super power. The White Clan Princess was the future successor to the Family Head. Thus, her prominent status could be imagined.

There was not much to say of the Great Smelting Kingdom Prince. He had already earned a similar reputation to the Nine Furnace Crown Prince a long time ago. Within the Sublime Smelting Divine Kingdom, the title of Crown Prince was an empty position. Currently, there were several powerful competitors vying for this seat, and this Great Smelting Prince was one of them. He was currently 45 years old and also ranked on the Destiny Decree. Although the combined power of his subordinates was weaker than Yang Yun, he was still extremely terrifying.

As for the Seven Prince High Prince Successor, his status was a bit poorer. However, his grandfather was ranked in the top two Divine Sea powerhouses of the entire Seven Star Divine Kingdom. That grandfather’s status was absolutely terrifying. If other Divine Sea Supreme Elders ran into him, even they had to greet him as if they were a junior.

This group of people consisted of some of the most illustrious characters of the Sky Spill Continent, princes amongst princes.

Because Xiaoxiao accompanied Lin Ming, she also followed him to this banquet. As she faced this crowd of young people that stood at the very peak of the Sky Spill Continent, even she, who she felt was worldly and had seen the ‘great world’, felt breathless.

Compared to these people in front of her, everyone she had ever come into contact with was nothing at all.

As the host, Yang Yun introduced everyone one at a time.

As every person was introduced, Xiaoxiao would be increasingly shocked every time. But as for Lin Ming, he remembered their appearance and background as well as silently estimating their strength. In the four Divine Kingdoms, it was inevitable that he would encounter these individuals in the future.

As Lin Ming was introduced, Yang Yun only used a few simple words to describe him, “The only Revolving Core talent to enter the Destiny Decree in a thousand years – Lin Lanjian.”

“Mm? He is Lin Lanjian!?” The Great Smelting Prince looked at Lin Ming, a bit astonished. He had also been wondering who Lin Ming was and why he was standing here. Now that the Great Smelting Prince knew that he was Lin Lanjian, even with his high and prominent status, he still held a deep respect in his heart when facing this sort of top talent that couldn’t be judged by common sense.

“You are Lin Lanjian?” In the pavilion, a black-clothed youth stood up. He was an Asura Divine Kingdom Prince.

“I am.” Lin Ming cupped his hands across his chest. He was a bit puzzled as he felt this black-clothed youth’s blazing eyes locked onto him. Just what problem did this fellow have with him? Was it related to Corpsemancer?

Or was this fellow one of those battle crazies that challenged every powerhouse they saw and now wanted to fight him?

However, Lin Ming never imagined that this black-clothed youth would suddenly step forward and point at Lin Ming’s clothes. “Lin Lanjian, I want to take a look at the armor you’re wearing. How about it?”

“Mm?” Lin Ming frowned. Randomly asking to view another’s treasure was extremely rude.

He didn’t expect the following explanation either. “Lin Lanjian, I suspect that your armor is the sacred relic of my clan, the Demon Emperor’s armor!”

Chapter 797 – Robbery

The entire square was left in silence. Yan Junxuan was still lying bleeding on the ground as several Misty Stream Sect Elders were glaring at Lin Ming.

Lin Ming’s brush speed was too fast. As soon as the words appeared they seemed to tear through the talent announcement list paper, carrying a sharp spear intent with them.

Every martial artist present was shocked.

“Lin… Lin Lanjian!!!!”

Some martial artists were befuddled for a moment. But in that instant, a light flashed in Lin Ming’s hand and a red long spear rushed out like a crimson flood dragon, directly striking the weak point of the spirit essence stone box’s barrier shield!

Penetrating Rainbow!

Energy roared. With an explosive crackling sound, the entire barrier shattered to pieces!

This explosion finally caused everyone’s minds to be shaken out of their daze. This wood spirit jade-masked youth was actually Lin Lanjian! And the red spear he used as well as the spear move absolutely proved this point.

He was planning to raise a ruckus at the gathering site?

The Demon Envoy who was personally garrisoning this square was furious. The chair he sat on broke apart as he stood up and fired himself towards Lin Ming.

The other Asura Divine Kingdom martial artists rapidly blocked the area, wanting to capture Lin Ming. Although they were far from being Lin Ming’s match, they could still manage to delay him a bit.

In this heavy encirclement of danger, a mere finger snap of time was enough to take one’s life!

Facing the trained and coordinated response of the Asura Divine Kingdom’s martial artists, Lin Ming simply seemed unaware of it all. He grabbed the box of spirit essence stones and stuffed it into his spatial ring.

“You dare!?!?”

The Demon Envoy’s eyes turned bright red. He finally understood that the reason Lin Ming came here today was to rob them!

The Asura Divine Kingdom Branch Division had a total of three Demon Envoys guarding the land as well as Elders and masters from various famous sects of the four Divine Kingdoms. Yet, underneath all of these personages’ eyes, Lin Lanjian actually dared to openly rob the reward they had posted!?!?

The Demon Envoy simply thought that Lin Lanjian had lost his mind. This was a suicidal action!

“If you want to die so badly then let me help you!”

The Asura Demon Envoy took out a 10 foot long overlord spear from his spatial ring. He gripped the spear with both hands and smashed it down towards Lin Ming!

This Demon Envoy’s strength was ranked 83 on the Destiny Decree. Against Lin Ming, who was only ranked near the end of the Destiny Decree, he could definitely instantly kill him!

The Demon Envoy’s spear strike came tumbling down as if an entire mountain range was collapsing. A terrifying flux of energy tore through space. If Lin Ming was struck by this spear attack then he would definitely be split in half.

A Revolving Core realm martial artist who was split apart at the waist could still maintain their life as long as they were treated in time. The Asura Demon Envoy planned to capture Lin Ming alive and torture out all of the details from him that concerned the Demon Emperor’s inheritances.

Lin Ming stared blankly on as the Demon Envoy’s spear came smashing down on him. This spear’s power and might far exceeded Lin Ming’s own Bury the Heavens and its speed had reached an incredible degree.

This was the strength of a top 100 ranked Destiny Decree master.

Lin Ming’s lips curved up in a grin. Energy erupted from his knees; the Gate of Wonder opened!

Breaking through the limits of the body and instantly reached the limit of speed, Lin Ming’s feet twisted as space distorted underneath him. With a single step, Lin Ming had vanished like a puff of smoke.

Although Lin Ming couldn’t directly face the Demon Envoy, after he had opened the Gate of Wonder, he could rely on his speed alone to show disdain for the Destiny Decree!

Bang!

The Asura Demon Envoy’s spear crashed into the high platform, causing the entire structure to loudly crumble into nothing. The earth broke apart and all of the surrounding martial artists were sent flying away by the shockwave. Those with weaker cultivations spat out great mouthfuls of blood.

And at this time, Lin Ming had already reappeared 1000 feet away.

The Asura Demon Envoy’s spear had missed.

He couldn’t believe it. His spear had missed!?

Not only had his spear speed reached the limit but it also contained the Concept of Space. It could be used to twist and lock down the surrounding space. Yet, his attack had actually been dodged by a mere late Revolving Core martial artist!?

This was not a speed that a Revolving Core martial artist could have!

This ghostly scene caused the Asura Demon Envoy’s heart to seethe with rage. He shouted out, “Stop him! Open the sealing array!”

At the moment the Asura Demon Envoy shouted out, three Asura Divine Kingdom martial artists shot towards Lin Ming. Two of them were impressively Life Destruction martial artists.

“Die!”

Lin Ming coldly spat out that single word. And, without even using a spear move, three arrows of battle spirit-infused true essence air shot out from Lin Ming’s mouth, directly colliding with the three Asura Divine Kingdom martial artist’s heads!

Peng! Peng! Peng!

With three loud bursting sounds, the three Asura Divine Kingdom martial artists’ heads blew apart like watermelons, their brain fluids showering into the air.

“What!?”

All of the heroic young elites present held their breath, unable to even think properly. They only felt their minds tremble. Of those three Asura Divine Kingdom martial artists, two of them were first stage Life Destruction martial artists that were absolutely not inferior to any of them. Yet, in front of Lin Lanjian, they had been nothing but ants. They had been shot to death by nothing but true essence air arrows!

In other words, if Lin Lanjian wanted to kill them, he would only need to breathe in their general direction. And the reason that he didn’t kill Yan Junxuan with a single breath just now was all in order to hide his strength.

This disparity couldn’t even be described by clouds and mud. This was the first time that any of them had encountered a talent that was terrifying to the extent of making them tremble with dismay. This was a strength that left everyone weeping in despair!

“You bastard!”

The Demon Envoy angrily shouted and thrust his spear towards Lin Ming. He revolved his true essence to the limit, completely opening all of his energy. With every step he took, mountains quaked and rivers surged!

Bang! Bang! Bang! Bang! Bang!

Massive five foot deep footprints appeared all over the entire square. All of these footprints were several feet wide and they sent countless shards of rock scattering into the air. All of the martial artists in the square were blown away like pieces of straw in a tornado, thrown out in all directions.

The Demon Envoy had only used his movement technique, but the dark energy hidden in the shockwaves was already enough to severely wound the weaker martial artists.

Lin Ming heard the sound of air splitting from behind him. He didn’t need to look back to know that the Asura Demon Envoy was chasing after him. He thought little of it, instead completely opening the Gate of Wonder. In addition, with the ethereal and exquisite ‘Golden Roc Shattering the Void’, his speed rapidly climbed to the extreme.

Woosh!

Lin Ming became a ray of light that cut through the vast horizon, crossing over a dozen miles in an instant. All of the martial artists still at the square were left dumbfounded.

Was this really speed that a human could possess?

Rumble rumble!

The sealing array formation that covered the entire Asura Divine Kingdom Branch Division began to activate. But to Lin Ming, this large-scale array formation had started far too slowly.

Moreover, he had already found a great weak point in this massive array. Since this array also originated from the Demon Emperor’s inheritance, Lin Ming had been able to easily unravel it.

“Penetrating Rainbow!”

With a thrust, Lin Ming’s spear stabbed into the weak point of the just now activated array. With a loud tearing sound, a section of the array dozens of feet wide suddenly burst open in front of him, allowing him to run out with ease.

“You lunatic!”

A loud shout came from somewhere else in the Asura Divine Kingdom Branch Division, rumbling outwards like a passing thundercloud.

The two other Demon Envoys also joined the chase!

In broad daylight, under the watchful eyes of everyone, as well as with three Asura Divine Kingdom Demon Envoys personally guarding the branch division, Lin Ming had actually made his way in and stolen away 300,000 spirit essence stones. This was too disgraceful!

Once news of this spread out, their Asura Divine Kingdom would lose face!

“We must overtake him!”

“We have to obtain the Demon Emperor’s inheritance!”

“After searching his soul, turn him into a corpse doll and hang him atop the gates of our Divine Kingdom’s cities! Let them see the glory and might of our Asura Divine Kingdom!”

“No one is allowed to dishonor the glory of our Divine Kingdom!”

The three Demon Envoys all wore black clothes. Their hearts raged with an inferno of hate and anger. Even if they caught Lin Ming today, this would still become a stain on their lives that they would never be able to erase!

One person fleeing with three people chasing. They cut through the skies like falling stars, flying into the far off horizon!

Within the square, the martial artists there were bewildered. Although Lin Lanjian’s name and reputation rang out like thunder in their ears, seeing was believing. They never imagined that Lin Lanjian would appear in the Asura Divine Kingdom Branch Division and openly challenge the very dignity of the Asura Divine Kingdom!

A man and his spear, Lin Lanjian by himself had demolished the Asura Divine Kingdom’s gathering of heroes, stolen away 300,000 spirit essence stones, instantly killed three Asura Divine Kingdom masters, and then… left without injury!

Just what kind of boldness was this!!!

In the face of an entire Divine Kingdom hunting after him, Lin Lanjian hadn’t hidden his identity and secluded himself in some remote mountain range. Instead, he had caused a ruckus in the Asura Divine Kingdom’s Jagged Slope Mountain Branch Division!

“This Lin Lanjian is too terrifying!”

“He looks just over 20 years old and yet he can contend with a Demon Envoy…”

“And when he fled, was that even human speed…?”

“Even the mountain sealing array formation wasn’t able to stop him. He cannot be judged by common sense!”

“What a monster!”

All of the martial artists in the square were talking amongst themselves. Many of the heroic young elites had pale and weak complexions. Compared with Lin Lanjian, the difference was simply too great!

“What do we do? Should we still involve ourselves in this?” Some martial artists already had the idea of withdrawing. Lin Lanjian was far too ruthless for them. He had even dared break his way into the Asura Divine Kingdom Branch Division that was guarded by three Demon Envoys.

“Don’t be afraid, that Lin Lanjian is only fast; his strength should still only rank at around 300 on the Destiny Decree. That, at least, shouldn’t be wrong. Otherwise he wouldn’t have run, but would have fought with the Demon Envoy!”

“If we join forces then we have no need to fear him. We also have many Destiny Decree masters here, and many of them are even above Corpsemancer. Moreover, we have the support of the Asura Divine Kingdom. After Lin Lanjian messed with the Asura Divine Kingdom Branch Division, the bounty on him will definitely rise again!”

“The Asura Divine Kingdom had their face swept to the ground and even had 300,000 spirit essence stones stolen away. They will never let this go.”

“Although you say that, I don’t think that Lin Lanjian will be able to successfully run away. Those are three Demon Envoys chasing him! Lin Lanjian’s speed is extraordinary but his strength and cultivation are far too low. Even if he relies on some sort of arcane skill or treasure to momentarily match the three Demon Envoys in speed, he won’t be able to keep it up forever. There is no way his endurance and thickness of his true essence will be able to last much longer. As for those three Demon Envoys, all three of them are sixth stage Life Destruction masters!”

“Not wrong. Perhaps that Lin Lanjian will perish here at Jagged Slope Mountain today. Although his cultivation and strength are amazing, he is still far too young. He will pay the price for his impulsiveness!”

As the numerous martial artists within the Asura Divine Kingdom Branch Division were speaking, Lin Ming’s chase by the three Demon Envoys had already continued for several hundred miles!

With the speed from the Gate of Wonder combined with ‘Golden Roc Shattering the Void’, Lin Ming produced a sonic boom as he flew in the air. He also used the black bat wings that Corpsemancer had left behind. Before this, Lin Ming had roughly managed to alter them for his own use. After all, this was still a heaven-step flight treasure. It could definitely increase Lin Ming’s speed.

With all three of these factors combined together, Lin Ming was a level faster than the three Demon Envoys. But, he controlled his speed so that the three Demon Envoys were following behind him.

Behind Lin Ming, just 10 miles away, the three Demon Envoys’ faces had darkened to the point of dripping water.

Chapter 798 – Unbelievable Speed

“This brat, how is this even possible!?”

The three Demon Envoys were running out of breath. They thought that Lin Ming used some kind of arcane ability that stimulated his bodily potential in order reach such extreme speeds. Those arcane abilities usually caused a few detrimental side effects, and were also impossible to maintain forever. However, Lin Ming didn’t seem like he had used up any strength at all, even after flying for such a long time. In fact, he seemed to have a great deal of energy left over. It also seemed that the more he flew, the faster he became! This was just too strange!

1000 miles….

2000 miles….

3000 miles…

4000 miles…

Once they reached 5000 miles, Lin Ming still hadn’t slowed down, even after passing over the entire Jagged Slope Mountain Range.

“Damn it! What should we do?”

The third Asura Demon Envoy asked. He was a middle-aged man, ranked 93rd on the Destiny Decree. He currently had a pained expression as he took a shard of stalactite essence from his spatial ring, bitterly swallowing it down.

“We’ve already flown for around 5000 miles, and yet he can still last this long!?” Another Demon Envoy took a jade bottle out from his spatial ring and swallowed a snow white pill.

“We’ve already consumed our true essence to the limit. His cultivation is inferior to ours, so it’s impossible for him to continue flying for much longer.”

The one who spoke was the leading second Demon Envoy, his words filled with self-confidence. He was ranked 83rd on the Destiny Decree.

However, what happened was….

6000 miles….

7000 miles…

It seemed as if Lin Ming wanted to fly out to a 10,000 mile distance. Not only that, but the more he flew, the faster he became! The first Demon Envoy had blue veins bulging out from his forehead.

This was simply impossible!

They had already flown an additional 2000 miles! This could already be considered as having flown far away, even with their standards….

The second Demon Envoy’s complexion turned extremely ugly. Just what sort of secrets did this Lin Lanjian have on him? Why was he able to flee so quickly, and for such a long time?

Another 1000 miles flew by as everyone approached the 8000 mile mark. Lin Ming stlil maintained a relatively relaxed state throughout.

A flying martial artist was the same as a running mortal. If they ran at their top speeds, then they would only be able to last for about 100-200 meters before falling the ground in complete exhaustion.

However, if they maintained 70-80% of their maximum speed, then they could maintain this for several miles.

Lin Ming was in the same situation. He was maintaining a flight speed of around 70-80% of his limit. After crossing 8000 miles, his consumption wasn’t too great. Furthermore, because he had already opened the Gate of Healing, his endurance and recovery ability had since far surpassed a normal martial artist. Thus, there was always an enormous amount of true essence in his dantian.

However, the three Demon Envoys behind him were in a much more miserable state. For the past 8000 miles, they had to fly as fast as they could, and the further they flew the more they fell behind. The third Demon Envoy had already consumed his third shard of stalactite essence.

“Don’t continue chasing.” The second Demon Envoy suddenly stopped. At the start of the chase, they had only been 10 miles far from Lin Lanjian. Now, they were over 100 miles away!

They had also taken several medicines to supplement their true essence. No matter how good the medicine was, repeatedly consuming these medicines would eventually cause impurities to appear in their true essence. If that happened, they would be unable to display their peak combat strength. To be in that sort of situation within the borders of the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom was undoubtedly dangerous.

“This Lin Lanjian must have some sort of top supportive flight treasure or some kind of special arcane flight ability. He might even have both.” The second Demon Envoy said with a gloomy tone.

For a late Revolving Core youth to surpass a sixth stage Life Destruction master in speed and endurance, this was simply too unbelievable!

“Damnit! Just how many amazing treasures are there on his body!?” The first Demon Envoy panted out. He had used up so much strength and effort, and had chased so far, just to end up empty-handed. Under their watch, they had only been able to watch helplessly as that Lin Lanjian stole away 300,000 spirit essence stones. This was simply too great a shame, and he could already see the news of this event spreading all through the martial cultivation world by tomorrow. The four Divine Kingdoms and all the powerful family clans in their hidden realms would regard them as absolute laughing stocks.

“I will capture that brat and skin him alive!”

The third Demon Envoy heatedly said. As he thought of the 300,000 spirit essence stones, he felt as if he would die from his intestines twisting in place.

There had been many rare, superior spirit essence stones worth 300,000 spirit essence stones in total. Even he couldn’t afford to use them during his training. He would only cautiously use a few dozen of those superior spirit essence stones if he was either breaking through a bottleneck in cultivation or attempting to cross over to another stage of Life Destruction..

To shamefully lose 300,000 spirit essence stones just like that, the three of them would definitely take the blame for this. They would definitely be punished by the Asura Divine Kingdom!

“Let’s meditate for some time and then return. There was no harvest from today, but I’ve managed to record a trace of Lin Lanjian’s energy. Even if he were to wear a wood spirit jade mask next time, I would still be able to identify him!” The second Demon Envoy said with a morose expression, before searching for a secluded area to meditate and recover.

They had already flown 8000 miles outwards. This area was desolate and deserted, without any transmission arrays nearby. If they wished to return, then they would have to slowly fly back. As the three Demon Envoys remembered this fact, they became even more depressed, and their expressions became that much uglier.

“They’ve finally stopped chasing me.”

300 miles away from the three Demon Envoys, Lin Ming’s stood suspended in the air, his lips turned upwards in a cunning smile. Although those three Demon Envoys had consumed a great deal of their energy, he wouldn’t be so stupid as to bite off more than he could chew, and challenge the three of them. Those three were still sixth stage Life Destruction powerhouses, after all, and the fires of their lives were still blazing vibrantly. These were characters that had hopes of reaching the Divine Sea. When they were youths, they were definitely Emperor level talents, and outstanding ones at that. Even if only one remained, Lin Ming still wouldn’t dare return to provoke them. At this time, he just fundamentally wasn’t a match for them.

……

Jagged Slope Mountain, Asura Divine Kingdom Branch Division –

“That Lin Lanjian was way too impetuous. I wonder just what’s happened to him. Unfortunately, this entire Jagged Slope Mountain has been sealed off, so there’s no way for us to catch up to him.”

“No kidding. It’s too unfortunate, we missed a great battle!”

“Hehe, sealing off this mountain is common, as Lin Lanjian is just that important. There are too many treasures on his body; he is simply a treasure himself.  Before he is caught, no news of this can be leaked out to others. Otherwise someone might catch up to him ahead of time, and the Asura Divine Kingdom would lose everything instead.”

The Elders of the various great sects were talking about whether or not Lin Lanjian would finally meet a dead end. At this time, however, three black-clothed men walked into the square. One of them was an old man who was in charge of the Asura Divine Kingdom’s Jagged Slope Mountain Branch Division.

The Asura Divine Kingdom had several dozen branch divisions set up all over the Sky Spill Continent. The leader of a branch division was called the Hall Master. Because there were too many Hall Masters scattered throughout the continent, their status wasn’t considered too high.

However, the Jagged Slope Mountain Branch Division was an exception. Because the Jagged Slope Mountain Branch Division was in charge of matters within the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom, their branch division was one of the largest. This branch division’s Hall Master was just strong enough to rank on the Destiny Decree. Of course, he was far from being able to compare with the Demon Envoys.

“Hall Master Situ!”

Several old men cupped their fists together in respect. They naturally recognized Hall Master Situ, due to frequently interacting with the Jagged Slope Mountain Branch Division.

Hall Master Situ cupped his fists in return and said, “Everyone, please remain patient. My Divine Kingdom’s Sir Demon Envoys are already pursuing Lin Lanjian. They should be able to capture him without incident.

As he spoke, he was also glad that the Jagged Slope Mountain Branch Division had three Demon Envoys garrisoning this place. Otherwise, there was no way that he could contend with Lin Lanjian. He simply couldn’t keep up with that strange, ghostly speed of his.

“As long as we can catch Lin Lanjian, then the matter of 300,000 spirit essence stones being stolen away in front of everyone, and the loss of face from that will be wiped clean. This could also be considered a great merit for me, as this gathering of heroes could be my rise to glory.”

As Hall Master Situ thought of this, his mood became much more pleasant.

Chapter 800 – Blood Washed Jagged Slope Mountain

For most of the famous sect Elders present, their fires of life were already subsiding; it was nearly impossible for them to take another step forward in their cultivation within their lives. In this case, the God Transforming Pill that could increase their chances of successfully reaching the divine Sea realm wasn’t too tempting.

The reason many of them had come to take a chance of obtaining the God Transforming Pill was in consideration of their disciples. Even if they swallowed the God Transforming Pill themselves, there basically wasn’t any chance for them to pass from the fifth to the sixth stage of Life Destruction.

This Life Bestowing Heaven Pill, on the other hand, was different. Not only did it merely attract the attention of the Elders present but it was a divine pill that they would go crazy over!

The higher boundary a martial artist reached, the more of their life potential they would have dug out, the more vibrant the fires of their life became, and the more difficult it was to extend their life. To a martial artist, an inferior 100 year medicine could lengthen their lives by dozens of years and even have the effect of resurrecting the dead. To a Xiantian realm martial artist, high quality 1000 year medicines had similar effects. But to a Life Destruction master, medicines that could extend their lives could be called legendary treasures. If one didn’t have the foundation of a Divine Kingdom, it was simply impossible to even think about obtaining one!

And this Life Bestowing Heaven Pill was one of those marvelous pills. Not only could it lengthen one’s life but it could also make the fires of their live much more ebullient, turning back their clock and making them younger by up to 500 years!

This was a life changing, heaven defying divine pill that even the four Divine Kingdoms only had a small number of. To these Elders, becoming 500 years younger meant there was a chance they could further enhance their cultivation. If this was combined with the God Transforming Pill, there might even be a chance of breaking through to the sixth stage of Life Destruction!

After reaching the sixth stage of Life Destruction, if they experienced another massive lucky chance then there might even be the faintest thread of hope to reach the Divine Sea! Although they would only be the weakest of Divine Sea masters, that was still the Divine Sea! They would be reborn! Their dantian would experience great changes and they would have at least 5000 years of life to spend as they wished! To them, this was the same as living like an immortal every day!

“Let’s attack together. He only entered the top 300 of the Destiny Decree half a month ago and his cultivation is only at the late Revolving Core realm. It’s impossible for him to have made another breakthrough in his cultivation or for his strength to have greatly increased in such a short period of time. We have four Destiny Decree masters here. As long as we join forces we can definitely capture him alive!”

Hall Master Situ shouted out. As he spoke, Lin Ming’s eyes suddenly locked on his body. The ice cold mask and the black lines that snaked down the mask seemed to exude a near infinite killing intent, making him feel as if he had fallen into a deep, icy lake.

However, he remembered the three Destiny Decree masters behind him. With him, that was a total of four great masters. They held an enormous advantage over Lin Ming. He was suddenly filled with courage and bravado again.

“Let’s attack together! Feng Yan, Ju Sun, go to the main temple and activate the protective array formation!”

Jagged Slope Mountain Branch Division’s main temple naturally had its own great defensive array. Even if Lin Ming was proficient in the Demon Emperor’s array formations, he wouldn’t be able to completely disregard it. Once the array formation started, it would be able to contain Lin Ming to a large extent.

The martial artists in the square immediately began running toward the great hall. As for the three famous sect Elders and the other Life Destruction martial artists, they all scattered away, spreading around and occupying favorable positions. They were ready to use all sorts of sneak attack methods on Lin Ming. Although they didn’t dare to directly face him, they could take advantage of the moment when he was fighting the four great masters to sneak in some attacks.

After all, Hall Master Situ’s reward was simply too tempting!

“Do not be afraid! We have an absolute advantage with our strength! Lin Lanjian must have consumed a great deal of his true essence in escaping; he can’t have much left!” Hall Master Situ’s voice echoed in everyone’s ears.

“All disciples of the Misty Stream Sect, follow my command! Prepare the Misty Stream Formation!” The Misty Stream Sect Sovereign was one of the three famous sect Elders. The Life Bestowing Heaven Pill was far too great an enticement to him; he had to obtain it at any cost! Moreover, he still had to take revenge for when his disciple, Yan Junxuan, had been heavily wounded.

The Misty Stream Formation needed 12 elite disciples to stand in formation. By relying on their mutual cooperation, the martial artists would be able to fuse their attacks together, combining the weak to defeat the strong. At this time, all of the people the Misty Stream Sect had brought over were outstanding disciples and all of them were familiar with the Misty Stream Formation. Once this formation was formed, then even though it might not be able to harm Lin Ming, it could still serve in a diversionary role.

All of these disciples were well-trained elites. Even though the situation was chaotic and tense, they still looked for their spot in an orderly fashion. The Misty Stream Sect Sovereign actually stood in front of these disciples, blocking off Lin Ming. Once Lin Ming started to attack, the Misty Stream Sect Sovereign would fend him off, ensuring that the Misty Stream Formation would successfully be formed.

At this moment, Lin Ming’s lips curved up in a fierce sneer. Although he didn’t place this battle formation in his eyes, that didn’t mean he would allow them to simply do as they pleased.

“Do you really think you can block me?”

Heavenly Demon martial intent, open to the limit!

Bang!

A terrifying force field energy rushed out like a tide. He revolved the Heretical God Force to the limit, simultaneously releasing the strength of the third level of the Eight inner Hidden Gates as he poured his large success bronze battle spirit into the energy of the force field.

Asura force field, omnidirectional suppression of the body and soul!

Death God force field, cutting down life and extinguishing all vitality!

The Misty Stream disciples that were laying down the Misty Stream Formation were suddenly enveloped by the dual force fields. Because the disciples with the weaker cultivations couldn’t withstand the pressure of the Asura force field, their heads exploded like watermelons as red blood and white brain fluid splashed all over the ground!

As for the others, their bodies suddenly shook, their eyes blew apart, their blood vessels burst, their meridians tore to pieces, and their dantian completely collapsed on themselves!

Peng! Peng! Peng!

With several muffled thumping sounds, several martial artists slumped to the ground. Many headless corpses still stood on their feet, their bodies twitching in response.

This sudden scene caused the many martial artists present to be stunned in fear. How had their comrades died just now?

They hadn’t even seen Lin Lanjian do anything!!!

It was as if he just glanced at them and they all died on the spot!

“Lin Lanjian! You dare to kill my Misty Stream Sect disciples!? I will take your life!”

The Misty Stream Sect’s Old Man Yan’s eyes turned blood red. He drew out a long sword from his spatial ring, revolving all of the energy within his body as he pointed it straight toward Lin Ming.

Lin Ming scoffed. “What a joke! You want to kill me but I can’t kill you? Do you think I should stretch my neck out and let you chop it off as you please?”

Old Man Yan had no intention of bantering with Lin Ming. He calmly stroked the edge of his sword, causing the blade to become translucent like jade. Energy trembled and a divine light shot into the blue skies.

“Skysplit Sword!’

Old Man Yan slashed his sword down at Lin Ming. The Misty Stream Sect was a strong fifth-grade sect so their inheritances were naturally good. This Skysplit Sword was the ultimate move of the Misty Stream Sword Art. One had to cultivate the inherited heart mantra to the highest level in order to use it.

According to the ancient texts of the Misty Stream Sect, when the Skysplit Sword’s might reached its pinnacle, a single sword strike could split apart the endless blue sky!

Zheng!

The sword light turned. It looked like a jade dragon descending down the mountains, emitting a harsh, whistling sound that passed through the clouds and could split apart stone.

Facing the sword of a Destiny Decree master, Lin Ming didn’t have much of an expression at all. He shook the long spear in his hand and the Concept of Fire wove together with the Laws of Space.

Law of Annihilation, Chain of Stars!

Peng!

Space shattered like glass. The flame energy fused with the power of space, condensing into tiny fragments that spun in the air like miniature stars. Then, they turned toward Old Man Yan and shrouded over his sword light.

Ca!

Harsh sounds of colliding energy filled the air. The star fragments tore into the sword light and terrifying true essence shockwaves exploded outward, causing a massive storm to set off in the surrounding area.

Under the impact of such a terrifying flow of energy, Old Man Yan was struck in the chest. He was sent flying backward, the blood tumbling in his body as he nearly vomited some!

“Sovereign!”

As the young elites of the Misty Stream Sect saw Old Man Yan sent flying back in such a miserable state, all of them were inexplicably horrified. The Skysplit Sword their Sovereign used was the ultimate finishing move of their Misty Stream Sect! How could this have happened!?

Meanwhile, Lin Ming didn’t give Old Man Yan any chance to recover. He turned the red spear in his hands and the Chain of Stars came out again!

This time, Lin Ming was the one taking the initiative to attack. The power of space condensed into countless space fragments that shot outward. Old Man Yan blocked some but many of the other martial artists were also caught within the range of the attack.

“Be careful!”

“Withdraw!”

Several Elders cried out in alarm while they simultaneously released true essence shields around them. However, the most they could protect was themselves; it was impossible for them to help anyone else.

The space fragments were just too fast. They sprayed forward like a hail of knives, recklessly firing toward the martial artists.

A part of the space fragments violently crashed into several Elder’s true essence shields, erupting into brilliant and deadly sparks of energy. But most of the space fragments had flowed toward the groups of ordinary martial artists. Most of them had a cultivation at the Revolving Core realm and some were even at the Xiantian realm. It was impossible for them to resist such an attack!

Peng! Peng! Peng! Peng! Peng!

Fresh scarlet red blood bloomed in the air. Miserable screams sounded out from all over. Several Revolving Core martial artists had their heads directly pierced through by these space fragments. Then, the savage and violent power of space broke out, causing their heads to burst apart and their brain fluids to mix with the rain of blood.

“Quickly, retreat!”

All of the surviving young martial artists from every sect and family clan instantly lost any shred of courage they had left. Their minds cracked in fear as they all fled away. They had originally come here thinking about obtaining the God Transforming Pill and all sorts of other lucky chances, but right now, the Lin Ming in front of them was no different from the devil himself!

No amount of wealth or lucky chances were as valuable as their lives!

However, they didn’t flee too far when they discovered a despairing truth that took away all their hopes. The entire great temple had been blocked off by the Jagged Slope Mountain Branch Division’s great array formation!

They couldn’t leave!!!

“Open it! Please, hurry up and open it!!”

Many of the young martial artists began screaming at the top of their lungs and there were even some martial artists that began launching attacks against the array formation. But let alone them, even Lin Ming who was skilled in the Demon Emperor’s array formation still required 10 breaths of time to break through it.

“Stop panicking! Open the grand temple’s killing array!” Hall Master Situ yelled out as he saw the situation spiraling out of control.

Several Asura Divine Kingdom Branch Division Protectors were already standing above the array formation runes. At this time, Lin Ming didn’t even bother glancing at them. He only flicked his fingers and three true essence air arrows fused with his battle spirit shot out.

These true essence air arrows were silent and invisible. With his large success bronze battle spirit attached to it and with the support of his Concepts, these air arrows were equivalent to the all-out attack of a three to four stage Life Destruction powerhouse using a heaven-step treasure!

With two ‘peng peng’ sounds, two of the true essence air arrows passed through the dantian of the Asura Divine Kingdom Revolving Core martial artists that had been standing on the array runes. The energy of the battle spirit burst out from within their dantian, causing their Revolving Core crystal nucleus to shatter apart.

Both people instantly died on the spot.

As for the last and strongest first stage Life Destruction martial artist, he loudly roared, retreating as he took out a high-grade earth-step treasure sword and cut down at the true essence air arrow. However, with a ‘kacha’ sound, that high-grade earth-step treasure was broken apart by the true essence air arrow. The air arrow didn’t slow down at all, piercing through the martial artist’s protective true essence before piercing through his head, causing a rain of blood to scatter out.

In an instant, that Life Destruction martial artist’s spiritual sea had been completely destroyed by the true essence air arrow.

Chapter 803 – Killing the Elders

Lian Shiyu certainly wouldn’t think that he was faster than Lin Ming. But relatively speaking, chasing him would be the most strenuous and tasking choice. If he were Lin Ming then he would prioritize killing those other three old men, otherwise he would waste too much time and give those three the chance to escape.

As long as Lin Ming decided not to chase him then after some more time passed, the three Demon Envoys would definitely arrive. Then he would be safe.

This was his only chance of survival.

As Lian Shiyu thought this, he pushed himself to the limit to escape. But at this time, he suddenly heard the whistling of true essence blasting out from behind him.

A thick and overwhelming killing intent shrouded down on him.

“Noo!”

Lian Shiyu’s heart filled with despair. He never thought that the speed he was so proud of would be overtaken in a mere five breaths of time by Lin Ming!

In front of Lin Ming, his so-called speed was just a joke!

Lin Ming had chased after him, the fastest of the four. Without a doubt, Lin Ming had decided to wipe out all four of them!

Filled with despair, on the verge of death, when one’s life became a flickering candle, that was the time when a person could often erupt with their life’s greatest potential.

When Lin Ming’s killing intent covered him, Lian Shiyu suddenly turned around. He spat out blood essence on his saber, turning the entire blade a deep blood red. Fierce bursts of wind howled through the air as true essence roared out. Lian Shiyu shouted like a madman, crazily cutting his saber down at Lin Ming.

Slaughter Soul Saber!

To use his own blood essence to stir the Slaughter Soul Saber, the saber became not only a material attack but one that could extinguish a person’s divine soul.

This was a cultivation method of harming oneself to harm the enemy. Even if he managed to cut down the enemy, he would still severely damage his own divine soul, unable to recover for a long time. And the reason that Lian Shiyu used this attack now was because he had been forced to his limits. He had discovered that Lin Ming’s defensive power was simply too freakish.

With his protective true essence, Demon Emperor Armor, and Lin Ming’s own terrifying physical bodily defense, all general material attacks against him were simply rendered useless. Even Old Man Yan’s Skysplit Saber had only lightly injured Lin Ming.

Since material attacks didn’t work then Lian Shiyu could only use the Slaughter Soul Saber.

This saber was only offensive without a single ounce of defense. Lian Shiyu was aware that if he fought with Lin Ming, he would sooner or later be defeated. He could only use this suicidal method to show Lin Ming he was a bone that would hurt to chew, forcing Lin Ming to give up on him and chase the other three.

As Lin Ming faced this menacing saber attack his mind stirred. A divine soul attack?

He could feel the strength behind this saber. It was impossible to dodge – he could only block it.

But once he blocked it, his speed would definitely slow for a period of time. And Lian Shiyu would use the repelling force to open up the distance between them.

Then, chasing him would take several more breaths of time.

At this moment he was pressed for time. If he wanted to settle these battles quickly then he couldn’t back down. If he delayed for too long then it would be much more difficult once others caught up to him. After all, this was still the land of his enemies. Once reinforcements rushed in then the situation would become increasingly troublesome.

With his long spear in hand, Lin Ming directly faced Lian Shiyu’s Slaughter Soul Saber. On the spear shaft, the Concept of Fire and the Space Laws wove together. He poured his battle spirit into it.

Bury the Heavens!

A spear stabbed towards the defenseless Lian Shiyu, completely disregarding his attack.

“What!?”

Lian Shiyu was shocked. He never imagined Lin Ming would completely ignore the threat of his suicidal attack and continue launching an attack towards him as before!

When martial artists fought, they particularly feared fighting ruthless individuals that didn’t care a whit for their lives. Especially when that ruthless individual was himself a powerful freak of nature!

It was already too late to take back his own attack. Lian Shiyu gave a loud shout and gathered all of his energy onto the saber point. His eyes shined with a maddeningly red light. “Let’s die together!”

He had complete confidence in his Slaughter Soul Saber’s divine soul attack. 500 years ago when Lian Shiyu was at the third stage of Life Destruction, he had relied on this attack to cut down a fourth stage Life Destruction master.

The spear and Slaughter Soul Saber crossed each other. Lin Ming’s spear stabbed towards Lian Shiyu’s chest, and the Slaughter Soul Saber cut towards Lin Ming’s waist, as if it would cut him in half!

Peng!

Peng!

Both of their bodily protective true essence simultaneously exploded into pieces. Lian Shiyu’s body was easily pierced through by Lin Ming, blood raining to the ground.

Although Lian Shiyu had managed to avoid having his vital heart point pierced at the final moment, true essence still surged into his body, violently destroying his insides and meridians. His wounds were no lighter than Hall Master Situ’s!

Lin Ming felt a burst of pain at his waist and a great energy transmitted into him. His body shook and he nearly spat out blood. At the same time, the violent flux of energy broke into his spiritual sea, turning into a blood red saber that wanted to cut Lin Ming’s spiritual sea in two!

Lian Shiyu was a Destiny Decree master. He damaged his own soul and combusted his blood essence as the price in order to send out this incomparably terrifying divine soul attack. Moreover, Lin Ming had taken the strike without dodging or blocking at all. The entire divine soul attack had struck him!

Lin Ming’s eyes exploded with a sharp light.

The Samsara martial intent revolved!

A massive black vortex began spinning atop his spiritual sea. It joined together with the azure battle spirit there and shot towards the blood red saber.

Ka ka ka ka!

The black vortex and the blood red saber collided. Wild energies unceasingly melted against each other.

“This brat really decided to take my Slaughter Soul Saber!?”

As Lian Shiyu saw Lin Ming stiffen for a moment, his distorted face curved up in a vicious smile. Even though he was severely wounded, he believed that Lin Ming’s current situation was even worse than his. He knew just how powerful his Slaughter Soul Saber was. Even if Lin Ming were to withstand the Slaughter Soul Saber’s physical attack, he wouldn’t be able to fend off the divine soul attack.

When masters exchanged moves, the moment of dazed absent-mindedness that occurred when the soul was damaged could often result in fatal consequences!

While he was frozen, take his life!

Lian Shiyu suppressed the excruciating pain in his chest and ignored the damage to his meridians to forcefully revolved his true essence. He prepared a second saber attack that would cut off Lin Ming’s neck!

Even if Lin Ming was wearing the Demon Emperor Armor, his neck wouldn’t be protected. With Lin Ming’s mind having fallen to illusion, his protective true essence would also reach the very depths of frailty. As long as this saber hit, it would definitely be able to decapitate Lin Ming.

“I’ve won!!!”

Saber light rose up. Lian Shiyu lifted the saber above him with both hands and was prepared to cut it down, when at this moment a cold light suddenly shot out from Lin Ming’s eyes, like a bolt of lightning crossing through the dark night sky!

W-what!?

When Lian Shiyu was locked on to by this light, he felt as if the flow of time around him instantly slowed down. He lost all strength to move his body.

An azure light flared out. The spear in Lin Ming’s hands shot forth like a viper, thrusting straight into Lian Shiyu’s chest.

Puff!

Protective true essence tore like wet paper. The heart ruptured and blood shot into the wind.

Lin Ming’s spear had mangled Lian Shiyu’s heart to shreds!

At this time, Lian Shiyu’s saber hung in the air, incapable of cutting down.

Lian Shiyu vomited a mouthful of blood. His pained chest only felt empty now. Lin Ming’s spear had erupted from his back, creating a massive hole through him. When this overlapped with the previous wound, Lian Shiyu’s vision began to slowly blur.

Lian Shiyu couldn’t believe that after his Slaughter Soul Saber solidly struck his enemy’s body, it actually hadn’t been able to cause any substantial damage.

“Just how… could… this be…” Lian Shiyu blankly looked at Lin Ming. Gradually, his pupils began to dim.

“Sorry, but I am similarly confident in my soul defensive ability…”

These were the last words that Lian Shiyu ever heard. In the next moment his head shot into the air, and his ruined body crashed into the ground like a dead dog.

Lian Shiyu had perished!

Lin Ming took Lian Shiyu’s spatial ring and without any pause at all he stepped onto Golden Roc Shattering the Void, chasing straight after Old Man Sun.

At this time, Old Man Sun had already flown almost a hundred miles away. He was ecstatic that the one Lin Ming had chosen to chase was not him. As long as he hadn’t been chosen, he had confidence he would be able to safely escape. Now, after flying for such a long distance, his mind was much more calm and stable then it was before.

‘I’ll fly out a few dozen more miles and the change direction. I’ll fall down and hide in the mountains, restraining all of my energy. There’s no way he should be able to find me then.’

This thought had just crossed Old Man Sun’s mind, when at this time, he heard the sound of intense air currents whistling behind him. This sound became increasingly close and increasingly loud.

“What!?”

Old Man Sun swiveled around to see Lin Ming, soaked in blood from head to toe, grasping that red long spear and shooting towards him at over twice his own speed!

“How can he be so quick! Did he already kill Hall Master Situ and Lian Shiyu!?”

Old Man Sun was frightened to the point where he felt his soul fly out from him. Only several dozen breaths of time had passed! The four Destiny Decree masters that had been at the Asura Divine Kingdom Branch Division were also divided into the strong and weak. The strongest had been Lian Shiyu, followed by Old Man Yan. Hall Master Situ and himself had been the weakest of the bunch!

Old Man Sun was well aware that if Lin Ming could kill Lian Shiyu in such a short period of time, then killing him would be as easy as tearing apart a piece of paper.

Lin Ming’s terrifying extreme speed caused Old Man Sun to completely abandon all thoughts of escaping. Now, with the meridians of his right hand burnt away he could only use his left hand. With only 60-70% of his combat strength left, the chances of defeating Lin Ming were less than zero.

“Lin Lanjian, don’t kill me. I can give you 70% of all the wealth I’ve accumulated in my sect!”

“Just die.”

Lin Ming didn’t bother with this Old Man Sun’s nonsense. He swept the spear in his hand straight towards Old Man Sun’s throat.

Old Man Sun released a miserable scream and desperately cut out his sword at Lin Ming. However, he only had his left hand holding this sword; how could he possibly contend with Lin Ming’s spear?

Bang!

With an explosion, Old Man Sun was sent flying backwards in a rain of blood. Lin Ming chased close behind.

Penetrating Rainbow!

Chi-la!

Old Man Sun dropped his sword. His entire left arm was covered in blood!

With a twist of his spear, Lin Ming’s spear cut through Old Man Sun’s protective true essence and pierced straight towards his dantian!

True essence erupted. His battle spirit sundered Old Man Sun’s Revolving Core crystal nucleus. Lin Ming grabbed Old Man Sun’s spatial ring and then continued on his way to kill the last Destiny Decree master.

Lin Ming had already left battle spirit marks on everyone. Normally, a martial artist would only comprehend their own battle spirit at the Divine Sea realm. Although these four old men were all Destiny Decree ranked masters, their potential wasn’t too great and none of them had managed to form their own battle spirit. Thus, it was impossible to undo the battle spirit mark.

In just several dozen breaths of time Lin Ming returned to the Jagged Slope Mountain Branch Division. At this time, the entire area was in chaos and all the low level martial artists had already fled away as fast and far as they could have.

Bang!

Lin Ming swept his spear across the front of the great hall. The walls collapsed, revealing a pale-faced and empty-eyed Old Man Yan. Lin Ming was about to kill him with his spear, when a sudden alarming premonition flashed through his mind. His body shot backwards in a conditioned reflex.

Puff!

A wisp of spear light thrust into the ground where Lin Ming had been standing. The rock shattered like glass and an immeasurably deep hole was formed in the ground.

“Who!?”

Lin Ming waved his long spear, his entire mind on full alert.

Chapter 814 – Nine Heavens Thunder Dominion

Bang!

Bi Ruyu’s claw smashed into the black swamp’s muddy ground, causing a massive amount of the slush to splash into the air. Purple flames burned the earth and countless mourning ghosts seemed to cry out in the flames, their souls seeming to be turned into fuel for the purple flames to burn even brighter.

Bi Ruyu’s hair was split apart and her eyes were ferocious. She looked up to see that Lin Ming had flash stepped a thousand feet away. Her strike had completely missed.

Lin Ming looked at the purple flames still burning on the ground, his expression slightly changing.

He simply wasn’t able to directly contend with Bi Ruyu at this moment; the disparity in their strength was far too great. He had opened the Gate of Wonder and used Golden Roc Shattering the Void to dodge Bi Ruyu’s attack. At this time, his extreme speed was the greatest advantage he could rely on.

“Brat, don’t think that your speed is invincible within Life Destruction. I will show you the power of a true top Life Destruction master!”

Bi Ruyu screeched, her voice ugly and horrifying like a tortured ghost. She suddenly bit down on her tongue and spat out a mouthful of blood before swallowing her tongue into her belly. In the next moment, her shriveled body emitted crackling sounds as her clothes broke apart and her hair went wildly flying into the air.

Bi Ruyu’s body began to grow, becoming larger and taller. Her claws became longer and her two hands nearly stooped down to the ground. Her elbows developed sharp spurs, her body became increasingly bent and a layer of fine fur covered her body. She looked just like the fabled corpse eating ghost ghouls of hell.

“This cultivation method…”

Lin Ming’s mind chilled. There was a myriad of demonic path cultivations with countless effects. Bi Ruyu had used a body altering cultivation method similar to Corpsemancer’s puppet technique. It was a strange cultivation method that changed the body with use of external forces.

Lin Ming would never despise such a technique that desired strength regardless of what cost had to be paid. When Corpsemancer had become ranked on the Destiny Decree he had only been at the fourth stage of Life Destruction, and that was all because of the strangeness of this cultivation method.

And now this Bi Ruyu in front of him didn’t have much of her lifespan left, yet she was still able to rank in the top 50 masters of the Destiny Decree. She certainly had to have her extraordinary aspects.

When Bi Ruyu’s body changed, the second Demon Envoy also moved. He preferred that Lin Ming hadn’t died. He wanted to personally defeat Lin Ming and capture him.

With a loud shout, the second Demon Envoy’s body seemed to blaze like an inferno as dozens of Blood Drinking Seals started to revolve around his body. His surname was Situ, and as a branch descendent of the Asura Divine Kingdom’s Royal Family Situ, what he practiced was the true ‘Great Desolate Halberd Art’.

“Rahh!”

Bi Ruyu let out an earthshaking roar as her body turned into a black line and shot towards Lin Ming. Her speed was no slower than Lin Ming’s extreme speed!

And from behind, the second Demon Envoy was closely following her. He grasped a long lance in his hand, the black lance light seeming to cut a hole through the void.

‘Great Desolate Halberd Art’ – Slaughter Path!

Lin Ming’s pupils contracted as he saw two people attacking him at the same time. He had no intention of fighting with Bi Ruyu and the second Demon Envoy – that was akin to suicide. At the same time, escaping from here wasn’t an option either.

Bi Ruyu’s current speed was no slower than his. It would be impossible to ditch her in a short period of time. Because Bi Ruyu was using this special technique to power up, she had simply lost all reasoning. In this 8000 Mile Black Swamp that was filled with dangers and more dangers, engaging this madwoman in an extreme speed chase was tantamount to suicide!

If they managed to annoy a divine dragon rank existence in this Sea of Miracles like that sea serpent, then a single breath would be able to kill all of them without leaving even a skeleton!

Lin Ming didn’t wish to perish here together with this crazy old lady.

He made a split-second judgement. He opened the Gate of Wonder and stepped onto Golden Roc Shattering the Void, rushing away at full speed!

In the skies, the dark clouds hung high in the air like titanic black mountains, completely obscuring the sun. Only the faintly dazzling thunder light illuminated the world.

As for how thick these dark clouds were, only the heavens would know.

Lin Ming was fast. In just several blinks of the eye he had rushed out over a dozen miles. Here, strong heavenly winds roared about like killer razor blades, blowing and slicing away at Lin Ming’s protective true essence as if it would break his defenses apart at any moment. If a lower level martial artist were to enter here then just this strong heavenly wind would be enough to slice them into pieces!

Lin Ming clenched his teeth. He opened the Heretical God Force and revolved his energy to the limit.

“Go!”

Lin Ming became one with his spear. He became a stream of light that directly pierced into the heavens. Bi Ruyu and the second Demon Envoy followed right after!

At this time, Bi Ruyu had already gone mad and the second Demon Envoy was also desperately wishing to capture Lin Ming. He had a feeling in his heart: if he could capture Lin Ming and obtain the Divine Kingdom’s rewards then he would be able to eliminate this heart demon and have high hopes of impacting the Divine Sea in the future!

The Divine Sea realm was the ultimate temptation to any Life Destruction powerhouse. Even though he had to brave the perilous 8000 Mile Black Swamp, he had still come!

Peng!

Lin Ming placed his spear before him and pierced through the dark clouds. A powerful impact force twisted apart all of the clouds nearby for miles. For a time, lightning tumbled and loud thunderclaps rang through the world!

Lin Ming was inundated by this infinite heavenly lightning!

Above the Sea of Miracles was the Nine Heavens Thunder Dominion. This was an area with endless thunder. If a general martial artist were to enter they would immediately turn into ash!

“Damnit!”

The second Demon Envoy was still sane and logical. As he saw Lin Ming submerge into the Thunder Dominion, his heart tightened. When Lin Ming had made it through the black fog without even the slightest of wounds, that had made him feel as if Lin Ming was as tough as a cockroach. Even this lightning might not be able to kill him.

“When the black fog covered the world I didn’t manage to see how you lived through it. But now that you’re in front of me, let me see just what methods you have! I don’t believe that with my rank 83 Destiny Decree strength, I would still be inferior to a mere Revolving Core child only ranked 280th!”

The second Demon Envoy grit his teeth. He galvanized his protective true essence to the limit and chased after Lin Ming.

He didn’t believe Lin Ming had a higher resistance to the black fog than them. He must have used some crafty method in order to survive!

Kakaka!

Thunder twisted into long whips that violently cracked against the second Demon Envoy’s protective true essence. His protective true essence began to rapidly melt, and the remaining power of thunder drilled into his body like a viper. The energy spread through him, manically rushing through his meridians and flesh. He had no choice but to revolve his true essence further to suppress it, making him slow down and his blood tumble.

As he looked up he saw that Lin Ming didn’t even slow in the least. He had already pierced over a dozen miles into the Thunder Dominion!

“This boy!!”

The second Demon Envoy’s pupils shrank. Was his body made from iron? He didn’t even need to slow down upon entering the Thunder Dominion?

Or was he forcefully withstanding the numbing feeling from the thunder in order to maintain his maximum speed to escape?

The second Demon Envoy’s speed continued to fall. But in front of him, Bi Ruyu didn’t seem to care at all about this surrounding thunder. She was like a psychotic madwoman as she rushed forwards, not even caring if the torrents of thunder that fell upon her wounded her body.

As the chase continued, Bi Ruyu and Lin Ming quickly cast away the second Demon Envoy.

The second Demon Envoy stared with wide eyes. He looked in the direction that Bi Ruyu and Lin Ming vanished off to. There was no need to explain how Bi Ruyu had accomplished this. She was amazingly strong to begin with and her strange cultivation method allowed her to become stronger in exchange for her current freakish appearance.

This strong defensive power that came from necrosis of the nerves gave Bi Ruyu enormous resistance to this thunder.

But what method did Lin Ming use?

The second Demon Envoy stopped, crestfallen. Continuing any further would surpass the limit of his body.

20 miles…

25 miles…

30 miles…!

Lin Ming constantly flew deeper in. The thunder began to change color. It went from blue white and faded into purple white. The power of thunder became even more violent and feverish. The arcs of lightning became as thick as an arm and the thunder light became increasingly savage.

Even with the Heretical God Seed suppressing the power of thunder within him, Lin Ming still felt bursts of paralysis.

The thunder here was too terrifying. The power of thunder that Lin Ming could contain within his body was reaching the limit. His skin was beginning to char and sizzle, his entire body releasing crackling ‘chi chi chi’ sounds.

He glanced back to see that Bi Ruyu was still closely chasing him in hot pursuit!

“This damned old hag is still chasing after me!

“My cultivation is too low. Besides my dantian there is nowhere else in my body that I can store energy. Compared to a Life Destruction powerhouse, my losses are far too great! Even with the heaven-defying Heretical God Seed, there isn’t enough time to refine this power of thunder. If I continue to gather the power of thunder into my body then my meridians will explode!”

Lin Ming grit his teeth and continued to flee forwards, deeper into the Thunder Dominion. At this point, the thunder had become a deep purple. Lightning roared. If the arcs of lightning were like thick whips at the start, they had now become dragons of thunder!

This was a true hell of thunder!

Not only did the thunder attack Lin Ming’s body, but also his soul. In the skies above his spiritual sea, thunder swam about like flood dragons, wanting to tear Lin Ming’s spiritual sea apart.

The Samsara martial intent and battle spirit began to revolve, sharing in this great pressure.

The power of thunder was easily able to harm one’s spiritual sea. If one didn’t have a firm will and the power of thunder attacked them then they would easily fall unconscious.

A strong numbing feeling flooded Lin Ming’s entire body. Lin Ming desperately pushed his true essence past its limit. The Heretical God Seed violently trembled as it forcefully absorbed the massive amounts of the power of thunder. Still, there was far too much left over that brutally broke into Lin Ming’s meridians.

His speed began to fall. But as his soul force locked onto Bi Ruyu, he was thankful that she was obviously reaching her limits.

Her speed had fallen by a great deal. At this time, her hair was split apart and countless areas of her body were scorched black. From time to time, currents of electricity arced on her body, emitting crackling sounds.

Her eyes were like ghosts. There was no pupil in them, only pure purple sclera, burst out with a fearful light that made one shiver.

‘Danger!’

Lin Ming’s heart gave birth to a sense of immense crisis. At the same time, Bi Ruyu moved. She screamed and her body suddenly accelerated. Her right hand turned into a claw, reaching out towards Lin Ming.

As her speed surged her skin and flesh also cracked. On her right arm, a white-robed ghost suddenly appeared, howling towards Lin Ming!

As this ghost appeared, most of it was immediately melted away by the endless power of thunder. However, the excess energy still made Lin Ming’s scalp tingle!

There was absolutely no way he could contend with this!

Lin Ming ignored all possible dangers of the Thunder Dominion. He decisively opened the Gate of Wonder to the limit and brought about its highest speed.

Golden Roc Shattering the Void!

Woosh!

Lin Ming twisted the void. A single step brought him 10 miles ahead!

A massive explosive sound blasted out from behind Lin Ming – he had dodged Bi Ruyu’s fatal attack. But as he slowed down his complexion suddenly changed. At the position he was in, the arcs of lightning around him had already turned golden. The arcs of golden lightning were only the width of a finger but they contained a horrifying annihilating energy as they crazily swelled up towards Lin Ming!

Chapter 816 – Heretical God Sprout

The Heretical God Force was an arcane technique left behind by an ancient Evil God. It had been the greatest stroke of luck for the Realm of the Gods Supreme Elder who found this cultivation method, but he had died before having the time to fully comprehend it.

Actually, as for what secrets the Heretical God Force had and just what would happen once he practiced it to higher levels, he actually had no idea where to even begin finding out. He could only blaze his way forwards and find out by practicing it.

He didn’t think that after withstanding the impact of a top grade heaven-step Thunder Soul as well as the near-infinite amount of golden thunder in a 10 mile radius, the Heretical God Seed would actually sprout!

The Heretical God Seed was in truth a theoretical object condensed from energy; it was not a real seed. Lin Ming had never imagined that the Heretical God Seed would develop like a real seed and actually bud.

After being flooded with energy for so long, had it finally obtained true life?

It was said that if a martial artist poured enough of their will and energy into a weapon, that weapon would slowly obtain its own life, giving birth to sword spirits or spear souls – this wasn’t unusual at all.

As Lin Ming was having all sorts of thoughts, at this moment, the Heretical God Seed let out a resonant cry. Two golden lights appeared on the surface of the seed; they were the eyes of that golden python.

The golden python fiercely struggled as it tried to break free from the Heretical God Seed. However, it was covered by an invisible barrier of energy. No matter how intensely it endeavored, it still couldn’t break free from the shackles of the Heretical God Seed.

Following its movements, the thunder origin energy in the surrounding area began to move restlessly once again, becoming increasingly manic. The golden thunder that had been sucked dry was appearing once again.

This was because of the top grade Thunder Soul!

Lin Ming looked within at the Heretical God Seed. The newly sprouted Heretical God Seed was waging a fierce battle with the uninvited top grade heaven-step Thunder Soul.

The top-grade Thunder Soul wished to swallow the Heretical God Seed, but the Heretical God Seed desired to absorb the Thunder Soul.

Zi zi zi!

The endless gold electric light in the surrounding area was attracted by both of them, everything flowing into Lin Ming’s body. At this time, Lin Ming didn’t even have the slightest bit of strength left. That last strike had completely overdrawn every last bit of energy he had left.

Seeing the endless golden thunder rushing towards him, Lin Ming bit his teeth and closed his eyes. At this point he could only entrust his fate to the Heretical God Seed.

Bang!

Lightning baptized Lin Ming’s body. Every pore, every length of his meridians, every inch of flesh underwent a baptism of golden thunder. Lin Ming’s entire body was flooded in a raging sea of thunder yet he actually didn’t feel much pain.

Although he was still numb like before, this sort of feeling was quite comfortable.

This surprised Lin Ming. It was as if his body had completely transformed into the body of the Thunder Soul.

The energy became increasingly powerful. The golden thunder howled and thunderclaps billowed in the winds. A normal martial artist would have long since turned to ashes in this situation. Even a powerhouse like Bi Ruyu, who had deformed her body for greater strength and also had a stronger resistance to the power of thunder, still wouldn’t be able to withstand this!

“Is this the effect of the Heretical God Seed sprouting? My affinity with thunder and perhaps even my affinity with fire has greatly increased!”

Lin Ming was euphoric over such a change.

Since the golden thunder wasn’t injuring him, he continued to pour the energy into the Heretical God Seed, helping it to subdue the top grade heaven-step Thunder Soul.

However, Lin Ming quickly discovered that in truth, the growing Heretical God Seed didn’t need his help. Of all of the surrounding golden thunder that was ruthlessly and violently surging into Lin Ming’s body, over 95% of it was being absorbed by the Heretical God Seed!

After germinating, the Heretical God Seed had become ravenous. It ate as much thunder energy as it could!

On top of the Heretical God Seed’s bud, a layer of brilliant purple light completely enveloped it. This purple light formed floating iridescent rings, all of them circling the Heretical God Seed and emitting a marvelous light.

In such a magnificent and glorious light, the Heretical God Seed slowly grew. With great difficulty, but steadily!

The power of thunder continuously rolled up around Lin Ming, forming a massive golden vortex.

A titanic amount of energy converged into the Heretical God Seed, completely vanishing without hope of return. The growing Heretical God Seed was like a bottomless abyss.

The top grade heaven-step Thunder Soul was completely suppressed by the Heretical God Seed. At this time it was nothing more than a tiny snake underneath the claw of a great eagle: it simply wasn’t able to resist.

Nearly all of the gathering golden power was absorbed by the Heretical God Seed. Even the energy essence within the Thunder Soul was being stolen away by the Heretical God Seed!

The top grade heaven-step Thunder Soul twisted in panic, its face full of fear and horror. But no matter how much it struggled or how violent it became, it could not escape the imprisonment of the Heretical God Seed.

Slowly, the Heretical God Seed’s bud grew an inch and two tender young stems stretched outwards. On top of these two stems, two leaves curled upwards. One leaf was red and the other was gold.

These leaves slowly began to grow. Not only were their colors different but they were also different shapes. The red leaf was shaped like a heart and the gold leaf was long and narrow, as if it were forming a small sword.

As Lin Ming looked at these two leaves, his heart shook. On top of that succulent red leaf, there was a golden red totem mark; that was the flame totem seal that Lin Ming had comprehended at Timeworn Phoenix City which had then engraved itself onto the surface of the Heretical God Seed. Now, that engraving had appeared on top of this red leaf.

That mark symbolized the Law of Fire, intertwined with the Concept of Fire and its principles.

Soon after, a tiny mass of fiery red lights appeared upon that luscious red leaf. That was the Burning Star Flame Flame Essence.

The entire leaf began to blaze with a brilliant fire. However, that tender leaf didn’t seem afraid of the fire at all. Instead, it became increasingly vibrant.

As time passed, the Heretical God Seed’s bud became longer and larger. But in comparison, the heaven-step Thunder Soul was becoming increasingly weak. The golden python had shrunk to a tiny size and it seemed entirely crestfallen. Its eyes revealed a pleading light as it surrendered; the Thunder Soul realized that it was simply impossible for it to contend with the power of the Heretical God Seed.

After another dozen breaths of time, that top grade heaven-step Thunder Soul crawled onto the Heretical God Seed’s other leaf on its own initiative. It turned into an arc of thunder that surrounded the leaf, turning the entire leaf a vivid gold, sparkling with faint electric sparks.

Thus, the Heretical God Sprout already had two different kinds of heaven-step energies within it. The first was the Burning Star Flame and the other was the tiny golden thunder snake.

At this time, there was a stabbing pain in his mind. Demonshine let out a horrified scream!

Lin Ming was alarmed. He looked towards his spiritual sea and saw that because he had overdrawn his soul and will and forcefully transferred a massive power of thunder from his body, it had caused scars to appear there.

This led to a portion of the golden thunder leaking in. it raged within his spiritual sea, causing lightning to flash in the skies of his spiritual sea. And the area were Demonshine was hiding had been struck by a bolt of thunder, causing the hair on his tail to light up.

Phantasmal existences like ghosts and divine souls especially feared the power of thunder. In particular, this strange golden thunder. Demonshine was frightened as he saw it. He jumped up and down, shouting out, “Lin Ming, hurry up and suppress this lightning! This Saint is about to get shocked to death!”

Lin Ming quickly transferred energy within his body to suppress the lightning. As he looked at the scar in his spiritual sea, he discovered that it was regenerating as it bathed in endless lightning.

Lin Ming’s final strike had forced the Heretical God Seed to take the last step towards evolution. Otherwise, his body would have been swallowed up by the Thunder Soul and the Heretical God Seed would have become a rootless plant. Even though it had the mysterious Laws twined into it, it still wouldn’t have been able to exist any longer, much less bud.

Lin Ming had withstood a tremendous pressure in that last strike. Even though his will far surpassed other martial artists’, moving around so much energy had caused him to seriously overdraw his soul force.

It was a very difficult process to heal a divine soul scar. Wanting to completely regenerate it would take a very long time.

However, what was strange was that even though such a formidable power of thunder had seeped into his spiritual sea, he didn’t feel discomforted at all. He only felt a slight tingling feeling as before.

Instead, as this scar was soaked in lightning, it seemed like it was absorbing the power of thunder to aid in its own regeneration, as if it were ordinary for there to be thunder flashing in the skies above his spiritual sea.

Lin Ming swallowed down a soul recovery pill and began meditating, no longer paying attention to the wound in his divine soul. Wanting to completely cure it would take an extremely long time and also require top heavenly materials – this was obviously impossible here.

Lin Ming thought for a moment and then looked upwards towards the heavens.

The skies were still pitch black, with endless arcs of lightning flashing throughout.

If there was this sort of golden thunder after entering just 50 miles into the Thunder Dominion, then what would it be like if he went deeper in?

The golden thunder was no longer a threat to Lin Ming. As it poured into his body, the tingling was actually sort of comfortable and there was even a certain extent of having his divine soul revitalized.

Without a doubt, these were the aftereffects of the Heretical God Seed sprouting.

If he were to go further and try absorbing an even stronger power of thunder with the Heretical God Seed, would it make it stronger? Could he capture an even more powerful Thunder Soul?

As Lin Ming thought of this, his eyes flashed with excitement. He directly shot forwards, deeper into the Thunder Dominion!

………….

Outside the Nine Heavens Thunder Dominion, under the endless black clouds, Bi Ruyu had already reverted to her true form. She pulled out a black robe from her spatial ring and quickly wrapped it around herself. Her hair was ruined, her body seemed more bent, her eyes were muddy and yellow, her teeth had become loose and hollow, and her black hair had turned white. Through that brief body transformation just now it seemed as if her appearance had aged by 10 years.

She trembled as she took out a small green bottle from her spatial ring. As she opened it, a pale green flame flushed out before being greedily swallowed down by her.

This pale green flame had been refined through the life fires of dozens of young girls. If she didn’t have it, then every time she used that body altering cultivation method she would age by dozens of years. It wouldn’t be long before she turned into nothing but a pile of bones.

After swallowing down this green flame, she recovered by a great deal. Her eyes became clear again and her hair darkened to its original black. It was only that she couldn’t conceal her old age. The wrinkles on her face piled up together, bringing with it a faint flavor of the dying.

After overdrawing her physical strength in that chase, and afterwards having to consume a great deal of energy in order to forcefully escape the distorted space within the Thunder Dominion, this had placed an immeasurable burden on the fires of her life which had already been flickering about like a fading candle in the wind.

Every tiny bit of life force she lost was extremely difficult to restore through the use of medicines.

“That damned brat, I will definitely pull out his soul and refine it into a pill!” Bi Ruyu gnashed her teeth. But at this moment, she suddenly paused, stunned.

She looked at the scene underneath her. “This is… what is going on here…?”

Chapter 824 – Death Reaper Curse

The energy of the black seal became increasingly strong, soon enveloping all the nearby space.

The second Demon Envoy was clearly aware of just how mighty this Saint artifact level divine sword’s energy was. Wanting to place his own spirit mark on it was easier said than done, especially since he was in a life or death battle with Lin Ming at the moment. If he separated a spirit mark to control this divine sword and a problem occurred, then it was likely Lin Ming would take the chance to end his life instead.

The safest method was to first seal away this divine sword and then place it into his spatial ring. He would be able to slowly deal with it in the future.

In front of such an unbelievably rare treasure, there were far too few people that could restrain their greedy nature.

Pointing his spear, the black seal whistled towards the Argent White Sword placing a heavy layer of pressure on it!

At the moment the seal touched the sword blade –

Gong!!!

A resounding sword cry impacted into the endless skies, as if a deeply slumbering Azure Dragon had been awakened!

A vast purple energy rushed out from the sword and instantly crushed the black seal to nothing. The black seal was connected to the second Demon Envoy’s soul force. The second Demon Envoy only felt as if someone had taken a 10,000 jin sledgehammer and smashed it into his head. His spiritual sea violently shook, nearly collapsing in on itself!

Blood began leaking from the corners of the second Demon Envoy’s eyes, running down his ears and dripping from his nose. The Argent White Sword was marked with the martial arts will of the Eightfall Thunder Emperor. Tens of thousands of years ago, the Eightfall Thunder Emperor had been the highest man under the heavens and he was particularly extraordinary in the aspect of martial arts will. At the middle Revolving Core realm he had formed his own battle spirit, and by the time he reached the Divine Sea his battle spirit had reached the silver boundary and even fused together with the thunder attribute because of his Thunder Force Field.

This martial arts will was supremely formidable to begin with. And after being tempered in the Thunder Dominion for tens of thousands of years, how could a martial artist on the level of the second Demon Envoy even hope of violating it?

This was the fury of the divine sword.

This was the rage of the Eightfall Thunder Emperor’s martial arts will!

At the moment when the second Demon Envoy’s soul suffered a backlash, Lin Ming had already been patiently waiting for this chance. He grasped his red spear and burst forwards!

Space shrank underneath his feet. Lin Ming appeared in front of the second Demon Envoy in just the blink of an eye.

His soul force touched upon the Heretical God Sprout, forcefully pulling out a thin wisp of golden red lighting. He poured this lightning into his red spear and smashed down at the second Demon Envoy’s head.

“Ahh!”

The second Demon Envoy was so angered that his eyes nearly popped out. He utilized the Concept of Space, distorting space to break and avoid this fatal spear.

However, just as the second Demon Envoy’s figure blinked several hundred feet away, he suddenly paled upon reappearing. This was because Lin Ming had also appeared in front of him, the cold spear in his hands just three feet from his head!

In terms of understanding the Concept of Space, Lin Ming had experienced several fortuitous encounters in his adventures and had even cultivated ‘Golden Roc Shattering the Void’, thus he was far superior to the second Demon Envoy. How could Lin Ming give the second Demon Envoy a chance to dodge?

“You!!”

The second Demon Envoy hurriedly lifted his spear to meet the strike.

This time Lin Ming didn’t decide to engage the second Demon Envoy in a suicidal strike, trading a severe wound for his life. After all, Lin Ming was in an extremely poor condition right now – he didn’t want to sustain another serious injury. This 8000 Mile Black Swamp was simply too dangerous for him in that state.

He slightly changed the trajectory of his spear and smashed it into the area where the Demon Envoy’s spear shaft connected with the spearhead. This was the weakest point of a spear.

Kacha!

The two spears slammed into each other. Although Lin Ming had taken the initiative and suppressed the second Demon Envoy’s spear, he still wasn’t able to injure him. This was the disparity brought about by the difference in their absolute strengths.

But at this moment, the golden red lightning hiding in the spear suddenly erupted outwards! It was like a sun rising in the deep night skies!

“Ahh!”

With a pitiful cry, the second Demon Envoy’s hands that he used to grasp his spear were charred to cinders. Now both his arms and both his legs and been completely ruined. Lin Ming didn’t give him a chance to catch his breath. His soul force touched on the Heretical God Sprout again, drawing out a second wisp of golden red lightning!

Although this lightning wasn’t too fast, the distance between him and the second Demon Envoy was small, and the second Demon Envoy’s entire body was also paralyzed.

The arc of lightning penetrated through the second Demon Envoy’s dantian!

Chi!

The second Demon Envoy’s lower stomach was turned to ash. A giant burnt black hole tunneled through his body.

“Lin Lanjian…”

Bitter hatred flashed through the second Demon Envoy’s eyes. He spat a mouthful of blood onto Lin Ming and grabbed his spear, a trace of malicious pleasure touching his lips.

“Death Reaper Curse… I curse you… in 100 days… you will die.”

As the second Demon Envoy spoke these last words, his body suddenly ignited with a blazing black flame. Lin Ming felt a sudden pain in his chest, a deep burning sensation as if someone had pressed a heated iron there.

He looked down at his chest to see that the area where the second Demon Envoy’s blood had splashed had left a black curse seal. The curse seal burned like hot iron, causing the surrounding skin to twist and turn black and red.

“This is…”

Demonshine suddenly spoke up, “This is the Death Reaper Curse! It as an extremely sinister and malevolent demonic path curse and the curse method is also similarly dire. Before the point of death, completely burn away your life force, including your soul and blood essence, taking all of that as a sacrifice to the Death Reaper, and beseeching the Death Reaper to slay your enemy. This curse… if you can’t undo this curse with your own strength then you will surely die in 100 days!”

“This…” Lin Ming’s mind turned cold. Humans certainly had a soul. But, after humans died, it was still a riddle whether or not they would be reincarnated. When a martial artist died their soul returned to the boundless universe. They always held a hope that they would reincarnate in a new life, but if their soul was destroyed after their death then that was truly the most miserable way to die.

Only some demonic path martial artists like Bi Ruyu would study such macabre cultivation methods that involved pulling someone’s soul and refining it, making a martial artist experience pain worse than death.

And now, in order to curse him, the second Demon Envoy had burnt away even his soul, turning into nothing but nihility. This was truly a depraved obsession. The stronger a martial artist’s will was, the stronger their obsessions were. And, the second Demon Envoy’s greatest obsession before he died was to kill Lin Ming.

“Can you break this curse?” Lin Ming asked Demonshine.

Demonshine helplessly spread out his paws, “I’m just a wisp of a remnant soul. I don’t even have a flesh and blood body or any true essence. The only energy I can move now is my soul force. When you were at the Xiantian realm I could still help you, but now… I’m a bit powerless.”

Demonshine poignantly said. Lin Ming’s growth was simply too fast. He could mostly only impart some of his experiences and knowledge to help Lin Ming now.

Lin Ming also felt sympathetic towards Demonshine. Demonshine had once been a Three-headed Divine Demon Hound, but all that was left over was a single head. Moreover, his divine soul had been seriously injured to begin with, and he still wasn’t even close to fully recovering.

All Lin Ming could do was wait until he was strong enough and then help Demonshine reform his divine soul and physical body.

“Then how can I break the curse?” Lin Ming said with a calm tone. He didn’t really think that he would die under this Death Reaper Curse.

“Easy. As long as you are strong enough – a lot stronger than the one who cursed you – then you can break it.”

“Got it.”

The Death Reaper Curse seemed mysterious, but in the end it was simply an energy-based final killing move. In order to break it all he would need was an even stronger energy.

“A hundred days. I should be able to break through Life Destruction before then. As long as I can successfully cross Life Destruction, undoing this curse seal shouldn’t be a problem.”

During this adventure in the 8000 Mile Black Swamp, Lin Ming had made a significant harvest. With the support of the golden red lightning, he was confident he would be able to cross Life Destruction within a hundred days.

Chapter 831 – Battle

“You really have no concept of death or danger! Do you really think you are invincible as long as you can cross Life Destruction? How ridiculous!” The one who spoke was Situ Haotian’s elder disciple – Situ Bai.

Situ Bai was not a genuine martial artist of the Situ Family Clan, but was a top talent adopted as a child and bestowed the last name Situ while also being received as Situ Haotian’s elder disciple. His Destiny Decree ranking was even higher than the Great Demon Envoy’s.

“I don’t need anyone else. After you reach Life Destruction, I, Situ Bai, will be more than enough to handle you!”

“Good. Then I’ll wait for you.” Lin Ming fervently said.

“Brother Hao, don’t be so hasty!” The Great Demon Envoy hurriedly said with a true essence sound transmission. Situ Bai didn’t understand Lin Ming, but the Great Demon Envoy did. He had suffered a great loss under Lin Ming and was well aware of the fate of those that underestimated him.

Situ Bai wanted to speak further, but at this time Situ Haotian coldly shouted, “Step back!”

“Master…”

“I said step back!”

“Yes…” Even if Situ Bai appeared unwilling to accept this, he could only withdraw.

Situ Haotian stepped forwards, his eyes shining as he stared at Lin Ming. “You want to challenge all of the Life Destruction powerhouses of my Asura Divine Kingdom by yourself?”

“Yes!” Lin Ming decisively replied as he faced Situ Haotian’s pressure.

“Little Brother Lin, you…” Shibai was bewildered. Lin Ming was simply too wild in his actions. How could a first stage Life Destruction martial artist challenge all of the Destiny Decree masters that were under the Asura Divine Kingdom?

Lin Ming took a deep breath. He said with a true essence sound transmission, “Patriarch Shibai, I thank you for all that you’ve done for me, but I cannot allow the Forsaken God Clan to withstand all of the enmity aimed at me. The consequences are too serious!”

As Shibai recognized the strong sense of conviction in Lin Ming’s voice, he said, “Do you really believe in yourself? Do you understand the top masters of the Asura Divine Kingdom?”

“I only understand a small part.” Lin Ming truthfully said. He had naturally looked over and remembered the Destiny Decree himself and understood the Life Destruction powerhouses on there that were subordinate to the Asura Divine Kingdom. But, the Destiny Decree was by no means an omniscient list. Lin Ming was sure that there were some Destiny Decree level masters that were hidden away deep within the Asura Divine Kingdom that no one was aware of.

To make this crazy promise, Lin Ming also had to take an enormous risk!

But he had to do so. In this swords drawn atmosphere, if Situ Haotian was pressured, how could Lin Ming not be pressured?

This was a gamble he made with his life on the line. The sword was already drawn but no one was willing to make concessions. If all this resulted in a stalemate, then the likely end of this would be… total war!

This was a war between two superpowers. Once they fought there would inevitably be a great loss of life as rivers of blood flowed through the land. Neither Situ Haotian, Shibai, nor Lin Ming could afford such a loss.

Taking a step back, they could avoid a total war that Divine Sea powerhouses would participate in, and instead limit it to the stage of Life Destruction level martial artists. This was a solution built from compromise.

Situ Haotian held his hands behind himself. His eyes narrowed a bit, but his vision seemed even sharper than before, as if he could see through Lin Ming!

He didn’t immediately agree to this challenge, nor did he refuse it. In his mind, he was rapidly analyzing just how strong Lin Ming was.

A hundred days ago, Lin Ming had been evaluated at rank 280 on the Destiny Decree. At the time, Lin Ming’s cultivation was at the peak of the late Revolving Core realm. Now, his cultivation hadn’t risen, so it was impossible for him to have made a substantial breakthrough in his strength.

Even if he was a heaven-gifted talent and had also obtained a number of hidden cards in these last 100 days, his strength still shouldn’t surpass rank 250-260 on the Destiny Decree. This in itself was already an extremely high evaluation.

A ranked 250-260 Destiny Decree master wasn’t much at all. The Destiny Decree had several great levels within its rankings. 200, 100, 50, 30, 10, all of these were completely different stages. Even if Lin Ming were to cross the great boundary of Life Destruction and his strength were to soar astronomically, he still shouldn’t rise too much.

However… Lin Ming was a monster amongst monstrous talents. He was not someone that could be judged by common sense.

The truth was that it wasn’t just Situ Haotian that couldn’t estimate Lin Ming’s strength, but even Lin Ming couldn’t understand his own strength. Demonshine also hadn’t been able to give any worthwhile advice. After all, a dual body and law cultivator like Lin Ming was extremely rare to begin with. If he were to use the power of thunder to cross Life Destruction, then in addition to his battle spirit, Heretical God Force, and all sorts of skills that were unique and great even in the Realm of the Gods, all of these factors made it so that his power levels were thrown into confusion. To estimate Lin Ming’s strength after Life Destruction and arrange him on the Destiny Decree, this was simply an impossible matter.

Moreover, Lin Ming didn’t know whether or not the Asura Divine Kingdom had any hidden super masters.

This fight was truly a gamble!

“You want to use this battle to resolve the war that could erupt between two Holy Lands?” Situ Haotian said with a coldly indifferent tone.

“That’s right! How about it? Is such a great Divine Kingdom actually unable to fight a young junior like myself?” Lin Ming was tranquil as he faced Situ Haotian’s dreadful aura.

And in this calm, Situ Haotian was able to sense the mockery behind Lin Ming’s words. This was simply despising him, and despising his Asura Divine Kingdom!

At the age of the Asura Divine Emperor, it was naturally impossible for him to be goaded into action by words. But currently, he had to admit that Lin Ming’s proposal was truly a well thought out compromise. Otherwise, even if he did stir up the other great Divine Kingdoms to join forces and attack the Forsaken God Clan with him, these so-called ‘allies’ would still demand a sky high price for showing up. Added to all the losses they would suffer in the war, the gains just weren’t worth the losses.

As the Asura Divine Emperor thought of this, he brought his hands in front of him. A faintly chilling killing intent exuded from his body. “Is this a life or death battle?”

These words meant that Situ Haotian had already agreed to this battle.

“Yes! Those martial artists that can enter the stage are limited to the Life Destruction martial artists of your Asura Divine Kingdom!”

“Good. Then it shall be as you say!” The Asura Divine Emperor agreed. Although this type of revolving battle of attrition wasn’t honorable, he wouldn’t send out invitations for heroes to challenge Lin Ming.

This battle concerned the national destiny of the entire Asura Divine Kingdom! Winning meant to recover the complete inheritance of the Demon Emperor. Losing meant that they would help establish a great enemy with limitless potential for the Asura Divine Kingdom. The difference in these results was massive!

Lin Ming took a deep breath and clenched his fists, his eyes shining as he stared at the Asura Divine Emperor. He had really agreed!

Lin Ming didn’t know whether he could win or what his true strength would be like after crossing Life Destruction. This gamble was filled with unknown risks. Even so, Lin Ming could feel his blood boiling over with fighting spirit, seething with excitement. He wanted this battle! He wanted a battle where he could slaughter his enemies and see their warm blood hit the floor!

Agreeing to this sort of gamble was mainly to reduce the pressure on the Forsaken God Clan. But at the same time, it was also because he wanted to use this pressure to force himself past his limits!

Lin Ming looked at the Asura Divine Emperor and said, “Since this is a life or death battle… my chips are all the inheritances on my body as well as the Demon Emperor Armor. And what about you? What stake are you placing in this bet?”

This was originally an unfair battle to begin with. Lin Ming would face countless enemies alone and losing meant he would be at the Asura Divine Kingdom’s mercy. But even if he won, there wouldn’t be any benefits for him. Lin Ming naturally wouldn’t agree to this sort of matter.

“What do you want?”

The Asura Divine Emperor wasn’t surprised. His tone of voice became increasingly calm, making others unable to guess just what he was thinking at this time.

Lin Ming pondered for a moment. He first thought of the Demon God Heartguard Mirror. As long as he could obtain it then he could complete the Demon Emperor Armor. It would become a treasure that was in no way inferior to the Cosmic Melting Furnace.

However, Lin Ming quickly decided against this.

The complete Demon Emperor Armor wouldn’t increase Lin Ming’s strength too much. It was only armor after all; it wouldn’t be good for him to rely on it too much. If so, then it would be better for him to demand heavenly materials that could increase his cultivation.

Moreover, the most important point was that the Demon God Heartguard Mirror was the honor and pride of the Asura Divine Kingdom. If was the symbol that they were the true successors to the Demon Emperor’s legacy. If the Asura Divine Kingdom were to lose such a thing, then they would become the absolute laughing stock of the entire martial world.

The Asura Divine Kingdom had announced that Lin Lanjian’s ancestors had stolen their inheritance along with the Demon Emperor Armor, causing a massive manhunt to capture him. And, if the result was that not only did they not recapture their inheritance, but they even lost the Demon God Heartguard Mirror, then wouldn’t they become the biggest joke in the world?

At that time, the Asura Divine Emperor might go mad with rage and disregard all shame to abandon his promise in front of everyone, instead choosing to suffer the losses and wage war with the Forsaken God Clan. This would not be a good result.

As Lin Ming thought of this, he came to a decision. He recorded everything he wanted onto a jade slip.

“10 jin of million year wood spirit jade, 10,000 Year Peach Pith, Dawnmist Flower, Frostfly Stone, Aldertree Spirit Water…”

Lin Ming recorded down 15 different types of materials. These past years, Lin Ming had been thoroughly studying alchemy in detail as well as researching the native plants of the Sky Spill Continent. All of these materials he listed could be found on the Sky Spill Continent but were extremely rare and precious.

With these materials he would be able to refine two miracle pills.

The first pill was a Bluedrop Heartmelting Pill. It would greatly reduce the time it would take to go from the first stage of Life Destruction to the second stage of Life Destruction.

The second pill was a Violet Electricity Heaven Ice Pill. It would be helpful in opening the fourth of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates. As for completely opening the fourth of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates, it was still lacking some. The body transformation path was simply far too costly in terms of resources. Even in the Realm of the Gods, wishing to collect all of the necessary materials was neither cheap nor easy.

Shua!

A white light flashed and the jade slip flew into the Asura Divine Emperor’s hand.

As the Asura Divine Emperor looked over the items Lin Ming wanted, he nearly crushed the jade slip in his hands!

He thought that Lin Ming would want the Demon God Heartguard Mirror, but he never expected that Lin Ming would choose heavenly materials instead. These things were more precious than the last! If all of them were added together, it would require seven to eight million spirit essence stones!

Moreover, many of these materials couldn’t be bought. Searching for them would also consume a massive amount of resources. The total value might be no less than 10 million spirit essence stones!

This Lin Ming was simply a greedy lion opening his jaws wide!

But in all fairness, if this were compared to losing the Demon God Heartguard Mirror, he would rather choose Lin Ming’s demand instead. He looked at Lin Ming and grit his teeth, “You are quite smart. You know to avoid touching this Emperor’s reverse scale while aiming for the greatest benefit for yourself. Good! I agree then!”

As Situ Haotian finished speaking, he suddenly turned to leave. The other martial artists of the Asura Divine Kingdom hurried to keep up with him. In this tense atmosphere, all of them were aware of just how on the edge Situ Haotian was.

With his strength and power, today he had actually been forced by the Forsaken God Clan and a mere late Revolving Core boy to agree to a battle that he didn’t want to agree to. Everyone could imagine just how volatile his mood was at this time!

As he was walking out of the Forsaken God Clan’s Realmheart Great Hall, Situ Haotian suddenly stopped. He swiveled around and coldly looked at everyone behind him.

“All of you are required to participate in this battle. Victory means endless rewards! Defeat means death!”

Chapter 832 – The Coming Storm, The Rising Tide

“Little Brother Lin, you were too impulsive!” Shibai helplessly said to Lin Ming after the martial artists from the Asura Divine Kingdom left. But even though he said this, he knew that the Forsaken God Clan by themselves were unable to shield Lin Ming from the wrath of the Asura Divine Kingdom. The Forsaken God Clan would need to have at least half the strength of the Seven Star Divine Kingdom before they and the Asura Divine Kingdom could tear into each other.

Lin Ming also didn’t know just what his chances of victory were. He looked at Shibai and said, “As far as I know, the Asura Divine Kingdom doesn’t have many top 20 ranked Destiny Decree masters, right?”

“Yes.” Shibai nodded, “But that is only on the surface. No one knows exactly what the truth is. Being in the top 20 of the Destiny Decree means you have an extremely high chance of reaching the Divine Sea! A top 20 Destiny Decree master might possibly become a future Divine Sea Supreme Elder, bringing their Divine Kingdom a massive increase in their national war strength. If the status of this type of person were to be exposed, then it is possible that they would meet all sorts of hostile plots and traps while out adventuring for their own lucky chances. They might even be killed by assassins sent from the Divine Kingdoms. Because of this, only the high level figures of the Asura Divine Kingdom would know just how many top Life Destruction powerhouses they truly have.

“Situ Haotian is a cunning old fox and fastidious in his nature. He is a lion that will use his full strength to capture even a rabbit. Don’t think that he’s afraid because he reluctantly agreed to your gamble. The truth is that he would never do that unless he had grasped an over 90% chance of winning. He would rarely gamble on anything, much less a fight so important to the Asura Divine Kingdom! The Asura Divine Kingdom’s background might be beyond your imagination. But Situ Haotian will not reveal this. He will wait until the point that his enemy shows their weakness and reveals all of their hidden cards before he finally strikes out with lightning speed and defeats his opponent!”

“I understand…” Lin Ming gripped his fists. He could already foresee how difficult this battle would be. The only reason that Situ Haotian had been so reluctant in agreeing was because regardless of whether it was victory or defeat, both endings would result in exposing some of the Asura Divine Kingdom’s hidden powerhouses. All of these powerhouses were of enormous value to the Asura Divine Kingdom. It would be difficult to withstand the loss if any of them died!

“You can cross Life Destruction in peace. My Forsaken God Clan will lend you a helping hand. Also, I’ve noticed that you have a wound in your spiritual sea that hasn’t recovered yet. My Forsaken God Clan has a master skilled in curing wounds to the soul.

The Forsaken God Clan were a people that countless talents had come from. Their clansmen had a bloodline seal – the Support Sphere, that could form a force field in a certain area and use this force field to enhance a martial artist’s strength. This included endurance, recovery ability, speed, defense, and striking power. It was even possible to increase the power of one’s will, soul force, perception, and so on.

As Lin Ming thought of this Support Sphere, he remembered Jue. “Patriarch Shibai, I have a matter to speak to you about.”

“Mm?” Shibai turned around.

Lin Ming recounted Jue’s story to Shibai. As Shibai listened to this he was startled. He obviously knew of a fellow clansman named Jue, but he didn’t know that she had been kidnapped.

As Lin Ming saw Shibai’s response, he had some questions that he couldn’t help but ask, “Patriarch Shibai, I don’t understand why the Forsaken God Clan hides away in this world. Moreover, since your Forsaken God Clan’s background far surpasses the majority of the Sky Spill Continent’s Holy Lands, how come the Northwest Great Desert would still dare to kidnap Jue? Don’t they fear that this matter would be discovered by you and that you would take revenge against them?”

Shibai bitterly sighed upon hearing Lin Ming’s question. He said, “It’s not that we want to hide in this world, but that we find it difficult to leave…”

“Mm?”

“Our Forsaken God Clan has to bear a bloodline curse. In this dimensional realm, there are array formations that have been laid down by our people throughout the generations, capable of weakening the power of the curse. But, these array formations do not exist outside. For our clansmen, the higher their cultivation is, the stronger the curse’s effects are on them. Only Xiantian realm martial artists and below can leave. As for Revolving Core and above, it is simply far too dangerous for them. They can at most leave for a few days before having to return.”

“The exception is if you are like Ancestor Emperor Argent, a super powerhouse with a formidable will and a body tempered through lightning. They would be able to rely on their own powerful strength and resist the curse outside! This is also the reason why the notes he left behind are so precious to my clan.”

“So it’s like that…” Lin Ming realized. No wonder the Forsaken God Clan hid in their own world and the other powers didn’t seem to fear them either. It was because they had no way to leave this dimensional realm.

………….

Three days later, Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom, West Imperial City, at the headquarters of Destiny Grasp…

“I want three different articles of news related to the movements of the four Divine Kingdoms…” A martial artist wearing a bamboo hat put a bag of spirit essence stones on the counter of Destiny Grasp.

A middle-aged man behind the counter lazily passed the bamboo hat man three cards.

As the man flipped through them, he was dazed as he read through the second card.

“The 280th Destiny Decree ranked Lin Lanjian has closed up to attack Life Destruction, and will challenge all Life Destruction masters of the Asura Divine Kingdom?”

This was shocking news!

The Forsaken God Clan, Lin Lanjian, crossing Life Destruction!

Lin Lanjian was known as the highest eternally rare talent underneath the heavens. With his late Revolving Core cultivation he had managed to rank on the Destiny Decree. If he were to cross Life Destruction, just what level would his combat strength rise to?

The bamboo hat man sucked in a deep breath. “I can’t miss an awesome event like this!”

This news quickly passed through every information channel. At the start it was a secret, then it became ordinary news, and finally it became common knowledge known by almost everyone!

The battle would take place in three months. Three months from now, regardless of whether Lin Lanjian could break through Life Destruction, the fight would begin. Moreover, this was a cutthroat life or death struggle!

“Lin Lanjian has finally declared war on the Asura Divine Kingdom! He was being hunted all this time, but now he has actually launched a counterattack!”

“I think this is a bit strange. Why would the Asura Divine Kingdom agree to Lin Lanjian’s demands? With their ability, couldn’t they just directly kill Lin Lanjian?”

Destiny Grasp’s information didn’t mention the Forsaken God Clan protecting Lin Ming. This caused many martial artists to be puzzled.

“There have to be reasons we’re not aware of. But don’t you think it’s impossible for Lin Lanjian to win this battle? Such an unfair match, could it have been suggested by the Asura Divine Kingdom? Lin Lanjian must have been forced to agree. Even though there’s no hope, he wouldn’t give up. Think about it. Even though he is known as the number one extraordinary talent of the Sky Spill Continent, the Asura Divine Kingdom’s background is still too deep. There wasn’t a limit of opponents placed on this match. Even though Lin Lanjian is strong, it’s impossible for him to fight a continuous battle of attrition!”

“Indeed. How could anyone win if there’s no limit to the number of opponents?”

The uproar became increasingly loud, like a coming storm, a rising tide. Not only did the four Divine Kingdoms hear of this, but even the surrounding Holy Lands, sects, and smaller countries also heard this news.

The number one rare talent of the Sky Spill Continent had challenged all the Life Destruction masters of the Asura Divine Kingdom. This grand event captured the attention of the entire continent.

Many martial artists crossed the hundreds of thousands of miles to come to the dimensional realm where the Forsaken God Clan lived. And at this time, the normally closed off Forsaken God Clan had opened their doors wide to the world, allowing all martial artists who came to enter. In Shibai’s mind, this battle naturally needed as many witnesses as possible and needed to be known of throughout the entire continent.

Otherwise, even if Lin Ming won, the stronger Asura Divine Kingdom might renege on their promises.

Chapter 837 – Golden Lighting Piercing the Sky

More people arrived throughout the day, none of them leaving. Underneath so many expectations, the pall of night finally fell…

The night was destined to no longer be calm. The atmosphere of the entire dimensional realm was extremely contained. All around the Elders Palace there were many heroes grouped, but very few of them were actually making a noise. One could even hear the gentle night wind whistling in the air.

The Elders Palace was still peaceful as before. Besides the occasional true essence vortex in the sky, there was no difference.

A metal spirit boat cut through the sky. On the side of this spirit boat was carved a long sword; this was the symbol of the Sublime Smelting Divine Kingdom.

A young man and woman in their twenties stood on the spirit boat, both of them looking down at the world with a extraordinary heroic spirit.

“That is the twin prince and princess of the Sublime Smelting Divine Kingdom, Ouye Qingfeng and Ouye Qingyun!”

“This is truly an event that has captivated the world. Ouye Qingfeng and Ouye Qingyun are both astounding characters in the Sublime Smelting Divine Kingdom. For just Lin Lanjian crossing Life Destruction, over 20 Princes have already arrived!”

Besides Yang Yun, who had arrived earlier, all of the other Princes had come at night, staying high in the skies where the other famed Elders of the large sects were. Although there was plenty of room in the skies, the common martial artists simply didn’t dare to stand side by side with these people. The pressure was simply too great.

“There are so many people watching! If Lin Lanjian fails to cross Life Destruction then that would truly be a joke!” No one had thought that an eternally unrivalled talent like Lin Ming would have any problems crossing Life Destruction. But someone had heard about the matter of the God Transforming Pills and had made a number of reasonable speculations from that. From that point on, some people began to suspect that Lin Ming wouldn’t be able to successfully cross Life Destruction.

“I also feel that Lin Lanjian is in a bit of a dangerous situation. If he tries to forcefully break through even though his cultivation isn’t sufficient, then his body might be obliterated and he would die.”

“Don’t be an idiot. Lin Lanjian is known as the number one eternally rare talent of the Sky Spill Continent. If he really perished while trying to break through the first stage of Life Destruction then that would just be too ridiculous. But after breaking through Life Destruction, his foundation might be unstable. Using the God Transforming Pills to forcefully enhance himself will definitely leave behind side effects.”

When a top talent crossed Life Destruction in a perfect manner, they simply wouldn’t need to use medicines. Those who needed to borrow the power of these medicines to cross Life Destruction were normally ordinary powerhouses, such as Xuan Wuji when he was crossing the fourth stage of Life Destruction.

As some of the martial artists were whispering to each other, a 10,000 foot beam of divine light suddenly shot out from the Elders Palace. It was like a keen sword that split the skies, causing the stars themselves to lose their luster.

An incomparable blood vitality lingered in the skies above the Elders Palace, merging with the 10,000 foot beam of golden light. Its brilliance was eye-catching and everyone who saw it was shocked. Could a mortal’s blood vitality truly be rich to such a degree?

Bang! Bang! Bang!

A faint rumbling sound came out from the Elders palace. It was a low and bass sound, deep enough to shake the earth. Deep within the Elders Palace, it was like a True Dragon was slowly waking up from a long sleep…

“That is…”

“He’s finally shattered his mortal form. Is he about to create his spirit body?”

“What a terrifying aura… who said that his cultivation was lacking and he needed three God Transforming Pills to forcefully cross Life Destruction? Could someone with an insufficient cultivation really have such an aura, as if the Laws of the world are being affected?”

……

Deep within the Elders Palace, Shibai and the two Great Elders were dripping with sweat, their concentration completely focused. Lin Ming had finished the sea serpent crystals and now the green heaven-step Demon God Bone was grasped in his hands.

At this time, all of Lin Ming’s meridians were bulging like balloons, the blood vessels sticking out from all over his body. His entire body was filled to the limit; he could detonate at any time!

Even though Lin Ming had entered into the ethereal martial intent state, he could still feel an unbelievably agonizing pain from the energy tearing through his body.

This still wasn’t enough!

Lin Ming grit his teeth and crumbled the heaven-step Demon God Bone in his hands!

A vast energy erupted, stirring up a storm of true essence within the seclusion chamber!

In such a terrifying storm of energy, the pressure within Lin Ming’s dantian could be imagined. The first Revolving Core had already reached its limits, unable to change any more. Only the second Revolving Core could change. From the size of a walnut it compressed to the size of a quail egg and then the size of a fingertip before finally compressing to the size of a little yellow bean.

The second Revolving Core became increasingly deep in color until it appeared inky black. The amount of energy compressed energy within it was not much worse than the Black Hole Revolving Core’s!

Lin Ming wasn’t able to control the second Revolving Core very well, thus he couldn’t compress it himself. But by relying on external forces, it had been forcefully squeezed into an existence near to that of a Black Hole Revolving Core.

At this moment, Lin Ming controlled his first Black Hole Revolving Core and forced it to smash into the second Revolving Core!

Bang!

In that split second, Lin Ming’s dantian finally exploded!

He vomited a mouthful of blood. Near his dantian, all of his meridians began to rupture and blood rained out into the air, turning into a fog of blood within the incomparably pure sea of heaven and earth origin energy!

Lin Ming’s body finally began to crack. But detonating his dantian was still not enough to completely disintegrate his tough physical form. It blew up large chunks of flesh and blood, but was still unable to thoroughly decompose his body.

With a decisive thought, Lin Ming then discharged the highly compressed golden red lightning within the Heretical God Sprout!

In a flash, a golden sun seemed to rise within the seclusion chamber.

Shibai’s eyes flashed with a sharp light. Before this, Lin Ming had already informed him that there was a power of thunder within him capable of turning even a Divine Sea Supreme Elder into ash. Once it detonated, everything around him and within the great array formation would be burnt to ash!

“We’re withdrawing!”

Shibai stretched out his hands to grab the two Great Elders, revolving his movement technique to the limit and then stormed away!

Kacha!

A golden divine thunder broke through the dome of the Elders Palace, directly impacting into the night sky. The deep night sky was lit up bright by this divine thunder as if it were morning. As everyone turned to look at this lightning, they felt a stabbing pain in their eyes as if they were turning blind!

This was truly a world shocking scene. The countless arcs of divine thunder in the air were like peerless immortal soldiers of a divine god. They blazed with an incandescent light, leaving a reflection in the eyes that turned into an eternal phantom, making it so that one would never forget!

“Is this really crossing Life Destruction!?”

“What a terrifying power of thunder, even though it’s so far away it can still make me shiver with fear!”

All of the surrounding martial artists stared at the shining golden thunder in the sky with blank eyes, as if they were watching something from a dream. This fantastical and incredible power that could change even the heavens and earth, perhaps this wouldn’t even appear if someone else were to break through to the Divine Sea!

Ka ka ka ka!

Not too far away, a great palace shook and then began to collapse, raising a storm of dust!

The palaces of the Forsaken God Clan naturally had array formations supporting their internal structures. Even so, they were still being shattered by this terrifying energy!

Yang Yun stood high above his divine carriage, looking on from a far distance, an unspeakable expression on his face. He gently traced his spatial ring and spoke to himself, “A new golden era is coming…”

The seclusion chamber had already turned into a sea of golden energy, with thunder manically howling within. Submerged in this sea of energy, Lin Ming’s body constantly exploded, again and again and again!

From fist-sized lumps of flesh to egg-sized lumps of flesh and then to bean-sized lumps of flesh… they constantly decomposed, until they were as small as dust!

If it were other martial artists, even dual body and law geniuses from the Realm of the Gods, then without their bodies being tempered by thunder and without the Heretical God Sprout to control this power of thunder, if they were to be submerged in this sea of brutal and overbearing energy then they would be turned into nothing but ash, instead of decomposing to their tiniest units like Lin Ming.

Bang bang bang!

The thunder did not end; instead, it became increasingly fierce. It was like the Nine Heavens Thunder Dominion of the Sea of Miracles had reappeared within the Forsaken God Clan’s dimensional realm.

Within the highest level of the Asura Divine Kingdom’s tower, Situ Yaoyue was watching all of this from a distance. Her lips curved up, revealing beautiful white teeth.

“I never imagined that Lin Lanjian could contain such a terrifying power of thunder within his body…”

Situ Yaoyue muttered to herself. Her limpid eyes flashed with a clear fighting spirit, her mind undeterred by the phenomenon occurring in the skies.

She had trained since childhood and had bitterly cultivated all this time. She had been through countless dangerous situations, and had even broken through to the seventh stage of Life Destruction. Now, facing a mere first stage Life Destruction martial artist, it was impossible for her to say that she didn’t feel some contempt for him. After all, Lin Lanjian was a genius, but wasn’t she a genius too?

Yet now she finally began to find the meaning in all this. At least this wouldn’t be a senseless fight that bored her.

“Lin Lanjian has the life of an Emperor. He has most likely inherited some unrivalled lucky chance. Yaoyue, if you can kill him, everything he has will be yours. In the future you might even become the highest under the heavens!” Situ Haotian’s voice suddenly resounded in her ears.

The highest under the heavens was the title used to describe an unrivalled, undefeatable Divine Sea powerhouse. Ever since Emperor Shakya broke through his martial path and ascended, no one else had filled that position. These years, there were some extraordinary powerhouses that had come close to being the highest under the heavens, but they did not far surpass all martial artists of the world. They could only be called one of the top powerhouses of the Sky Spill Continent. For instance, the Highest Divine Emperor of the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom, the Imperial Grand Uncle of the Sublime Smelting Divine Kingdom, or even the Netherworld Great Emperor from 3000 years ago that had died in the South Sea.

Although Situ Yaoyue was talented, she was far from becoming the highest under the heavens. Her only chance was if she could cross the eighth stage of Life Destruction. However, the eighth stage of Life Destruction was not simple to cross at all. Looking over the last 100,000 years of history in the Sky Spill Continent, the number of Divine Emperors that had crossed eight stages of Life Destruction could be counted on a single hand.

“The highest under the heavens?” Yaoyue’s slender eyes narrowed, her vision becoming increasingly firm. She gripped her fists, “I will!”

…………..

With the raging destruction of energy, even the Sky Lock Array began to tremble. Two God Transforming Pills, a heaven-step Demon God Bone, a top quality spirit essence stone, all of their energy was released into the raging sea around Lin Ming. And as Lin Ming’s body was submerged in this sea of energy, it decomposed into its most basic tiny units, fully absorbing the surrounding energy and undergoing a most fundamental change.

The essence of Life Destruction was to use energy to transform the body and then reform into a spirit body that could hold true essence throughout.

And during this process of transformation, not only did Lin Ming undergo a baptism of energy, but he was also being tempered by thunder!

Every cell within Lin Ming’s body twinkled with the glory of thunder. Under the control of the Heretical God Sprout, the power of thunder penetrated deep into every single cell.

Thunder was the power of destruction but also the power of life. When a vicious beast underwent their tribulation, their body would be tempered by thunder, making their physical form even more formidable. And now, Lin Ming was undergoing a similar transformation, having equally wonderful results from different methods!

Chapter 849 – Without Equal

Hu – !

Five Poison King quickly laid down his array. In the blink of an eye, a purple fog emerged from the ground and completely enveloped him. This purple fog was Five Poison King’s special defensive array formation that contained his particular poisonous true essence. If a martial artist broke through this array formation, then even if they had bodily protective true essence, as long as they were touched by this purple fog then the poison would sneak into their body and injure them.

“You also don’t seem afraid of death?”

Lin Ming walked forwards, one step at a time.

Five Poison King quickly laid down a second array formation and another layer of purple fog appeared, making the defense even tighter. He said without emotion, “We are already dead. As long as we can wound you, that is enough to bring luck to our descendants.”

“So that’s how it is…”

As his voice fell, a shimmer of cold light suddenly burst out from Lin Ming’s eyes. It looked as if he took a single casual step forwards, but several miles disappeared underneath his feet, making it seem as if he had teleported past the poison arrays. The two poisonous gas array formations that Five Poison King laid down weren’t able to hinder him in the least.

With Lin Ming’s current understanding into the Concept of Space, if an array formation didn’t have the Space Laws integrated into it then it was simply useless in front of him.

Chi chi chi!

Purple thunder poured into his red long spear. The top grade heaven-step Nine Heavens Thunder Soul burst out in all its radiant glory!

Chasing Thunder!

A spear thrust out, quick as lightning, simply not giving Five Poison King the least bit of space to respond.

In that instant, all the poisonous fog was covered by a net of crackling purple lightning. Five Poison King issued a roar and threw out the array disc in his hand. The array disc rapidly spun in the air, ready to explode at any moment. However, Lin Ming’s speed was far too quick. Space distorted and he vanished in in a twinkling light.

A spear thrust through Five Poison King’s body. Sizzling thunder charred his entire body black.

And at this time, Five Poison King’s body blew up without any indication. All sorts of poisonous blood and venom rained down in all directions!

Lin Ming’s pupils shrank as he instantly drew back.

Bang!

Five Poison King blew up with his poison arrays. A terrifyingly potent poison shout out in all directions, causing a large hole to appear even in the array formation-supported mountain,

Lin Ming had already retreated five miles away. His bodily true essence fiercely vibrated with a sizzling sound. This was the sound of his protective true essence colliding with the poison.

“What a strange poison. It can even pollute true essence.”

Lin Ming didn’t have any expression. The silver battle spirit stirred and a spear of will chopped out, instantly extinguishing the poison.

The special characteristic of a battle spirit was that it could be attached to any object and could cut apart all. This included material objects, souls, force fields, energy, heart demons, true essence, and so on.

Defeating Five Poison King in a single move hadn’t exceeded the expectations of the martial artists present.

“He also killed him in a single move, how fierce!”

“But… Lin Lanjian was touched by the poison. I don’t know if this will be a problem for him.”

“Doesn’t look like there’s an issue.”

“I don’t know…”

The poison arts of the demonic path were extremely strange. Sometimes, after being poisoned, it wouldn’t seem as if there was a problem, but the poison would suddenly manifest after a period of time, turning a martial artist’s body into bloody pus.

Of course, to the surrounding martial artists, someone with Lin Ming’s strength certainly wouldn’t be reduced to that sort of situation. However, coming under a slight influence was still likely. This was a revolving battle. As long as these minor influences accumulated they would ultimately become fatal.

“This little beast, even the Five Poison King’s explosion wasn’t able to harm him!”

“Humph! And so what? Every battle will consume some of his strength. I want to see just how long he can last. White Bone King, go out! As long as you can wound him then I will release your family clan from slavery!”

Throughout the centuries, the Asura Divine Kingdom had fought wars in all directions in order to conquer anyone who dared to challenge their authority. And the top powerhouses of these conquered influences would have a slave seal planted within them and then be turned into a slaughter puppet.

White Bone King was one of those powerhouses. His family clan had been a fifth-grade family clan, but the patron of his family clan had been enemies with the Asura Divine Kingdom. Afterwards, their patron collapsed and the White Bone King’s family clan was implicated in the ensuing mess.

White Bone King was tall and broad. He wore an armor of bones, and as he walked the pieces struck and grinded against each other, emitting ‘ka ka ka’ sounds.

Because he had been transformed with all sorts of secret techniques and he also had a slave seal planted in him, White Bone King didn’t have any intelligence in his eyes. But, Situ Bonan’s promise seemed to stir a strange compulsion in his mind, awakening the memories deep within his heart.

“Kill!”

White Bone King bit out this word. With ‘chi chi chi’ sounds, countless bone spurs appeared from all over his body. He rushed towards Lin Ming like a cannonball!

Lin Ming’s eyes flashed with an interested light. The bone armor of this White Bone King in front of him wasn’t forged from the bones of others, but rather came from his own skeleton.

A bone transforming specialist martial artist was really unusual.

However, this was far from being able to make up the absolute disparity in strength.

Bang!

With the sound of a collision, White Bone King’s frontal bone spurs all shattered. In the next moment, the long spear turned around and smashed into White Bone King’s head!

White Bone King’s bone armor burst apart like shattered porcelain. His spine cracked and his neck twisted off. His head flew a thousand feet away, crashing into the floor with both eyeballs burst apart.

Lin Ming’s figure appeared a thousand feet away, a slightly numb feeling in his right hand. These bones were much harder than he had imagined.

This was already the third match. Situ Haotian’s eyes were cold. He vowed to disregard all cost to bring this revolving battle to its ultimate end. “Crimson Blood Demon, your turn!”

Roar!

A red demon covered in blood rushed onto the arena stage. These demonic path martial artists practiced all sorts of evil and dark mystical cultivation methods. Many times it was impossible to tell whether they were a man or ghost.

However, regardless of what shape Lin Ming’s enemy took, the gap in absolute strength could not be surpassed. The Crimson Blood Demon rushed forward in a suicidal manner, wanting to bring Lin Ming down with him. But Lin Ming shot his silver battle spirit-imbued red spear forwards and with the sound of rolling thunder it pierced through the Crimson Blood Demon’s body like an arrow!

The Crimson Blood Demon exploded in a shower of bloody rain. The long spear smashed into the arena ground hundreds of feet away, ripping a large crumbling hole into the array formation-protected arena ground.

The Crimson Blood Demon’s cause of death was nearly the same as Yaksha King’s.

“The fifth match, Nightmare King!”

Situ Bonan’s eyes were red with raging anger. He immediately sent out another master.

Bang!

Nightmare King’s soul illusion attack was directly torn apart by Lin Ming’s battle spirit.

With a whistling sound, Lin Ming’s long spear shot forwards. Nightmare King wanted to dodge it, but the Concept of Space and the Concept of Time within the spear made it unpredictable and unblockable.

Nightmare King forcibly avoided having his heart pierced through, but nearly half of his body was ripped off by the spear.

Nightmare King flew backwards but Lin Ming stepped forwards, crossing through space and instantly appearing in front of him. A fist punched out.

Body Tearing Bone Shattering Fist!

Peng!

The half-torn Nightmare King was simply unable to dodge this sudden attack. He instantly burst into a rain of blood.

After Lin Ming crossed the first stage of Life Destruction, all of the cells in his body were transformed, activated by energy and now able to all breath in unison. The power of Flow like Silk had risen by a great boundary. With a single punch, even a 100 foot tall boulder would be completely smashed into powder.

The fifth match, victory again.

So far, none of the martial artists that entered the arena stage had been Lin Ming’s match!

“Sixth match, Earth Bowing Monster!”

….

“Seventh match, Black Iron Demon!”

…

“Eighth match, Soul Eater!”

…

“Ninth match, Green Hair Corpse Puppet!”

….

Every new match was sounded with a new bell ring. Because the matches were too fast, before the first ring faded away, the next ring already began to sound out.

Back and forth, this vibrant ringing bell sound echoed through the world, shocking everyone’s minds again and again.

This was simply a bloody massacre. No matter what strange demonic path techniques these slaughter puppets used, Lin Ming would finish the fight within three breaths of time.

During this time, it was inevitable that Lin Ming would have frontal collisions with these powerhouses. According to all reasoning, although these collisions might not result in Lin Ming being wounded, they should at least create disorder in his true essence or cause his aura to be unstable. But Lin Ming continued fighting as if he didn’t even know what exhaustion was.

At least it was impossible to tell if there was something wrong with him from his exterior appearance.

11th match…

12th match…

13th match…

…

18th match!!

The Lin Ming on the arena stage had turned vicious and ruthless. At this time, he was like a True Dragon that had awoken from a deep slumber. His powerful body seemed invincible to all attacks. All enemies that appeared before him were torn to pieces, completely swept away without any ability to resist!

All of the surrounding martial artists were bewildered. These martial artists that died under Lin Ming’s hands weren’t some random cabbages. The lowest of them were at the peak fifth stage of Life Destruction, and there were even sixth stage Life Destruction masters. A thousand or two thousand years ago they were characters that ruled the Destiny Decree of their eras. Some of them might have even been ranked in the top 100 of the Destiny Decree!

And these people were chopped apart by Lin Ming as if they were vegetables and then tossed to the side, over and over again. Lin Ming only used several moves, but these moves, no one was able to dodge them!

Every single one of these attacks contained a powerful strength; the consumption of energy shouldn’t be minor. If a general martial artist was strong, they would still find themselves short of breath after using these moves several times. They would have no choice but to supplement themselves with medicines. But, no matter how good these medicines were, the supplemented true essence would have differences with their own true essence. Eating up enough of these pills would cause the energy within their bodies to turn impure, causing their combat strength to plummet.

But Lin Ming hadn’t even taken a single pill yet. And looking at his appearance, he didn’t even have the least bit of disorder in his breath. Was he even human?

20th match…

Bang!

The demonic path slaughter puppet that stepped onstage had his head burst apart by Lin Ming’s spear. Red and white brain mass sprayed onto the ground before immediately being charred by the power of thunder in the air. That demonic path martial artist’s headless corpse plopped to the ground.

There was a cold gasp of air from outside the arena stage. It had come from a slaughter puppet that knew it would only be dying by entering the stage. If he were just a normal person then he wouldn’t have dared to go onstage. Even walking into the jaws of death shouldn’t be done in such a miserable manner.

In fact, even the rest of the slaughter puppets were frightened by Lin Ming. After killing 20 people, Lin Ming’s aura made him seem as if he were a wild vicious beast from ancient times. The accumulated killing intent had formed an invisible energy field around him. Just by approaching him one would feel pressured and find it difficult to breathe.

Even Situ Haotian was a bit deterred and made weak-hearted by Lin Ming’s dominating aura. Every slaughter puppet that he sent onstage was a massive pile of spirit essence stones!

Had the slaughter puppets he sent out even been able to exhaust Lin Ming’s strength?

As he looked at the perfectly calm Lin Ming onstage, Situ Haotian lacked the assurance to continue like this. His eyes turned and his vision locked onto a red-clothed little boy.

“Imperial Scholar Xuan, it’s your turn next.”

“Huh?” The red-clothed little boy’s heart shrank, a cold sweat suddenly streaming down his entire body.

Chapter 852 – Fighting Situ Luosha

The entire arena was already wrecked beyond repair. The sheared mountain top was crisscrossed with fissures that were several miles long and hundreds of feet deep. If it wasn’t for the Asura Divine Kingdom’s array formation supporting the entire area, then this place would have long collapsed into the ground.

Ruined meat, blood, and bits of organs were scattered all over the place. There were some corpses that weren’t even taken away because of how miserable their deaths had been.

The entire arena was filled with the strong acrid smell of blood.

However, the shaft of Lin Ming’s spear was not stained with blood and his clothes didn’t even have the slightest bit of damage. His white clothes were as clean as fresh snow. He fluttered high and proud above the arena, his clothes waving in the wind and his hair flying in the air.

His expression was light and breezy, as if he wasn’t even worried about this life or death battle. With his handsome, jade-like looks and his leisurely manner, he was extraordinary and refined, like an immortal cavalier exiled from the heavens.

Within the seamless heaven and earth, the ethereal and elegant Lin Ming stood high above the bloody arena that resembled an Asura slaughter field. This sharp contrast made one feel as if this scene was unreal, as if all this death before him had nothing to do with him at all.

Time slowly passed. Soon, half an hour had passed and the Asura Divine Kingdom still hadn’t set anyone out to battle.

All of the martial artists were impatiently waiting.

“What’s going on? Is the Asura Divine Kingdom admitting defeat?”

Many martial artists couldn’t help but think this. The Asura Divine Kingdom’s background was truly powerful; in a single breath they had sent out 20 slaughter puppets. No one dared to look down on the Asura Divine Kingdom’s war strength, but now it seemed that Lin Ming was even stronger!

“It’s time. Go to battle…” Situ Haotian nodded at Situ Luosha. Even if he was worried that Situ Luosha would fall here, he still had to send him to fight.

After all, Situ Yaoyue’s life was far more precious than Situ Luosha’s!

“Be careful. If you cannot defeat him then retreat. As long as you are alive then I can protect you.”

Situ Haotian said to Situ Luosha with a true essence sound transmission.

“Your Majesty, rest assured that I shall definitely defeat Lin Lanjian. I will not disappoint your graciousness!” Hearing that Situ Haotian would guarantee his life, Situ Luosha was grateful. But, he would not retreat. This battle was one he had to win.

“We’ve already been waiting half an hour, how interesting. Situ Haotian is delaying time in order to break down Lin Lanjian’s momentum.” On the great jade ship, the White Clan’s Fairy Snow Gale saw Situ Luosha step into the arena and faintly smiled. “This is the same as acknowledging that everything he did before this was in vain. Lin Lanjian’s hidden ability is too great; Situ Haotian has really eaten it this time.”

When a strong opponent fell, it would carve a sense of intention in the victor’s bones, a faith that they would win, creating a sort of invisible energy field that would drive them to victory. This would cause a martial artist to fight even more vigorously. Situ Haotian obviously feared this.

Old Man Good Fortune laughed, “Situ Haotian is so careful, but how useful will it be to waste this time to break down Lin Lanjian’s momentum?”

The accumulated faith that a martial artist gathered in himself would stay for a few days – it certainly wouldn’t be broken in just half an hour. The most that Situ Haotian did was diminish some of the momentum Lin Ming gathered, but he hadn’t broken it.

Under the attention of all, Situ Luosha finally grasped his spear and fell down from the Godspeed Boat. He fell onto the mountain ring, distantly facing Lin Ming.

“It’s Situ Luosha! Situ Luosha is finally fighting!” As the impatient martial artists saw the black-clothed Situ Luosha slowly fly into the arena stage, all of their eyes turned wide as they locked onto him.

“I thought that the Asura Divine Kingdom would still send out some suicide troops to wear down Lin Lanjian some more, but I never imagined they would directly send out Situ Luosha. Does this mean that the Asura Divine Kingdom still has hidden powerhouses it hasn’t used?”

“How could there be so many hidden powerhouses? Ten years ago, Situ Luosha was already ranked in the top 15 of the Destiny Decree. Now his ranking is 12 and no one still knows just how strong he is. I hear he is already nearing the Divine Sea realm. He should already be the Asura Divine Kingdom’s strongest Life Destruction martial artist!”

A battle between top masters could always make one’s blood boil with excitement. Especially this battle between the mysterious peak ranked Destiny Decree masters Situ Luosha and Lin Lanjian. Situ Luosha’s strength was an unknown variable, but so was Lin Ming’s. Those with a discerning eye could see that he had never put his full force forth in any of the previous battles. There were likely many Concept and Laws and martial skills that he hadn’t used.

Unknown against the unknown, this was truly a battle that filled with heart with anticipation. Everyone wanted to know just what the limits of their strength were!

Hualala!

A pair of massive black wings unfolded from behind Situ Luosha, keeping him suspended in the air. It wasn’t strange for a martial artist to have a pair of treasure wings – even Corpsemancer had his own pair. But, Situ Luosha’s pair of wings was different. It was not a treasure that had been refined, but a true part of Situ Luosha’s body.

These were wings of flesh and blood!

Without a doubt, Situ Luosha had the bloodline of another species in his blood. It was probable that this even included a special bloodline seal ability!

“Lin Ming, with my peak sixth stage Life Destruction cultivation, even if I emerge victorious against you, it is not a win for my martial path. But I will not hold back. In this battle I will kill you with everything I have!”

As Situ Luosha spoke, several thousand crimson red Blood Drinking Seals suddenly flew out from his body. Then, a scene that startled Lin Ming occurred. These Blood Drinking Seals completely immersed into Situ Luosha’s black wings. The Blood Drinking Seal tightly pasted themselves onto the feathers, causing the black wings to instantly become red like blood!

“This combat method…” Lin Ming sucked in a breath of cold air. Without a doubt this was a stylistic cultivation method that Situ Luosha had devised from the ‘Great Desolate Halberd Art’. He was the same as Lin Ming, a martial arts grandmaster who was stepping onto the path of creating his own set of martial arts!

No matter how good others’ cultivation methods were, they were still others’; they might not suit someone else. For instance, Situ Luosha. By combining his special bloodline characteristics with the ‘Great Desolate Halberd Art’, he could display an absolutely stronger combat effectiveness.

‘Truly worthy of being one of the Destiny Decree’s peak ranked chosen prides of heaven!’

Although Lin Ming’s current talent far surpassed the standard of the Sky Spill Continent, he still wouldn’t underestimate the powerhouses of this world. This was because they were characters that stood out from a trillion or even hundreds of trillions of lives.

Ding!

A great bell that stood above the sheared off mountain top rang out once again, resounding through the dimensional realm.

The fight had officially started!

Situ Luosha acted first. Without any hesitation he grasped his long spear and turned into a black beam of light that shot forwards. His speed surpassed imagination!

Countless spear shades filled the air, creating a brilliant tapestry that blinded the eyes!

“You want to compare speed?”

Lin Ming’s lips curved up in a smile. What he feared the least was comparing speed. Or, it was more accurate to say that he didn’t fear comparing in any aspect. Whether it was physical strength, endurance, will, or anything else, it was enough to make his opponents vomit blood in frustration.

Without opening the Gate of Wonder, Lin Ming only used ‘Golden Roc Shattering the Void’ to create a series of phantom shadows in the air. The red spear in his hands wove through the universe, completely meeting all of Situ Luosha’s spear shades together.

Peng peng peng peng!

Like a crashing wave on a breaking shore, the entire mountain arena reinforced by the Asura Divine Kingdom’s array formation began to violently tremble. Spear wind savagely hewed off massive chunks of stone before crushing them into powder. Clouds of broken rocks and dust began to rush into the clear skies!

A black and red energy were like two flood dragons violently clashing in the desert, twisting around and staring down at the world with contempt!

“What speed, I can’t even see clearly!”

All of the heroic young elites present had already retreated 10 miles out. With their sight, watching this battle from 10 miles away was no problem at all. However, they simply couldn’t make out Lin Ming and Situ Luosha’s movements; their speed was just too fast.

It wasn’t just them, but even the famed Elders of the various sects were blind as to what was happening. All they saw was a storm of black and red light weaving together in the skies. But as for the exact happenings, none of them were able to distinguish anything in that battle of extreme speed.

“It seems like… they are evenly matched?” An Elder from a fifth-grade sect said with uncertainty.

“Maybe…” Another fifth-grade sect’s Highest Elder echoed. He was also a Destiny Decree master and yet he wasn’t able to see just who had the upper hand so far. This was truly a disgraceful matter for him.

Peng!

Situ Luosha’s two wings spread out. His blood red wings seemed as if they were carved from pure ruby. After the Blood Drinking Seals were fused into them they had become incomparably sharp, able to cut down several spear lights by themselves.

A faint red light shot across the skies like a rainbow. Six blood red feathers quietly separated from behind Situ Luosha, circling around Lin Ming and aiming at his limbs, back, and head, before shooting out together!

Meanwhile, Situ Luosha stabbed his spear at Lin Ming’s dantian.

“He’s fast!”

An excited light flashed through Lin Ming’s pupils. If he didn’t open the Gate of Wonder then just by using ‘Golden Roc Shattering the Void’, his movements were even slightly slower than Situ Luosha’s. This was already enough to startle Lin Ming. It seemed as if Situ Luosha’s special bloodline ability was also connected with extremely fast movement.

Bang!

A red long spear swept out, drawing a full moon completely around him. The blazing spear light completely blocked all of Situ Luosha’s attacks.

Kacha!

The two collided for the first time. A fierce storm of true essence suddenly stirred up, causing raging true essence to fill the air. The array formation that held together the mountain seemed unable to bear this, and a crack several hundred miles long appeared within it!

To Lin Ming and Situ Luosha, this arena was only a boundary. The true battlefield was in the sky!

Bang bang bang!

Thunder flashed, space trembled. Lin Ming took his dantian as the center and released a dazzling purple light. This was the glory of thunder!

Wild and stormy thunder condensed, forming substantialized purple scales all over Lin Ming’s body. Section by section, they covered his entire body. Arcs of electricity flashed from these scales formed from the power of thunder, deeply piercing into Lin Ming’s acupoints, connecting him to the tyrannical power of thunder around him.

The power of life – Thunder Battleform.

This was one of the most famed techniques of the Eightfall Thunder Emperor. Using thunder as the power of life and changing the body, stimulating it to produce a greater strength. This was a type of supportive martial skill. In order to use it, one had to have a thorough understanding of the Laws that formed its foundation. Otherwise, recklessly using this technique would not stimulate their life potential but would instead damage their organs and meridians.

As the martial artists present saw Lin Ming’s entire body began to be covered with purple scales, they didn’t sense anything unusual. But the several Divine Sea powerhouses, especially the Forsaken God Clan’s Elders and Patriarch Shibai, were actually dumbfounded!

This was really the Thunder Battleform!

This was a unique skill that the Eightfall Thunder Emperor had once relied on to walk the world unrivalled. Although the complete jade slip inheritance had been left in the Forsaken God Clan, no one had been able to successfully practice it!

Chapter 854 – Admitting Defeat

On the sheared and shattered mountain peak, Situ Luosha knelt on the ground. His entire body was covered in blood and he was barely supporting himself with his black long spear. He looked up, his stubborn eyes locked onto Lin Ming.

Even though he had been severely wounded, his eyes were still burning with a brilliant and fiery fighting spirit, unwilling to concede.

Or perhaps it was because conceding was also insignificant. Because… this was a life or death struggle!

Lin Ming waved his long spear and pointed the top towards Situ Luosha’s forehead. Although he had a decent impression of this Situ Luosha and they had no previous enmity, in this life or death battle, Lin Ming had no intention of showing empathy or compassion to his enemies.

As a martial artist of the Asura Divine Kingdom, Situ Luosha was already destined to be his enemy. To show benevolence to the enemy was to be cruel to himself. If Situ Luosha had won this fight, then Lin Ming’s fate would have been to suffer a life worse than death.

Spear light surged. A faint trace of pale gold thunder sizzled on Lin Ming’s spearpoint.

Situ Luosha also stood up. Behind him, over 30% of the thousands of Blood Drinking Seals broke apart, covering his entire body in a blood fog once again.

This was likely to be their last clash. But, the victor of this match was already clear at a glance!

“Situ Luosha will certainly lose.”

“No kidding! The disparity is too great!”

At this point, even a Xiantian realm martial could see where the direction of this battle was leading. Lin Ming obviously had a great deal of strength left over but Situ Luosha was now spent, a bow with no more arrows. With these two completely inverse conditions, the gap was obvious.

“Stop!”

As Situ Luosha was preparing to burn his Ancient Profound Hawk blood essence and risk his life once more, Situ Haotian’s cold voice suddenly shouted out.

This shout was like billowing thunder. Some of the martial artists flying in the air were nearly knocked unconscious from the shock.

“We admit defeat in this match! Luosha, withdraw!” With a distortion of black light, the black-robed Situ Haotian appeared in the skies above the battlefield. His calm and indifferent pupils overlooked the fierce battle between Lin Ming and Situ Luosha without any emotion at all.

But from his eyes, one could sense an indescribable dignity, as if the words he spoke were the commands of heaven.

However, Lin Ming didn’t feel the slightest bit of pressure in front of these eyes with their inviolable majesty. Instead, his mouth curved in a satire-filled smirk. “Withdraw? This is a life or death struggle! For every two people on this arena stage, only one is allowed to leave alive. Now that Situ Luosha has lost he can withdraw, but if I were to lose, then I should let you do with me as you please? What sort of reasoning is this!?”

Facing Situ Haotian’s pressure, Lin Ming was still able to loudly retort to a Divine Sea Supreme Elder. This courage left all the heroic young elites present ashamed at their own inferiority. This was not a question of just being psychologically frightened. The key issue was that a Divine Sea Supreme Elder held an aura within them that naturally formed a force field. Just looking at them could scare someone witless!

Shwa!

A white shadow instantly appeared in the distant arena skies, directly confronting Situ Haotian.

This was Shibai.

“Since we set a life or death struggle, you must understand the rules of a life or death struggle. If you wish to change your mind now and say that this is a simple friendly spar, then that is also fine! Little Brother Lin will not kill your people but you can forget about taking away Little Brother Lin!”

Shibai was also worried about the background of the Asura Divine Kingdom. Even if Lin Ming seemed outrageously powerful at the moment, he still didn’t dare to have 100% confidence that Lin Ming would be the one to finally emerge victorious. Thus, he put forth these conditions to ensure his absolute safety.

But how could Situ Haotian possibly agree with Shibai’s suggestion. If he cancelled this life or death battle then that meant admitting defeat ahead of time. Everything he had done before now would all have been in vain.

“One million spirit essence stones or equivalent heavenly materials!”

Situ Haotian was unambiguous as he directly spoke out this sky high price. But, his intentions were clear. He intended to trade this price for Situ Luosha’s life.

“Your Majesty…” Situ Luosha’s heart twitched. At this moment, he felt nothing but the greatest shame and humiliation of his life. As a sixth stage Life Destruction martial artist, he had been completely suppressed by a mere first stage Life Destruction junior! Even after combusting his blood essence, he still wasn’t able to injure his opponent! Finally, he had to depend on His Majesty the Divine Emperor to lay down his pride and redeem his life with spirit essence stones.

Situ Luosha had never felt this utterly incompetent.

To someone like him who was almost insufferably arrogant, this would undoubtedly be a significant setback to his future martial path.

“One million spirit essence stones to buy the life of a future Divine Sea powerhouse, your plan is quite good!” Shibai taunted.

Back in the confrontation at the Realmheart Great Hall, Shibai had feared that Situ Haotian would become mad and lose all reasoning. But now, Shibai didn’t fear Situ Haotian at all. A massive number of influences had tried to win over Lin Ming in these past few days, including the Sublime Smelting Divine Kingdom, Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom, Holy Land sects and family clans and many others, all of them sending gifts in great heaps.

Of course, Shibai didn’t expect that these influences would help the Forsaken God Clan if the Asura Divine Kingdom were to wage war against them. But, what Shibai could affirm was that they wouldn’t join the side of the Asura Divine Kingdom in a war. Also, the Death Reaper Curse that the Asura Divine Kingdom had used to track Lin Ming had been eliminated from his body. Even if a great war were to break out, them wishing to kill Lin Ming would not be easy at all. Those influences would not do something so thankless in exchange for fatally offending the future highest under the heavens.

As long as those other influences didn’t help the Asura Divine Kingdom, then by relying on the absolute defenses of this dimensional realm, the Asura Divine Kingdom would have to continuously weigh over just whether or not they should try to invade this land. After all, they didn’t have a top level super master like the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom’s Highest Divine Emperor.

“1.5 million, that is my bottom line!” Situ Haotian said with finality, his expression extremely gloomy.

“And if we don’t agree?” Shibai asked back.

“Then use your spear!” Situ Haotian coldly said, his eyes filled with a murderous intent. Although a Divine Sea powerhouse’s value far surpassed 1.5 million spirit essence stones, he was still a proud and lofty Divine Emperor. Just because he was willing to yield once didn’t mean he would be coerced into making endless concessions forever.

“Good, then I agree!” The one who spoke was Lin Ming. The Asura Divine Emperor appearing had already been showing sufficient face, and he had also made enough concessions. In any case, killing Situ Luosha and enraging this Asura Divine Emperor to the point where he might do something crazy was of no benefit to him.

Moreover, Situ Luosha’s attitude wasn’t too bad. Lin Ming had neither injustice nor enmity with Situ Luosha. And most importantly of all, Situ Luosha had already been surpassed by Lin Ming; in the future, it was impossible for him to ever be his match again.

And 1.5 million spirit essence stones’ worth of materials was also enough to move Lin Ming’s heart. It could be called a pie falling from the sky.

“The Asura Divine Emperor has lowered his head…”

“Yah. To Situ Haotian, yielding in front of the eyes of everyone here is probably worse than paying 1.5 million spirit essence stones. This is a Divine Sea Supreme Elder lowering his head to a first stage Life Destruction junior. This sort of thing has probably never happened in the entire 10,000 year plus history of the Asura Divine Kingdom!”

“This Lin Lanjian is too horrifying! When he reaches the Divine Sea in the future he will be like a dragon ascending to the heavens! He will rule the entire Sky Spill Continent for 10,000 years!”

“Hey, that’s not necessarily true. This type of character might ascend upwards, just like Emperor Shakya did in the past.”

It was unknown just who said these words, but it left all of the heroic young elites excited. To them, the elusive Realm of the Gods was a land filled with infinite appeal. All of them wished to go to the legendary Realm of the Gods described in the ancient texts to broaden their horizons. But that was actually impossible for them. Ascending into the Realm of the Gods was far too difficult.

The 22nd match ended once more with Lin Ming’s victory!

But this time, Situ Luosha wasn’t without achievement. He had forced Lin Ming to use the power of the Thunder Dominion here twice in a row, and he also used the main form of the Nine Heavens Thunder Soul as well as the explosive power of thunderfire with Chasing Sun. In such an intense battle, it was inevitable that Lin Ming would have consumed some energy.

“What a good seedling. A dual Thunder and Fire Law explosion, those two Concepts were perfectly combined together. That should have been a martial skill that he created himself.” Old Man Good Fortune praised without hesitation.

Normally, a martial artist only had a single attribute physique, skilled in just a single one of the five elements. It was extremely rare to see a dual attribute physique. And as for someone like Lin Ming. who had an extremely high talent in both aspects of thunder and fire, this was the first time that Old Man Good Fortune had seen something like this.

“Thunder and fire… those aren’t part of the domain that I’m skilled at.” Old Man Good Fortune stroked his beard, slightly shaking his head.

“Oh?” Fairy Snow Gale’s heart stirred as she heard this. “Listening to Senior Good Fortune’s meaning, are you planning on accepting him as a disciple? Although Senior may not be proficient in the Concepts of Thunder and Fire, you understand the Concepts of Space and Time. In that alone, you are absolutely the number one master in the entire Sky Spill Continent! And Lin Lanjian also has excellent achievements in the Concepts of Space and Time. If he can obtain your guidance, that would be an amazingly extraordinary lucky chance!”

As for Old Man Good Fortune’s name and birth, perhaps no one knew besides him. People only knew of his title. In the superstitions and beliefs of the world, good fortune had always represented the Great Dao, represented the boundless universe.

The axis of space, the eons that passed since ancient times, the universe was the fusion of space and time. It was said Old Man Good Fortune’s nickname had come from this. In terms of the Concepts of Space and Time, no one was able to reach him.

It was exactly because of his deep understanding towards these mysterious and elusive Concepts that Old Man Good Fortune was considered someone close to being the highest under the heavens. Rumors said that he once even fought the Nine Furnace Highest Divine Emperor in fierce combat until they reached a standstill.

Although the Nine Furnace Highest Divine Emperor did not have the strength of the highest under the heavens, he could actually be called the one that possessed the most authority under the heavens. He had the unreserved support of an entire Divine Kingdom at his back, and yet he still wasn’t able to defeat a wild and free-spirited crane like Old Man Good Fortune, someone who didn’t even come from a sect. From this alone it could be seen just how powerful Old Man Good Fortune was.

“Accept him as a disciple? Haha…” Old Man Good Fortune chuckled as he shook his head, “Useless old me already has a foot half into the coffin, so how could I teach such an eternally rare talent? When he steps into the Divine Sea, or perhaps even before he steps into the Divine Sea, his strength will already surpass mine! What use is there in me teaching him anything?”

“Surpass Senior in strength before the Divine Sea? That’s impossible!” Fairy Snow Gale’s eyes widened like saucers. She didn’t speak out of respect to Old Man Good Fortune, but because she sincerely believed in her words. Old Man Good Fortune was a late Divine Sea powerhouse, and with his achievements in the Concepts of Space and Time, he could be called unrivalled within the world!

Fairy Snow Gale could also barely accept if Lin Ming became the highest under the heavens after breaking through to the Divine Sea, but for him to do so before that, even she felt this was far too overstated!

“The disparity between Life Destruction and the Divine Sea is enormous. Aren’t Senior Good Fortune’s words a bit too exaggerated?” If it wasn’t for these words having come out of Old Man Good Fortune’s mouth, then Fairy Snow Gale would have only snorted in contempt.

“There is no exaggeration. Little Snow, you must remember that an Emperor powerhouse is not the same as a Divine Sea powerhouse. A Divine Sea martial artist is an Emperor level powerhouse, but an Emperor level powerhouse isn’t necessarily a Divine Sea martial artist…”

Early access Patreon chapters

Chapter 860 – Great Desolate Blood Halberd

The so-called thunder spirit body, fire spirit body and water spirit body, those were in truth not special physiques, but rather what some geniuses were called when they had an extremely high talent in one of the five main elements. In terms of physicality, they weren’t that different from someone ordinary.

As for the Ancient Phoenix Saint Body, that was completely different. That was a divine body that had once existed in the Sky Spill Continent during ancient times.

Although the history of the Sky Spill Continent from 100,000 years ago and further back was missing, there were still some glorious family clans with a long legacy that had managed to obtain some ruined jade slips or carved stones from ancient times, and had thus obtained minor understandings of the situation back then.

According to the available records, in the Sky Spill Continent of 100,000 years ago, that was when warlords and rivals all rose up together, with countless peerless heroes filling the land. The so-called Ancient Phoenix Saint Body was a physique that came from a special family clan. In terms of comprehending the Fire Laws, they excelled far more than everyone else on the continent. They could also summon a flame phoenix phantom and other such miracles that Lin Ming was performing right now.

Of course, no one could tell if these stories were true or false, and only a minor number of those present had heard these legends. There was simply no one that was able to confirm that Lin Ming’s physique was the Ancient Phoenix Saint Body.

But without a doubt, there was definitely something special about Lin Ming’s physique, otherwise it would have been impossible for him to display such a terrifying energy.

Originally no one thought that Lin Ming had a divine body or divine bloodline, and he would always be handicapped because of this. But now it seemed that not only did Lin Ming have a divine body, but this special physique was even superior to the Extreme Violet Dantian! Otherwise, since Lin Ming and Situ Yaoyue’s cultivations were separated by so many small boundaries, how could her Cage of Darkness have been shattered by Lin Ming?

This was the embodiment of physique disparity.

All of the other heroic young elites couldn’t help but be emotionally affected. A monstrous talent, lucky changes that defied the heavens, and now he even had a divine body!

How could any other hero of this era still call themselves a talent in front of him?

……………

Lava tumbled and splashed into the skies. Within the lake of lava, there were still some rocks that hadn’t completely melted yet. These rocks contained certain types of minerals that made them have a much higher melting temperature.

Lin Ming stood on one of these flame-scorched rocks, supporting himself with his spear. Because he had burnt the blood of the Ancient Phoenix just now, he had consumed an enormous amount of energy. Even with his endurance and energy, he still felt it a bit difficult to withstand.

Bang!

Five miles in front of Lin Ming, the lake of lava suddenly exploded. Situ Yaoyue rushed out, looking like a mess. In that confrontation just now, she had directly faced the flame phoenix phantom that had rushed out from Lin Ming’s body, and had to expend some of her blood essence to use her strongest attack – Demon Moon Extreme Heaven. Even so, she had been shaken and injured by the energy shockwaves. When this was coupled with her Cage of Darkness being shattered by the great torrential waves of flame, this had caused her to suffer a serious backlash, and now her injuries had become far worse. When she had fallen into the lava now, her protective true essence was like a candle in the wind, nearly fading away. Her hair and clothing had been ignited by the lava and burnt away. If she hadn’t used the Concept of Darkness to form new clothes for herself then she feared half of her body would have been publicly exposed by now.

“Lin Lanjian!” Situ Yaoyue stared at Lin Ming, her eyes brilliant and shining. Since she was born, she had never experienced such a difficult battle before. The Extreme Violet Domain and Cage of Darkness had both been broken and she had been seriously injured.

In terms of battle spirit and speed she was inferior to begin with. What she was proud of was her understanding into the Concept of Darkness as well as her Extreme Violet Dantian.

But when compared with Lin Ming, her Concept of Darkness was broken by Lin Ming’s Concept of Fire, and her Extreme Violet Domain was inferior to Lin Ming’s two force fields. Although she had a dantian variation, Lin Ming had an even more formidable divine body.

There was no need to compare their other aspects.

Every single domain she excelled in had been defeated one by one under Lin Ming’s hand. Her once haughty arrogance had already lost all of its support.

Situ Yaoyue grit her teeth and pointed her spear right towards Lin Ming’s forehead. Since the fight had reached this point, she could no longer back down. She had also seen that Lin Ming had consumed a massive amount of energy just now when he used that secret divine body technique. If they continued to fight, it was still uncertain just who would win and who would lose!

Woosh!

Suddenly, a violent and wild blood light shot into the skies. All of the flowing lava underneath Situ Yaoyue’s feet froze, turning into black volcanic rock.

A strong infernal energy dissipated into the air, causing all of the martial artists present to feel their heartbeats quicken with fear. There were even some that found it hard to breathe. Just now it was like Situ Yaoyue had opened up an ancient sealed demon box, releasing an ancient demonic spirit!

“That is…”

Lin Ming’s pupils shrank.

In Situ Yaoyue’s hands, there was actually a blood red war halberd!

This halberd was 10 feet long and the shaft was as thick as an arm. Countless symbols were inscribed upon it. On the foot long halberd edge, there was a cruel demon engraving. Its expression was fierce and hideous, lifelike to the point where it seemed it would jump out. All those that looked at it couldn’t help but feel their souls trembling in fear.

With Situ Yaoyue’s delicate body holding this massive and thick halberd, it left an immense visual impact on everyone present.

‘That is…’ Lin Ming’s eyes widened. ‘That is the Great Desolate Blood Halberd! That is the weapon the Demon Emperor once used!’

It was unexpectedly held by the Asura Divine Kingdom! Lin Ming sucked in a deep breath. Thinking of it, this wasn’t too surprising. The Asura Divine Kingdom was a super Holy Land with a 10,000 year inheritance. Their background was immeasurably deep. Since they had the Demon God Heartguard Mirror, it was also natural that they might have been able to obtain the Great Desolate Blood Halberd.

Lin Ming was extremely familiar with the Great Desolate Blood Halberd. Back at Revered Master Tianguang’s birthday banquet, Lin Ming had fought Lei Mubai, and the weapon he used had been a replica of the Great Desolate Blood Halberd. Afterwards, Lei Mubai had perished under Lin Ming’s hands, and that replica became Lin Ming’s possession.

Then Lin Ming had gone to the South Sea battlefield in order to practice the ‘Great Desolate Halberd Art’ and had used this halberd for a very long time. This was also the reason why he tried to walk on the slaughter path. But afterwards, he discovered that he didn’t have much talent in the slaughter path, thus he no longer used the halberd and switched back to his spear.

The halberd and spear were similar pole-type weapons. Lin Ming had practiced martial arts for many years and naturally had a deep understanding into those two types of weapons. As he looked at the Great Desolate Blood Halberd in Situ Yaoyue’s hands, he could sense an evil demonic energy coming from it. That was truly an unlucky and ominous weapon!

‘Saint rank artifact… also the halberd has an evil demon energy on it that causes it to rise above a normal Saint artifact!’ Lin Ming instantly judged.

The Great Desolate Blood Halberd was obviously the final card Situ Yaoyue had hidden.

“In the end… she still had to use it…”

On the Godspeed Boat, Situ Haotian began to slowly shake his head. When he had given the Great Desolate Blood Halberd to Situ Yaoyue, he had urged her again and again to never use it until she was forced to bring out her last resort. And now, the time had come for her to bring out that halberd.

The Great Desolate Blood Halberd was a dangerous and unlucky treasure. After the Demon Emperor flew into the Realm of the Gods tens of thousands of years ago, the Great Desolate Blood Halberd had changed hands several times. With it, one could be called an earth-shaking character that awed the world.

However, written in the ancient records, it showed that Emperor level powerhouses that wielded the Great Desolate Blood Halberd had died horrible, unnatural deaths. Even Divine Sea Supreme Elders were the same. They could be said to have insufficient destiny, and thus were killed by the unlucky curse that existed on the blood halberd.

There was even a case a thousand years ago of this occurring. The Netherworld Great Emperor had also obtained the Great Desolate Blood Halberd, and he had eventually died a miserable death when several Emperor level powerhouses joined forces to exterminate him.

At the time, Situ Haotian had participated in the siege of Silent Demon Emperor City, and the Great Desolate Blood Halberd had thus been obtained by the Asura Divine Kingdom. For this blood halberd, the Asura Divine Kingdom had to give up many other things.

After Situ Haotian obtained the Great Desolate Blood Halberd, he didn’t use it. Instead, he sealed it up and suppressed it deep within the Asura Divine Kingdom’s dimensional realm. The Great Desolate Blood Halberd’s ominous and unlucky history was well documented; even a powerhouse that was close to being the highest under the heavens like the Netherworld Great Emperor had still died because of its curse. Situ Haotian certainly didn’t think he was stronger than the Netherworld Great Emperor, thus he hadn’t used this weapon for the entire thousand years.

Even when he gave this halberd to Situ Yaoyue, he still sealed away the majority of the Great Desolate Blood Halberd’s strength. That was merely how things were. Situ Haotian had told her again and again only to use this weapon as a final resort, fearing that she wouldn’t be able to withstand the curse of the blood halberd.

“So it was the Great Desolate Blood Halberd. The Asura Divine Kingdom is really holding nothing back!”

“Hehe, Situ Haotian isn’t a brash idiot. He’s always been extremely careful; the majority of this unlucky halberd’s strength should have been sealed away. Situ Yaoyue should still be able to withstand it. Even so, although this girl won’t die to the curse, her destiny will certainly be affected. This is not a blessing for her.”

On a spirit boat, two Divine Sea Supreme Elders were casually talking with each other.

The Great Desolate Blood Halberd was extremely famous. Many of those famed sect Elders present certainly recognized this ominous halberd. For these past tens of thousands of years it had drunk countless amounts of blood, including even that of Divine Sea Supreme Elders!

Legends said that this ominous halberd only needed to be casually dropped to be able to crush a mountain. It wasn’t an exaggeration to say that this was the world’s greatest ominous weapon!

“To think that it’s the Great Desolate Blood Halberd. This battle between the strongest Life Destruction powerhouses is truly full of winding paths and changes, with startling events happening again and again. I thought that Lin Lanjian had the advantage, but now that Situ Yaoyue has brought out the Great Desolate Blood Halberd, I have no idea just what will happen!”

“Lin Lanjian is in danger. That ominous halberd is as heavy as a mountain. A mere scratch or bump would be enough to crush someone to death. If that fell from her hands, it would shatter mountains, let alone when it is moved by energy. I wonder just how Lin Lanjian will block it?”

“He might be able to evade it and win through speed. Lin Lanjian’s speed is called the highest below the Divine Sea. He can still fight.” A sect Elder thoughtfully said.

Situ Yaoyue grasped the Great Desolate Blood Halberd and stood proud and arrogant above her island in the lava sea. “Lin Lanjian, this is the world’s greatest ominous weapon. Today, I shall sacrifice your blood to it!”

As she spoke, she rushed forwards. She wielded the desolate halberd downwards like a falling avalanche!

Lin Ming’s face was decisive and cold. He evenly lifted his long spear and sneered, “The Great Desolate Blood Halberd may be called the greatest ominous weapon in the world, but just how much of its strength could you possibly display?”

“Humph! Then come and try it out! Meet my move!” Situ Yaoyue said as she smashed the halberd down at Lin Ming. The Great Desolate Blood Halberd was incomparably heavy. Situ Yaoyue had to expend all of her true essence in order to move it, without having any left over to use martial skills.

But, none of this mattered. Absolute power could break apart all techniques. Just wielding the Great Desolate Blood Halberd could be said to be her strongest martial skill!

This simple attack smashed onto Lin Ming. At this moment, it was like a mountain was falling down on him!

Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. The Eight Inner Gates opened, the Heretical God Force erupted!

He spread his feet wide and sank his waist down, transmitting strength through his spine. With the support of the Gate of Limit, 1.5 million jins of strength erupted with his red spear!

To meet spear with halberd, all of the martial artists present stared with wide eyes, dumbfounded at what they were seeing. Even the Divine Sea Supreme Elders were startled.

He wanted to directly resist the Great Desolate Blood Halberd!?

Dang!

Spear and halberd crossed. An explosive ringing sound burst through the clouds and cracked stones, sounding like a thunderclap in everyone’s ears and making their hearts feel faint. The red rock underneath Lin Ming’s feet instantly shattered and a massive shockwave caused the lava beneath him to surge into the air, forming a tsunami of lava that was hundreds of feet high, directly impacting into the horizon!

Lin Ming held his spear with both hands. Because of the immense pressure, the spear shaft had curved like a crescent moon.

However, he had truly been able to frontally block the Great Desolate Blood Halberd’s attack!

On the other side of the blood halberd, Situ Yaoyue’s beautiful face was twisted, her eyes wide with utterly incredulous disbelief!

Chapter 866 – Divide the Void

The situation had originally been disadvantageous for the Asura Divine Kingdom, but Situ Haotian’s miraculous chess move had caused the road to curve once more, adding new variables!

In this fight, if he could end it in a draw, then not only would Situ Haotian gain immeasurable fame, enough to deter the world, but he would also be able to solve Situ Yaoyue’s problem.

“He must defeat Situ Haotian in three moves or at least dominate him. Otherwise it will be impossible for him to command everyone’s respect. Can Old Man Good Fortune really do this?”

“If this were four thousand years ago when Old Man Good Fortune was still at his peak state, then that certainly wouldn’t be a problem. But now… I think the situation is an unknown!”

“Situ Haotian is too cunning and limited this match to only three moves. Old Man Good Fortune can’t change anything now even if he wanted to. After all, he’s the senior here.”

“Perhaps… Old Man Good Fortune will avoid this battle and use some casual excuse to refuse Situ Haotian. Although this will be enough to save his face, that will be the same as showing weakness. He won’t be able to meddle in Lin Lanjian’s affairs anymore!”

Everyone’s eyes turned to Old Man Good Fortune. Shibai and the other Forsaken God Clan martial artists looked a bit tense. All of them couldn’t help but think that 8000 years of life really did seem just a bit too old. And didn’t this elderly man seem as if he were in the last years of his life?

To suppress Situ Haotian with overwhelming strength in three moves, the chances were a bit unknown…

Old Man Good Fortune’s blue clothes fluttered in the wind. He held onto his peach walking stick, a kind and benevolent smile still hanging on his face. However, as this smile fell into the eyes of others, it appeared abstruse and profound. Old Man Good Fortune lightly coughed and said, “You know… being so stubborn isn’t always good…”

These words didn’t show if Old Man Good Fortune was planning to accept the match or not. Situ Haotian’s eyebrows shot up, “Senior Good Fortune, do you have no intention of directing this Emperor?”

“Haha…” Old Man Good Fortune stroked his white beard and said with a smile, “I don’t think I can direct you, but for a senior to be able to exchange some moves with a junior, at least this old man’s legacy might not be wasted in the coffin. This can also be considered good fortune.”

The surrounding martial artists all became excited as they heard Old Man Good Fortune speak. He had really decided to fight!

Those two were among the top powerhouses of the Sky Spill Continent! This sort of fight could be said to be rarer than a once in a millennium battle!

Existences of their level would only fight in the eruption of a national war or to compete for lucky chances. Otherwise, they simply wouldn’t bother fighting. If they did vigorously battle then they would have to consume their energy. Once they damaged their life source or harmed the fires of their life, the gains simply wouldn’t be equal to the losses.

Situ Haotian narrowed his eyes. At this moment he was like a massive dragon that was charging his strength, containing a potent and terrifying power within him. Once he erupted, it would truly be an earth-shaking event!

Old Man Good Fortune grasped his peach walking stick and hobbled over to stand in front of Situ Haotian. Compared to Situ Haotian’s dominating aura, he was simply like a normal old man without any special characteristics at all.

“Senior Good Fortune, let’s go up.” At this time, Situ Haotian’s fighting spirit was blazing. He had no intention of underestimating Old Man Good Fortune at all. He would go all-out in this battle!

He could not lose!

“Alright.” Old Man Good Fortune’s feet lifted off from the ground as he floated upwards without a sound. His green ox mount rode over from the clouds to position itself underneath Old Man Good Fortune’s feet.

Like this, Old Man Good Fortune rode his green ox and ascended into the skies.

The two flew 10,000 feet high in the air. As for the younger martial artists, they had moved far into the distance under the direction of their Elders. Those who were still staying within the 10 mile range were all powerful characters.

“A battle between Divine Sea Supreme Elders.” Lin Ming sucked in a deep breath, his heart filling with anticipation. This would be the most high level battle he had witnessed to date.

Near Lin Ming, Shibai was a bit worried. Just what would the result of this match be? Could Old Man Good Fortune really subdue Situ Haotian in three moves?

“Senior Good Fortune, do you not plan on putting away your mount?”

10,000 feet in the air, Situ Haotian frowned a bit as he saw Old Man Good Fortune ride up on his green ox. Once this battle began it would definitely be an apocalyptic scene. That mount would be crushed into goo.

“No need. This green ox will ride into battle with me.” Old Man Good Fortune said with a smile.

Situ Haotian guessed that the green ox was some sort of contract beast, but he didn’t care too much about it. It was a perfectly justified matter for a martial artist to fight with their contract beast.

“Divine Emperor Haotian, you may make your move.” Old Man Good Fortune reminded him.

“Then this Emperor shall do as you wish!” At this time, Situ Haotian naturally wouldn’t care about modesty or humility. In this battle he had to guarantee at least a draw. If he was able to put pressure on Old Man Good Fortune, then that would be even better!

Situ Haotian had kept a low profile for all these years and had collected a number of special trump abilities. Facing this Old Man Good Fortune, who was near the end of his life, he was confident he could put pressure on him.

Bang!

A great strength erupted. Situ Haotian extracted a black halberd from his spatial ring. This war halberd was 10 feet long and released bursts of fierce black light. The shaft of the halberd was etched with compact and complex patterns. This was impressively a quasi-Saint artifact!

Counting this unknown black halberd, the Asura Divine Kingdom had continually revealed two quasi-Saint artifacts and one Saint artifact.

Among them, although the Demon God Heartguard mirror was a quasi-Saint level artifact, because it was a defensive treasure its value was in no way inferior to an offensive Saint artifact.

At this time, Situ Haotian’s thick black hair was flying in the wind. He seemed like a god that overlooked mortals, looking down at the world with arrogance and contempt!

“God Murder!”

Omm –

A loud ringing cry emerged from the black war halberd, followed by an endless amount of energy that extended outwards like a growing galaxy. Situ Haotian had used the strongest killing move of the ‘Great Desolate Halberd Art’, a move that required the strength of the Divine Sea to use.

Facing this terrifying strike, Old Man Good Fortune still rode on his green ox. His blue clothes gently waved in the wind. With a calm expression, he lifted his hands and drew a line downwards. A star-like energy suddenly appeared like a fleeting illusion, falling down and cutting off the world.

Bang!

Situ Haotian’s terrifying attack smashed towards Old Man Good Fortune. However, just as his attack reached 10 feet away, it simply vanished into the void, disappearing forever. It was like an invisible endless abyss had appeared in front of Old Man Good Fortune. Any energy that came towards him simply faded away with no trace left!

“What!?”

All of the martial artists watching from afar were dumbfounded. Situ Haotian’s horrifying attack had vanished just like that. Old Man Good Fortune still calmly rode his green ox, his blue clothes fluttering in the wind. As this scene fell into everyone’s watching eyes, they felt an inestimable feeling.

Lin Ming was also stricken; Old Man Good Fortune had easily divided space!

At this time, although Old Man Good Fortune was standing still and seemed close by, the truth was that he was in a completely separate world. Between him and Situ Haotian was an invisible moat that could not be crossed. No matter what sort of monstrous supernatural strength came rushing towards him, it would all fall into this unknown space, unable to harm even a single hair of Old Man Good Fortune.

Just how deep did one’s comprehension of the Space Laws have to be in order to use such a heaven-defying ability with such casual ease?

Lin Ming sucked in a breath of cold air. The Concepts of Space, Thunder, and Fire were all the same in that they were divided into multiple levels. Until now, Lin Ming had only encountered a  single level, and that was to distort and shrink space. His elusive and ghostly attacks and movements all depended on this. It was the first time that he had seen Old Man Good Fortune’s method of utilizing the Concept of Space. Without a doubt, Old Man Good Fortune’s actions today had opened up a great mystical door for Lin Ming.

With his first attack unsuccessful, Situ Haotian was still calm without the least bit of panic. Everything had gone as he had expected. “Heaven’s Divide. Senior Good Fortune’s technique is truly astounding. Since the first move failed, here is the second!”

As Situ Haotian spoke to here he suddenly emitted a loud shout. His voice didn’t even seem as if it could be that of a human. In that instant, a savage dragon seemed to awaken within his body. His joints began to emit popping sounds and his muscles rose, bulging out in all directions. His body began to grow, and in just several breaths of time he actually grew a whole 10 feet taller. His muscles had become as hard as rock. His face was ferocious and ravenous, and both his eyes were a bright blood red.

After transforming his body, Situ Haotian’s aura had soared by several times, the power of his blood vitality billowing into the sky like a blazing blame. At this time, he was filled with insufferable arrogance, like a demon god that had arrived in the world, overlooking all of existence!

Even if Old Man Good Fortune was able to divide the void, Situ Haotian now had sufficient strength to break it!

As Lin Ming saw Situ Haotian morph his body, he was startled. Situ Haotian’s body had actually become that of a Giant Demon. This was… just how had he done this? In that moment, he could clearly feel a rich and pure Giant Demon bloodline from within Situ Haotian. This bloodline was exactly the same as the Giant Demon blood essence that Lin Ming had seen when he opened the Cosmic Melting Furnace!

The Cosmic Melting Furnace had contained two masses of Giant Demon blood essence. The first mass had been absorbed by the Magic Cube and the second mass was given to Demonshine.

“Demonshine, what’s going on here? Could Situ Haotian come from the Giant Demon race’s bloodline?”

Lin Ming asked with a true essence sound transmission. Ever since Lin Ming had decided to attack Life Destruction, Demonshine had temporarily left Lin Ming’s body. Whether it was crossing Life Destruction or his life or death struggle with Situ Yaoyue, Lin Ming had a chance of dying. Thus, Demonshine had chosen to leave Lin Ming’s spiritual sea for the moment.

“He doesn’t. It’s just that this Situ Haotian must have obtained some Ancient Giant Demon blood essence from somewhere and then transplanted it into his body, thus he gained the ability to transform his body. This sort of bloodline is far inferior to your own Ancient Phoenix bloodline.”

The Ancient Giant Demons that once existed on the Holy Demon Continent were different from the currently existing Giant Demons. Those Ancient Giant Demons had a bloodline that contained a powerful strength. Of course, this couldn’t even be compared to the bloodline of a God Beast like a True Phoenix or True Dragon.

However, what Situ Haotian used was the blood essence of the Ancient Giant Demons and what Lin Ming had was only the most ordinary blood of the Ancient Phoenix, and the quantity was far less too. Thus, the disparity in their bloodlines wasn’t too great at this moment.

As Lin Ming was engaged in these thoughts, he suddenly heard a martial artist near him cry out in alarm. “A divine body! Battle Demon Emperor Body, that is also another kind of divine body!”

“The Asura Divine Emperor has a Battle Demon Emperor Body? I’ve never even heard of that before!”

“When the Asura Divine Emperor was born, he didn’t have a divine body. He only relied on his own extraordinary talent to reach where he is today. It’s likely he obtained this current divine body from some lucky chance somewhere.

“In just a single day I’ve seen two divine bodies as well as the Extreme Violet Dantian. This has really been an eye-opener!”

As these people were all crying out in acclaim, Lin Ming was dumbfounded; he simply didn’t know whether to laugh or to cry. So this was what they thought the so-called divine body was. It appeared that everyone who possessed a physique different from that of the average man and was able to display a stronger combat strength was referred to as having a divine body.

Plot of the Ancient Devil

Chapter 870 – Myriad Spirit Pill

Several months had passed since Lin Ming and Situ Yaoyue’s cataclysmic battle. Duanmu Qun left his sound transmission mark at the Forsaken God Clan and left. As for Yang Yun, Li Yifeng, the Holy Land Holy Sons, Princes, High Successors, and other such characters, all of them had left one after the other.

However, Lin Ming’s momentum was simply too great. When one great influence left, a smaller one would come again. Even though Lin Ming had already declined to receive visitors for a long time, there were still many representatives of smaller influences entering and leaving the dimensional realm. It didn’t matter that they couldn’t see Lin Ming; they never had this hope to begin with. It was enough for them to see someone from the Forsaken God Clan.

In any case, they did not need to personally hand over gifts to Lin Ming. They only needed to pass them through the Forsaken God Clan. According to the customs of the Sky Spill Continent, all gifts would be recorded in the register. While no one expected to form good relations with Lin Ming like this, they only wanted to express their friendly attitude.

After several months, although the gifts received from those small influences were rather small individually, there were just far too many. With every small influence sending 8000-10,000 spirit essence stones, several hundred of these gifts added up to two or three million spirit essence stones. Shibai sold or exchanged all of these gifts for more heavenly materials. Then, this formed a massive amount of medicinal herbs for Lin Ming.

As Shibai thought that the total value of all these materials was 16-17 million spirit essence stones, he was left speechless. Just what kind of physique did Lin Ming have? He was simply the same as a bottomless pit. With so many resources, it was enough to raise a martial artist all the way to the Divine Sea realm. Of course, this was all provided that they had sufficient talent.

Even so, all this was just for Lin Ming to attack the second stage of Life Destruction?

Shibai didn’t know that Lin Ming was opening the Gate of Pain; he only thought he was trying to cross another stage of Life Destruction. In his opinion, since Lin Ming had consumed resources to break through into the first stage of Life Destruction, he would have to consume an equal or greater amount of resources for future breakthroughs.

In the seclusion chamber, the Cosmic Melting Furnace was spinning around with the Burning Star Flame raging around it. Lin Ming casually threw a medicinal herb into it. A brief moment later, this herb was melted by the fires into a viridian bubble that was wrapped by true essence and slowly flew out.

With a pinch of his hand, a streak of red fire shot out and the green liquid evaporated, leaving behind a faint wisp of plant essence that had been refined by Lin Ming.

Success. This was the 920th ingredient.

Lin Ming let out a light sigh, not bothering to wipe the sweat off of his forehead. He used a million year wood spirit jade bottle to slowly store away this essence energy.

He was currently concocting a special medicine named the Myriad Spirit Pill. One had to withdraw the plant essence from thousands of medicinal herbs, fuse them together and then refine it multiple times, finally producing a Myriad Spirit Pill!

A normal alchemist would never choose to create such a pill. This was because the refining process was extremely tedious and cumbersome, and the consumption of soul force was also immense! Not just that, but it required a massive amount of wood spirit jade. Wood spirit jade was no less valuable than spiritual plants. Thus, there was simply too much unnecessary cost and waste involved in refining a Myriad Spirit Pill.

However, Lin Ming’s current situation was special. With such a massive pile of medicine herbs in front of him, this was the best time for him to refine the Myriad Spirit Pill. As for the massive amount of wood spirit jade required, he simply didn’t need to worry about that. The various influences had sent him so much wood spirit jade that it had piled into a little hill, and there were even more treasures that were carved from wood spirit jade.

Ho – -!

Another medicinal herb was melted by Lin Ming into a green bubble. This green bubble was carefully zapped by a lick of fire before turning into a wisp of plant essence.

This process required a great deal of care and concentration. The slightest fluctuation of soul force could cause the medicinal herb to be scorched into ash.

There was already a great deal of herb ash at Lin Ming’s feet. These were from the medicinal herbs he had used to practice. Even a top alchemist master could easily make a mistake; alchemy had a very high demand on one’s soul force.

Lin Ming’s alchemy technique certainly couldn’t be considered at the top; there just hadn’t been enough time since he had begun learning alchemy. But, Lin Ming had inherited the memories of that Divine Realm alchemist, including all of his attainments and experiences. All of these were things that could not be taught. After Lin Ming had inherited these memories, he was able to integrate them within himself, making his progress in alchemy surpassingly quick.

And the most important factor was that Lin Ming’s understandings into the Concepts and Laws of Fire were top notch, as was his control of the power of fire. With the Burning Star Flame at his command, he could twist the flame into whatever shape he wanted, or even divide it several times. This was something that a normal alchemist would find impossible difficult to do.

“The next one!”

With the support from the Gate of Healing, Lin Ming’s ability to sustain his true essence was freakishly abnormal. After such a long time of expending true essence, he still didn’t show any signs of running out of true essence. Instead, it was his soul force that began to lag behind.

The Gate of Healing could only restore physical strength and true essence, also increasing the rate at which someone recovered. But as for the consumption of soul force, it simply couldn’t do anything at all.

Chi!

A medicinal herb worth several thousand spirit essence stones turned to ash in Lin Ming’s palm.

“My soul force has reached its limit; it will be hard to continue.” Lin Ming did not stop because of this failure. He continued to refine for some time, but eventually the success rate became far too low. Then, Lin Ming finally stopped refining the medicinal herbs. He stoppered the wood spirit jade bottle and temporarily ended his creation of the Myriad Spirit Pill, instead taking out the lowest level medicinal herbs from his spatial ring and starting to practice with them.

In a situation where he had seriously overdrawn his soul force, Lin Ming nearly failed every time he tried to refine a pill. Piles of ashes grew on the ground. Lin Ming felt a splitting headache and then his vision suddenly went dark as he slumped to the ground, unconscious.

Alchemy was a very good tempering technique for one’s mental strength and soul force. Every time one overdrew their divine soul, after recovering, their divine soul would be more formidable than before. This was the reason that most martial artists chose to learn a secondary skill as an occupation.

As Lin Ming was sleeping, although he was unconscious, the ‘Overbearing Soul Tactic’ was still running of its own accord, subtly revitalizing Lin Ming’s soul.

He quickly entered into a deep sleep and rested like this for several days.

After an unknown period of time, Lin Ming awoke from his slumber, feeling spirited and well rested. His mindset was extremely clear and energetic. He took out the wood spirit jade bottle without pause and began to refine medicinal herbs again. After he exhausted his soul force, he fell asleep once again.

This process continued again and again. Like this, over half a year passed.

Jin after jin of superior wood spirit jade had its essence refined out and then combined with the plant essence of the 1000-2000 medicinal herbs, fusing together as one before being placed in the wood spirit jade bottle. At this time, the Myriad Spirit Pill was 80% complete.

Lin Ming’s soul force had also made considerable progress in this past half year. At the start he was only able to perform alchemy for three days before sleeping, but now he was able to last for five days. After crossing Life Destruction, the potential of his soul had been completely dug out and exposed, and it was only continuing to increase.

Although soul force could not directly influence a martial artist’s strength, it was actually one of the main limiting factors of what realm a martial artist would reach. If one didn’t have a powerful soul force then they wouldn’t be able to control too much true essence. If a Revolving Core powerhouse’s soul force was combined with the body of a Divine Sea master, their body would probably burst apart in an uncontrollable explosion of energy.

During this process of using up massive amounts of true essence while continuously restoring it, Lin Ming was rapidly approaching the second stage of Life Destruction. This was also reasonable. Lin Ming’s foundation was just far too stable, making it so that he reached the peak first stage Life Destruction as soon as he made his breakthrough. At that time, he had only been a step away from the second stage of Life Destruction.

Crossing from the first to the second stage of Life Destruction was much easier than opening the Gate of Pain. This was because where he had once been limited to disintegrating his body through exploding his dantian, Lin Ming could now store energy throughout his body, detonating it everywhere in order to destroy himself. It would not be as difficult as breaking into the first stage of Life Destruction, thus Lin Ming was not worried at all.

Several more months passed. Lin Ming had already closed up for an entire year!

The Forsaken God Clan had finally calmed down. As for Situ Yaoyue, per the original agreement she had been housed in the Realmheart Great Hall, unable to take even half a step out.

This appeared as if it were to prevent Situ Yaoyue from escaping. However, Situ Yaoyue was only a Life Destruction martial artist. There was simply nothing she could do against the layers upon layers of array formations that covered the Forsaken God Clan.

No, this was mainly to protect Situ Yaoyue. If she were to somehow die here within the Forsaken God Clan, then the consequences would be disastrous.

Although the Realmheart Great Hall was known as the cornerstone of this world that even the highest under the heavens couldn’t break, the Asura Divine Kingdom still sent a Divine Sea powerhouse to constantly protect Situ Yaoyue.

Since this guardian had to stay in the same room as Situ Yaoyue and accompany her at all times, it was best for them to be a woman. Also, they had to be absolutely trustworthy, which meant that they would need to be a direct descendant of the Situ Family Clan. Beside the malicious and sinister Situ Yaoxi, who would likely get into all sorts of trouble at the Forsaken God Clan, the only other choice was Situ Haotian’s younger cousin – Situ Qingzhao.

Situ Qingzhao was 2000 years old, only half the age of Situ Yaoxi. In addition, due to her nature of loving beauty, she had been willing to consume some of her cultivation to maintain her youthful appearance, thus she looked as if she were Situ Yaoyue’s big sister.

“Yaoyue, you are being too harsh on yourself. If you continue to overdraw your energy you will damage your soul and possibly leave hidden wounds in your spiritual sea.” Situ Qingzhao couldn’t help but say as she watched her niece bitterly cultivate with dedication. It could even be called self-torture.

“Aunty Qingzhao, you don’t have to try persuading me. Even if there are some hidden wounds left over, I still have ways of eliminating them after I reach the Divine Sea. Lin Lanjian is the shame of my life and I must return this loss to him. He is indeed a peerless genius. Now that I was defeated by him, he has surpassed me and it is no longer possible for me to catch up to him, all that will happen will be me falling further and further behind. The only chance I have is to break into the Divine Sea! As soon as I break into the Divine Sea I must challenge him again! That is my final chance as well as my only chance!”

Although Situ Yaoyue was arrogant, she wasn’t so delusional as to think she could stand shoulder to shoulder against Lin Ming in the future. But this life or death struggle was her life’s greatest disgrace; she had no choice but to avenge her loss.

She had been publicly pounded into the ground like a stake in front of the world’s heroes, leaving an eternally unforgettable shame in her heart. Then Divine Emperor Haotian had stepped forwards for her sake, but even he had been suppressed by Old Man Good Fortune. The Asura Divine Kingdom had been forced to pay out a price of over 10 million spirit essence stones for her, making it so that these events would haunt her forever.

If she wanted to defeat Lin Ming, she only had a single chance. And that was to break through to the Divine Sea while Lin Ming was still at Life Destruction!

Old Man Good Fortune had given Lin Ming three years of time. This was because he predicted that Lin Ming would have the qualifications to tussle with or at least preserve his life against a weak Divine Sea Supreme Elder at that time.

That meant that her time left remaining… wasn’t much at all!

As Situ Yaoyue was bitterly cultivating, in the seclusion chamber, Lin Ming’s refinement of the Myriad Spirit Pill had reached its final stage!

Refining the Myriad Spirit Pill was a very laborious task with many steps, and required a massive amount of medicinal herbs. Even though Lin Ming had an extremely high regenerative ability, it still required a full year for him to complete it.

Of course, his harvests for this past year had been tremendous. After overdrawing his energy again and again and again, Lin Ming was ready to break through to the second stage of Life Destruction at any moment. At the same time, he had built a solid foundation of his soul force for when he needed to impact the Divine Sea in the future.

Lin Ming carefully took the small wood spirit jade bottle that contained the plant essence of thousands of medicinal herbs, and then gently tossed it into the Cosmic Melting Furnace…

Chapter 875 – Second Stage Life Destruction

With Lin Ming’s current strength, he was far from being able to protect himself if he entered the Temple of Marvels. But, if he could obtain the protection of Old Man Good Fortune, then even a top level character like the Nine Furnace Highest Divine Emperor wouldn’t even be able to touch him.

Lin Ming only casually knew Old Man Good Fortune and had no particular reason to trust him. But as he thought of it, Old Man Good Fortune was like a wild crane that leisurely flew through the world with no influence behind him, and without any conflicts of interest, there was just no reason to harm him. Moreover, for someone at his rank, there was very little in this world that would cause him to scheme. And even Old Man Good Fortune had been planning something, he could have just abducted Lin Ming from the dimensional realm by force and Shibai would have only been able to watch helplessly as that happened. There would have been no need to wait for today.

“Little Brother Lin, what do you plan on doing?” Shibai asked.

“No matter what I do, first I must break through the second stage of Life Destruction.” There was only a month until the time to enter the Temple of Marvels. Increasing his own strength first would be the safest bet. If he crossed the second stage of Life Destruction and also opened the Gate of Pain, then Lin Ming had no idea just how strong he would become at that time.

Although it was impossible for him to contend against the likes of Situ Haotian, he believed he would have enough strength to safely escape Situ Yaoxi or Situ Bonan with his life intact.

“Break through the second stage of Life Destruction? Great!” Shibai was startled, but not too surprised. Lin Ming had stepped into the peak of the first stage of Life Destruction a year ago, and after such a long time passed, it wasn’t strange for him to break into the second stage.

Two days later, Lin Ming closed up once again. After opening the Gate of Pain, Lin Ming’s physical strength and mentality were at their highest peak. Successfully breaking through the second stage of Life Destruction was nearly guaranteed.

When Lin Ming first crossed into Life Destruction from the Revolving Core realm, he had used his dantian as the core to disintegrate his body, so it hadn’t been easy at all. But for breaking through to the second stage Life Destruction, he was able to use all of the true essence within his body and flesh to thoroughly decompose his body. This was a much simpler process, and Lin Ming also had ample amounts of golden red lightning stored in the Heretical God Sprout.

Within the seclusion chamber, layers of array formations covered the central platform. Lin Ming stepped onto the central array platform and then revolved all the energy within his body and divided his 360 acupoints into 72 points.

These 72 points covered his entire body. With Lin Ming’s control, he crazily absorbed true essence. Then, with his dantian as the center, he erupted!

Golden red lighting poured out from the Heretical God Sprout. Combined with the energy throughout his body, it thoroughly broke down his body. All his meridians ruptured as a rain of blood shot into the air. Lin Ming turned into a vague blood fog that was filled with an incomparably pure heaven and earth origin energy.

Normally, if a person’s body exploded like this then they would be deader than dead. However, the miraculous and marvelous Laws prevented this from happening. This could be called the Heavenly Dao, and the road of martial arts was only a single path of exploring the Heavenly Dao. When a martial artist cultivated martial arts, they were conquering the Heavenly Dao to use for themselves, thus the reason why cultivating the martial path was considered to be defying the will of heavens.

On a human’s journey on the road of martial arts, there were unknown Laws that would protect them during these crucial moments. When they were about to break through the boundaries of Life Destruction, their body would completely disintegrate, with energy fusing into their every cell. Then, all of this would be locked into a small area, forming an accommodation for their soul. This primordial life soup was similar to the amniotic fluid that surrounded a baby in their mother’s womb, allowing the martial artist to maintain their fires of life.

Rich heaven and earth origin energy would fuse into this primordial life soup, tempering all the cells with energy and ejecting the impurities. These cells would then begin to reform into a spirit body.

The grade of the spirit body all depended on how thoroughly a martial artist disintegrated their body and how pure the energy was that tempered their cells.

In this primordial life soup, Lin Ming’s consciousness was incomparably clear. It was like he had become a liquid life form. He swam in a sea of energy, able to examine every cell in his body and watch as his flesh and blood were tempered by energy, slowing changing.

…………….

A month soon passed. The results of the investigation of the Temple of Marvels returned. The four Divine Kingdoms had joined forces to jointly send 30 test puppets into the Temple of Marvels. Finally, only two had returned: one from the Sublime Smelting Divine Kingdom and one from the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom. This was because the test puppets those two Divine Kingdoms had sent out had been the strongest. Especially the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom’s. In order to obtain the best and the most information they could on the Temple of Marvels, they had even sent out a Divine Sea level puppet.

Even the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom only had a single such puppet. They had consumed a massive amount of heavenly materials in order to freeze its fires of life and seal it away, and now was the best time to use it.

“All those below the Divine Sea will be in dire peril if they enter. And those at the Divine Sea have a chance of dying, but they can most likely return alive.”

The results of the investigation were extremely satisfying. It had to be said that the Temple of Marvels was a place of ancient ruins that floated over the skies in the Sea of Miracles. It wouldn’t be strange for all who entered to die.

However, with the protection of a Divine Sea powerhouse, then the most extraordinary disciples of the four Divine Kingdoms might be able to go in to experience and adventure. Not to mention the massive lucky chances that likely existed in the Temple of Marvels, but even if these young disciples weren’t able to obtain any great treasures for themselves, just going in and expanding their horizons by experienced such a high level mystic realm would be extremely advantageous for their future growth.

………….

Forsaken God Clan, Dimensional Realm –

In the seclusion chamber, Lin Ming slowly woke up. He was lying naked on the floor. After his body was broken down and reformed, it gave off a feeling that he had been resurrected from the dead.

The second stage of Life Destruction had been successfully crossed.

From outer appearances, Lin Ming lacked a touch of sharp and dominating aura. All of it was restrained within him, making him see as if he were an elegant young man that loved to read books and recite poetry.

Lin Ming stretched out his hand and countless arcs of purple electricity formed in the air. These electric arcs were thin and long and gathered together like strands of silk, forming substantialized purple cloth. After a moment, this purple silk wrapped around Lin Ming’s body and formed a loose robe.

This loose robe covered all the beautiful hard lines of Lin Ming’s muscles, making him seem like a young student scholar. However, Lin Ming’s eyes flashed as if thunder was contained within them. These shining sparks were actually the power of thunder that had deeply penetrated into every cell of Lin Ming’s body, almost having the same effect of carving the Thunder Laws into his body.

In terms of Lin Ming’s cultivation, although he had just stepped into the second stage of Life Destruction, he had already reached large success of the second stage. Despite the fact that he wasn’t yet at the peak, this couldn’t be considered too far from the third stage of Life Destruction. This was the superiority that came from having an incomparably solid foundation. Once one broke through, they would easily be able to touch upon the next realm.

With every step Lin Ming took, he could feel that every breath he took contained a touch of fragrance. Even his bodily fluids like his saliva and sweat had an aromatic and fresh scent. This was because after he was reborn with a spirit body, not only were there no impurities in his body, but any casual movement he took was able to direct heaven and earth origin energy into his body, flooding every corner of his being with that pure energy.

Mortals loved to describe the bodily fragrance of a fairy maiden as having been untouched by the fires and smoke of men, their bodies not smelling like the wine and meat of the mortal world. The reason for this was because they ate rare spirit flowers and fruits every day, and what they drank was the fresh mountain dew of the early morning. Only through this way could they guarantee that their bodies weren’t tainted by the impurities of common mortals.

But Lin Ming didn’t need to do any of this. He could eat rice and meat just like a common mortal, and because he now possessed a spirit body, he would naturally eliminate all impurities from his body and refine pure energy.

This was also the reason why the Life Destruction stages were called the process when a martial artist was reborn.

“Little Brother Lin, Old Man Good Fortune’s letter has arrived. He will arrive at Port State in three days and wait for you there.” As Shibai saw Lin Ming leave seclusion, his eyes brightened for a moment before he spoke. For someone like Lin Ming, it would only be strange if he failed his breakthrough.

“Okay.” Port State was a city located in the Sublime Smelting Divine Kingdom. It was close to the 8000 Mile Black Swamp and not too far away from where the Temple of Marvels was located.

“Little Brother Lin, I will personally bring you to Port State. But everything after that will depend on your own ability. You must be extra cautious. Although you broke through to the second stage of Life Destruction, it is still far away from making up for the gap between you and a Divine Sea powerhouse.”

Shibai said in his estimation. He didn’t know that Lin Ming had broken through the Gate of Pain, so it was naturally impossible for him to estimate Lin Ming’s combat strength.

“Then I must trouble Patriarch Shibai,” Lin Ming didn’t refuse the offer.

Three days later, at a courtyard deep within Port State, a Godspeed Boat flew in and dropped off a young man and woman. These two appeared as if they were 20-30 years old, but the truth was that they had already practiced martial arts for over sixty years. They only had a youthful appearance because they had crossed Life Destruction at a very young age.

These two people were the hidden Ascetics of the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom and some of the most astounding youths of their generation. The young man was named Yang Mu, and his cultivation was impressively at the seventh stage of Life Destruction. However he didn’t have a dantian variation, so he was slightly inferior to Situ Yaoyue in that aspect. Nonetheless, his comprehension of Laws actually surpassed hers, and he had also comprehended an elementary battle spirit.

The young woman was named Qin Yu. She was not part of the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom’s royal family, but rather a disciple with a different last name. Although her cultivation was only at the sixth stage of Life Destruction, if one looked carefully at her dantian, they could see that all sorts of strange phenomena were occurring within. There seemed to be a faint space developing within her dantian and her true essence also appeared as if it were condensing into liquid. This was the sign that she was beginning to enter the Divine Sea!

After a martial reached the Houtian realm, that was the time they opened their dantian and would begin to train it. During the Houtian realm, one’s true essence would be a mess without any organization to it, so their reserves of true essence would be extremely limited.

Once the true essence within the dantian condensed into a cyclone, there would then be order. The total amount of true essence would increase and it would also become much easier to control.

And after arriving at the Revolving Core realm, true essence would solidify into a Revolving Core crystal nucleus. During this time, their total true essence quantity would rise several times.

During the stages of Life Destruction, there would be no changes in the dantian. Rather, a martial artist’s physical body would transform into a spirit body and they would gain the characteristic of saving true essence in their flesh. This would again cause the total quantity of true essence within them to increase by several times.

After arriving at the Divine Sea realm, a martial artist’s body would be completely soaked in true essence, without any more space to store more. And at this point, countless billions of years ago, the innumerable Supreme Elders that had forged the foundation for the road of martial arts had developed a new path. This was to form a minor dimension within the dantian, and after true essence liquefied, to store that true essence within!

The size of this minor dimension depended on a martial artist’s foundation and strength; it could be small or large. When an eighth stage Life Destruction powerhouse finally reached the late Divine Sea realm, that minor dimension would be extremely vast. The liquid true essence would surge and tumble just like a vast sea. Thus, this boundary was called the Divine Sea!

To a martial artist, the Divine Sea realm was a major leap upwards. The word ‘Divine’ also indicated that martial artists who stepped into this realm gained the power of a god in the eyes of mortals. Their fists could shatter the skies, their feet could crack the earth, and they were capable of upturning the oceans. They were simply omnipotent beings!

And now, this young woman named Qin Yu had given birth to a rudimentary minor dimension within her dantian, with half of her true essence liquefied. This was the sign that she was a half-step into the Divine Sea realm!

Once one reached half-step Divine Sea, then barring any accident, they would be able to become a Divine Sea Supreme Elder within two or three years.

This Qin Yu was already destined to become a Divine Sea powerhouse.

Chapter 891 – Seize

An endlessly stretching demon claw fired towards Lin Ming like a twister. A terrifying aura completely locked down the surrounding space, making it so that Lin Ming couldn’t dodge even if he wanted to.

At this critical moment, Lin Ming’s pupils contracted and he suddenly thrust out the Great Desolate Blood Halberd in his hands.

Ohh!

The flaming phoenix cried out, the Nine Heavens Divine Thunder impacted straight into the dark skies.

The intense collision caused all of the space around Lin Ming to explode. The intertwining power of thunder and fire was actually unable to resist the power of that demon claw.

This was the disparity of absolute strength. When coupled with the creeping influence of that demonic charm, even if Lin Ming’s attributes repelled Yang Yun, he still wasn’t his match.

Bang!

Thunder and fire were forcefully torn apart. Although part of that demon claw was melted away, it still grasped down on Lin Ming’s body!

His protective true essence ripped apart along with his clothes, revealing the Demon Emperor Armor beneath.

Although the quasi-Saint artifact level Demon Emperor Armor was tough, it still had a fatal flaw in the hole at the chest. The Ancient Devil was treacherous and cunning; all of the attack’s energy slipped past that flaw.

Puff!

Lin Ming spat out a mouthful of blood, his entire chest covered in red! The Thunder Battleform nearly completely vanished. The disparity was just too great!

Yang Yun chased forwards, sending out another claw. Lin Ming wasn’t able to gather himself; he simply wasn’t able to resist.

“Hehe, be a good little boy and obediently let me seize your body!”

This claw easily enveloped Lin Ming. Lin Ming was caught in this hand as if he would be crushed at any moment.

“Essence! Energy! Soul! Devour all!”

That massive devil phantom appeared behind Yang Yun once again. The devil opened its great maw and a black vortex appeared, beginning to attract everything towards it. Lin Ming felt his spiritual sea become restless. The blood vitality within him raged and his true essence trembled as if it would be pulled out from him at any moment.

Essence, energy, and soul were the three treasures that comprised a human being, the life vigor of an individual. Essence was vitality, power of the bloodline, the very basis of the mortal body. Energy was origin energy and the dantian’s true essence. The soul was the primordial spirit, the marriage of spirit and will.

The Ancient Devil wanted to swallow up Lin Ming’s essence, energy, and soul. Once he lost those three things, he would lose everything that he was!

At this life or death moment, Lin Ming’s mind was still unbelievably calm. That Ancient Devil didn’t dare to directly seize his body because it wasn’t willing to engage in a showdown of will and soul. First, he would suck away his vital essence and weaken him to increase its strength. At that time it would have a much higher assurance of possessing Lin Ming.

In other words, even if the Ancient Devil knew that Lin Ming’s final trump card was his silver battle spirit, it still didn’t have anything it could do. This was because in order to possess Lin Ming’s body, it had no choice but to engage in a showdown of will.

In that instant, the silver battle spirit within Lin Ming’s spiritual sea howled forth. His originally restless soul force was immediately suppressed and his will stabilized!

But the power of blood and all of the energy within his body seemed as if it would break out at any moment.

“Silver battle spirit, sword of will!”

Lin Ming shouted out loud, and a silver white sword of will shot out from between his eyebrows. This sword of will had the power of thunder poured into it. This projection of will mixed with the power of thunder thrust straight towards the Ancient Devil behind Yang Yun!

The sword of will could only be used to extinguish bodies of will, spiritual beings that had no physical existence. For instance, when Lin Ming had crossed Life Destruction and the Purple Lion Thunder Source had attacked him, it had been injured by the battle spirit manifestation of his will. And this current Ancient Devil soul in front of him was also a kind of will body!

“Hehe, how naïve! Although I am not afraid of your silver battle spirit, that doesn’t mean that I’ll freely engage you in a battle of wills. Return!”

In that moment, the giant devil phantom behind Yang Yun was sucked back into his body without the least bit outside. When the Ancient Devil still had a mortal form, its cultivation had been extremely high and its battle spirit accomplishments were no worse than Lin Ming’s. It was only because its soul was incomplete so its will was slightly weakened, thus it didn’t want to give Lin Ming even the slightest chance.

Lin Ming could feel the Ancient Devil stop absorbing his life vigor. And at the same time, Lin Ming’s sword of will chopped through the void!

Once a soul entered a body, that soul would only enter the world of will for a will showdown if they so decided on their own initiative, otherwise, it was impossible to use a battle spirit to directly kill the life of another. This was the reason that a battle spirit had to be attached to a material object.

With his true essence moving restlessly and his blood vitality also suppressed, Yang Yun suddenly stretched out his demon claw and grasped out at Lin Ming. “Jejejeje, I do not need to swallow your essence, energy, and soul in order to kill you all the same! In front of me you are nothing more than a little baby: useless and weak!

“Netherworld Demon Claw!”

Monstrous ghosts filled the skies and space itself was torn apart like paper. Lin Ming tightly guarded his mind and the power of thunder within the Heretical God Sprout burst out without hesitation.

“Power of death! Sword of Judgment!”

Purple lightning condensed into the phantom of a divine sword, slashing through the infinite skies! This was also one of the Eightfall Thunder Emperor’s famed unique techniques. The power of thunder was most effective at suppressing ghosts and demons; the Sword of Judgment was Lin Ming’s most effective attack method!

“Humph, the Eightfall Thunder Emperor’s Sword of Judgment? Even if the Eightfall Thunder Emperor were to personally arrive here, he still might not be able to harm me. Your cultivation is simply far too low to the point that it doesn’t even matter at all! Break for me!” The Ancient Devil could sift through Yang Yun’s memories. It was well aware of the Eightfall Thunder Emperor and his Sword of Judgment, and simply didn’t place it in his eyes at all.

The Netherworld Demon Claw smashed into the Sword of Judgment. A tiny bit of that demon claw was melted away by the power of thunder, but the Sword of Judgment was directly grasped by that Netherworld Demon Claw and shattered to bits!

The Sword of Judgment was connected to Lin Ming’s will. As it shattered, his face turned paper white. At this time, the power from burning the Ancient Phoenix blood had nearly all faded away. Burning the Ancient Phoenix blood simply required too much true essence. Even if his true essence reserves were extremely deep right now, he still couldn’t sustain this continued combustion of the Ancient Phoenix blood. When he fought Situ Yaoyue, he had only burnt this blood for a very short time.

Once Lin Ming lost the support of the Ancient Phoenix blood, it would no longer be possible for him to resist the Ancient Devil.

“Is your strength almost gone? What a pity. If you had the Electric Violet Kirin Saint Body and could reach the same degree as your Ancient Phoenix Saint Body, as well as reach a third stage Life Destruction cultivation, your power of thunder might pose a little bit of a threat to me. But now, everything you’re doing is merely the useless struggles of the dying!”

Yang Yun attacked once again. The only reason that the fight had dragged on to this point was that the Ancient Devil wanted to possess Lin Ming’s body. Otherwise, if it wanted to kill Lin Ming, he would have been long dead by now.

As Lin Ming saw Yang Yun rushing at him, his eyes flashed with a crazed light. He bit down on the tip of his tongue, burning the blood of the Ancient Phoenix even as he spat forth his blood essence!

Instead of having his body seized by others, he might as well burn his soul, combust his life source, and desperately fight with every last ounce he had!

“You want to combust your life source? Your body is already mine, how can I let you ruin it? Time Laws, Concept of Stagnation!”

In that moment when Lin Ming was about to burn his soul, he suddenly felt the flow of time slow down around him. The fluttering of his fires of life, his heartbeat, his nerves, his will, his divine soul, everything slowed down, nearly coming to a screeching halt. It was like he was an old wooden puppet that was thickened with age and dirt.

Time Laws!

Lin Ming’s consciousness sobered in that moment. He wanted to use his own understanding of the Concept of Time to break through this time cage, but compared to the Ancient Devil, his strength was like a little gust of wind blowing against a titanic tree; the disparity was too great!

The Ancient Devil before him had a boundary that was far too high. It was an existence that Lin Ming could hardly even look up to!

“It’s over!”

Yang Yun waved his hands and an infinite darkness came falling down. Lin Ming felt like the space around him had condensed into reality and he was mired in this thick darkness. He was unable to breathe, unable to even hear his own heartbeat!

Concept of Darkness!

This Ancient Devil was a fierce elite from 100,000 years ago. It was both skilled in the Concept of Time and the Concept of Darkness. It was exactly because it could change the flow of time with its Concept of Time that it could survive for 100,000 years in the Sea or Miracles. In terms of just its understandings towards the Concept of Time, the Ancient Devil surpassed even Old Man Good Fortune.

Lin Ming gradually lost control of his body. His limbs turned cold, his heart paused, and he found it hard to even have a single thought.

He poured the entirety of his will into his spiritual sea, tenaciously clinging onto that last bit of clarity in his mind. He waited for the Ancient Devil to enter and attempt to seize his body so that he could carry on the final battle of wills.

This would be Lin Ming’s last chance to make a comeback!

If he lost this battle then he would turn to nothing, leaving nothing behind but a zombie corpse. In this world, this body of his would no longer have anything to do with him.

“You want to cling to your body and attempt a final battle with me in a struggle for your body? I do not fear you! Let me tell you, when I still had a body, my cultivation had reached a boundary that you cannot possibly imagine! My true form’s battle spirit has already reached silver perfection, just a single step from becoming a gold battle spirit! That is far higher than your elementary silver level! Do you actually think you can win? How stupid of you! Hahahaha!”

The Ancient Devil’s voice clearly resounded in Lin Ming’s ear. But Lin Ming tightly maintained his spiritual sea, no longer allowing his will and belief to be shaken by these words. He had already suffered a loss to this demonic charm and he wouldn’t fall for it a second time. He was well aware that the reason the Ancient Devil was wasting so much strength to weaken him was because this being didn’t have a complete assurance it could steal his body. Otherwise, there was no reason it would spout so much crap, all in order to tear down his own confidence and will. Even this current blabbering was the same!

Perhaps it might have really achieved a perfect silver battle spirit, but after 100,000 years of being sealed in the Sea of Miracles, its soul must have been severely wounded. The soul was the vessel of will. Once the soul was damaged, one’s will would inevitably weaken. Although those ancient Supreme Elders’ wills could endure for over 100,000 years without extinguishing, that will was incomparable to how it was in their peak form.

“Fight! I must win this fight!” Lin Ming’s mind was incomparably firm and filled with determination. In that moment, his silver battle spirit howled, faintly seeming as if it would evolve to the silver small success level!

“This brat actually isn’t fooled by me, but that doesn’t matter. All that means is that I will have to consume some of my vital primordial essence. Victory is already guaranteed.”

The Ancient Devil had already spent an immense amount of effort creating his plans. It had been preparing for this for thousands of years already in the Sea of Miracles. It started with Yang Yun, and then came to the Sky Spill Continent and continued the next steps in its grand plan. Finally, it had chosen Lin Ming to be its mortal vessel. How could it possibly fail at the final step?

“Give me your mortal body!”

The Ancient Devil roared and split its soul in two. The more formidable part thrust through the chaotic darkness, penetrating into Lin Ming’s body!

The Ancient Devil left behind a third of its soul as support. In these last 100,000 years, the Ancient Devil had developed a character that could not be more cautious. It left behind a third of its soul in Yang Yun to control him. The Ancient Devil did not trust anyone. If Yang Yun decided to do something to him while it was seizing Lin Ming’s body and it finally became the victim in all this then it truly would be an idiot.

Another reason was to guard against any helper of Lin Ming’s. It would be able to call upon this leftover soul to support it at any time.

Chapter 903 – The Goddess In Ice

Bang!

In the Road of Emperor’s world of will, Lin Ming’s will turned into a stream of light as he smashed into a golden statue. The violent impact caused his entire body to split apart!

“Break!”

Bolts of lightning, the power of fire, the power of space, and the Time Laws recklessly washed downwards, completely enveloping that golden statue!

Ka ka ka!

Cracks began appearing in the golden statue. Lin Ming had already exchanged over 600 moves with it, constantly barraging it and constantly breaking it apart. He exhausted every single one of his techniques before forcefully grinding that gold statue to nothing.

“It’s finally over!” Lin Ming’s shattered will form began joining back together. His mind was dizzy and his footsteps were muddled. It felt like the first time he had drawn his body inscription symbol and had overdrawn his soul force in the process.

The will light that had followed the Demon Emperor’s one had stranded him here for a full half year!

During this half year, Lin Ming had been constantly fighting, carrying on a life or death battle with this golden battle spirit. This nameless Supreme Elder had clearly lived over 100,000 years ago. Before he died, his boundary was also much higher than the Demon Emperor’s had been. If his complete will form had been here then Lin Ming simply wouldn’t have had any ability to resist.

Lin Ming relied on his unyielding perseverance and tenacious will. After constantly breaking himself against that golden battle spirit and continuously polishing and tempering his battle spirit again and again, only then did he eliminate it!

And in the process of this battle, every time Lin Ming’s will form was broken, his battle spirit gained more and more experience. During this half year, his battle spirit became more solid, more real, and increasingly sharp, as if it were faintly about to break through to the silver large success level.

Lin Ming’s battle spirit was just like a treasure spear. The materials and array formation used to forge it were all top class of top class ingredients, but it simply hadn’t been sharpened.

With a deep foundation the potential would be immense. But if it wasn’t sharp enough then a battle spirit wouldn’t be able to display its true strength. First he had to sharpen and whet his battle spirit, creating a keen edge. This would allow Lin Ming’s battle spirit to quickly bloom in terrifying glory.

And in this world, the best place to temper a battle spirit was likely this Road of Emperor. It had been created by an Empyrean from the Divine Realm, and could even be refined to complete a divine artifact.

After the gold battle spirit shattered, it turned into pure energy that nourished Lin Ming’s battle spirit. Within Lin Ming’s spiritual sea, the mist around the spear-shaped battle spirit became increasingly thick, as if it were condensing into droplets.

His battle spirit was now near the silver large success stage. He was only separated by a thin layer of film; he would break through at any moment.

And at this time, there were still two will lights left!

Lin Ming looked at the end of the Road of Emperor and let out a long breath. As he looked at the next will light, he saw that the flames were a deep blue color. Looking at this light, he discovered that it was easy to fall into an illusion when watching it and be trapped for eternity. It resembled the smoky waves of an endless sea. This will light contained an unblemished and hallowed energy. It was calm and profound, yet containing a deep power.

Lin Ming sat down in meditation, entering the ethereal martial intent to adjust himself to his best condition.

Then, he resolutely entered the will world of that ghostly blue fire.

This world of will was located at an unfathomably deep seabed. The dark blue seawater seemed as if it were carved from the purest gems. Exquisite small fish swam through the water, and Lin Ming knew that these fish were phenomena transformed from the purest will energy.

At the seabed, the sand looked like crystal clear pearls. There were fascinating and bewitching jade shells that were scattered over the ground, making the entire landscape seem like a dream.

And among this sand, there was a massive shard of chilling ice silently laying there. Lin Ming gazed at this ice shard and was suddenly shocked. Sealed within this shard of ice was a young veiled woman.

This young woman was curled into a round fetal position, grasping both of her knees. Her long and slender legs shined like clear crystal, and her beautiful face rested between her knees. Her long black hair hung down like an inky waterfall, covering up her body.

This young woman appeared exactly the same as the goddess from the Eternal Demon Abyss!

“If the penultimate will light contains the sealed will and spirit mark of the goddess, then is Empyrean Primordius sealed within the last will light?”

Lin Ming sucked in a breath of cold air. These final two will lights were actually from Supreme Elders! It was impossible to imagine just what degree of formidability their will forms reached!

“Empyrean Primordius sealed away the goddess’ will form here. Did he think that after the goddess died, she could reincarnate through the Samsara Road? And in the Eternal Demon Abyss, there is also the Great Emperor’s heart that is sealed within the goddess. That heart is able to destroy all evil spirits and beings that dare move against the goddess’ corpse, and is even able to preserve her lifelike appearance after 100,000 years!”

All sorts of thoughts flashed through Lin Ming’s mind. He harbored a deep respect for this goddess that was deeply sleeping in this shard of ice. Within, it looked as if she had merely fallen asleep. Even her long eyelashes appeared as if they were gently trembling.

Sunlight spread through the deep blue seawater, illuminating the entire land with brilliant splendor. A faint silver sheen of light glinted off of the skin of that young woman, making her seem as beautiful as a fading dream.

“Senior?”

Lin Ming tried to communicate with the goddess’ will form but failed. His perception simply wasn’t able to penetrate through that shard of ice. Even so, he could feel a powerful will contained within the goddess’ body. This was not a gold battle spirit, but an existence that surpassed even that.

“Demonshine, what is the boundary above a gold battle spirit?” Lin Ming suddenly asked.

“That is the blue soul battle spirit. The battle spirit will become dim and ethereal like smoke, and it will return from gold back to its original color. There is no way I can see through this goddess’ boundary.” Demonshine helplessly spread his doggy paws.

Lin Ming’s mind stirred. If he could take out the goddess’ sealed spirit from this will light and then fuse it into her sleeping body within the 1000 mile forbidden zone, would the goddess then be resurrected?

Without a doubt, Empyrean Primordius made many preparations for the goddess’ rebirth. Could it be that he wished for a successor to revive her?

It could even be that Empyrean Primordius had left behind his life’s inheritances within the Eternal Demon Abyss and the Sea of Miracles, all in order for destined individuals to find it!

“Empyrean Primordius placed the goddess’ life on a higher level of importance than his own. I wonder just what this goddess was to him? Lover? Daughter?” Lin Ming shook his head. These two explanations were not necessarily true. An Empyrean had a seemingly limitless lifespan. What scenes or events would they not have experienced in their lives? Would they really be captivated to such an extent by something like a lover? As for a daughter, that didn’t seem as if it could be justified either. As long as a martial arts Supreme Elder desired, they could have tens of thousands or even millions of children in their long lives.

“If I can reach a high enough boundary on the road of martial artists, perhaps I really can defy the will of the heavens and change the fate of life, reviving the goddess. At that time, I will discover just what Empyrean Primordius’ Samsara Road is, and just what secrets are contained in the Eternal Demon Abyss.”

As Lin Ming thought like this, he left the goddess’ world of will. The goddess’ will form was completely different from all those he had seen. It did not attack him, nor was there any way he could communicate with it. Since there was nothing he could do, he could only step back.

But as Lin Ming left the world of will, he suddenly felt a wave of energy break into his body like a gushing tide. The battle spirit in his spiritual sea rapidly condensed, and the thick mist around it became increasingly solid at a breakneck pace. His battle spirit had instantly broken through to the large success silver level! And the flow of energy did not stop there. From the early large success silver level, it rapidly climbed to the peak of large success!

Chapter 908 – Massacring Emperors

Asura Force Field. Capable of suppressing true essence, bodily strength, the soul, organs, and the spiritual sea. When a martial artist with insufficient cultivation was covered by the Asura Force Field, their spiritual sea would shatter and their heart would stop beating.

Death God Force Field. Formed from endless killing intent. Killing intent was itself a type of energy field. When a martial artist developed the desire to kill, they would emit an invisible energy. Once this killing intent reached an unparalleled level, it could even cut off all life vitality, extinguishing fires of life!

Prime Emperor Force Field. Reproducing the grandmist space. Here, Laws were suppressed, life was suppressed, the divine soul was suppressed, all of existence was suppressed. It would shatter the vast majority of supernatural powers. True essence, origin energy, battle spirit, will, soul, all would returning to nothingness, all would return to chaos!

Now, once these three great force fields were superimposed together, they formed the parts of the complete Heavenly Demon martial intent.

Although, this was only superimposing them over each other – it was in no way fusing the three together. Even so, it wasn’t the same as one plus one plus one equals three.

With the support of the other two great force fields, all of the fissures within the Prime Emperor Force Field completely vanished. The Prime Emperor Lotus Flower behind Lin Ming became even more succulent and vivid!

The grandmist space rose suddenly and sharply, expanding outwards, soaring into the skies!

“What a useless bluff. Watch as I shatter your force field!” With the fight reaching this boiling point, the Steppes Master put forth everything he had. He had a strong premonition that if he couldn’t kill Lin Ming today, he would die here!

“Great Demon Assassination Art, Apocalypse End!”

As the Steppes Master, Luosha’s martial skills were endlessly varied. As he saw his Concept of Blood suppressed by Lin Ming, he instantly changed styles. Demonic clouds roiled around him, rumbling through the air.

And behind him, the evil demon claw that the old Imp sent out was swallowed up by the endless dark clouds, combining with them.

A two-star Demon Emperor and a three-star Demon Emperor combined attacks. Their energies fused together, destroying all!

By now, Lin Ming had opened the Heretical God Force and all four of the Eight Inner Hidden Gates. Deep between his eyebrows, a flaming red light flashed out, blazing like a fire. From there, a vague red phoenix phantom shot into the skies, turning into a pure energy that integrated with the grandmist space!

Lin Ming had completely opened 100% of the Heretical God Force even as he burnt the blood of the Ancient Phoenix!

He had exerted his complete strength in a single breath. This was because simultaneously opening all three force fields was far too consuming of his true essence. The Prime Emperor Force Field now covered 500 feet of space. If anyone were to enter this space, it would truly be entering another world, not unlike stepping into a dimensional realm!

“Grandmist battle spirit, fusion!”

Sou!

With two Demon Emperors attacking the Prime Emperor Force Field together, a silver gray spear-shaped battle spirit shot out from between Lin Ming’s eyebrows. As this battle spirit appeared, it naturally collapsed and then fused together with the grandmist space.

A battle spirit could be used to directly kill an enemy, but it could be attached to any object. This included physical matter, true essence, and force fields. Although the grandmist space was able to isolate Laws and will was ineffective here, to Lin Ming, who was the master of this space, none of that mattered.

With the grandmist battle spirit combined together, the Prime Emperor Force Field expanded by another 300 feet!

Bang! Bang!

With two explosive sounds, in the moment that the Steppes Master and the old Imp broke into the grandmist space, all of their Laws became invalid. Their billowing demon essence began to rapidly melt like pure snow underneath the sun!

Moreover, the deeper they went, the faster their energy melted away. Even the Steppes Master and the old Imp’s protective demon essence began to dissolve!

“This is bad!”

The Steppes Master was shocked speechless as he watched with his own eyes as his bodily protective demon essence was melted by this strange and unknown space!

Kacha!

The Steppes Master’s black lance light was the first to explode. Then, the old Imp’s evil demon claw shattered. The two great supernatural powers, the attacks of two Emperor level powerhouses, had collapsed before they even reached Lin Ming’s body!

“Retreat!”

The Steppes Master and the old Imp rapidly drew backwards. In this grandmist space, they could only use brute force to tear apart this force field. Otherwise, all Laws and energy became invalid.

To an essence gathering system martial artist, energy was the basis for their style of combat. How could they continue fighting if they couldn’t utilize energy?

The Steppes Master thought that the combined strength of two Emperor level powerhouses would be able to tear apart Lin Ming’s Prime Emperor Force Field with brute force. But before the attacks had arrived, they had already melted away!

The Steppes Master and the old Imp tried to escape the grandmist space, but how could Lin Ming give them such a chance. With a thought, the grandmist mist spread forwards. At the same time, Lin Ming launched a movement technique and chased after the Steppes Master and the old Imp.

The truth was that the current Steppes Master and old Imp weren’t able to summon the demon essence within their bodies. If Lin Ming could use Penetrating Rainbow, a single spear strike would be able to slaughter them.

But supporting the galvanization of three great force fields into the Heavenly Demon martial intent was far too energy consuming. Lin Ming only had enough true essence by opening the Heretical God Force and burning the blood of the Ancient Phoenix at the same time; there was no leftover energy for him to use in an attack.

Ka ka ka!

Cracks began to appear in the Steppes Master’s protective demon essence; it was nearing the point of collapse. His complexion immediately changed.

“Split up and run!”

The old Imp roared out. The two of them chose different directions to run in, escaping at full speed!

Lin Ming’s grandmist space was less than a thousand feet long and wide, moreover, the Steppes Master and old Imp were both a good distance from the center of the force field. It would only take a brief moment to leave with their speed.

Seeing the edge of the force field in front of him, the Steppes Master’s eyes turned blood red. He had already reached his limits.

Lin Ming’s cold gaze locked onto the Steppes Master; he would kill him first!

Divine sense erupted and more force field energy came crashing down. In that instant, the Steppes Master’s last bit of energy completely collapsed. With an explosive ‘peng’ sound, his protective demon essence finally exploded!

The Steppes Master’s expression drastically changed. “Brat, I’ll die together with you!”

The Steppes Master had already gone mad. After realizing that Lin Ming had locked onto him, he didn’t even bother trying to escape anymore. He changed direction and rushed towards Lin Ming!

Facing the desperate attack of the Steppes Master, Lin Ming remained unmoved. More and more of the force field came crashing down on the Steppes Master. The Steppes Master wanted to send out an attack, but his body was empty; where did he have the energy to do anything?

“I… ahhhhh!”

The Steppes Master issued a miserable scream, but even this last cry was swallowed up by the grandmist space. His clothes disintegrated like they had been worn out over endless years, becoming powder that vanished into the wind. Then, his flesh began to crack apart. His meridians exploded, and pieces of flesh and blood flew into the grandmist space where they were instantly annihilated, turning into nothing. Then, his muscles, skeleton, marrow, organs, brain…

Grandmist space turned all matter into entropy and chaos. Even time and space could come under the influence of the grandmist space, where it could easily collapse into a singularity. Yin and yang hadn’t divided and the five main elements hadn’t even formed. In this case, once one lost the protection of energy, how could a flesh and blood physical form still survive? It would simply be returned to nothing within the grandmist space!

Hu – !

In just several breaths of time, the Steppes Master was like a sand sculpture that eroded away, his body dissipating and wafting away in countless particles of dust, with nothing left behind! The entire process had been silent. Sound needed a medium to travel through, thus a martial artist wouldn’t be able to hear anything but the sounds produced within their own body. The medium of the grandmist space was grandmist energy, an existence that was as heavy as stars. If one wanted to vibrate it and transmit sound waves, then how would that even be possible?

Like that, an Emperor level powerhouse had strangely died in utter silence. He had thoroughly perished without even bones left!

This terrifying scene left all the surviving High Lords and Tower Masters horrified, cold sweat streaming down their backs. Just what kind of ability was this? It was just a force field, and yet it was able to massacre a two-star Demon Emperor!

In the moment that the Steppes Master died, the old Imp actually let out a roar and ran out of the Prime Emperor Force Field!

He was still a three-star Demon Emperor after all. Even though he was old, his demon essence was still far more vast and deep than the Steppes Master’s. Just as he flushed out of the force field, his bodily protective demon essence exploded into pieces.

Peng!

The old Imp’s clothes all tore apart. He had felt the moment when the Steppes Master had died. This had left him shaken and panic-stricken. As soon as he rushed out, he rapidly fled deep into Heavenly Cloud Skysplit Tower.

Heavenly Cloud Skysplit Tower had been built and refined by Empyrean Primordius himself. The tower body was incomparably firm and it was impossible for anyone to break or mar it. With the various protective arrays within, it could be considered to be layered in traps and secrets.

The old Imp was the previous Steppes Master; he was extremely familiar with the layout of Heavenly Cloud Skysplit Tower. He was confident that with his own knowledge of Heavenly Cloud Skysplit Tower, that as long as he could draw a few miles away from Lin Ming, he would be able to take several transmission arrays and escape from this damned place.

And now because Luosha had attracted Lin Ming’s killing move, that had already won enough time for the old Imp. With his speed he was just like a nimble little mouse, rapidly traveling through the transmission channels of Heavenly Cloud Skysplit Tower and dashing 10 miles away.

“Monster! He’s just a monster! How could I have possibly encountered such an abnormal freak?!”

The old Imp hysterically shouted. How could a 25 year old possibly be so fierce!? This surpassed all common sense. Whatever Eightfall War Emperor, Demon Origin Emperor, Archaic Eternity Emperor, or even that Six Fingered Sin Fey that died in the Eternal Demon Abyss, when they were all 25 years old, all of them would be nothing but garbage in front of Lin Ming!

If the old Imp had known all of this earlier, he would never have come here to die, no matter what rewards Luosha promised him.

As Lin Ming watched the old Imp vanish in the blink of an eye and sneak into the complex maze-like roads of Skysplit Tower like a mouse, running into all directions, his lips curved up into a smile. Did this old Imp want to compare speed with him?

What he feared the least was a competition of speed. Without mentioning the Gate of Wonder or Golden Roc Shattering the Void, Lin Ming had comprehended the third level of the Concept of Thunder – Extreme Speed!

Of the seven elemental energies of metal, wood, water, fire, earth, wind, and thunder, wind was famed for its speed. However, wind was not the fastest. That honor belonged to thunder!

Golden Roc Shattering the Void, Mystic Lightning Shade!

Twelve different colored thunder symbols formed from threads of lightning began to shine from all over Lin Ming’s body. The dazzling threads of lightning had fully fused into Lin Ming’s flesh, gleaming with a blinding radiance.

After opening the Gate of Wonder and stepping on Golden Roc Shattering the Void, he also activated the arcane support ability, Mystic Lightning Shade!

In that instant, countless arcs of lightning crackled off of Lin Ming’s body. His body suddenly disappeared as he reached incredulous speeds.

The surviving martial artists felt their knees weaken as they almost slumped to the ground. In a one on one fight, Lin Ming was a monster amongst monsters. Even if one wanted to escape, he still had such ghostly speed! Even if someone were able to temporarily suppress Lin Ming by superiority of cultivation, as long as they couldn’t kill him then he would only need to return in two years to take his revenge.

How could such a person ever allow his enemy to live?

Chapter 909 – Sixth Opening of the Magic Cube

The dozens of miles of chaotic and convoluted roads within Skysplit Tower had all lost their meaning underneath Lin Ming’s steps. He flashed through in just a few fleeting moments, leaving nothing behind but a phantom of thunder!

“Transmission array! I’ve arrived!”

As the old Imp saw that transmission array, his eyes brightened with joy. He would already be lucky to escape from here with his life; how would he still care about his battle spirit being weakened?

The battle with Lin Ming had already cost him 200-300 years of his lifespan. But even when this was taken from the 1000 years of life remaining, he still had a great deal of time to live. How could the old Imp possibly give any of this up?

Hundreds of miles would only take a few breaths of time for an Emperor level powerhouse to travel. But with a dark killing star chasing from behind, the old Imp simply wouldn’t give him that much time.

But as he turned his head, he saw Lin Ming grasping the Great Desolate Blood Halberd, flitting forwards with the speed of ghosts and gods. He had already caught up to him!

“What!?!? How could you be so fast!?” As the old Imp saw Lin Ming barreling towards him, both of his eyes widened like full moons. A look of disbelief flashed across his face. He had run out for just one or two breaths of time, and yet he was overtaken by Lin Ming already? Was this kind of speed even possible?

“Wait… wait wait wait!” The old Imp’s eyes nearly popped out of his head with despair. He anxiously blurted out, “I don’t have any enmity or injustice with you, I was only helping out others for some wealth. I was only working for Luosha and I have no conflict of interests with you. If you let me go then there are massive benefits I can give you. I can teach you the High Chaos Devil Arts of my Imp race, and I can tell you where the greatest treasures of our Imp race are located! I can even give you massive amounts of Demon God Bones! If you kill me then you will only be able to obtain the items in my spatial ring, and as for all of those hidden treasures I just mentioned, you will never be able to obtain them, even if you search my soul. My soul force is powerful. Before I die, I can definitely self-destruct my spiritual sea. If you kill me, you will not obtain any of my secrets at all!”

The old Imp immediately threw out several conditions that he thought were quite tempting. Especially the High Chaos Devil Arts; he believed Lin Ming would be particularly interested in that. The High Chaos Devil Arts was a soul attack technique. The old Imp discovered that even though Lin Ming had a strong soul force, he still hadn’t cultivated any soul attack martial skills. If he had this High Chaos Devil Arts then he could increase his number of attack methods.

Hearing the old Imp’s conditions, Lin Ming only chuckled, “I don’t want any of that. All I want is one thing.”

“What do you want then?” The old Imp’s mind raced. As long as Lin Ming was willing to put forth some conditions then there would be hope and he could bargain with him. If the old Imp could keep his life, then giving everything he had to Lin Ming would be worth it.

Lin Ming grinned. “I only want… all of your blood essence. I wish to use it to open something.”

Steppes Master Luosha’s body had disintegrated to nothing in the grandmist space and had been completely destroyed; there was no blood essence left over to open the Magic Cube with. Fortunately, the old Imp was still here. As a three-star Demon Emperor, his blood essence was of a higher quality anyway.

“You are seeking death!”

The old Imp’s heart burned with a rage. If all of his blood essence was drawn out then his fires of life would also be extinguished. This Lin Ming was simply playing with him.

“Then I’ll bet everything against you! Let’s perish together!”

The old Imp burst out with a loud roar, suddenly biting down on his tongue and spitting out blood essence. Behind him, the chaos demon spirit phantom appeared once more, except this time it was much weaker and fainter than before. The High Chaos Devil Arts were his life’s greatest supernatural power, but this strongest soul attack of his was actually suppressed by Lin Ming. Now, he could only use material attacks.

“Heavenly Demon Suppression!”

The old Imp stretched out a withered palm and slashed at Lin Ming. Lin Ming raised the Great Desolate Blood Halberd and the Prime Emperor Lotus Flower bloomed once more. He intended to use the force field to avoid the old Imp’s true body and attack the chaos demon spirit phantom behind him.

Peng!

Cracks began to appear in the chaos demon spirit phantom behind the old Imp; this caused the old Imp’s attack to weaken by over half.

By not fully activating the Prime Emperor Lotus Flower with his complete strength, this left enough energy for Lin Ming to attack.

“Concept of Thunderfire – Penetrating Rainbow!”

A highly compressed power of thunder and fire crazily gushed out from the Heretical God Sprout. The Great Desolate Blood Halberd came falling down, crashing into the chaos demon spirit phantom.

In that instant, the scene was similar to sledgehammer striking a thin pane of glass. The chaos demon spirit phantom directly exploded, and Lin Ming’s Great Desolate Blood Halberd continued with vigor, crashing into the old Imp’s chest.

The old Imp’s protective true instantly exploded as Lin Ming’s halberd smashed into his chest, creating a large dent and forcing the old Imp to vomit out a mouthful of blood.

As this strike succeeded, Lin Ming didn’t give his enemy a chance to escape. The Prime Emperor Force Field dispersed, and he waved the blood halberd in his hands, space cracking around it.

“Law of Annihilation, Chain of Stars!”

Ca!

Countless space fragments stabbed into the old Imp’s body like innumerable sharpened knives. Blood splashed into the air. The old Imp’s supernatural powers had been shattered by Lin Ming’s battle spirit, and his own battle spirit had fallen by two small boundaries because of it. He had been injured in the grandmist space and his origin of life was greatly damaged. Now that he faced Lin Ming, who his most skilled soul attacks were useless against, he simply didn’t have the strength to resist.

“You…” The old Imp’s face was covered in blood. His body was like a broken water bag filled with space shards. He looked like a grieving spirit that had been dismembered during life; it was beyond miserable.

“If you want me to die, then I won’t let you be any better off!”

The old Imp fiercely slammed down on his tongue, directly biting it off. He spat out blood essence as energy erupted from his body! He wanted to burn all of the blood essence within him, so that even if Lin Ming killed him, he still wouldn’t have any blood essence to open the Magic Cube!

And an Emperor level powerhouse, even if their body was crushed, could instantly mobilize the energy in their body even if they had just a small amount of consciousness left over. Wanting to instantly kill them wasn’t easy.

Lin Ming sneered as he saw this. His fist came pounding out, surrounded by a dim silver gray light. This was his grandmist battle spirit.

“Concept of Stagnation!”

At that moment, the flow of time around the old Imp suddenly slowed down. He felt as if his body had been petrified, and even his thoughts slowed down. The energy circulating in his meridians slowed down to a crawl. He wanted to burn all of his blood essence to commit suicide, but he lacked the force to do so!

The old Imp’s eyes widened with unwillingness and despair.

The Concept of Time… he had comprehended the Concept of Time…

Body Tearing Bone Shattering Fist!

Peng!

Lin Ming’s fist smashed into the old Imp’s forehead and thousands of vibrating true essence filaments imbued with his grandmist battle spirit broke into the old Imp’s body. All of the old Imp’s meridians shattered, and even his spiritual sea collapsed!

With Lin Ming’s current understanding towards the Concept of Stagnation, he could bring the flow of time to nearly a standstill for a split-second. It was enough to completely kill the old Imp and even disintegrate his soul.

No matter how powerful the vitality of a Demon Emperor was, they were finished once their spiritual sea shattered.

Plop!

When the effects of the Concept of Stagnation ended, the old Imp fell onto the ground like a pile of crushed meat, blood splashing everywhere.

As Lin Ming saw the old Imp thoroughly die but still retain 90% of his blood essence, he relaxed. If the old Imp had really burned off all his blood essence, then that would really have been troublesome. In order to open the Magic Cube again, he would have to find some other Emperor level powerhouse in the Holy Demon Continent and kill them. But Lin Ming wasn’t a bloodthirsty killer. He needed a reason to kill others – he wouldn’t slaughter innocents.

“I never thought that the Prime Emperor Force Field obtained through the Road of Emperor could combine with the Asura Force Field and Death God Force Field, and massacre Emperor level powerhouses in such a manner. In the grandmist space, all Laws are annihilated, all energy is annihilated, and even all life and matter is annihilated, forcing all to return to the nothingness of chaos. But what a pity, this is truly a thorough killing method. After killing someone, nothing will be left behind. Even a spatial ring will be annihilated…”

Before Lin Ming obtained the Prime Emperor martial intent, he never thought that the so-called ability to massacre Emperor level powerhouses would be like this.

“I can’t indiscriminately use this killing method too much. Besides some tougher Saint artifacts, nothing else would remain.” Lin Ming shook his head. He hadn’t fused the three martial intents together, he had only superimposed them on top of each other. The power was already very strong, and in addition with the grandmist battle spirit fused into it, and the support of the Heretical God Force and the combusting Ancient Phoenix blood, it was able to massacre all Emperor level powerhouses weaker than himself.

As for those opponents that were stronger than him or were equally as strong as him, the grandmist space could still weaken their strength, increasing his chances of victory.

To weaken an enemy’s offensive power and defensive power by 60-70%, the result of a fight could be imagined. But, the only problem was that stimulating the complete Heavenly Demon martial intent consumed a massive amount of true essence. It was not easy for Lin Ming to do.

Lin Ming took out a small jade bottle from the Extreme Violet Ring and received all of the old Imp’s blood essence into it. Then, he wiped this blood essence onto the area of his chest where the Magic Cube was.

Until now, Lin Ming still couldn’t activate the Magic Cube with his strength. He could only let the Magic Cube act as a passive form of defense.

Lin Ming was very clear that the Magic Cube was a divine treasure that countless powerhouses within the Divine Realm had desperately struggled for, even paying with their lives in the process. Its function was certainly not so simple as holding soul fragments. As for what other uses it had, that still remained unknown to Lin Ming.

Hiss… hiss…

The old Imp’s blood essence was absorbed by the Magic Cube. In the next moment, Lin Ming felt a bit dizzy before he arrived at the space within the Magic Cube once again.

Since the time when Lin Ming killed a Life Destruction powerhouse to open the Magic Cube, over six years had passed!

In these six years, Lin Ming’s strength had crossed over the Life Destruction realm and reached the Divine Sea! It had to be known that Lin Ming had only obtained the Magic Cube when he was 15 years old. In the 10 years since then, Lin Ming had cultivated from Body Transformation to the Revolving Core realm in four years. But for his strength to rise from Life Destruction to the Divine Sea, that had taken a full six years. It was obvious just how difficult that step was to take!

The space within the Magic Cube was still dim and hazy as before. Countless soul fragments floated around like stars, slowly orbiting a central sphere of light. It looked like a wonderful and strange galaxy.

Lin Ming swept his perception through the area and quickly found two of the largest soul fragments. They were over a foot wide, much larger than the head of an average person.

These two soul fragments were naturally left behind from the Ancient Devil that resided within Yang Yun’s body. They contained exquisite Time Laws, Darkness Laws, and also fairly complete memories. This likely included the Ancient Devil’s weaknesses or secrets of the Eternal Demon Abyss.

The soul fragment that Lin Ming wished to choose this time was naturally a soul fragment of the Ancient Devil.

Chapter 917 – Kill, Kill, Kill!

As that blood red lotus fully bloomed, Situ Yaoxi felt an invisible energy field overwhelm the skies and fall over the world. This force field was desolate, bleak, and carrying with it the aura of the Great Dao Laws, making one unable to defy it and have no choice but to prostrate themselves to the floor in awe and worship.

Covered in this energy field, she felt the last dregs of power leave her body. Her true essence collapsed and dispersed away, and she lacked even the strength to grab a chicken. It was like she had turned back into a common mortal. Let alone attack Lin Ming, she didn’t even have the ability to run away.

“How could this happen?!” Situ Yaoxi said in panic. She was completely flustered. A martial artist was used to relying on their own strength. If they lost all of their strength and turned back into a mortal then how could they not be panicked?

Lin Ming didn’t even bother to glance at Situ Yaoxi. He grabbed Situ Yangon like a chicken and lifted him off the ground.

“You… what are you doing!?” Situ Yangon pedaled his legs in the air. Lin Ming’s hands were like a pincer, inescapable.

Lin Ming grinned devilishly, ignoring all of Situ Yangon’s miserable howls, “Didn’t you say you knew many obscenity path cultivation methods to suck up her primordial yin? Hehe, I will make it so that you’ll never be able to use these techniques again.”

“You… what are you planning to do!?” Situ Yangon thought that Lin Ming’s cold smile was like an inhuman devil’s. He shouted out even louder, trying his hardest to revolve his true essence, but no matter what he did, it was useless.

Lin Ming ignored Situ Yangon’s struggling. He lifted him higher, positioned himself between Situ Yangon’s legs and then shot his knee upwards!

Splat!

With the sound of a cracking egg, Situ Yangon let out a pitiful scream like a pig that was being butchered. Sticky blood dripped downwards. He felt a horrifying pain between his legs that made him wish he was dead!

Lin Ming’s knee strike had destroyed his functions as a man!

Martial artists’ capacity to withstand pain was extremely high. They could clench their teeth and break an arm or break a leg. They could even use heavenly materials to make up for their losses. But sexual organs were different; that was also where the dignity of a man was located. The psychological trauma of losing this part was even worse than physical pain.

“I was castrated… I was castrated… I, Situ Yangon, have resolved myself to become a Divine Sea powerhouse level extreme talent, and now I’ve been castrated by another!”

Situ Yangon’s pupils lost their focus. His lips trembled as he muttered to himself again and again. At this moment, his entire world had become dark and dreary!

Lin Ming sneered. Then, with a hard tug of his arm, there was a shockingly grotesque ‘ka ka ka’ sound as both of Situ Yangon’s hands were ripped off by Lin Ming! Lin Ming crushed Situ Yangon’s palms in his hands, even pulling out his bloody tendons!

Situ Yangon squealed like a pig. His entire body shook; this was a fate worse than death!

Like this, Lin Ming had crippled a fifth stage Life Destruction extreme genius. Without weapon, without martial skills, and without even true essence, he relied on only his physical strength to waste away Situ Yangon. This was a truly ridiculous level of strength!

Lin Ming tossed away Situ Yangon like a dead dog and then turned towards Situ Yaoxi and Situ Meiyue, his face filled with a fierce wrath!

At this time, both of Situ Yaoxi’s legs were trembling, and Situ Meiyue was frightened to the point of curling up on herself. Her chest was violently heaving up and down and her beautiful face was as white as paper. She painfully said, “No… don’t…”

As Situ Meiyue saw Lin Ming walk towards her, her legs gave way and she slumped to the ground. Her strength had vanished from her body and there was nowhere for her to retreat to. She was the same as Situ Yaoxi; underneath the effects of this strange force field, all of the true essence within her body had become stagnant. If it weren’t for Lin Ming deliberately not killing them, they would have been turned to ashes long ago!

“Weren’t you about to tear off her clothes and hack her to thousands of pieces?” Lin Ming first moved towards Situ Meiyue.

“I… I wouldn’t dare, I wouldn’t dare!” Situ Meiyue cried out. She had her own pride, but that was built over a foundation of absolute strength. And now that she was shrouded in the force field and had lost all of her strength, she was no different from a mortal. If she couldn’t do anything, just where would her pride come from?

Outside of the array, Lan Yunyue watched blankly as all of this happened. She had no idea what was going on within the array formation. Those three people were obviously extremely powerful characters that could overturn the heavens, but how come they had turned into common people in front of Lin Ming? They didn’t even have the strength to resist him and were letting him mess with them as he wished.

“Don’t kill me, no, please, I’ll do anything you want, I’ll even be your slave, please don’t kill me!” Situ Meiyue’s heart of martial arts was originally shakier than Situ Yaoyue’s and Situ Luosha’s. With the threat of death hanging over her head, she was completely cowed.

“Slave? Humph, I have no need for you! Let me show you what it means to reap what you sow!”

Lin Ming suddenly thrust out his hands and tore off Situ Meiyue’s clothes. Then he slammed his palm at her chest.

Pulse Cutting Palm!

Peng!

A violent true essence rampaged into Situ Meiyue’s body where it recklessly destroyed everything in its path. All of her meridians shattered and she vomited out a mouthful of blood. Her true essence was broken up by Lin Ming and even her dantian ruptured, with origin energy rapidly dissipating from her!

Lin Ming’s palm had completely wasted away all of Situ Meiyue’s remarkable abilities!

Situ Meiyue certainly knew just what had happened. Her lips shivered, her expression like a dying light. As a proud daughter of heaven, she was used to being haughty and standing above all others. To suddenly fall from the position she had in the clouds, the pain in her heart could be imagined!

Lin Ming grabbed Situ Meiyue and tossed her out of the Spectral Blood Skylock Array, right at Lan Yunyue’s feet. He had already become one with the Spectral Blood Skylock Array and he could open it however and whenever he wanted.

“I won’t kill you, I will let you keep your life. I’ve abandoned all of your abilities but you’ve still crossed six stages of Life Destruction. Although your supernatural powers are shattered, your mortal body was still tempered after all and you’ll have at least another thousand years of life. From this point onwards, you are her servant. You will act as her dog and bag and never violate a single order she gives. If you serve her diligently then perhaps I might restore some of your strength. Otherwise I will slowly hack you apart and make you wish I had killed you instead!”

Lin Ming had originally wanted to do to Situ Meiyue what she had been planning to do to Lan Yunyue. He would rip off her clothes and then slowly cut her apart. But as he began, he felt a tinge of disgust and loathing and thus chose a second punishment method instead.

“I’ll be a slave or servant…” Situ Meiyue’s lips shivered. For the proud and haughty her to serve a mortal for the rest of her life, that was even worse than killing her.

“Lin Ming… Lin Ming… you beast, I won’t let you go even when I’m a ghost!” Situ Yaoxi’s body trembled with anger and also with fear. In front of Lin Ming, she had no strength to resist him.

“Next is you!” Lin Ming slowly arrived in front of Situ Yaoxi, a fiendish grin hanging on his lips.

But at this time, the sound of bustling footsteps came from the other side of the door. Lin Ming turned to see several martial artists burst into the room. Most of them were juniors from the Asura Divine Kingdom, and there was even Elder Sun, whom Lin Ming had planted a tracing mark in.

“What happened here!?” As the others outside heard the pained screams coming from inside the front hall, they used their perception to investigate. However, their perception was blocked off from this area by some unknown force. By the time these people rushed over, they just happened to see this pitiful scene in front of them.

“Lin Lanjian!”

Elder Sun immediately recognized Lin Ming. However, he was still accustomed to calling Lin Ming by his fake name. This was because the name Lin Lanjian was his eternal nightmare!

“Hey, you’ve all made it here. Since you’ve come, don’t plan on leaving.” A cruel smile appeared on Lin Ming’s face.

Chapter 924(A) – Settling the Cycle of Karma

The space within the Extreme Violet Ring was sizable and comfortable. When Lin Ming received the Lin Family Clan into his spatial ring, he had left the majority of the buildings intact. As Lin Ming saw these buildings, memories began to emerge within his mind.

Hidden Smoke Hall. Rain Flower Pavilion.

As Lin Ming looked at these places that once resembled the most noble and upper crust society of the family clan, he felt emotions swell within him. These were areas that only the young masters and ladies of the family clan could enter. They would ride on wooden sedans and enjoy the flowery scenery. They would be accompanied by groups of servants as well as having trays of fruits and exquisite desserts waiting for them at any time.

When Lin Ming was young, this represented the ultimate lifestyle in his mind. He had longed for this type of wealthy life, and thought that after he grew up and reached the peak of martial arts, he could also become such a top character. But now, none of this was what he pursued.

In the past, Lin Ming came to the Lin Mansion several times with his father to prepare for great feasts. His job was to debone meat. With his sharp boning knife in hand, he would slice vicious beasts into various parts, and watch as his father cooked them into a number of different dishes.

Besides that, he and the Lin Family didn’t have much exchanges.

In the blink of an eye, ten years had passed. To martial artists that lived for tens of thousands of years, ten years was an insignificant period of time. But as Lin Ming recalled the memories of his childhood, all of those scenes and recollections of the past seemed blurry and remote.

The Lin Family descendants all arranged themselves according to rank and seniority and stood behind Lin Wanshan. A respected mortal family like the Lin Family had strict rules and tedious customs. Now that they were greeting Lin Ming, they naturally couldn’t show poor etiquette.

As the Lin Family descendants looked at Lin Ming, their eyes were filled with both respect and unease. To a legendary character like Lin Ming, all of them had been influenced by him, but very few had ever seen or heard from him. In the past several years, the Lin Family’s status had grown several times over, and they had faintly become the Sky Fortune Kingdom’s number one family.

Lin Wanshan had been assigned the title of Duke Lin. The Lin Family’s properties and businesses were countless. They could be said to be at the zenith of their glory. Even the Sky Fortune Kingdom Emperor Yang Lin had to be respectful when seeing Lin Wanshan. Not only did Lin Wanshan not need to bow, but he was even offered a site. In private, Yang Lin also had to call Lin Wanshan ‘Uncle Lin’.

Such respect and courtesy was rarely honored ever since the founding of the Sky Fortune Kingdom. Lin Wanshan wasn’t an idiot to think that Yang Lin treated him with respect because he appreciated his talents. Rather, all of this was because of Lin Ming. Even Yang Lin becoming the Emperor was because of Lin Ming’s support.

The truth was that after Lin Ming left the Seven Profound Valleys, the Lin Family descendants had no idea what degree Lin Ming had reached. They only knew that he was extremely fierce. Even after Situ Yaoxi and the others came, they still had difficulty understanding the situation of the world; those people already completely surpassed their imaginations.

Some Lin Family juniors and even elders began to pay their respects to Lin Ming and bow. This wasn’t unusual. According to the customs of the Sky Fortune Kingdom, if an Empress were produced within the family clan, then when the empress returned to her home, there would be a grand festive celebration. Everyone in the family would bathe in incense and there would be great banquets for days, ceremonial worshipping of ancestors, and events all around. Even the Patriarch of the family would have to bow down on both knees, even if he were the Empress’s father.

Now Lin Ming’s status was countless times higher than a mere Empress of the Sky Fortune Kingdom. According to the customs of a mortal family, everyone had to bow to Lin Ming.

There were many Lin Family descendants. Merely among the servants there were over a thousand sharing the same surname. As Lin Ming gazed upon such a large family, he actually didn’t feel much of a sense of belonging.

In his mind, his true family were his parents, his sister, and Lin Xiaodong, Mu Qianyu and Qin Xingxuan. Everyone else could only be considered distant relatives.

“Everyone, there is no need for such ceremony. Uncle Lin, please rise, I cannot afford such courtesy. When I left home in the past to pursue the road of martial arts, I never imagined I would bring such great blessings and such great disasters to the Lin Family. After the beast tide ended, I haven’t set foot in Green Mulberry City. I didn’t think that you all would be drawn into my troubles.

“Nephew Lin, you can’t say that. As long as the family clan remains prosperous in the future, then let alone losing a hand, I wouldn’t even blink if I had to sacrifice my life.

Lin Wanshan honestly and earnestly said. To a traditional respected family, the prosperity of the family clan and the passing of the glory onto the next generation was the most important matter. Even a clansman’s life was expendable in the face of such an important matter.

Lin Ming’s eyes moved to Lin Wanshan’s left hand and he saw that his hand had already been cut off. Lin Ming sighed. In this calamity, many Lin Family descendants should have died. There were even many that had lost their feet or arms, and all of this was because of him. He took out some pill bottles from his spatial ring and said, “Here are some medicinal pills that can regenerate limbs. For all those who had their arms or legs cut off, please take these pills to restore them.”

Spirit medicines that could regenerate mortal limbs weren’t considered too precious. Lin Ming had put out many different types of medicines, but none of these medicines were suitable for high level martial artists. To a high level martial artist that had crossed Life Destruction, their body would reform into a spirit body. If their arm was cut down and an ordinary untempered arm was attached in place of the old, then that would become nothing but a burden to them. In a fight, once true essence flooded into that limb, it would simply explode when it became unable to withstand the amount of true essence.

Of course, to a mortal and their daily life, none of this was a problem.

As Lin Wanshan saw all of these spirit medicines, his heart was overjoyed. No one wished to be disabled for the rest of their lives. As the rest of the Lin Family descendants saw these spirit medicines, that tiny trace of resentment they held towards Lin Ming also vanished.

“And here are some other medicines. Although they are useless to me, if a mortal were to take them, they can prologue life and eliminate all diseases. They can live for over a hundred some years. As for the rest, it’s to help raise the martial artists. Allow the martial arts masters of the family to eat these and it’ll allow them to break through the body transformation realm, and help their cultivation increase by leaps and bounds. If a Houtian master were to eat these medicines, it can even help them break through to the Xiantian realm.

As Lin Ming spoke, he took out another massive pile of medicinal pills. All of these medicines pills had been obtained from the countless martial artists he had killed. These were only basic low level medicines, but to a small sect they were priceless treasures.

Just these dozens of medicinal pills that could allow a Houtian master to break into the Xiantian realm was enough to make a third-grade sect go crazy with jealousy. One can see this from just how much effort Qin Ziya had spent in order to obtain a Heaven Opening Pill.

“These, these are spirit pills that can allow a Houtian master to break into the Xiantian realm?” Lin Wanshan gulped with some difficulty. He had some experience and certainly knew how precious these types of miracle medicines were. They were truly precious! A single one of these pills was equivalent to a city!

Lin Ming had casually handed out several dozen of these pills.  That was equal to several dozen cities worth of wealth. Lin Wanshan was unavoidably uneasy that such precious treasures were placed within the family clan.

Lin Ming saw through Lin Wanshan’s thoughts and said, “Rest assured, the sects that will be jealous of these pills are small sects; they won’t dare to move against the Lin Family. As for those sects that dare to move against the Lin Family, they won’t care about these low level medicines.”

Lin Ming waved his hand. These words caused all of the Lin Family descendants to fall into a incredulous daze. To casually hand over so many pills on the level of a Heaven Opening Pill and still call them low level medicines, Lin Ming’s boundary was simply unimaginable.

Lin Ming thought for a moment and then pulled out a set of puppets from his spatial ring. There were a total of 18 puppets, and each one resembled a cruel demon, grim and savage as if they were devils that had crawled up from hell.

These were the puppets left behind by Corpsemancer. He had used these puppets when he was still at a low stage of Life Destruction, but after he entered the Destiny Decree, these puppets weren’t too useful to him anymore. They remained as only part of his collection. Lin Ming originally didn’t have any use for them, but now they actually came in handy.

Lin Ming took out a jade slip and placed his soul mark on it. He poured some true essence into the jade slip and passed it to Lin Wanshan “Just for emergencies. I give these puppets to the Lin Family as protective guards. If the Lin Family suffers a disaster one day, they can use this jade slip to control the puppets and safely pass through that calamity. This jade slip can be given to the Patriarch of the Lin Family. It can be considered a keepsake of the Patriarch and passed down through generations.

As Lin Ming spoke, the Lin Family descendants stared at the puppets with curiosity and horror. Corpsemancer was a bloodthirsty individual that loved death and chaos. These puppets had mostly been crafted from the corpses of top masters, and their skin and bones were tempered by sacrifices. These 18 puppets had crossed through oceans of blood, and the killing intent they exuded was nearly thick enough to condense into reality. If a mortal looked at them for too long, their souls would be damaged.

“Don’t look at them,” Lin Ming calmly said. He sent out an energy wave that completely isolated the killing intent emanating from the puppets.

The mortal Lin Family descendants were all lost in a stupor until Lin Ming sealed off the puppets’ killing intent. Their consciousness slowly returned, and a cold sweat began to ooze off their bodies. If just looking at these inactive puppets could do this to them, then it was hard to imagine how powerful they would be once activated!

Lin Ming flicked his fingers and 18 gray balls of energy shot into the 18 puppets; this was the compressed Heavenly Demon Force Field. He said, “Any one of these 18 puppets can easily sweep away the Seven Profound Valleys. If the 18 of them join forces, their power will increase a hundred times over. It will be enough to protect the Lin Family and guarantee your safety.”

“Sweep, sweep away the Seven Profound Valleys? 18 join forces, their power will increase a hundred times over?”

Lin Wanshan’s eyes widened as he heard Lin Ming’s words. Although he knew Lin Ming had reached a boundary that none of them were able to comprehend, the Seven Profound Valleys was still a heaven-like existence to the mortals of the Sky Fortune Kingdom. Even the Emperor wasn’t able to defy them, and the Seven Profound Valleys could even remove the Emperor if they wished. If that wasn’t heaven, then what was?

And such a heaven could be easily swept away by a single puppet. The psychological impact to Lin Wanshan could be imagined!

Lin Ming said, “That’s right. But the true essence I left behind in this jade slip is only enough to activate these puppets two times. Once they have been activated two times and the true essence is exhausted, the force field I left within the puppets will swallow them up and reduce them to dust. This is also to prevent other sects from coveting these puppets and bringing trouble to the Lin Family.”

“Only two times…” As Lin Wanshan heard these words, he thought it was somewhat a pity. It was obvious that Lin Ming had the ability to activate these puppets many more times, but he simply didn’t want to do that. For him to destroy these puppets after they were used, proved that these puppets weren’t worth anything to Lin Ming.

Lin Ming continued, “Two times is the limit. This is to prevent the descendants of the family clan to use these puppets to wage war with the world, recklessly plundering other lands and committing evil.”

“For a large family clan to rely on external forces to establish itself, that will make the family clan’s foundation shaky and able to fall apart in a single night. Placing a limit of two times is so that the family clan will only use them in periods of great calamity. If the Lin Family wishes to develop, then they must rely on their own foundations. As for what possible calamities may come your way, that will likely only happen when the switching of dynasties occurs, and that is only something that happens every several hundred years. These 18 puppets will guarantee the Lin Family a thousand years of prosperity. That alone should be enough.”

Chapter 929 – To Another Level

“The Heretical God Sprout grew.”

Lin Ming was overjoyed as he saw the Heretical God Sprout that had grown by an inch. He could clearly feel that the Heretical God Sprout’s strength increased by a great deal. This would help him to perceive the Concepts of Thunder and Fire to an even higher degree in the future. It was as if there was some divine power assisting him. After he ascended to the Divine Realm, chances were likely that he would join the Ancient Phoenix Clan and receive the direction of Fairy Feng. At that time, with the support of the Heretical God Sprout, his strength would surely rapidly rise.

After the Purple Lion Thunder Source was completely absorbed, lightning began to twinkle above the Heretical God Sprout. Lin Ming closed his eyes and sensed within himself, nodding with satisfaction. The Heretical God Sprout’s control of energy was far better than what he had imagined. After the Purple Lion Thunder Source entered the Heretical God Sprout, most of its energy was absorbed by the Heretical God Sprout and the control of that energy also fell into Lin Ming’s hands.

If the Purple Lion Thunder Source’s spiritual wisdom was a general, then the energy of its body was the army. But now, all military power was held by Lin Ming.

This feeling of controlling all was very gratifying. As Lin Ming’s strength grew, the chances of the Purple Lion Thunder Source betraying him would also become increasingly low.

“Demonshine, after absorbing the Purple Lion Thunder Source, I feel as if my entire body is flooded with energy. Breaking through to the fifth stage of Life Destruction shouldn’t be difficult!”

“You want to break through to the fifth stage of Life Destruction? You haven’t even entered the fourth stage of Life Destruction for a full year, and you want to break through to the fifth stage? Your cultivation has been far too fast recently. If you don’t suppress this speed it’ll cause your foundation to be shakier and make it harder for you to advance in the future.”

A general Emperor level talent would step into Life Destruction at 50 years of age. From that point on, they would pass a stage of Life Destruction every 7-8 years, finally reaching a maximum of six or seven stages.

But for Lin Ming, he nearly crossed a stage of Life Destruction every year. In less than five years he had crossed four stages of Life Destruction and was about to cross the fifth.

Lin Ming’s cultivation had risen too quickly, and more importantly, for these last five years, Lin Ming hadn’t experienced true combat too much. Without tempering himself in the fires of the battlefield, this would cause his comprehension of Laws and martial skills to be flawed and imperfect, resulting in further instability within his foundation.

Lin Ming said, “I know, but I can still make up for it in the future. As long as I break through to the Divine Sea realm and calmly cultivate, I’ll be able to calm down and solidify my energy. Although it will be a great deal of work, I’ll face Yang Yun soon and I must increase my strength as much as possible before then. A year from now, Yang Yun’s strength will absolutely surpass Whitedemon’s. With my current cultivation, even if I absorb the Purple Lion Thunder Source, I don’t think I’ll be able to defeat him.”

“Indeed. Yang Yun is proficient in the Concept of Time. If he changes the flow of time and seals himself up within a space, he might be able to train for ten years in this one year. I fear he might even break into the middle Divine Sea.”

Demonshine said with a bit of worry. Eight stages of Life Destruction, breaking into the middle Divine Sea, as well as Yang Yun’s cultivation methods not being too bad to begin with, if all of these factors were combined together then Lin Ming truly was in a dangerous position.

“Yang Yun can indeed change the flow of time, but to change the flow of time in an enchantment requires a martial artist to constantly revolve the power of Laws to maintain it. If he wishes to put forth his full heart and effort, completely investing in cultivating his supernatural powers, it’s actually difficult to maintain the change in time flow to a 10 to 1 degree.”

A martial artist had to wholeheartedly devote their attention to cultivating. The reason that Lin Ming’s ethereal martial intent was so amazing was because it allowed him to eliminate all distractions from his mind.

The best condition for cultivation was to remain in a selfless state, free of all distractions. To cultivate in such a manner and also maintain the enchantment was extremely difficult. When Old Man Good Fortune had done so in the past, it was because he had reached a bottleneck in his cultivation for thousands of years already. The so-called closed door seclusion was actually sitting in meditation, self-cultivation his soul, becoming aware of the Laws, and tempering his will. It was incomparable to what Yang Yun needed to do.

In order to cultivate in a 10:1 time flow enchantment, he would have to have another powerhouse devote themselves to maintaining the revolution of Laws. This was the only way in which he would be able to completely invest himself in cultivating. But wasn’t it easier said than done to find a powerhouse like that, who would also serve him for so many years?

In truth, Lin Ming could accomplish his. With his current understandings into the Concept of Time, he could also achieve this point to a degree. Although he couldn’t change the flow of time to a 10:1 ratio, 5:1 or even 6:1 wasn’t a problem.

Lin Ming received the grandmist space and flew straight to the cave dwelling that the Eightfall Thunder Emperor had opened in the past.

This cave dwelling was located on one of the floating islands. But, this floating island was actually not located in the 100 mile Thunder Dominion, but within the 90 mile Thunder Dominion.

This was the only floating island within the 90 mile Thunder Dominion. As for the islands in the 100 mile Thunder Dominion, even the Eightfall Thunder Emperor didn’t have the ability to approach them.

Lin Ming flew into the Eightfall Thunder Emperor’s cave dwelling. The plain and simple cave revealed an ancient and timeless atmosphere, no different from the last time that Lin Ming was here. The stone tablet within the cave dwelling stood tall, with the same words engraved on it as before.

“If fate will not accommodate my clan, then I shall break the shackles of fate. If the heavens will not accommodate my clan, then I shall go against heaven’s will and cut down all immortals!”

These words contained a thrilling sword intent, causing those who saw it to feel awe in their hearts.

As Lin Ming’s boundary grew, he could increasingly feel just how powerful the Eightfall Thunder Emperor of the past was.

“Since ancient times, several unrivalled powerhouses appeared from the Sky Spill Continent that have been given the highest under the heavens title. Even amongst all of them, the Eightfall Thunder Emperor was outstanding.

The so-called highest under the heavens was someone that had the ability to instantly kill off all other powerhouses from their era. This was not merely defeating them, but killing them.

Before the appearance of Yang Yun and Whitedemon, even Old Man Good Fortune wasn’t able to achieve this degree of strength. This was why he was only considered the quasi strongest under the heavens.

Among the several highest under the heavens that had appeared throughout the years, there existed the strong and the weak amongst them. Whitedemon could only be considered as being on the weaker end.

Lin Ming sucked in a deep breath and sighed, “Even though I absorbed the Purple Lion Thunder Source, I shouldn’t be much stronger than him. Defeating him should be easy, killing him is extremely difficult though. If this were in ancient times, I could only be considered the lowest level of the highest under the heaven individuals within the Sky Spill Continent.”

In terms of pure quantity of peerless powerhouses, the Sky Spill Continent was far inferior to the Holy Demon Continent. Correspondingly, the Holy Demon Continent’s highest under the heavens was much stronger.

And above the Holy Demon Continent, there was also the endless sea that existed around the two continents. That boundless area was over 10 times larger than the Sky Spill Continent and Holy Demon Continent combined! The number of powerhouses that existed there could be imagined.

Even such a vast world was an insignificant speck of sand in the three thousand boundless universes. There were countless worlds and dimensions that were far more powerful than the Sky Spill Continent.

And beyond all of that, there was the far more terrifying Divine Realm!

As Lin Ming thought of this, he deeply felt that the road he walked upon still had a near infinite distance to go. Becoming the highest under the heavens within the Sky Spill Continent wasn’t anything special.

After his battle with Yang Yun, he brought to completion all of his ties to this world. He would ascend into the Divine Realm, stepping onto a wider stage and meet even greater challenges.

Lin Ming set down an array formation in the Eightfall Thunder Emperor’s cave dwelling. With his current understandings into the Concept of Thunder, he was already able to isolate the ruinous lightning from the 90 mile Thunder Dominion.

The 8000 Mile Black Swamp was a land filled with great dangers. There would always be some risks if Lin Ming were to cultivate here. When laying down array formations, he did so diligently and meticulously.

After a full day passed, Lin Ming fused the Laws of the grandmist space into the array formations he recalled from the Ancient Devil’s memories, arranging three layers of great formations. He sat down on the Eightfall Thunder Emperor’s stone bed and took out the 12 thunder dao fruits as well as the 20 top grade spirit essence stones from his spatial ring.

Of these 12 thunder dao fruits, one of them had already been eaten up by Lin Ming, leaving behind only the peel that contained the marks of the mysterious Thunder Concepts. Up until now, Lin Ming hadn’t managed to find the time to thoroughly perceive them.

This time, Lin Ming picked up a thunder dao fruit and used a dagger to slowly peel off the skin near the stalk, revealing a red fruit flesh that glowed a beautiful red.

The fragrance of wine drifted upwards, the aroma sharp and refreshing. It smelled like millennium aged wine, and the highest quality aged wine at that.

“Mm? This thunder dao fruit seems different from the one I ate before. That fruit was cream colored and white, but this one seems bright red like flesh and blood.”

The crystalline fruit flesh actually had bright red vessels that ran through it. The intoxicating aroma assaulted his senses, tantalizing and sweet.

Lin Ming cut off a piece of the fruit with his dagger and gently touched it with his fingers. It was bouncy and thick. He swallowed it down. As the fruit flesh entered his mouth, it melted without him even needing to chew. The fragrance dissipated down his throat, turning into a refreshing energy that filled his limbs, flowing to his heart, his dantian, and his head.

In that moment, Lin Ming felt as if he was drunk. His mind was dizzy and his arms and legs turned soft. All of his bones loosened, as if he would melt to the ground.

The second thunder dao fruit had an effect that was completely different from the first. It caused Lin Ming to feel as if he were floating on clouds; light and satisfied.

“What a strong and strange medicinal efficacy. It seems every thunder dao fruit is different.”

Lin Ming took advantage of the time before the medicinal efficacy of the thunder dao fruit faded and began to revolve a Divine Realm thunder cultivation method that was left behind on one of Jiang Ziji’s jade slips – ‘Thunder Sovereign Edict’. Within Jiang Ziji’s great collection, it was of the few cultivation methods that could be practiced without the Electric Violet Kirin bloodline.

Thunder energy mixed with true essence, circulating around and around again.

Lin Ming hadn’t entered the ethereal martial intent, but although he was half-drunk and half-awake and his mind seemed to be blank, his thoughts were incomparably clear. Although his actions were slow, energy crazily swelled up within his body.

This strange condition was similar to when a mortal martial artist drank wine to utilize the drunken fist. It was a cultivating state that was superior to the ethereal martial intent, similar to being hypnotized. In this state, there was no fear, no astonishment. In this state, one felt as if they had dug out their full potential and that any impossible matter had become possible.

Two hours.

Four hours.

Lin Ming digested the energy from the thunder dao fruit. As he was finished absorbing the energy, he would wake up from that strange state and eat another slice of the thunder dao fruit’s bright red flesh.

This fruit flesh contained an extremely great deal of energy. A normal thunder-attribute martial artist would be able to eat no more than 4, maybe 5 slices, otherwise their bodies would burst apart from all the energy. To eat more, they would have to discharge all the excess energy, but doing so was a complete waste.

Lin Ming didn’t have such a problem. The Heretical God Sprout had risen to another level and it swallowed up all the energy it was offered.

During such a high intensity training period, Lin Ming’s understandings towards the Thunder Laws became increasingly clear. Light shimmered around his body, brilliant and dazzling, as if he were about to turn into an immortal. And behind Lin Ming, dao diagrams began to partially reveal themselves, looming over him. They were abstruse and mystical, etched with lines that seemed to contain the most mysterious Thunder Laws.

Chapter 932 – Postcelestial Dao Diagram

The fifth stage of Life Destruction, shatter and reform the core, carving the form of elementary Laws on the surface of the Revolving Core. As long as one could reach the sixth stage of Life Destruction and thoroughly condense the Laws into their Revolving Core, they could officially cross Life Destruction and attempt to break into the Divine Sea.

The highest levels of Life Destruction were divided into nine stages. The first three stages reformed the spirit body, the second three stages reformed the core, and the last three stages reformed the divine soul.

After crossing six stages of Life Destruction, one could rely on their own strength to reach the Divine Sea. But the last three stages pertained to the future strength of a martial artist and how far they would be able to walk on their path of martial arts. The more formidable a soul was, the more energy it was able to manipulate. The soul was also related to the will; it was the carrier of the battle spirit. If one’s soul wasn’t powerful, their potential was limited.

In the cave dwelling, Lin Ming’s physical body had already become a loose fog of flesh and blood. He was slowly tempering himself in the sea of energy.

One day. Two days. Three days.

After half a month passed, within that blood fog, energy and essence began to gather together, forming a Revolving Core.

The process of forming the Revolving Core was extremely slow. A faint atmosphere of source energy lingered around the Revolving Core, condensing into a dao diagram.

When source energy naturally evolved, it would also naturally form a dao diagram. This was the so-called ‘postcelestial dao diagram’. The postcelestial meant that the dao diagram was naturally formed, whereas precelestial meant that it was man-made.

When source energy formed a postcelestial dao diagram, it would contain the inherent Great Dao of martial arts principles. This was also the so-called natural Laws.

Of the many dao diagrams, the most eye-catching and distinct one was the purple dao diagram. This dao diagram was ten feet wide, and the dao patterns engraved upon it shone like arcs of light, similar to bolts of thunder. The evolution was complex and enigmatic, containing profound mysteries and truths. This was the dao diagram of Thunder Laws. Lin Ming had perceived the thunder-attribute jade slip that Jiang Ziji left behind and had also eaten the thunder dao fruits, grasping all of the Great Dao fragments within the fruits. Out of all the Laws that Lin Ming comprehended, the Thunder Laws were far above all others!

A close second to the thunder dao diagram was a round red dao diagram. This red dao diagram was 8 feet wide, and the traces that throbbed on its surface where like countless beating flames. This was naturally the Fire Laws dao diagram. Lin Ming had the bloodline of the Ancient Phoenix and also trained for a long period of time at Timeworn Phoenix City. He had even meditated on the chaos stones. The fire dao diagram also had unrivalled might.

Following that, the Space Laws and Time Laws dao diagrams were far from being as impeccable as the first two; many of its traces were faint and blurry.

Behind that, there was the Darkness Laws that had just barely managed to form a dao diagram. There were many sections missing.

As for the final Wind Laws and the Concept of Vibration, they didn’t form dao diagrams. They condensed one inch long square symbols that were eclipsed underneath the dazzling radiance of the two great dao diagrams of thunder and fire.

When crossing the fifth stage of Life Destruction, and during the period when the elementary form of Laws were being carved into the surface of the Revolving Core, if dao diagrams were to form at this period, then that was an extreme phenomenon. It represented the peak solidity of foundation and also of great achievements in the future.

In the boundless universe there were countless martial artists. From body transformation to Houtian, Xiantian, Revolving Core, Life Destruction, Divine Sea, and then slowly continuing upwards to Divine Transformation, Divine Lord, Holy Lord, World King, and finally to reach the boundary of Empyrean.

It was unknown how many martial artists had died on the road of martial arts. To nearly all of them, they had taken a World King to be their final goal. Within the 3000 great worlds of the Divine Realm and also including the countless smaller worlds, there were only a total of 3000 World Kings. Moreover, this number was accumulated over several hundreds of thousands of years. To step onto the throne of a World King, one had to encounter many lucky chances. They had to have a great will, great intelligence, a strong heart of martial arts, heaven-defying talent, the direction of skilled masters, and countless resources stacked upon each other. Only when everything came together would one have a small chance of achieving such a boundary.

Lin Ming had now condensed postcelestial dao diagrams at the fifth stage of Life Destruction. Although this didn’t mean that he would become a World King in the future, this was considered a solid step towards reaching the peak of martial arts.

After three days passed, all of the dao diagrams disappeared as they fused into Lin Ming’s Revolving Core crystal nucleus. Lin Ming’s body began to slowly form. First his skeleton, then his muscles, blood vessels, meridians, and finally his skin and his hair.

Lin Ming sat naked on the stone bed, his body glimmering with a bright light. He could feel that the vigor of his essence, energy, and soul had reached an entirely new level. If he were to fight with Whitedemon now, he was confident he could easily defeat him, and perhaps even kill him.

Just as Lin Ming was thinking about what his next step would be, he suddenly heard an earthshaking explosion spread through the nine heavens. Even the island he was on began to tremble because of the sound. The ceiling of the cave began to tremble and release dust and stone powder, as if it would collapse at any time.

“Mm? What’s that?”

Lin Ming was startled. This shouldn’t be a Thunder Source or some other holy object. Just from the momentum and prestige of this sound, if it really were a Thunder Source then it was a Thunder Source on a completely different level from the Purple Lion Thunder Source. There was no way that Lin Ming was a match for it.

After thinking for a moment, Lin Ming decided to carefully hide his energy aura. He quietly creeped towards the cave entrance to see what was happening.

Bang bang bang!

The deafening sound continued. It sounded like chains and rings slapping against each other.

This sound seemed able to rupture the heavens and earth. If an ordinary person were to hear this, even their soul would be shattered.

Lin Ming held his breath and arrived at the cave entrance. He cautiously released his perception to investigate the situation outside. What he saw caused a chill to crawl up his back and into the skies!

Above the nine heavens, there were actually several hundred thick iron chains that formed a massive web, spreading out in all directions. These iron chains were hundreds of feet thick, and each one was covered with dense layers of symbols. The hundreds of chains formed a faint great array that seemed to separate the world. At this moment, this massive network of chains violently trembled, as if some utterly terrifying existence attempted to break free from the bindings of these chains!

Ka ka ka!

The demonic sounds of the chains colliding with each other caused Lin Ming’s mind to shiver. It was like he was listening to the death knell of a grim reaper from the abyss of hell.

He discovered that every iron chain was connected to a floating island. These chains penetrated deep into the mountains on the islands, where they were suppressed by the magnetic god trees.

“Roar!”

The ancient desolate beast that was locked within the great array of chains suddenly emitted a thunderous cry. The terrifying howl shook the world. As Lin Ming heard this sound, he felt all of his blood tumble as his face turned white.

“What a terrifying roar. Could there be a God Beast locked within this array formation?”

Lin Ming remembered the great dragon within the Eternal Demon Abyss that was likely a God Beast. He didn’t doubt that if a normal Divine Sea powerhouse were to face the frontal roar of whatever God Beast this was, their souls would likely be expelled from their body and broken down into nothingness!

Lin Ming wanted to ask Demonshine just what this was, but he sensed that Demonshine had fallen into the very depths of his spiritual sea and remained absolutely quiet there, impossible to wake up no matter who called to him. This sort of invisible and intangible great roar contained an inherent energy that was extremely damaging to the divine soul. Even though Demonshine was hidden within Lin Ming’s body, he still had to completely seal himself off lest he be grievously wounded by this roar!

And at this moment, with the sound of billowing thunder, all of the countless thunder balls that floated around the skies suddenly shot into the magnetic god trees. The several hundred islands and the several hundred magnetic god trees suddenly bloomed with a brilliant purple gold divine light. Vast and endless thunder energy raced down the chains, turning the chains a radiant purple gold.

The roaring God Beast seemed to withstand a brutal pain. It emitted a miserable howl as the power behind its voice weakened. It had obviously been injured by the thunder attack of the array formation.

From the cave dwelling of the Eightfall Thunder Emperor, Lin Ming was able to clearly see everything that happened. Each thunder ball that floated within the 100 mile Thunder Dominion contained an incomparably terrifying power. Even though Lin Ming had reached the fifth stage of Life Destruction and also had a profound understanding of Thunder laws, he still didn’t dare to impulsively enter the 100 mile Thunder Dominion. It could be seen how ghastly these thunder balls were.

But now, the countless thunder balls gathered together to deliver the sealed God Beast a nearly lethal blow. It was hard to imagine just what level of power this attack reached!

It was highly likely that this was the work of an Empyrean level existence!

“So these hundreds of floating immortal islands were only the base of the great chain array, and those magnetic god trees only served as the focal eye to gather all of the energy. A magnetic god tree of this size would be a treasure even within a large sect of the Divine Realm, and yet someone used several hundred of them to seal off this God Beast existence. Could such a bold tactic be the work of Empyrean Primordius?”

“No, that’s wrong. Empyrean Primordius controls the power of chaos. When I passed through the Road of Emperor, I was able to experience the grandmist space that he left behind and even gained a minor understanding towards him. If Empyrean Primordius were the one to arrange this array formation, he should’ve used the power of chaos as the foundation, not these Thunder Laws.”

“Could it be that this is an array formation left behind by Empyrean Primordius’ enemy?”

As Lin Ming became aware of this point, he thought it more and more probable. Empyrean Primordius’ enemy was definitely also an Empyrean. If they were an Empyrean skilled in Thunder Laws, creating such a great array was also reasonable.

But just what did this great array seal off, and for what reason?

Lin Ming’s mind raced with thoughts. At this time, the roars that enveloped the skies begun to fade away. Demonshine’s weak voice resounded in Lin Ming’s mind, “This is incredible, seriously incredible. These chains might possibly be the legendary dragon trapping cables. Every link of the chain has a weight that surpasses the Great Desolate Blood Halberd. A single dragon trapping cable has 1080 links, and there are several hundred dragon trapping cables here. The weight of them all added together surpasses a small meteor. Could there really be a True Dragon trapped within?”

“It might be Empyrean Primordius’ contract beast that is sealed within. Who knows just what’s going on.”

Lin Ming shook his head. Although this was undoubtedly related to Empyrean Primordius, it wasn’t something he could explore with his current boundary.

The God Beast that was locked away in the skies had stopped roaring, and the dragon trapping cables also vanished into thin air, leaving nothing but the hundreds of immortal islands floating around as they had been before. The only difference was that the thunder balls in the air had become 70% smaller.

Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred as he saw this. After a brief moment of hesitation, he slowly and carefully made his way towards the 100 mile Thunder Dominion. With Lin Ming’s strength, he didn’t have the ability to enter the 100 mile Thunder Dominion. But the struggle of the God Beast just now had greatly depleted the energy within the 100 mile Thunder Dominion. The thunder balls had all dimmed down, with less than 30% of their energy reserves remaining.

Perhaps he would be able to absorb some to give Yang Yun a happy surprise?

If he could borrow some of the power of these thunderballs that supported in sealing off a God Beast, just what would it be like if it struck Yang Yun?

Lin Ming was filled with anticipation.

He completely focused his mind on the Heretical God Sprout and slowly approached the 100 mile Thunder Dominion. The barrier between the 90 mile Thunder Dominion and 100 mile Thunder Dominion simply wasn’t able to stop Lin Ming who was skilled in Thunder Laws.

Lin Ming smoothly arrived at a fist-sized thunderball.

Chapter 935 – Command the World

“Kill? You want to go and kill Yang Yun now?” Li Yuxiao stammered, his eyes wide open. He never expected that Lin Ming would have this idea. If an ordinary person were to learn of Yang Yun’s plans, they would subconsciously think of escaping. Yang Yun had arranged a wide network of transmission arrays, but no matter how great it was it still wouldn’t be enough to cover the vast and endless sea. As long as Lin Ming hid deep enough in the deep sea, somewhere that was several dozen million miles beyond the nearest transmission array, Yang Yun would have to run his legs off if he wanted to find him.

Lin Ming actually didn’t think of running away. Instead, he decided to take this chance to kill Yang Yun. This was really bewildering.

“Little Brother Lin, don’t you think this might be a bit reckless?” Shibai asked, a bit unsure. He felt that Lin Ming’s idea was too crazy, but it was also consistent with Lin Ming’s usual style. He had always been like this. At just the late Revolving Core realm, Lin Ming dared to risk his life to cross into Life Destruction and challenge every Destiny Decree master of the Asura Divine Kingdom by himself. Moreover, he had obtained victory in the end. This was a valor and determination that couldn’t be possessed by the average person.

“After closing up, Yang Yun should be more powerful than Whitedemon. Even if his supernatural powers haven’t been completed, he still has the qualifications to be the highest under the heavens.” Fairy Snow Gale pressed her eyebrows together. She didn’t try to persuade Lin Ming, instead only stating this fact. She didn’t know about the battle between Lin Ming and Whitedemon, so she could only guess just how strong Lin Ming was.

However, according to the choices and actions Lin Ming took in the past, he wouldn’t make such an insane decision unless he had confidence in himself.

“Highest under the heavens? That is only the Sky Spill Continent’s highest under the heavens.”

Lin Ming’s words left everyone speechless.

“Only the Sky Spill Continent’s highest under the heavens.”

How could any of them respond to such brave words? In Fairy Snow Gale and Lu Yuxiao’s life, their ultimate goal was to reach the late Divine Sea realm, but even that seemed a nearly impossible dream. As for someone like Shang Yuetian, he only managed to break through to the Divine Sea with lucky chances. His life’s goal was to find heavenly materials that could extend his life and help him stay on the mortal coil for a few hundred more years. As for the late Divine Sea realm? Becoming the highest under the heavens? Those were simply legendary existences to him, stories that had no relation to him at all.

It could be said that to everyone here, Yang Yun was the same as those ancient inimitable kings like the Demon Emperor and the Eightfall Thunder Emperor; a nearly unreachable boundary for them. But to Lin Ming, it wasn’t all that much.

“Little Brother Lin, you…” Shibai wasn’t sure what to say for a moment. “Yang Yun has deeply hidden abilities and his talent is also high. He’s just over 40 years old but his cultivation is at the eighth stage of Life Destruction, early Divine Sea realm. If you underestimate him, then the one who eats a loss will be you.”

Lin Ming shook his head, “Patriarch Shibai, life in the universe is endless and infinite, and the road of martial arts has no end or limit. Although Yang Yun is formidable, he is still only at the eighth stage of Life Destruction, early Divine Sea realm. Within the Divine Realm, this sort of talent isn’t much at all.”

“And in terms of lucky chances, he managed to encounter the remnant soul of the late Divine Transformation Ancient Devil and obtained his guidance. Even with all the resources at his disposal, so what? Within the Divine Realm, there are geniuses that have World Kings as their masters! Moreover, their talent, their resources, everything they possess is countless times superior to Yang Yun!

“Within the three thousand boundless universes, there’s countless individuals like Yang Yun. But nearly all of them perish as they walk on their own roads of martial arts. If Yang Yun was better than average in an aspect, it would be that his plans and ambitions are high. But on the road of martial arts, one needs a great destiny, a great will, great talent, and nearly endless resources gathered today. Only then would they have a faint hope of continuing forwards. In this, Yang Yun is far from comparing to any of them.”

“If a mere Yang Yun can force me to hide deep within the South Sea for 8-10 years before returning, then I have no need to further walk down my road of martial arts. I might as well stay in the Sky Spill Continent and be happily content with being the ‘highest under the heavens’.

Lin Ming’s words left everyone, especially proud-hearted talents like Duanmu Qun, utterly silent. Lin Ming clearly intended to enter the Divine Realm and already was planning his ascension.

While those present all laid their eyes on the late Divine Sea as their goal, Lin Ming already looked above that towards the Divine Realm, seeing the geniuses there as his competition!

Such a disparity could no longer be put in words.

Fairy Snow Gale was silent for a while, and then said with a worried voice, “Lin Ming, although you taking advantage of the time when Yang Yun’s devil arts haven’t reached perfection could be considered grasping the time, but time is still inferior to terrain. Yang Yun is cultivating deep within the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom’s Divine Palace. The Nine Furnace Divine Palace has a great array formation protecting it; it won’t be easy for you to forcefully break in.”

Fairy Snow gale was from the White Clan, one of the subordinate family clans of the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom. She had a very good understanding into the layout and defensive measures in place at the Nine Furnace Divine Palace. The deepest center of the Nine Furnace Divine Palace was the area within the entire Sky Spill Continent with the richest and purest heaven and earth origin energy. It was natural to assume that Yang Yun was cultivating there.

“What Fairy Snow Gale says is correct. But although time isn’t as important as terrain, terrain isn’t as important as the will of the people. In order to complete his supernatural powers, Yang Yun has already lost the heart of the people. Even if the Nine Furnace Divine Palace has a great array formation, it still needs people driving the activation to display its might. Since Yang Yun is in closed door seclusion, how can he possibly do so? As for others, even if they are the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom’s Divine Sea powerhouses, they likely won’t be going to give their lives for someone like Yang Yun who was willing to kill his own great grandfather. He’s a devil who used despicable strong-arm tactics to take control of all the Divine Sea powerhouses under the heavens.”

“With such injustice, there’s no support from him among his people. Now is the time to strike. Fairy Snow Gale, Divine Emperor Li, Sage Shang, I ask you to help gather all of the Divine Sea powerhouses that have a tracing mark planted within them to gather here. I’ll help erase all of their tracing marks at once, and afterwards we’ll go through the transmission arrays Yang Yun has set up to go straight to the Nine Furnace Divine Palace. I’ll place down an array plate, gather everyone’s attacks together, and break through that great array formation. At that time, Yang Yun and I will have our final showdown!”

Lin Ming’s words were filled with a gritty daring and also held a deep confidence and glory. This was the so-called king’s aura. If someone heard these words, it was easy for them to be infected by the stirring emotions.

Fairy Snow Gale sighed in her heart. This sort of confidence and valor was slowly accumulated over time. If Lin Ming didn’t cultivate the martial path and stayed in the mortal world, he’d still be able to become an emperor among the people.

“Okay. I’ll summon everyone.” Shang Yuetian and Li Yuxiao said in unison. In order for Yang Yun to complete his devil arts, he had offended every Divine Sea powerhouse in the world. All these wandering people only lacked a leader to rally behind. Once they found one, they could unite and launch a counterattack on Yang Yun.

Lin Ming was the best choice to be that leader.

After they had their tracing marks erased from them, they’d inevitably be grateful to Lin Ming. With dozens of Divine Sea powerhouses joining forces in a single barrage of attacks, even the Nine Furnace Divine Palace’s array formation might not be able to withstand them. Trapped there, Yang Yun would have dug his own grave.

Shang Yuetian and the others all lit up a series of sound transmitting talismans. Over half of Yang Yun’s transmission array network had been completed. With knowledge of the approximate position of the martial artists as well as these sound transmitting talismans that could travel millions of miles, it would be quick to spread the message and gather everyone here.

…..

Shua! Shua! Shua!

Array symbols were drawn and shot into the array, joining together with an array flag. An array disc spun around in the air, quickly expanding and evolving into a large array formation as it slowly fell down.

There was a man and woman here. Both of them were Divine Sea powerhouses that were arranging a long distance transmission array.

This was the task that Yang Yun had given them.

Looking at the great array formation being completed, the man let out a light breath. He sighed, sounding a bit morose as he said, “That’s the 12th transmission array finished and we still have 20 days left. It seems that finishing this task won’t be a problem. Though I have no idea whether or not there’s any problems or mistakes when these transmission arrays are created.

This transmission array task was an absolute order upon death by Yang Yun. If they couldn’t complete them in time, the consequences would be disastrous.

The woman was silent as if she didn’t hear anything that was being said.

As the man saw this, his heart ached. He gently whispered, “Yu’er, don’t worry. Perhaps things aren’t as bad as they seem. Maybe there’s some other reason those several Divine Sea powerhouses went missing.”

The man didn’t know how to comfort and assure her. The man and woman were a married couple. The woman was called Yu’er, and she had a tracing mark left in her by Yang Yun. But that didn’t matter. What was important was that she possessed a variation bloodline called the moonlight bloodline.

Before now, seven Divine Sea powerhouses that possessed a variation bloodline had gone missing. Three of them were determined dead, and the other four were likely to have perished. The one who did all this was most likely Yang Yun. How could she not feel despair about all this? She felt like nothing more than a lamb in a cage, waiting to be slaughtered.

The man spoke a few words but couldn’t continue. He was a bit stronger than Yu’er. If this were the past and her life was in danger, he definitely could have spoken some brave words that he would protect her and keep her safe no matter what. But now, facing Yang Yun, all he felt was hopeless. The disparity between them was just too great. If he said any words about protecting his wife, even he wouldn’t believe them.

As the man was thinking about what to say, a flame suddenly lit up in front of him. It was the light of a sound transmitting talisman. The message was passed to both the man and the woman.

“Li Yuxiao. What could the Seven Star Divine Emperor want from us?”

The man was startled as he heard the message. He solemnly listened on. The sound transmitting talisman was very lengthy. When Li Yuxiao’s message mentioned Yang Yun cultivating the Great Blood Refining Art and killing the seven variation bloodline Divine Sea powerhouses to help do that, the man’s entire body trembled with rage. But as for Yu’er, her face turned paler than death and her lips quivered.

Although Li Yuxiao had no evidence, neither of them doubted his words. The two of them were also able to distinguish between right and wrong, and there was also no reason for Li Yuxiao to lie to them.

In the past they had only made some faint guesses as to what happened and they still held onto some hope. But now that they knew the exact situation, this knowledge pushed them into the abyss of despair.

“Yang Yun, that damned beast!”

The man clenched his jaws, his heart overflowing with rage and animus.

It had to be known that within many demonic path cultivation methods, the slaughter path and obscenity path weren’t separated. If his wife were to be taken by Yang Yun, then who knew just what would happen to her!

He wholeheartedly cultivated martial arts his entire life, even reaching the highest level of this continent, the Divine Sea, becoming a Peerless Emperor.

But in the end, he couldn’t even protect the woman he loved.

The man clenched his fists until his nails broke his flesh, drawing blood. However, as the message continued, his hands actually gradually relaxed. His eyes flashed with anticipation, surprise, and disbelief.

“Lin Ming has returned. He wants to gather all Divine Sea powerhouses of the Sky Spill Continent to attack the Nine Furnace Divine Palace, and he can even erase the battle spirit tracing mark in us?”

As the man looked at his wife, he could also see that she was shocked by the message. But within this shock, there was also a budding glimmer of hope.

Even if they couldn’t defeat Yang Yun, just erasing the tracing mark was a lifesaving favor.

“Not even four years have passed and Lin Ming wishes to fight Yang Yun? How could he have such strength?” The man muttered. “He also says he can remove the tracing marks. Does that mean his battle spirit has reached silver perfection? Is that even possible?”

Yu’er crumpled the sound transmitting talisman flame in her hand. She bit her lips and said, “No matter what it is, I must go and take a look. Even if I have to die in battle, I won’t allow Yang Yun to treat me as a pig to be raised in a pen.”

Chapter 939 – Complete Massacre

“Break!” Lin Ming roared out. The grandmist space had the power to swallow all Laws. However, even then one needed the energy to support it. Lin Ming’s current boundary was insufficient so it was impossible to reach a degree where he could swallow the entire Nine Furnace Great Array. This was a ultra-protection array that even the combined attack of 50 Divine Sea powerhouses couldn’t break. It represented the pinnacle of array formation achievements in the Sky Spill Continent!

However, if it were just the 12 cracks in the Nine Furnace Great Array where the energy lines were weak and shallow, Lin Ming could actually break through them!

Si si si!

The Heavenly Demon martial intent divided into 12 streams that rushed towards the 12 cracks in the Nine Furnace Great Array. In that moment, there were no powerful energy collisions, no dazzling divine lights, and no earthshaking bangs. The 12 cracks silently disintegrated!

The Nine Furnace Great Array was an array formation that contained the five central elements, gathering all elements as one. The power was incomparable. But in the face of the grandmist space that negated all Laws, even such an array formation was suppressed.

Every tiny spot that disintegrated was formed by countless tiny energy seals and formed a complex energy backbone, similar to a spider web. And like a spider web, every space between the energy lines that disintegrated was only the size of a grain of rice. Let alone a human being, even a fly would have trouble passing through them. As long as this gap was created, no matter how small it was, an invisible and intangible force field could pass through.

Lin Ming shouted out. The Heavenly Demon Force Field divided into 12 streams and flooded into the Nine Furnace Great Array, surging towards Situ Bonan and the others.

Lin Ming didn’t have the ability to rip apart the Nine Furnace Great Array. But if he could kill the Divine Sea powerhouses inside that were managing the nine stabilizing divine furnaces, the Nine Furnace Great Array’s power would weaken by over 50%. At that time, breaking this large array wouldn’t be difficult anymore.

“What!?”

At this time, Situ Bonan could clearly feel a vast and boundless, extremely terrifying energy pour down over him. This sort of feeling was like a mortal witnessing a great volcano erupting and watching as a trillion jins of lava rained down on them!

“Damn! What power is this, he can actually break into the Nine Furnace Great Array!? Let’s defend this little beast’s attack together, then repair the Nine Furnace Great Array!” Situ Bonan hysterically shouted. The other nine Divine Sea powerhouses didn’t dare to delay. They temporarily withdrew the energy they were pouring into the divine furnaces to resist the Heavenly Demon Force Field.

However, the Heavenly Demon Force Field was a transcendent divine might level ability. It was the capital that Empyrean Primordius relied on to walk unhindered in the boundless universe. Even if Lin Ming could only display the tiniest amount of its prestige, it was still more than enough to massacre Divine Sea martial artists.

“Death!”

Lin Ming waved his hand, his voice cold to the extreme. This aura was similar to the fabled Yama of hell, a lord who was able to sentence all to life and death with but a single brushstroke!

Bang!

Grandmist space erupted within the Nine Furnace Great Array. The five deep sea powerhouses that bore the brunt of this attack trembled. The protective true essence around their bodies melted like snow under the sun, disappearing as it entered the grandmist space.

Disintegrate all rules, decompose all energy, this was the chaos grandmist!

“How is this possible!?”

The several deep sea powerhouses were bewildered, horrified. They used their ultimate trump cards to resist this energy. Even if they were weaker, they wouldn’t be shocked if their true essence exploded in a shower of sparks before it disappeared. But they never thought that it would disappear without a trace, slowly dissipating into nothingness.

This was the first time they had ever seen something like this. How could they not be panicking?

However, this horror only lasted for less than the blink of an eye. The grandmist space covered them after which the five Emperor level deep sea powerhouses felt their protective true essence shatter. Their clothes, skin, muscles, meridians, bones, everything began to crumble down before turning into dust that disappeared into the wind. This was a complete and total annihilation.

As everyone witnessed this, their eyes turned round. Let alone those with Situ Bonan, even those 50 plus Divine Sea powerhouses standing on Lin Ming’s side felt a cold chill crawl up their spines and their palms to turn slick with sweat.

It was natural for Lin Ming to defeat a Divine Sea powerhouse; even instantly killing a Divine Sea powerhouse wasn’t a surprise. But when separated by the Nine Furnace Great Array and also dozens of miles away, to easily kill five Divine Sea powerhouses and with one of them even being at the middle Divine Sea realm, this was truly terrifying.

If Lin Ming could accomplish that, that also meant that he could take any of their lives with but a thought. Even if they were separated by dozens of miles, the result would be the same. Even with a great protective array between them, none of that would matter!

This sort of supernatural power already surpassed their scope of understanding.

Moreover, these five died in the most miserable way. Their death crept up on them silently and rapidly; a cruel death wasn’t even enough to describe it. This was true annihilation. They quietly dissipated into nothingness; even their bones and energy left this world!

In that silence, to watch the ghastly scene of five Divine Sea powerhouses turn into trillions of motes of dust, that was truly a fearful matter.

And from start to finish, Lin Ming hadn’t moved at all. Besides an enchanting red lotus blossoming behind him, he hadn’t even lifted a hand.

This scene was truly hair-raising!

What sort of cultivation method did this supernatural power come from!?

“How is this possible? How…” Situ Bonan’s eyes were like full moons. He was well aware that the only reason he hadn’t died just now was because Lin Ming hadn’t aimed at him, but instead killed the five other Divine Sea powerhouses. Otherwise, he would’ve died already, his fate the same as the dead.

With just a thought he had killed them from dozens of miles away, treating the Nine Furnace Great Array like it was nothing at all. He was simply a demonic monster!

“Run!”

This was the only thought of the survivors. None of them had the courage to face the monstrous Lin Ming.

“Run away?”

Lin Ming’s lips curved up in a cruel sneer. He only killed five first because he didn’t have full assurance he could kill all 10 Divine Sea powerhouses at once. But now that he had killed off half of them, killing the other half was that much easier.

“Grandmist space, massacre!”

Energy erupted from Lin Ming’s body. The Heavenly Demon martial intent surged out like a light-speed tsunami, rapidly swallowing up the five fleeing Divine Sea martial artists!

“Ahhhh!”

Situ Bonan emitted a miserable wail. He was the weakest and also at the last years of his life. He fell and was the first to be swallowed up by the Heavenly Demon martial intent.

Peng!

With a light sound, Situ Bonan’s protective true essence directly shattered. He watched helplessly as the grandmist space disintegrated his legs, his torso, his arms, and then his neck.

Within the grandmist space, his old flesh fell off like dead and dry bark. Blood poured out, his meridians shattered, everything silently turned to dust.

Nothing was more frightening than watching his own body dissipate like dust.

“No! Noooo!”

Situ Bonan cried out with one last unwilling roar before he was completely swallowed by the grandmist space. Everyone watched as he futilely struggled before finally being decomposed into nothingness.

Just like Situ Bonan, the other four Divine Sea powerhouses weren’t able to escape either. They were sucked into the grandmist space one at a time. With despairing cries, their protective true essence shattered and their bodies crumbled apart!

From the point that Lin Ming managed to break into the Nine Furnace Great Array, he had only taken several breaths of time to kill 10 Divine Sea martial artists. He hadn’t even taken half a step, easily slaughtering them all.

To kill with just a thought, this was the majesty of a true death god, the executioner of life and death!

“Lin, Sage Lin…”

At some unknown time, the 50 some Divine Sea powerhouses seemed to unanimously agree to halt their attacks. What happened just now was no different from a dream to them. Those 10 Divine Sea powerhouses were not random minions, but Supreme Elders at similar levels of power. But facing Lin Ming, none of them had the ability to resist. If they were in their place, they would’ve encountered a similar fate.

To face someone who could kill them by just lifting a finger, they certainly felt a heavy pressure.

“Sage Ling’s supernatural powers are peerless. I didn’t think that you’d be able to contend with Yang Yun, but now I see that my judgement and experiences are shallow.”

Sage Heavenmirror sighed as he watched Lin Ming, his voice full of respect and awe. He was renowned as the god of divination, but even he couldn’t imagine that Lin Ming possessed such strength.

Lin Ming shook his head, “The reason I was able to kill those 10 Divine Sea martial artists is because I used a special martial skill. Although I didn’t move, the truth is that I was attacking with my complete strength; it wasn’t as easy as you think it was. Otherwise, I would’ve killed those 10 Divine Sea masters together instead of killing five first and then the other five.”

It wasn’t easy for Lin Ming to galvanize the grandmist space; he had to display his complete strength. And if he were to drive the grandmist space to the limit, he wouldn’t have any remaining energy to use martial skills.

But although he said that, when others saw this scene, what they witnessed was that Lin Ming killed others from dozens of miles away with just a thought, not even moving to do it.

“Alright everyone! Now that the 10 Divine Sea powerhouses that were managing the Nine Furnace Great Array are dead, that is the same as a tiger losing their teeth and claws. Let’s attack together and shatter that barrier!”

Although Lin Ming’s Heavenly Demon martial intent could dissolve the Nine Furnace Great Array to a certain extent, he wasn’t able to completely destroy it. To do that he required the strength of the others.

“Okay!”

50 plus Divine Sea powerhouses attacked again with everything they had. Dozens of light beams gathered at an array disc, condensing into a rainbow dragon that howled towards the Nine Furnace Great Array.

Bang!

The great array violently trembled. Everything within a thousand miles was completely razed to the ground by the tyrannical energy. Luckily, the Nine Furnace Divine Palace symbolized the absolute majesty and glory of the Divine Kingdom and didn’t allow mortals or martial artists to live nearby. Otherwise, this battle would’ve cost countless lives.

After the Nine Furnace Great Array lost the support of 10 Divine Sea powerhouses, it wasn’t able to withstand the massive joint attack. The energy barrier trembled more and more, and then with a loud ‘ka ka ka’ sound, a great crack finally appeared!

As soon as one crack appeared, more cracks rapidly expanded outwards, spreading through the entire array. With a long explosion, the Nine Furnace Great Array completely collapsed!

This was the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom’s highest array formation that represented the total accumulation of tens of thousands of years. If there were enough Divine Sea powerhouses overseeing it, then even the joint attack of 100 Divine Sea powerhouses along with the highest under the heavens wouldn’t have been able to break it!

When Yang Yun was at the Temple of Marvels, he had suppressed the many Divine Sea powerhouses with lightning speed, then killed Yang Laotian and Ouye Hua afterwards. Only due to that was his plan able to progress smoothly. Otherwise, if Yang Laotian holed up in the Nine Furnace Divine Palace for dozens of years, then Yang Yun would’ve had a big headache.

Chapter 945 – Ashes to Ashes

The light vanished and silence fell over the world. Lin Ming’s face was white and a trickle of blood dripped down from the corners of his mouth. That last strike had consumed nearly all of his strength and even cost him a bit of his life essence. This life essence could be restored later but it would require a great deal of heavenly materials.

With Lin Ming’s current level of strength, simultaneously using the Purple Lion Thunder Source and the blood of the Ancient Phoenix to activate the dual thunder and fire dao diagrams, then fusing them together was simply too much strain on his body. After all, he was still only at the fifth stage of Life Destruction.

The surrounding area within a thousand miles was completely razed to the ground. Below Lin Ming’s feet, there was a massive abyss dozens of miles deep. This was carved into the ground by Lin Ming’s final strike.

The over 50 Divine Sea powerhouses had already retreated a hundred miles away. As they watched the horrifying earth rending battle between the two come to an end, they were left speechless. For the last 100,000 years, several people appeared that qualified to be the highest under the heavens. After Yang Yun cultivated the Great Blood Refining Art, his strength could be considered among those people. But even so, he was still slain by Lin Ming. What was most terrifying was that Lin Ming was only at the fifth stage of Life Destruction. Since ancient times, the highest under the heavens always had at least a middle Divine Sea cultivation. The disparity between the fifth stage of Life Destruction and the middle Divine Sea realm was far too great. If it were an ordinary fifth stage Life Destruction martial artist, they probably wouldn’t even be able to rank on the Destiny Decree. As for a middle Divine Sea master, they could exterminate a hundred regular fifth stage Life Destruction martial artists with a wave of their hand!

Lin Ming’s foundation was already unimaginable; it was impossible to imagine. If this continued then it was likely he would be able to break into the legendary ninth stage of Life Destruction. His strength would then reach heights beyond anyone’s wildest dreams!

Without a doubt, Lin Ming was destined to ascend into the Divine Realm. But the legends and stories he would leave behind on the Sky Spill Continent would have no equal, whether it was now, in the past, or in the future.

“Yang Yun’s not dead yet?”

Lin Ming fixed his eyes, peering deep into the abyss. Yang Yun was no more than several pieces of flesh and blood, but his head still remained intact. His fires of life were weakened to the point of extinguishing and his aura was thin as cobwebs.

Lin Ming moved, landing in front of Yang Yun.

“…Lin… Ming…”

Yang Yun was bleeding from everywhere. His teeth were shattered and his tongue was bitten off cleanly. He managed to use a slight bit of energy to simulate his voice, but it still came out blurry.

“The feeling of all your ambitions being smashed apart, do you find it hard to reconcile with?” Lin Ming indifferently asked. As he looked at Yang Yun, there wasn’t any emotion in his eyes. Yang Yun had used all means possible to reach his goal no matter how nefarious they were. Now that his fate ended up like this, he deserved nothing less.”

“Hehe…” Yang Yun demonically grinned, his eyes filled with loathing and venom. “You stand in front of me as a victor, but one day, others will stand in front of you the same way. You’ll share the same fate as me, hahahahaha!”

He hated Lin Ming! He hated Lin Ming to the depths of his soul!

It was said that when people died their final parting words would be peaceful. But when Yang Yun died, all he did was crazily curse.

The original Yang Yun, whether he was lying or just exceptional at hiding his true thoughts, his outwards appearance was always that of a handsome gentleman. There was no comparison to this dying rabid dog in front of him.

It could only be said that Yang Yun had become completely demented after losing himself. His original character had completely disappeared.

Lin Ming grimly sighed. This was the fate of recklessly fusing your soul with someone else. Thinking about it, he was also extremely lucky. The divine object, the Magic Cube, was able to cleanly erase a soul mark and allow him to absorb only the memories, making it so that he was never influenced by another person’s thoughts.

This Magic Cube had caused the struggle of countless great figures within the Divine Realm. Just what secrets and uses did it truly have? What was it made from and how was it created?

The Magic Cube had a mysterious origin that was impossible to guess. In fact, up until this point, Lin Ming depended on the Magic Cube too many times. He absorbed the memories of some others, but these people had all been characters on the same level of the Demon emperor. They couldn’t compare to the Holy Lords or World Kings of the Divine Realm, much less an Empyrean.

The Magic Cube certainly had other functions. It was just that his boundary was too low to understand or utilize them.

As Lin Ming was thinking about this, he suddenly felt a burning heat emanate from his chest. This feeling came from the Magic Cube!

Ever since the Magic Cube fused into Lin Ming’s body, he never found it again. It was simply as if it had vanished. He couldn’t make contact with it or activate it. Even when he crossed Life Destruction and his body burst apart into a fog of blood, he still wasn’t able to detect a single trace of the Magic Cube.

To the Magic Cube, Lin Ming was only able to passively accept its wishes. But at this time, he was able to feel the slightest bit of will from the Magic Cube. Lin Ming only felt this trace of will when he fed the Magic Cube some blood essence.

“The Magic Cube wants to swallow Yang Yun’s blood essence?” Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred. Yang Yun was only a Divine Sea powerhouse. Before this, Lin Ming already fed the Magic Cube the blood essence of a Divine Sea Supreme Elder; the blood essence of the old Imp form the Blood Slaughter Steppes. He thought that the next rank of blood essence the Magic Cube would want would be from a Divine Transformation master. He never thought that the Magic Cube would actually be interested in Yang Yun’s blood essence.

“Jejejeje, Lin Ming, I know that you want to climb onto the peak of martial arts, but there are countless martial artists just like you, which one of them doesn’t wish to reach the peak!? How many of them will finally fail before they get there!? The road of martial arts is paved with the lives of others! Sooner or later, you’ll be the same as me, the same as me!”

Yang Yun crazily shouted out, cursing with his final breath. Lin Ming glanced at him in pity. He quietly sent out a layer of energy that covered Yang Yun’s ruined body.

“You! What are you doing?” Yang Yan was shocked. He suddenly discovered a powerful attractive force acting on him. The power of his blood vitality rapidly left his body. It was gathering towards Lin Ming!

“You, you want to swallow me!?” Yang Yun’s face gruesomely distorted. He was far too familiar with this feeling. He cultivated the Great Blood Refining Art for several years and had sucked up the life of countless vicious beasts and divine body and variation bloodline Divine Sea powerhouses. How could he not know what Lin Ming was doing?

Hu!

Blood essence rapidly left Yang Yun’s body. He was so angry that his eyes popped out of his head, a monstrous, heaven-shaking hatred within them. However, as his life force left his body, his every thought and motion slowed down and down.

Masses of blood fog formed phantoms in the air. There were flood dragons, strange fishes, white tigers, massive snakes, all sorts of Saint Beasts, all of them were swallowed up by Lin Ming. More accurately, all of it was swallowed up by the Magic Cube.

A faint scarlet vortex appeared on the surface of the Magic Cube. All of these blood phantoms were minced apart by this vortex.

Finally, the scarlet phantom of a hydra was also swallowed up by the Magic Cube. At this point, all of Yang Yun’s blood essence was completely absorbed.

Yang Yun’s face was already white and filled with defeat; his last breath was near. Lin Ming couldn’t help but sigh at just how tenacious Yang Yun’s life was. Normally, if a Divine Sea powerhouse had their head chopped off they would live for less than ten breaths of time. But Yang Yun struggled around and around, still hanging onto that single breath.

This was obviously because of the Great Blood Refining art. Yang Yun had refined countless bloodlines into himself that were filled with an exuberant and stubborn vitality, including even the stalwart hydra bloodline.

“It looks like even Whitedemon was swallowed up by Yang Yun.” Lin Ming recognized the hydra phantom; he sensed the aura of Whitedemon coming from it. Within the Divine Realm, the hydra bloodline was also a considerably powerful clan with countless clansmen spread throughout.

“Lin Ming, there’ll be a day, when you…”

Yang Yun was sending out his final curse, but as he spoke, his head suddenly split apart. A crack appeared from his forehead, extending down to his lower jaw like a knife that passed through a watermelon. His head exploded.

Yang Yun’s voice was stopped short. He had thoroughly died.

However, at the moment when Yang Yun’s head split apart, a tiny wisp of remnant shot out, its soul force extremely weak. It violently thrashed and twisted about. This soul emitted the aura of the Ancient Devil.

This was a wisp of the Ancient Devil’s remnant soul that Yang Yun hadn’t fused with, instead choosing to suppress it within his spiritual sea. Now that Yang Yuns’ spiritual sea had broken apart, this tiny wisp of soul had no place left to hide.

The Magic Cube didn’t seem to have any interest in swallowing up this soul wisp, instead remaining silent. In the Temple of Marvels, the reason that the Magic Cube swallowed the Ancient Devil’s soul was because it had taken the initiative to deliver itself to the Magic Cube when it tried to seize Lin Ming’s body.

“Yang Yun has already died and you still have a wisp of soul left over? That’s really persistent of you.” Lin Ming’s eyes flashed with a cold light as he pinched that wisp of soul in his fist.

Screech screech!

That soul wisp sent out tiny screams as it was pinched between Lin Ming’s fingers, as if it were a large rat that had been caught around the neck.

A thought entered Lin Ming’s mind. This was the voice of the Ancient Devil. “Don’t kill me! Don’t kill me! I know many secrets about the Sea of Miracles and the Eternal Demon Abyss! I also know where many powerhouses have left their treasures! You still haven’t truly entered the Sea of Miracles, I can lead you there to seek treasures!”

The Ancient Devil furiously struggled. However, Lin Ming only sneered. He twisted his fingers, and with a lighting cracking sound, the Ancient Devil was completely annihilated.

At this point, Yang Yun, Whitedemon, and the Ancient Devil were all dead!

Lin Ming took a deep breath, tracing his chest. The Magic Cube remained quiet. Although it had absorbed blood essence this time, it didn’t open the Magic Cube space.

This made Lin Ming feel a tinge of regret. It seemed that in order to open up the Magic Cube again, he would need the blood essence of a Divine Transformation realm powerhouse.

Lin Ming hypothesized that it wasn’t the Magic Cube that absorbed blood essence, but rather that powerful soul deeply sleeping within the Magic Cube. That is, the Saintess that used the Magic Cube to devour the souls of 10,000 Divine Realm Supreme Elders.

Each and every one of those Divine Realm Supreme Elders had been super powerhouses. If the Demon Emperor were ranked amongst them, he would only be extremely ordinary. But every single one of them was completely exterminated with a single move from that woman.

That woman likely needed blood essence to repair her own soul.

Before this, every time she had opened the Magic Cube after absorbing blood essence was only to inform him that she needed the blood essence of stronger powerhouses to recover.

And now, the Magic Cube sucked Yang Yun’s blood essence of its own volition. That explained a question, and that was that Yang Yun’s blood essence was finally at a high enough level for the woman to use.

This should also be because Yang Yun cultivated the Great Blood Refining Art, and the blood vitality within his body was far too exuberant and potent. A normal Divine Sea powerhouse would not have the qualifications to have their blood essence be used by that woman, because that Divine Sea boundary was far too low for her.

Chapter 958 – Obtaining Treasures

Lin Ming looked as far as he could. He was able to vaguely make out a crimson long spear within the center of the blazing sun. Countless runes shined on its body and a vast and boundless atmosphere surged out from it.

Even though the nine suns hanging in the skies were the brightest of the many stars, they all had minor differences between then; some had a weaker light and others had a stronger light. The light of the Phoenix Blood Spear was one of the brightest; it was one of the most brilliant saint treasures. This proved that even though the Phoenix Blood Spear was a top grade treasure, it was still positioned at the top of its rank!

Besides the Phoenix Blood Spear, the Sunpierce Sword’s light wasn’t any dimmer. The sword was clearly a top saint artifact amongst all top grade saint artifacts. This was also within reason. Although the Ancient Phoenix Clan’s inheritances varied with all sorts of weapons in use, the most common weapons were swords and spears.

There were many female disciples in the Ancient Phoenix Clan and the vast majority of them preferred to use swords. As for spears, because the Ancient Phoenix Clan waged war against many other sects in ancient times, they had to ride colossal firebirds and golden crows. During those dire times, a spear would be far more convenient than a sword.

“It’s a wonderful spear.” Lin Ming couldn’t help but praise.

“Naturally, if we could obtain such a top grade saint artifact, that’d be awesome; I have no idea just how much our strength would increase. Moreover, the top grade saint artifacts all have the Laws of the Great Dao inscribed into them. If you can perceive them through meditation, it will be greatly beneficial.” A disciple standing next to Lin Ming said, a besotted look on his face.

“Dream on! You’re far from being qualified to obtain a top grade saint artifact. Only Senior-apprentice Brother Huang has such a chance.” Another male disciple ruthlessly poked apart the disciple’s daydreams.

“Oh, that’s right, Senior-apprentice Brother Huang, did you come this time to take a top grade saint artifact?” A female disciple echoed.

Huang Yuegong chuckled as he heard this question. He swung his fan and said, “That’s right, this time I indeed came for the several top grade saint artifacts. As for those high-grade saint artifacts, although they are precious, I do not lack them.”

“It’s just that, the top grade saint artifacts are far too difficult to obtain. Whether it’s the Sunpierce Sword or the Phoenix Blood Spear, both are extraordinary specimens of top grade saint artifacts, nearing the existence of transcendent saint artifacts. Even for me, I only have a 30% chance of success.”

“Even Senior-apprentice Brother Huang has just a 30% chance of success?” A disciple said with a wide open mouth.

Song Baifeng humphed, “What do you know? I have guarded the Saint Artifact Pavilion for so many years and no one has managed to take the Sunpierce Sword or the Phoenix Blood Spear. They are true top grade saint artifacts! You must know that even most disciples of Phoenix Hall use medium-grade saint artifacts, not high-grade saint artifacts. Those that can use high-grade saint artifacts are truly outstanding individuals within the Phoenix Hall!”

Song Baifeng’s flattery had reached perfection. Every word he spoke aimed to bring up Huang Yuegong, making him enjoy it very much.

However, what Song Baifeng said was also the truth. Most Phoenix Hall disciples used medium-grade saint artifacts. The disciples managed to enter Phoenix Hall after breaking into the Divine Transformation realm and then undergoing a strict test. As for those that directly entered Phoenix Hall by crossing through nine stages of Life Destruction, that was a minority.

“Senior-apprentice Brother Huang, show us your prodigious skills!” A female disciple said.

“Yeah, let us open our eyes!” Several disciples quickly repeated. Huang Yuegong swung his fan, thinking for a moment before snapping it shut. “I suppose I will try again this time. Although I made sufficient preparations this time, the truth is my chances aren’t too great. A top grade saint artifact really is too hard to obtain.”

“Junior-apprentice Sister Jun. how about we try taking a treasure together?”

Huang Yuegong said to Jun Yunrue.

“Mm, alright.”

At this time, Jun Yunrue had also found a saint artifact she liked; it was a sword, a medium-grade saint artifact. In fact, it was at the peak of medium-grade saint artifacts.

Jun Yunrue and Huang Yuegong flew up at the same time. Jun Yunrue flew toward the sword saint artifact while Huang Yuegong approached the top grade Sunpierce Sword.

The Sunpierce Sword’s light was in no way inferior to the Phoenix Blood Spear. Compared to the top grade saint artifact ring or saint artifact vestment, it was much more brilliant! As the several disciples saw Huang Yuegong fly toward the Sunpierce Sword, all of their eyes turned wide, including Song Baifeng’s. They steadily locked their eyes on the sky lest they miss a single moment of glory.

Puff!

Like a fish jumping into the sea, Huang Yuegong was directly sucked into the scorching sun that was the Sunpierce Sword, disappearing without a trace.

As for Jun Yunrue, she flew into the medium-grade sword’s light to start the test of Saint Artifact Pavilion.

The other disciples eagerly waited. They looked at that blazing sun in the air, awe and expectation etched on their faces.

“Junior-apprentice Sister Lin, what did you encounter when you took that low-grade saint artifact?” A fellow disciple, Zhang, asked. He never attempted taking a treasure before.

Lin Junzhi said, “It was a complex test. Those saint artifact stars seem to have their own world within them. Senior-apprentice Sister Jun and Senior-apprentice Brother Huang are both attempting to take saint artifacts at a much higher grade, so the difficulty of their test should be far more difficult than mine.”

As Lin Junzhi spoke her eyes never left the star that Jun Yunrue vanished into. She hoped with all of her heart that Jun Yunrue would be able to pass the test and obtain the saint artifact.

Time slowly passed. Fifteen minutes flew by. The light of the two saint artifact stars in the sky began to shine increasingly bright. Lin Ming silently looked, carefully branching out his sensation and remembering the faint changes within the characteristics of the light. He could faintly feel that the every saint artifact star that floated in the sky was in truth part of a great array formation, and each saint artifact served as the eye of that array. This array formation was incomparably mysterious; Lin Ming could only speculate.

He suddenly thought of something and asked Song Baifeng, “Could there be 9999 treasures within Saint Artifact Pavilion?”

Song Baifeng glanced at Lin Ming with some shock. He said, “That’s right, there’s exactly 9999 saint artifacts. 9000 low-grade saint artifacts, 900 medium-grade saint artifacts, 90 high-grade saint artifacts, and 9 top grade saint artifacts.”

The Ancient Phoenix Clan worshipped and revered the number nine. Nine divided by nine was one and to pass nine was to return to one; this was a symbol of a phoenix being reborn through nirvana.

Nine was the extreme numeral; it in itself contained the principles of the Great Dao.

Saint Artifact Pavilion was in truth a low-grade spirit artifact. At its core, these 9999 saint artifacts composed a great array formation. Once a saint artifact was taken by a disciple, Phoenix Cry Palace would add in a new one to ensure that the total number of saint artifacts in the Saint Artifact Pavilion would always be the same.

Lin Ming understood more and more of this great array formation’s mysteries as he watched. He unconsciously sunk his thoughts into comprehending it. At this time, he suddenly heard a light sound in the air. He looked up and saw that Jun Yunrue was ejected from the star in the sky that shimmered like a moon. Her complexion was flushed red as she landed on the ground.

“Senior-apprentice Sister Jun, how was it?”

Several disciples quickly circled her.

Although Jun Yunrue’s breath was a bit rapid and she consumed a great deal of energy, her eyes were actually filled with excitement. She didn’t reply to everyone’s questions, instead looking up at the sky. After several breaths of time, the star in the sky began to gradually dim down, converging in on itself until it became a coldly shining treasure sword that fell down.

Zing –

As the treasure sword fell into Jun Yunrue’s hand, it released a clarion cry.

Jun Yunrue successfully obtained the saint artifact!

“Congratulations senior-apprentice sister, congratulations!” Several disciples shouted out, overcome with happiness but also envy. This was a medium-grade saint artifact! Besides the elite disciples of Phoenix Hall, the others usually only had low-grade saint artifacts.

Jun Yunrue was currently only in Golden Crow Hall, soon to rise to Vermillion Bird Hall, but she managed to obtain a medium-grade saint artifact already. Once she entered Phoenix Hall, there was a high chance she would be able to obtain a high-grade saint artifact!

“Senior-apprentice Sister is fierce, you actually managed to obtain a medium-grade saint artifact sword. Senior-apprentice Sister’s strength will surely rise a great deal in the future!”

“That’s right, haha, with senior-apprentice sister supporting us in the future, we can surely move undaunted!”

As several disciples gleefully rejoiced, Jun Yunrue also couldn’t conceal the euphoria on her face. “Alright, alright, that’s enough flattery. If you all can display enough talent that Honorable Master Fairy Feng will admire your ability, she will surely reward you. At that time, what would a mere medium-grade saint artifact be worth?”

Jun Yunrue glanced at everyone. At this time, the burning sun that was the Sunpierce Sword began to violently tremble.

Everyone was startled. They looked up and heard an explosive sound as that sun burst out with a light ten times brighter than before. In that moment, someone was thrown out from the blazing sun; it was Huang Yuegong.

After Huang Yuegong was ejected, the blazing sun’s light gradually weakened down before returning to normal several breaths later.

“Senior-apprentice Brother Huang!”

“Senior-apprentice Brother Huang are you okay!?”

Several disciples quickly went over to help him as they saw him being tossed onto the ground. In particular, Song Baifeng was the most attentive. He faithfully rushed over to give him mouth to mouth.

“Young Master! Young Master!” Huang Yuegong’s two lackeys arrived at his side like a bolt of lightning. They quickly took out all sorts of pills from their spatial ring, prepared to force feed him.

“What are you all freaking out for, I haven’t died yet!”

Huang  Yuegong was enraged with shame. He shoved away the two lackeys that were trying to push pills in his mouth and looked at the Sunpierce Sword star in the air, his face darkening. It still hung there as before, continuing to dazzle like a sun with heavenly light, like a proud divine god  that was looking down at the world, mocking all the mortals that presumptuously bit off more than they could chew.

“This damned sword!” Huang Yue indignantly spouted out. His eyes flashed with an ominous light. He came here today with great hopes of obtaining this treasure, but now he failed to obtain the sword and also lost face, especially since it was in front of Jun Yunrue. He wanted to use this chance to impress and conquer Jun Yunrue, but now his face swept the floor.

As he looked at Jun Yunrue, he could see that she managed to obtain the sword she tried for. This caused Huang Yuegong to be even more ashamed. Today, three people tried to obtain a saint artifact and only he failed.

Song Baifeng was looking at the situation and saw Huang Yuegong’s dilemma. He quickly said, “Sir Huang is fierce to face the Sunpierce Sword for half an hour. I’ve guarded Saint Artifact Pavilion for 30 years and the number of people that could withstand half an hour within the light of the Sunpierce Sword can be counted on two hands!”

Song Baifeng could be considered as restoring a bit of Huang Yuegong’s face. Although Huang Yuegong knew that Song Baifeng was clearly spouting drivel, he tacitly allowed him to do so.

Chapter 959 – Towards the Phoenix Blood Spear

“Sir Huang, would you like to try taking a high-grade saint artifact? Saint Artifact Pavilion has many high-grade saint artifacts that are of a very high quality. Although they cannot compare to the nine top grade saint artifacts, they are still quite formidable. With Sir Huang’s strength, taking a high-grade saint artifact should be no problem at all!” Song Baifeng improvised some advice on the spot as he saw Huang Yuegong’s face being swept all over the ground.

A high-grade saint artifact and a top grade saint artifact were different in terms of value by over a hundred times; they were on two completely different levels. Huang Yuegong certainly didn’t want to take a high-grade saint artifact, but taking a top grade saint artifact was easier said than done. What Saint Artifact Pavilion tested was talent and potential; these two factors normally wouldn’t change much no matter how high a martial artist’s cultivation grew. If there wasn’t some great lucky chance, then even if Huang Yuegong cultivated to the Divine Transformation realm and returned to attempt taking a top grade saint artifact again, the result would likely more or less be the same.

He thought of this, then glanced at Jun Yunrue. He stood up and said, “Okay, as a disciple of Phoenix Hall, I can take two saint artifacts from Saint Artifact Pavilion. Since I haven’t taken any before, I can take a high-grade saint artifact as my first and the Sunpierce Sword as my second!”

Since it was far too difficult to obtain a top grade saint artifact at this time, he might as well take a high-grade saint artifact to recover some of the face he lost here. Otherwise, as a chosen pride of the heavens who had an unfathomable image to his junior-apprentice brothers and sisters and as someone who was revered and respected by so many, if his only memory of this place were to be being flung to the ground almost vomiting blood after failing to retrieve a saint artifact, then that really would be too shameful.

He decided to try a second time. In Saint Artifact Pavilion, every attempt was 1000 phoenix cry seal marks. Of course, with his status, Song Baifeng wouldn’t pursue this matter at all.

Huang Yuegong looked at the numerous saint artifacts in the sky and said, “Of the high-grade saint artifacts, I have a sword, a vestment, and a ring. What I’m still missing is a pill furnace!”

He settled on a star that shined like a full moon. He directly rushed up and submerged into that light!

Just from how bright the light was one could extrapolate that the pill furnace Huang Yuegong wanted to take was a peak high-grade saint artifact. Between high-grade saint artifacts, there was a massive difference in value between the best and the worst. If he could obtain a peak high-grade saint artifact, it would be of great help to enhance his strength.

“As expected of Senior-apprentice Brother Huang, he immediately chooses such a fierce treasure. I can’t believe that this is his alternate to the Sunpierce Sword.”

“That’s right, this is a boundary that we can’t imagine.”

The disciples beside Jun Yunrue felt ashamed at their own weakness. They could only barely manage to obtain a low-grade saint artifact.

After Huang Yuegong sunk into the bright moon-like star, the light became increasingly dazzling until it began emitting beams of golden light that seemed like they could cut apart the void.

After an incense stick of time passed, Huang Yuegong calmly flew out from the shining light. He stretched his hand out and the shining light began to rapidly shrink until it fell into his palm where it spun around.

The light continued to converge. After several breaths of time, that brilliant light turned into a small, ordinary seeming bronze furnace.

“He did it!”

“Completely mind-blowing! A high-grade saint artifact was taken just like that in five minutes. Senior-apprentice Brother Huang is so fierce!”

This shocked all of the young disciples present. Jun Yunrue was already so strong but even she found it difficult to obtain a medium-grade saint artifact.

Huang Yuegong obtained a high-grade saint artifact with such ease. In terms of potential and talent, they were on completely different levels.

“This is incredible. Senior-apprentice Brother Huang is so amazing and yet he can’t obtain the Sunpierce Sword. Just how much stronger is the Sunpierce Sword!?”

“No kidding. There’s even several more top grade saint artifacts. I wonder just what sort of monster would be able to obtain them.”

“It’s already good if I can reach Senior-apprentice Brother Huang’s level. There really is no way I can compare!”

The several young disciples all exclaimed out loud. From listening to their compliments, Huang Yuegong’s face finally improved some.

He casually threw the furnace to his lackeys and deliberately said in his most casual tone, “Hold it for me. It should be of some use when I’m practicing alchemy later. It’s a decent transition furnace for me.”

Transition?

As the several young disciples heard this word, they were left speechless. Such an extraordinary pill furnace was actually just a transitory item for others. Really, comparing oneself to others could aggravate someone to death.

Song Baifeng laughed, “Sir Huang is indeed Sir Huang. This is a peak high-grade saint artifact called the Triple Shroud Divine Furnace. Although this furnace isn’t a top grade saint artifact, it isn’t too far off!”

Song Baifeng continued to flatter again and again. Huang Yuegong only laughed. Since others were busy repairing his reputation with gold, he certainly wouldn’t stop them.

“It’s fine. Although I didn’t manage to obtain the Sunpierce Sword this time, I still managed to take this Triple Shroud Divine Furnace. It’s adequate. Junior-apprentice Sister Jun, do you plan on leaving now? How about we head out together?” Huang Yuegong felt as if he had restored enough of the face he lost, and now his words were much more gallant than before. He invited Jun Yunrue out once again.

Jun Yunrue faintly smiled. “Senior-apprentice Brother Huang, we can leave on our own in a bit. But I brought Junior-apprentice Brother Lin here and he hasn’t tried obtaining a treasure yet.”

“Oh? Junior-apprentice Brother Lin?” Huang Yuegong recalled that Lin Ming hadn’t yet taken a treasure. The memory of a Divine Sea martial artist was outstanding; they wouldn’t forget something they wanted to remember. The only reason Huang Yuegong had forgotten about this matter was because he had directly taken Lin Ming as an attendant and ignored him.

“It’s no problem. Junior-apprentice Sister Jun, I’ll wait for you.” Huang Yuegong glanced at Lin Ming and impatiently said, “This junior-apprentice brother, hurry up.”

As Huang Yuegong and Jun Yunrue spoke, everyone’s eyes turned to Lin Ming. Lin Ming ignored Huang Yuegong as he looked up at the sky, his eyes passing over the nine top grade saint artifacts one at  a time. He asked the guard captain Song Baifeng, “Senior Song, is there a limit to what grade saint artifact we can attempt to take depending on what hall we are in? Or can we choose whichever we like.”

“Of course. You can choose whichever you like as long as you have the ability to do so. Do you want to return to the entrance? The worst saint artifact here are medium-grade saint artifacts. The low-grade saint artifacts are near the edge.” Song Baifeng casually said as he looked over to Lin Ming.

“No need.” Lin Ming faintly smiled. “Here is fine.”

“Oh? You are quite confident in yourself. Did you ascend from the lower realms? You martial artists that ascend from the lower realms are normally far too confident when you first come to the Divine Realm. You will slowly understand just how terrifying the Divine Realm is and what your place within it is too. Every attempt here will cost you 1000 phoenix cry seal marks, so don’t blame me for not reminding you.” Song Baifeng sized up Lin Ming, waiting for him to back down. Those disciples that ascended from the lower realms were usually the top masters of their own great world and correspondingly arrogant. But compared to the geniuses of the Divine Realm, they were far from being comparable.

“Senior-apprentice Sister Jun, it might be a bit difficult for Junior-apprentice Brother Lin to take a saint artifact from here.” Lin Junzhi whispered to Jun Yunrue. She already obtained a saint artifact so she knew how difficult the test was.

“It shouldn’t be a problem. Don’t forget that Junior-apprentice Brother Lin is someone who Honorable Master values highly. Taking a medium-grade saint artifact shouldn’t be a problem for him at all.” Jun Yunrue believed in Lin Ming. Or rather, it was better to say that she believed in Fairy Feng’s judgement. She turned to Lin Ming and said, “Junior-apprentice Brother Lin, don’t be nervous. It’s good enough if you can bring out your true strength. Pick something that you like.”

“Thank you senior-apprentice sister. Well, I guess it’s my turn.”

Lin Ming rose into the sky, his feet stepping on Golden Roc Shattering the Void. His movements were erratic and ghostly as he passed through the many medium-grade saint artifacts and arrived at the height of the high-grade saint artifacts!

Here, the medium-grade saint artifacts floated at the lowest position in the sky. The high-grade saint artifacts were above them, and finally the top-grade saint artifacts were located at the zenith of this space.

“Junior-apprentice Brother Lin, could he be planning on taking a high-grade saint artifact?” Lin Junzhi’s large and watery black eyes widened. Before she finished speaking, Lin Ming had already passed the height of the high-grade saint artifacts and reached the highest point of this space!

That was the elevation of the top grade saint artifacts!

“What!?”

“What is he planning on doing?”

It wasn’t just Lin Junzhi that was surprised, but even Jun Yunrue was watching with widened eyes. She stared blankly on as Lin Ming flew towards the nine top grade saint artifacts.

His goal was the Phoenix Blood Spear!

The light of the Phoenix Blood Spear was even bright than the Sunpierce Sword. It was the peak existence amongst all nine top grade saint artifacts, approaching a transcendent saint artifact!

Did Lin Ming really choose the Phoenix Blood Spear?

Or perhaps he was curious and just wanted to take a closer look?

Lin Ming was extremely fast. Jun Yunrue didn’t even have time to respond before Lin Ming rushed in front of the blazing sun that was the Phoenix Blood Spear. Moreover, he didn’t seem to be slowing down at all; he wanted to rush directly at it!

Jun Yunrue, Lin Junzhi, and the others were all bewildered. Even Song Baifeng and Huang Yuegong were stunned with disbelief. Their expressions were replaced with silly looks as they watched Lin Ming.

“Is he crazy?” Huang Yuegong sneered. This Lin Ming was simply a madman. Although the test wasn’t life-threatening, if the disparity was too great then he might possibly injure his soul. Even he couldn’t obtain a top grade saint artifact and yet this Lin Ming actually wanted to try taking one like an idiot. Did he even look in the mirror?

“How perversely incredible, I thought that martial artists that ascended from the lower realms were reckless, but I’ve never seen one like this.” Song Baifeng was at a loss for words. Martial artists that ascended from the lower realms tended to be crazy at the start, but no matter how crazy they were they were still somewhat smart. This Lin Ming, on the other hand, was just brain dead.

Puff!

Lin Ming directly sank into the most dazzling light.

Everyone on the ground was stricken, their eyes like full moons. They never thought a scene like this would occur.

Huang Yuegong queerly smiled. “Junior-apprentice Sister Jun, this junior-apprentice brother of yours is quite, quite special.”

Huang Yuegong emphasized the last word. In front of Jun Yunrue, in order to maintain his image, he naturally wouldn’t say any words that would embarrass her. After all, she was the one that brought Lin Ming here.

However, Song Baifeng didn’t have such qualms. He laughed and said, “Sir Huang is too polite. In the words of us coarse people, they call this ‘forced by a large tiger’. Someone that is truly an idiot and ignores all consequences to rush in. Haha, that is just too suitable for him.”

Huang Yuegong smiled at Song Baifeng’s words. He waved his fan several times.

As for Jun Yunrue, she blushed red, extremely embarrassed. The other young disciples also weren’t feeling too good. Lin Ming hadn’t given them any hint at all and had rushed straight toward the Phoenix Blood Spear. This was simply beyond their expectations.

Chapter 965 – Blinding Spear Light

Huang Yuegong smiled as he watched Lin Ming stare at the Phoenix Blood Spear. He leisurely swung his fan and thoughtfully said, “There’s no need to keep looking. That top grade saint artifact isn’t easy to obtain. You can only look but you can’t touch.”

“Hehe, boy, continuing to look is useless. One of them will be our young master’s sooner or later. However, a brat like you should already be proud to have even a tiny fraction of our young master’s talent.” A lackey spouted with a pompous tone.

Lin Ming ignored him and continued to look at the sky.

The lackey saw that he was being ignored and angrily said, “You little shit, I am speaking to you! Are you deaf!?”

There were some people with a strong sense of slave mentality and self-esteem. They would happily wag their tails in front of their masters, but they actually wouldn’t endure the insults of commoners. This was because they normally groveled and were insulted in front of others too much. They had traded in whatever shred of dignity they had left for status and power. If they couldn’t even keep their swagger in front of commoners, they would certainly be angry!

“Motherfucker you are courting death.” The lackey had an impulse to fight. In his opinion, Lin Ming only had a fifth stage Life Destruction cultivation. He definitely wouldn’t be a match for a Divine Sea powerhouse.

Just as he was about to make his move, the blazing sun in the sky radiated with an even brighter light than before, as if it would explode at any moment. It instantly eased down with the light rapidly retracting in on itself, turning into a three foot thick beam of light that fell downward!

In this beam of light was a dim shadow that spun around. It was a long spear!

“This…”

Huang Yuegong’s eyes widened. The two lackeys behind him, as well as Song Baifeng, JunYunrue, and the others, were all dumbstruck.

“That spear, is that the Phoenix Blood Spear!?”

“The Phoenix Blood Spear is coming down? How is that possible?”

As the red saint rank spear flew toward Lin Ming, the unbelievable result had become an undeniable truth!

Lin Ming had obtained the Phoenix Blood Spear!

Huang Yuegong’s fan fell on the ground with a plop. The faces of the two lackeys behind him, as well as Song Baifeng’s, were twisted in a complex puzzle. Even that sensible and naïve Lin Junzhi wasn’t any different. She rubbed her eyes as if she was seeing things.

This was a top grade saint artifact! A top grade saint artifact that contained terrifying power!

As the saint spear neared, it began to emit thrumming sounds. From the start, there wasn’t any sound. But as it appeared, it became increasingly loud, increasingly resonant, as if a True Dragon that was caged for a long time was emerging from its deep slumber. As excited whistling sounds filled the air, within the rich energy of Saint Artifact Pavilion, a potent infernal energy was stirred up by the Phoenix Blood Spear. The energy formed weak red ripples in the air that revolved around the Phoenix Blood Spear like a hundred flaming birds.

To have the surrounding energy submit in worship of its own volition, and to be able to command the infernal energy and origin energy around it, this spear managed to achieve such phenomenons.

Wuwuwu – !

The Phoenix Blood Spear issued out a clear cry as Lin Ming firmly grasped it in his palm. Although the spear hadn’t reached the level of forming its own artifact spirit, it still seemed to have a life of its own. This was truly a weapon worthy of being called a peak existence amongst all top grade saint artifacts.

With a top grade saint artifact in hand, a Divine Sea powerhouse’s strength would greatly increase. An early Divine Sea martial artist could use this to defeat a late Divine Sea martial artist!

Moreover, this was a peak top grade saint artifact!

In truth, even a high-grade saint artifact was enough to cause most disciples of Phoenix Hall to go mad with envy. Even though Huang Yuegong had such a prestigious background, he still only had three high-grade saint artifacts.

Lin Ming grasped the nine foot nine inch Phoenix Blood Spear and thrust it toward the vast skies. At this moment his figure was tall and straight. His handsome appearance, the ethereal temperament that was untainted by the world, the faint frosty bloodthirsty underneath, and the Phoenix Blood Spear that overflowed with killing intent; all of these factors complemented each other, making it seem as if a high principle of the Heavenly Dao was contained within him!

This sight caused an inexplicable feeling to surge in the hearts of Jun Yunrue and the other women present. Lin Ming actually managed to take a peak top grade saint artifact!

“How is this possible…”

Huang Yuegong looked at Lin Ming in a daze. He had estimated Lin Ming’s limit would be two incense sticks of time, and Lin Ming had indeed lasted for two incense sticks of time before he left the test. However, the truth was that it wasn’t that he only lasted for two incense sticks of time, but that it only took him two incense sticks of time to obtain the recognition of Saint Artifact Pavilion’s artifact spirit!

As he recalled how he was filled with such confidence in his predictions, the charitable disdain he had shown when he obtained a high-grade saint artifact, and even the moment he said he would help guide Lin Ming, Huang Yuegong felt as if he were nothing more than a clown!

“This fellow, is the Saint Artifact Pavilion artifact spirit blind? How can he possibly surpass me? He is only someone from the lower realms, someone with a background no different from a beggar! But me, I am a direct descendant from one of the Ancient Phoenix Clan’s three great family clans, the Huang Family Clan! In the entire Phoenix Cry Palace, my talent should be at the peak! But now, I’m completely surpassed by him!”

Huang Yuegong’s face twitched. This was the most disgraceful event in his entire life. Compared to a martial artist from the lower realms, it wouldn’t be an exaggeration to say that the difference was like a prince and a beggar. But now, that prince was defeated by the beggar!

As for Song Baifeng, he began to feel some fear. How could his luck be so bad. He had casually extorted someone this time but somehow managed to offend a monstrous genius, Lin Ming. If this fellow were to rise up in fame and glory in the future, wouldn’t that mean that his life was over?

His thoughts raced. Just as he was thinking about how to remedy the situation, another startling scene caused his jaw to nearly drop to the ground.

He saw that in the sky, the scorching sun that represented the Phoenix Blood Spear slowly disappeared. But at the same time, at an even higher space, a bright red spot of light formed, condensing into a seed that slowly fell down toward Lin Ming’s Phoenix Blood Spear.

“That is, that is the source power left behind in Saint Artifact Pavilion by the old Palace master, it contains the old Palace Master’s comprehension of Laws and is supposed to be a reward only bestowed upon the most extraordinarily talented of disciples!” Song Baifeng blurted out, his expression as if he had seen a ghost. He guarded Saint Artifact Pavilion for many years and had a very good understanding of the place. He never thought that when Lin Ming obtained the Phoenix Blood Spear, he would also obtain the approval of Saint Artifact Pavilion’s artifact spirit to such an extent that it would actually gift him a wisp of the old Palace Master’s source power!”

The Phoenix Blood Spear was originally a peak top grade spirit weapon. This wisp of source power also contained a blood mark of the old Palace Master; that was incomparably pure blood of the Ancient Phoenix. If that were to be absorbed into the Phoenix Blood Spear, the Phoenix Blood Spear would come infinitely close to being a transcendent saint artifact!

If a few more heavenly materials and sacrifices were refined into the spear, there truly would be a chance that it would transform into a transcendent saint artifact. After becoming a transcendent saint artifact, with the Phoenix Blood Spear’s origins, it would be very easy to form an artifact spirit. A transcendent saint artifact with an artifact spirit was a spirit artifact!

A spirit artifact – that was an existence he could simply not imagine!

He could already foresee the terrifying potential Lin Ming would unveil in the future. By offending such a person, he would never again have another restful night of sleep!

Chapter 967 – Ready to Fight

“Junior-brother Lin, don’t listen to him!” Jun Yunrue was afraid as she saw Lin Ming appear as if he were listening; she thought he might think of switching sides to being one of Huang Yuegong’s subordinates and thus be on Xiao Jiuyang’s side. She quickly said, “You cannot believe Huang Yuegong’s words; he is lying to you!”

“Hey, Junior-apprentice Sister Jun, you can eat anything you want but that doesn’t mean you can speak however you want. How are my words lies? Of the three great family clans, no matter which one, all of them have countless members from the outside. If we want to develop we certainly can’t rely on just our own members. If Junior-apprentice Brother wishes, I can immediately bring him to see an Elder of my Huang Family Clan.” Huang Yuegong’s voice was cold. Although he wanted to obtain Jun Yunrue as a toy and helper, compared to a top grade saint artifact she was nothing at all.

“Huang Yuegong! Junior-apprentice Brother Lin is my Honorable Master Fairy Feng’s person. With Honorable Master, who would dare to move against her!”

“Fairy Feng? How hilarious!” Huang Yuegong shook his head, snickering.

“If there was not Fairy Feng, Lin Ming might have some safety. But because of her, Lin Ming is now the enemy of the world! Who is Fairy Feng? Some slut of common origin! You think that she can reach the level of Sage Jiuyang? Open your eyes and take a good look! Of the Ancient Phoenix Clan’s 72 palaces, just which Palace Master comes from a common mortal background!? Of those Palace Masters, even if they aren’t from the three great family clans, they are still from famous great families. For instance, Senior-apprentice Brother White Daohong is from the White Family Clan. If Fairy Feng wants to compete for the throne, heh, she is simply biting off more than she can chew. A hundred years from now when the Palace Master retires and Senior Sage Jiuyang takes the throne, do you think he’ll get rid of all opposition?”

Huang Yuegong devilishly grinned, not caring about how ruthless his words were. He did not fear offending Fairy Feng, because he knew that a hundred years from now, the one to become the new Palace Master would be Sage Jiuyang. Fairy Feng was simply unable to compare with him.

And now, Huang Yuegong had enough status in Phoenix Cry Palace that even Fairy Feng couldn’t do anything against him.

“Junior-apprentice Sister Jun, let me advise you that even birds know to choose good wood for their nests. If you are willing to follow me, I will assuredly favor you as my good little pet. Medium-grade saint artifacts, pills of all kinds, everything can be yours. In this world, people should be smart about the choices they make. Do you know that little story I told you? That story is not some folktale, but a true story. That little girl’s uncle tried investigating what happened to her afterward but finally gave up with nothing to show for. Do you know why? Because there will always be people in this world more ruthless than you!”

Huang Yuegong seemed to be happier the more he spoke. He was venting all the pent up gloominess from being slapped in the face by Lin Ming.

Lin Ming was patiently listening. In truth, he wasn’t just listening to Huang Yuegong’s nonsense for fun, but because he wanted to have a better understanding of the real situation in the Ancient Phoenix Clan so that he wouldn’t suffer a loss later because of his own lack of knowledge.

Through his own reasoning, Huang Yuegong was exaggerating matters, but not by much. The Ancient Phoenix Clan was indeed far too large. With 72 palaces and three great family clans divided all over the Divine Realm, in a situation where there wasn’t a foreign enemy they were forced to band together against, the cohesion and comradery throughout wasn’t too great. In the Ancient Phoenix Clan, even if one had talent, it was still possible to summon a calamity upon your head if there wasn’t protection!

“Huang Yuegong, you can dream on!” Jun Yunrue’s face was red with fury. If she had any favorable impressions of Huang Yuegong before, after listening to him refer to her as a pet and also wanting to have her join his harem, she was fuming.

“Humph, it seems you would rather do things the hard way! Jun Yunrue, you will regret everything one day, because the one that is destined to become the next Palace master is Senior Sage Jiuyang! When that time comes and you wish to seek refuge under me, I don’t know if I’ll even bother to see you! Humph!” After reaching this step, Huang Yuegong no longer bothered trying to maintain his image. This caused Jun Yunrue to huff with anger.

Huang Yuegong no longer bothered with Jun Yunrue. His eyes moved to Lin Ming and he said in a low voice, “Lin Ming, you best think about it carefully. I have a set of high-grade saint artifacts, a high-grade ring, high-grade vestment, high-grade spear, high-grade bracer, and high-grade pill furnace, all to trade for your Phoenix Blood Spear! You should know that the value of each of these five treasures is inferior to your Phoenix Blood Spear, but if combined they might not be any worse. Moreover, you can obtain the asylum of my Huang Family Clan, so what is there to lose?”

As Huang Yuegong finished, Lin Ming laughed, he laughed recklessly.

“What are you laughing about.” Huang Yuegong frowned.

“I’m laughing at how wonderfully calculated your plan is. Five high-grade saint artifacts to trade for my Phoenix Blood Spear? Although I might not understand saint artifacts too much, even I know that every grade will have a difference of at least ten times. This Phoenix Blood Spear in my hands is a peak top grade saint artifact, and it also has the source strength of the old Palace Master fused into it. What you just offered me might be only enough for a top high-grade saint artifact. If I wanted to trade in my Phoenix Blood Spear, I could trade in 200-300 of your kind of saint artifacts. And yet you want to use just five of them to trade for my Phoenix Blood Spear? Do you think I’m an idiot or something?”

As Lin Ming spoke, blue veins started to stick out from Huang Yuegong’s forehead. Huang Yuegong forcefully restrained the anger in his heart and coldly said, “When people are too greedy, sometimes they will die because of it!”

Lin Ming sneered. “How ridiculous. You want to trade for my several hundred high-grade saint artifact value Phoenix Blood Spear with only five? And I am greedy if I don’t? Is there such a truth in this world? Those two worms behind you keep on blabbering about how I have the background of a beggar, and indeed, compared to a chosen pride of heaven from the Divine Realm, I am truly a beggar. But the current question is, if I wanted to sell you the Phoenix Blood Spear as a beggar, can you afford this beggar’s spear even with your entire net worth?”

Lin Ming mercilessly mocked. His words were like a palm that slapped Huang Yuegong. Beside him, Jun Yunrue was excitedly applauding in her heard. She wanted to cry out ‘well said’. Such a counterattack really vented her anger!

Huang Yuegong’s face was red to the point of looking like a liver. He had always been wealthy, but against this top grade Phoenix Blood Spear, if he went according to its market price, then even if he sold everything he still wouldn’t be able to afford the spear head. He only had fve high-grade saint artifacts himself, so how could he not be angry?

Huang Yuegong was angry from shame, and from behind him, his two lackeys that were scolded as dogs by Lin Ming suddenly rushed forward!

“You brat, you are courting death!”

The two lackeys were like dogs whose tail had been stepped on. They wildly shouted. They were Divine Sea martial artists that were servants of a great family clan, so how could they allow a fifth stage Life Destruction martial artist from the lower realms to insult them?

The two lackeys took thick sabers from their spatial ring and chopped out at Lin Ming’s head. These two sabers were saint artifacts, and although they were the worst among the lowest grade of saint artifacts, a saint artifact was still a saint artifact. As the two sabers cut out, killing intent surged forth!

Lin Ming chuckled. “Sixth stage Life Destruction early Divine Sea realm? How laughable!”

These two lackeys’ strength was 108,000 miles from comparing with Yang Yun, let alone someone like Lin Ming. Especially since he acquired the Phoenix Blood Spear!

“Let me take a good look at the might of this divine spear!”

Lin Ming stepped forward and his spear thrust out. He did not use true essence nor did he open the Eight Inner Hidden Gates. All he used was his pure physical strength combined with the Phoenix Blood Spear to attack!

Hu-!

A sharp and resonant cry filled the air, as if a divine phoenix had awoken within the Phoenix Blood Spear. In the surrounding world, all of the origin energy was stirred up around the Phoenix Blood Spear without need for Lin Ming to do anything. With a thrust of his spear, the saber lights of the two lackeys were shredded to pieces.

A beam of light recklessly swallowed their bodies. The two lackeys miserable screamed out as their protective true essence exploded. Flesh and blood burst out from their chests. Fragments of ribs mixed with crushed meat rained down on the world!

The two cried out like pigs being slaughtered. They flew backwards and crashed into the ground, blood pooling around them.

In a single exchange, the two of them were sent to the point of life and death with a single strike from the Phoenix Blood Spear. This was not Lin Ming’s strength but the power inherent within the Phoenix Blood Spear. Lin Ming only released the spear’s power into the world.

Two Divine Sea martial artists were actually easily defeated by Lin Ming. Lin Junzhi and the other young disciples were shocked so much their mouths closed shut. Although someone who was willing to be a lackey was normally limited in talent and strength, they were still martial artists that relied on themselves to break into the Divine Sea. But in front of Lin Ming, they were no different from little children, unable to resist at all!

“This isn’t surprising at all! Junior-apprentice Brother Lin’s strength is stronger than what we imagined. We thought that he was only able to kill the weakest of Divine Sea powerhouses, but now it seems he is far better than that, especially now that he has obtained the top grade saint artifact, the Phoenix Blood Spear!”

Jun Yunrue flourished her long sword and stood by Lin Ming, vigilantly looking at Huang Yuegong. At this moment, Huang Yuegong’s anger reached the extreme. He was a volcano that was about to burst!

“Lin Ming, if you want to beat a dog you must look at their owner. You actually dare to attack my lackeys? Very well then!”

An incomparably sharp killing intent surged out from Huang Yuegong, causing the surrounding temperature to drop. A soft sword jumped into Huang Yuegong’s hand as if it had a mind of its own. This was Huang Yuegong’s favored sword, a peak high-grade saint artifact!

With sword in hand, Huang Yuegong’s aura changed. He was now similar to a resting ancient vicious beast. He hadn’t attacked yet, but once he did it would come crashing out like a bolt of thunder!

Lin Ming’s expression was dignified. Putting aside the disparity between their weapons, Huang Yuegong’s strength far surpassed his own.

Lin Ming’s current strength was equivalent to Yang Yun if he had managed to reach the middle Divine Sea realm. Yang Yun’s talent wasn’t too amazing. In terms of foundation, there was no way he could compare to the geniuses of the Divine Realm.

Moreover, Huang Yuegong had crossed nine stages of Life Destruction. As one of the more talented individuals of Phoenix Hall, how could he not be extraordinary?

Beside Lin Ming, Jun Yunrue and the others all felt as if this was their last stand. The pressure in facing Huang Yuegong was simply too great.

At this moment when all daggers were drawn, a strange fluctuation appeared in the skies. A massive face slowly appeared, and a vast and compelling voice rang through the world. “Saint Artifact Pavilion is the deposit of Phoenix Cry Palace’s great weapons. According to the palace’s rules, those who dare to fight here will be suppressed for 1000 years!”

This massive face was Saint Artifact Pavilion’s artifact spirit. As it spoke, colossal energy was released from the sky, falling down on the entire world and instantly imprisoning an area of space.

Lin Ming, Huang Yuegong, Jun Yunrue, and everyone else were unable to move.

Chapter 970 – Top of the Storm

“Fairy Feng, you wish to arrange this fifth stage Life Destruction baby into Phoenix Hall?” As Lin Ming and Fairy Feng received Phoenix Hall status token, the old man in charge of registration frowned. He suspiciously glanced at Lin Ming. The old man was the First Vice Hall Master of Phoenix Hall, surnamed Sun, with a Divine Lord realm cultivation.

“His foundation is solid enough but his cultivation is simply too low. Unless a Life Destruction martial artist is at the ninth stage, they cannot enter Phoenix Hall.”

“Is that right? I know that although Phoenix Hall has rules stipulating disciples needing to be at the ninth stage of Life Destruction or Divine Transformation realm to join, there are some martial artists from great families that can join during Life Destruction or even the Revolving Core realm. Those with a deep background and proven potential can be made an exception to enter prematurely.”

Fairy Feng’s words exposed Old Man Sun’s tricks. But Old Man Sun was not embarrassed. Instead, he smiled and said, “Yes, you said that one needs to come from a great family and have great potential, but is this boy from some wonderful background?”

Old Man Sun sized up Lin Ming. Lin Ming had just entered the Divine Realm and his true essence still retained the unique characteristics of a lower realm martial artist. One could see that he simply didn’t have an extraordinary origin.

Fairy Feng calmly said, “Lin Ming entered Saint Artifact Pavilion and obtained the approval of the artifact spirit. He even received the Phoenix Blood Spear. Is that enough qualifications to enter?”

“Mm?” The old man’s eyes shone as he heard Fairy Feng’s words. “The Phoenix Blood Spear! So that’s what happened! The one who obtained the number one saint artifact of Saint Artifact Pavilion was this young boy?”

The old man looked over Lin Ming once more, a hint of surprise in his eyes. He thought for a moment. “A martial artist from the lower realms can actually obtain the Phoenix Blood Spear. That’s quite magical. Fairy Feng, you’ve got some good eyesight. You’ve actually managed to pick up a treasure from the garbage dump.”

As he stared at Lin Ming, the old man’s eyes contained a strange and inexplicable meaning. Lin Ming remained silent. He could faintly feel that this old man had a Divine Lord realm cultivation, and perhaps he even surpassed the early Divine Lord realm. But as for what boundary he was truly at, he could not say. This sort of existence was not something he could contend with.

This sort of old monster with such a high cultivation naturally wouldn’t target him because of a top grade saint artifact. But Fairy Feng had mentioned to him that this old man was one of Sage Jiuyang’s people. He naturally had to be more vigilant against him.

“If you obtain the approval of Saint Artifact Pavilion’s artifact spirit, you can indeed enter Phoenix Hall. But, let me get the ugly talk out of the way first. If your future achievements are lacking, then I’ll have no choice but to kick you out. That might be a very big psychological attack on you, so you must consider this clearly before joining,” Old Man Sun slowly sad.

“If I am inferior to others, then senior will not need to drive me out; I will leave myself.”

“Good. Then here is your status token.” Old Man Sun casually tossed a token into Lin Ming’s hand. This was a golden red token with the image of a phoenix carved in the front and with the words ‘Lin Ming Command’. It was the same as the Golden Crow Hall’s token except for some minor differences.

“From this point on, you are a disciple of my Phoenix Hall and must follow my rules and accept my jurisdiction. Private battles are forbidden between disciples of Phoenix Hall. If there are problems that cannot be solved through more amicable means, you can fight. However, you must do so under the watch of a Hall Protector and your fight shall be carried out on the Nirvana Altar. The loser must pay the agreed upon price. As for anyone that dares to break these laws, they will be imprisoned for a thousand years!”

What Old Man Sun said weren’t just the rules of Phoenix Hall, but the rules of the entire Phoenix Cry Palace. But Phoenix Cry Palace had its own strict hierarchies. If a disciple of Firebird Hall or below were to offend their superiors or malign a disciple of Phoenix Hall, they could be directly executed by said disciple and it wouldn’t be considered violating the rules.

Fairy Feng said, “Lin Ming, you will be cultivating here from now on. I will leave you a jade slip that I spent 300 years of my cultivation on. It has a wisp of my incarnation within it. During a period of danger, as long as you crumble this jade slip, my incarnation will appear and my true self will also arrive within three breaths of time. Of course, this is as long as you don’t leave the world of Phoenix Cry Palace. “

Once a martial artist reached a certain boundary, they could form their own incarnation. The strength of this incarnation would depend on just how much of one’s cultivation was poured into it. However, the cultivation used to form the incarnation wasn’t lost; it could be taken back at any time. Only if the incarnation were to be killed, would the cultivation be lost.

“Haha, an incarnation formed from 300 years of cultivation, Fairy Feng, you really have hedged your bets on this Lin Ming. I fear you can only refine 2-3 incarnations like this or it would start affecting your training.

Old Man Sun chuckled. He knew that Fairy Feng giving Lin Ming the incarnation jade slip in front of him was to act as deterrence. She wanted all those who had dark intentions against him to give up.

“Lin Ming, come with me. Today just happens to be the day that I lecture, so come and listen.”

As Old Man Sun spoke, he waved his sleeves and a red light wrapped around Lin Ming. Together, they went directly toward the region of Phoenix Hall. This region was 100,000 miles wide and was one of the largest complexes in Phoenix Cry Palace.

Here, every disciple had their own mansion, and the size and degree of opulence of these palaces far surpassed any royal palace in the world of the mortals. There were pavilions built on lakes, glorious jade temples and palaces, vast gardens, spring baths, and even hunting grounds. There were daily meals specially prepared, and every palace was staffed with mortal maids and servants. These hundreds of people handled all trivial aspects of life and did so meticulously.

Some disciples even had three palaces and six courtyards in their residences with harems filled with 3000 beautiful women. This was truly the life of an emperor.

In fact, within Phoenix Cry Palace, there were a massive amount of people that weren’t Ancient Phoenix clansmen. These people were only ordinary people from the Divine Realm. They were recruited here to work the variety of chores that needed to be done. Most of Phoenix Hall’s maids and servants were these types of people.

In Phoenix Hall, besides the many disciples’ mansions, there was also a great number of smelting trial fields, training arrays, as well as forests that were filled with vicious beasts. These places occupied the majority of the region.

When Lin Ming entered the core area of Phoenix Hall, the disciples were gathered in the lecture hall to listen to the lectures. Phoenix Hall would have Divine Lord realm powerhouses that would pontificate on various topics every day, for several hours at a time. This included the Ancient Phoenix Clan’s cultivation methods, martial skills, Fire Laws, and many other subjects. There were even lectures on the Concept of Time and the Concept of Space.

Today’s lecturer was Old Man Sun.

The lecture began at noon. Old Man Sun turned into a beam of light and brought Lin Ming to the lecture hall.

“Mm? Hall Master Sun brought someone along. Is that a new disciple?” Phoenix Hall only had a few hundred disciples. Divine Transformation martial artists accounted for 90% of them. These people all knew each other, so they were able to instantly recognize a fresh face.

“He’s only at the fifth stage of Life Destruction. Is he a junior from a great noble family?”

“How could that be possible? He’s clearly someone from the lower realms, and it doesn’t seem as if he’s been at the Divine Realm for too long. I wonder why he is accompanying Hall Master Sun. Could he have come to listen to the lecture? But only disciples of Phoenix Hall are allowed in on the lectures.”

As everyone was discussing, Old Man Sun suddenly pressed down his hands and all the disciples immediately quieted down. “Everyone, this is a new disciple to my Phoenix Hall. His name is Lin Ming. In the future, he will be staying at Yang Phoenix Hall!”

Phoenix Hall was in truth comprised of two different halls. One was them Yang Phoenix Hall and one was Yin Phoenix Hall. Yang phoenix and yin phoenix designated male and female phoenixes. Males where yang phoenix and females where yin phoenix. Male disciples stayed at Yang Phoenix Hall and female disciples stayed at Yin Phoenix Hall.

“Mm? So he really is a new disciple of our Phoenix Hall!”

“He’s only at the fifth stage of Life Destruction and he’s also a martial artist from the lower realms. How could he possibly have the qualifications to enter? Could his talent be that extraordinary?”

Old Man Sun’s declaration stunned all the disciples present. Many of them glared at Lin Ming with suspicious eyes. Among them, there were those who had to diligently cultivate and reach the Divine Transformation before they had the chance to enter Phoenix Hall, but Lin Ming was only at the fifth stage of Life Destruction. If the resources available to Lin Ming now were far better than what they had available to them back then, they certainly would feel ill at heart.

“Haha, none of you need suspect Lin Ming’s talent. With the matter of the Phoenix Blood Spear being taken, it’s caused quite the uproar. You should all know that it was taken by Lin Ming, and he also managed to obtain the approval of Saint Artifact Pavilion’s artifact spirit. He naturally has the qualifications to enter my Phoenix Hall.” Old Man Sun casually said.

“What? The one who took the Phoenix Blood Spear was him!?”

“A lower realm martial artist managed to take the Phoenix Blood Spear!”

All of a sudden, the way everyone looked at Lin Ming changed. They never imagined that this ordinary but handsome youth would actually be the new owner of the Phoenix Blood Spear.

“I really cannot understand the judgement of Saint Artifact Pavilion’s artifact spirit. My Phoenix Hall has so many talented senior-apprentice brothers that have tried to take the Phoenix Blood Spear and all of them failed. But now a lower realm martial artist actually managed to do so? I don’t believe that his talent or potential is greater than ours!”

A disciple said, refusal thick in his voice. The method that Saint Artifact Pavilion used to determine a martial artist’s talent and potential was not through a fixed standard. Everything was completely up to the own determination of the artifact spirit. This caused some disciples to feel as if a great injustice befell them. They suspected that the Saint Artifact Pavilion artifact spirit had made an unfair judgement.

“I also use a spear. I never imagined that the top divine weapon of Saint Artifact Pavilion, the Phoenix Blood Spear, would actually fall into the hands of a lower realm martial arts. My six years of hard work have all been for naught….”

A disciple sighed, feeling a bit regretful. This situation was as if an unparalleled beauty had appeared in a sect, and her talent lay at the pinnacle of the world, a junior-apprentice sister whose every aspect was perfect. If anyone was able to double cultivate with her, it would be greatly beneficial to one’s own cultivation, possibly even helping one to break through a bottleneck.

Countless male disciples would pursue her but all of them returned with empty hands, defeated. But later, a common man who just entered the sect would manage to obtain this perfect junior-apprentice sister with unparalleled beauty. How could others not feel envy?

Old Man Sun stood on stage, holding his hands together and allowing the disciples below to speak as they wished. He faintly smiled, not interfering.

As Lin Ming saw this, he could only ruefully smile. This was a truly inexplicable and baffling hatred. This Old Man Sun had 90% intentionally done this. With just a few words, Lin Min was pushed onto the top of the storm.

After half an incense stick of time, the noise gradually died down. Old Man Sun then said, “Alright, Lin Ming, you look for a place to sit down. I will now start my lecture. During my lecture, everyone is forbidden to speak.”

Old Man Sun waved his voluminous sleeve and sent Lin Ming into the crowd. Immediately, the eyes of the several disciples around him focussed on him.

Chapter 978 – Overpower

The first level of the Fire Laws was Burning Heat; that was the foundation of all Fire Laws and also the most basic attribute of fire.

The second Concept was Annihilation; that was the manifestation of fire’s strength. The ability to destroy all and to burn away all of existence!

However, when things reached the extreme, they would return to the opposite. Once annihilation reached the extreme, it would actually become creation!

From flames flaring from nothing, that was creation.

From flames starting out weak and becoming a raging inferno, that was creation.

When a spark touched upon the grasslands and set the entire world ablaze, that was also creation.

When fields of rice grew from the ruins made by flames, producing a greater, more abundant harvest, that was similarly creation.

A star itself was a massive burning fireball. Underneath the shining light of the sun, all lives thrived; that was creation.

Even in human history, because fire saved men from ignorance, mankind finally became prosperous and gave birth to a glorious martial arts civilization.

Fire could destroy all life but it could also breed all life. When a wildfire blew through a forest, it gave birth to new growth in spring. After annihilation there was creation!

Hua Yanguang’s comprehension of Fire Laws already reached the third level. After crossing the ninth stage of Life Destruction and withstanding the baptism of the Heavenly Dao, his understanding of Fire Laws had increased even further; he even managed to form the Blue Lotus Domain. The Blue Lotus Domain was a phenomenon that would occur when one’s understanding of the third level Fire Laws reached the peak. Moreover, not everyone was able to do this.

Within the Blue Lotus, all life was created. It rapidly grew from several hundred feet to 10 miles in size, enveloping Lin Ming within.

“Haha, once you’ve entered my Blue Lotus Domain, you’ll definitely lose. Do you know what a domain is? In this domain, I control everything. The Blue Lotus Domain is a true phenomenon! Only a martial artist that has the life of an Emperor can accomplish this after practicing the Fire Laws to the extreme of the third level. This sort of person is beyond rare, but I am actually someone capable of doing so! I am destined to become a new king of the Divine Realm!” Huo Yanguang wildly laughed. Before crossing the ninth stage of Life Destruction his Blue Lotus Truefire was still unable to form a domain. His uncle speculated that he would be able to do so after reaching Ninefall, and his predictions came true!

“Go die! Blue Lotus Truefire, black flames, combine!”

Huo Yanguang slashed out his sword. As the Blue Lotus Truefire burst outward, he also poured in the black flames from the Blackfire Blade!

The billowing black flames were filled with a thick demonic energy. As the flames swept out, it seemed as if countless pained souls were being burnt within the flames, filling them with the power of death and destruction.

However, the deathly black flames sent out by the Blackfire Blade joined with the Blue Lotus Truefire that symbolized the power of life, fused into one!

As the surrounding disciples saw this, all of their eyes turned wide. Even the four Divine Transformation Hall Protectors had a change in expression. There were the Blue Lotus Truefire that wielded the power of creation as well as the black flames that wielded the power of death! This was fusing life and death together, creating a new might that approached the source of the Great Dao! This sort of attack was the highest manifestation of Huo Yanguang’s understanding of the Laws of the heavens and earth. Even if someone on the level of Song Baifeng were standing here, the power behind this attack would instantly kill them.

“Incredible. This attack is too fierce.”

“After reaching Ninefall, Huo Yanguang’s understanding towards the Heavenly Dao has greatly strengthened. He’s actually able to use such a move. Life and death are originally two polar opposites, wanting to fuse them is easier said than done!”

“Prepare yourselves. When Lin Ming is defeated, we must instantly save him. Do not let his life be in danger or we won’t be able to deal with the consequences.”

The four Divine Transformation realm Hall Protectors gathered their potential, preparing to rescue Lin Ming. This was their duty as the arbiters and witnesses of this battle.

As Lin Ming faced this monstrous flame, his complexion slightly changed. Without having crossed the ninth stage of Life Destruction and withstanding the baptism of the Heavenly Dao, it was impossible for him to compare with such a mysterious comprehension of Laws. A Ninefall genius of the Divine Realm was no simple matter!

Since he couldn’t compare with comprehension of Laws, he could only break through with absolute strength!

Lin Ming started to recite a string of strange syllables. Except for himself, no one was able to understand what he was saying.

“The world originates from grandmist. You are the source of all creation. When fire creates life, that is also you creating life. You are the home to which all returns after destruction. When all life is destroyed, everything shall return to grandmist. The annihilation of fire is also your annihilation! The space you form shatters all Laws! Fire belongs to the five elements. The five elements cannot exist. Life and death belong to essence energy. Essence energy cannot exist!”

In that moment, Lin Ming’s eyes bloomed with a black-gray light. A faint mist formed in Lin Ming’s eyes; that was the elementary form of grandmist energy!

After hiding the dazzling Prime Emperor Lotus Flower, the grandmist space was compressed to an area of 50 feet around Lin Ming. However, this sort of compression actually caused the grandmist space around Lin Ming to be even more solid and realistic!

What could the Blue Lotus Domain even be considered as? In this world, grandmist was the origin of all things. Grandmist space was the most source domain! The Blue Lotus Domain could only be considered a tiny branch of the Concept of Fire; it was simply unable to compare!

Chi-la!

The atmosphere trembled. A tearing sound filled the air. The dual flames released by Huo Yanguang were actually constantly annihilated by some invisible strength!

Lin Ming was like a divine dragon leaping through the sea, crashing through the winds and waves, unstoppable and indomitable! All the fire was completely broken by the Phoenix Blood Spear!

Whether it was the Blue Lotus Truefire that wielded the power of creation or the black flames that wielded the power of death, both were suppressed by the grandmist space.

Concept of Creation? Concept of Death? If all fire was extinguished, what Laws could there still be?

“What!?”

Huo Yanguang never imagined that this could happen. Lin Ming had been struck by his black flames with the power of death within them and should have been struggling to suppress his energy. Against this all-out attack of his, Lin Ming shouldn’t have had the strength to resist. He should’ve been defeated and severely wounded, but the result ran contrary to all his expectations. Lin Ming actually broke through his finishing blow!

As Huo Yanguang saw Lin Ming barreling towards him, he felt as if he were facing some ancient god. It was like some ancient god had resurrected and arrived in this world.

The aura Lin Ming exuded was the boundless vigor and atmosphere of grandmist energy. It was not a strength that a mortal should have.

The pressure of this energy left everyone stricken!

Many of the disciples present thought Lin Ming was bound to lose. But Lin Ming managed to use some move that was so potent that Huo Yanguang’s fused flames of death and creation were completely annihilated!

“What kind of strength is that? Even my heart is racing from it. That incomparably mystical energy has an aura of an unrivalled powerhouse from the Divine Realm, but it just doesn’t have the power behind it!” The four Hall Protectors were stunned. They were planning on saving Lin Ming, but now they might have to save Huo Yanguang instead!

“My domain, my Blue Lotus Domain was broken!?” Huo Yanguang could clearly feel that the Blue Lotus Domain he was so proud of, the Blue Lotus Domain that he had declared that only a peerless Emperor level talent could have, was actually ruthlessly torn apart by some invisible power coming from Lin Ming, as if it were nothing but paper!

“How can this be!? What kind of strength is this!? Is this also a domain? Damn it all! You are ferocious enough, but do you think you’ve won just by breaking it once!?”

Huo Yanguang’s pride was torn apart just like his Blue Lotus Domain. That Blue Lotus Domain had actually collapsed at the first strike.

He stepped on the Ghostly Firefade Steps and drew back while he repeatedly slashed out with the Blackfire Blade. A bronze flow of energy shot out from between his eyebrows, condensing into a small sword that fused into his domain.

“Bronze perfection, divine sword battle spirit, reinforce my domain!”

A battle spirit was invisible and intangible. It could be added to anything to strengthen its power and tenacity.

At this moment, Huo Yanguang used his greatest strength, utilizing every ability he had. Domain, Laws, true essence, and battle spirit, he used everything to win this fight and his consumption was equally great.

As Huo Yanguang’s battle spirit fused into the Blue Lotus Domain, the domain was immediately augmented, causing Lin Ming’s speed to be greatly hindered.

Lin Ming’s lips curved up in a smile.

“Silver perfection, grandmist battle spirit, break this domain for me!”

A silver gray battle spirit shot out from between Lin Ming’s eyebrows and fused into the Phoenix Blood Spear. The saint spear’s edge became far sharper than before!

This battle spirit was only a step away from reaching the gold level. After reaching the gold battle spirit boundary, he could use the battle spirit to directly kill others; he wouldn’t even need to attach it to anything. There were even those that could project the battle spirit world into the real world, causing a martial artist to be lost within it. Against a battle spirit that was just a single step away from reaching the gold level, how could Huo Yanguang’s battle spirit compare? Not to mention, Lin Ming’s battle spirit was tempered in grandmist energy and had taken in the grandmist attribute.

Peng, peng, peng!

The Blue Lotus Domain was ripped open. The Blue Lotus Truefire and burning black flames were all swept away by Lin Ming’s Phoenix Blood Spear. They melted away like snow underneath the blazing sun, fading into nihility!

This was overpowering, completely overpowering!

“Perfect silver battle spirit? Is that a perfect silver battle spirit? Am I imagining things!?”

A Divine Transformation realm Hall Protector’s eyes widened like two full moons. Because Lin Ming’s battle spirit had a special attribute, he wasn’t able to confirm at first. But after seeing the shape and power of the battle spirit, he could tell that it was undoubtedly a perfect silver battle spirit!

“What kind of joke is this? He’s only at the fifth stage of Life Destruction and I am at the late Divine Transformation realm, we’re separated by the entire Divine Sea realm as well as four stages of Life Destruction and three boundaries of Divine Transformation, but even so, his battle spirit is only a level worse than mine?”

Of the four Hall Protectors, besides the leader of the four who had a small success gold level battle spirit, the other three had elementary gold battle spirits. That was only a single level better than Lin Ming’s perfect silver battle spirit.

From the fifth stage of Life Destruction to late Divine Transformation, that was a difference of a ridiculous number of boundaries and yet their battle spirits were only a single level apart!

As for the other disciples, their battle spirit mostly paused at the bronze level. There were only some outstanding middle and late Divine Sea disciples that were able to achieve an elementary silver level battle spirit. As for silver perfection? Not even an early Divine Transformation realm martial artist might be able to accomplish that!

More importantly, They could see that Lin Ming’s battle spirit was of an extremely high quality and even had a special attribute to it! When Lin Ming’s battle spirit broke into the gold level, his comprehensive strength would rise by a massive amount!

A perfect silver grandmist battle spirit combined with the strongest grandmist space domain collided against the perfect bronze ordinary battle spirit combined with the third level Concept of Fire’s Blue Lotus Domain. What kind of result would that produce?

Not even utterly overpowering was enough to describe it!

Chapter 985 – Strange Protective Charm

As the Magic Cube throbbed, Lin Ming was startled. “This is? The Magic Cube actually has some strange reaction to the protective charm necklace?”

“What is happening here? This is only a top grade saint artifact. Something of this level shouldn’t have any value in front of the Magic Cube, so why is there such a response?”

If it were some high level mystical treasure, how come the person who refined it or the Phoenix Cry Palace Elder didn’t notice anything?

Lin Ming’s mind raced, but he had no change of expression on the surface. To Song Baifeng, Lin Ming was only grasping this protective charm necklace to feel it increasing the strength of his will.

“How is it Sir Lin? This protective charm is wonderful and it also works as a simple accessory. Once you step into the Divine Lord realm, this protective charm won’t be as useful to you and you can definitely bestow it upon a good friend of yours. Then again, Sir Lin is handsome and elegant, dashing and charming, and your talent is also extremely high. I fear that in the future, Sir Lin will have to beat off the countless beautiful women that struggle to jump in your bed and be your concubine.”

Song Baifeng went all-out in his flattery but Lin Ming didn’t listen to a single word of it. He took a deep breath and calmly put the necklace away. He smiled at Song Baifeng and said, “Thank you for assisting me Senior-apprentice Brother Song. I’ll be on my way first.”

“Haha, no need, no need, if you have any matter in the future, please inform me,” Song Baifeng nodded and sent Lin Ming away. As he watched Lin Ming vanish, he took a deep breath and said to himself. “At least I’ve resolved the problems from last time. This sort of character will grow to unimaginable heights. Solely with him obtaining the recognition of Saint Artifact Pavilion’s artifact spirit, he is someone I absolutely cannot afford to offend.”

Song Baifeng guarded Saint Artifact Pavilion for many years and had a deep understanding of how Saint Artifact Pavilion’s artifact spirit judged others. Some Phoenix Hall disciples suspected that the artifact spirit sometimes had a problem in its judgement, but Song Baifeng was deeply aware of just how cruel and sinister the tests of the artifact spirit could be. Every genius it approved of was bound to shine in glory as long as they didn’t perish halfway!

Lin Ming had already returned to his own residence. In order to ensure absolute safety he didn’t even go to Fengxian Palace.

After entering deep into an array formation covered chamber deep underground, Lin Ming laid down several more layers of array formations. He carefully took out Saint’s Will and looked over it. He didn’t sense anything strange.

After searching through it with his sense, he didn’t discover anything out of place. He couldn’t imagine just why the Magic Cube had a reaction to it.

Frowning, Lin Ming wore the protective charm on his neck, wanting to see how it would increase his willpower. But as he put on the protective charm, an unbelievable scene happened. The protective charm slipped into his chest, disappearing like mud into the sea.

“The Magic Cube swallowed it?”

Lin Ming’s eyes widened. He sank his mind within himself to sense the Magic Cube, but he was left disappointed as he couldn’t feel anything. Ever since the Magic Cube fused into Lin Ming’s body it had simply vanished, and no matter how he tried to contact it or how he used his sense to investigate it, he couldn’t even find a shadow of the Magic Cube. Even when he first crossed Life Destruction and disintegrated his body into tiny particles, he still couldn’t find the Magic Cube.

There were only some unique circumstances when the Magic Cube would appear, such as when it absorbed the blood essence of a powerhouse. Or when something provoked the Magic Cube’s dignity. At that time, it would display an awe-inspiring strength that went beyond Lin Ming’s understanding.

What was the protective charm necklace and why was it swallowed by the Magic Cube?

Lin Ming looked down at his own chest. The red string that hooked around the protective charm was still here; it hadn’t been absorbed by the Magic Cube. But, the end of the red string where it tied onto the protective talisman had been torn off; it was obviously due to the Magic Cube.

Lin Ming took up this red string and analyzed the material with his senses.

At a bare minimum, Lin Ming inherited the memories of a Divine Realm alchemist and array master, as well as those of the Ancient Devil. He had a great deal of understanding into many materials.

After analyzing the red string, Lin Ming was actually startled. This red string looked ordinary, but it was actually the tendon of a winged rain dragon. After being tempered in dragonwood oil, it was refined multiple times through a variety of complex processes before this end product was produced.

Although the winged rain dragon wasn’t a True Dragon, it still had a very rich dragon bloodline within its body. It was not what those vicious beasts that were transformed by a drop of a God Beast bloodline could compare with. This dragon tendon thread was only a foot long and was one of many strands, but it was still exceedingly precious!

However, it was clear that the Magic Cube was not interested in this red thread. Moreover, it cut it apart without Lin Ming noticing at all.

From this, it could be seen that the winged rain dragon tendon thread could not compare with the value of the protective charm itself.

Lin Ming thought for a moment, then muttered, “If I’m guessing correctly, the senior supreme elder who refined this protective charm should’ve used an unknown material that it accidently obtained. He didn’t know what the material was, but he discovered that it had the property of increasing will and soul force to some extent. Afterwards, it was refined into Saint Will’s protective charm, and this string was added on. The true worth of the protective charm likely far surpasses the value of a top grade saint artifact. It’s an ancient relic, but as for what it is, the refiner supreme elder didn’t know, Phoenix Cry Palace’s Elder didn’t know, and I certainly don’t know. But the Magic Cube knows. If I didn’t have the Magic Cube, I would’ve only assumed it was an ordinary top grade saint artifact protective charm necklace.“

Lin Ming wanted to understand just what it was, but unfortunately the Magic Cube had swallowed it and there wasn’t any significant change.

The Magic Cube was the start of Lin Ming’s road of martial arts. It was his foundation and origin.

However, Lin Ming’s current achievements were also due in large part to his own effort and desperate struggles. The Magic Cube hadn’t given him much, besides some memory fragments from characters on the level of the Demon Emperor and Fairy Feng. Within these memory fragments, besides the Heretical God Force, there wasn’t anything truly too spectacular.

Still, Lin Ming was well aware that the power of the Magic Cube was far from being revealed. It definitely had more capabilities than the pitiful function of providing him with soul fragments. The Magic Cube caused Divine Realm Holy Land level influences to struggle for it with their lives, so how could it be a common relic? It had to be known that the entire Ancient Phoenix Clan with its 72 palaces and three great family clans was only a Holy Land after everything was added together!

During the battle for the Magic Cube, numerous Holy Land masters had joined in. Of these people, someone on the level of Fairy Feng could only be considered at the bottom of the group. Above that were characters on the level of the Phoenix Cry Palace Master, Ancient Phoenix Clan Highest Elder, or even Ancient Phoenix Clan Patriarch.

But even with 10,000 of these supreme elders gathered together, they were killed off by the Verdant Feather Holy Land Saintess with just a single move!

That Saintess cultivation reached a degree so terrifying that even Lin Ming couldn’t imagine it. Of course, for her to be able to kill off 10,000 supreme elders, that was by relying on the horrifying power of the Magic Cube.

Chapter 990 – Hell of Fire

As the blue-clothed man spoke, several Firebird Hall disciples carefully flew out from range of the spirit ship’s protective array formation. They desperately urged their protective true essence to the limit, but in the violent fire origin energy, their protective true essence shook and creaked, seeming like a bubble that could burst apart at any moment.

They all had Life Destruction realm cultivations; there was not a single Divine Sea martial artist among them.

This was because besides Phoenix Hall, all three other halls only had rookie disciples attending the Ancient Phoenix smelting trial. The senior disciples no longer had any value in raising, and all junior disciples were required to be younger than 33. In the Divine Realm, a martial artist could be considered the cream of the crop if they could cultivate to the early Divine Sea by the age of 33. In Phoenix Cry Palace, nearly all of these disciples were gathered at Phoenix Hall. All other hall disciples were at the eighth stage of Life Destruction or below.

In fact, most Firebird Hall disciples didn’t even have the ability to step into the eighth stage of Life Destruction; it was already excellent if they stepped into the Divine Sea with a seventh stage Life Destruction cultivation. If they didn’t have some great lucky chance, it’d simply be impossible for them to reach Divine Transformation. However, the Firebird Hall disciples that were here all passed the qualification test and they could be considered the highest percentile of the elites. It wouldn’t be an issue for them to reach the eighth stage of Life Destruction, but they were still far from reaching the ninth stage.

Elder Sun frowned as he saw these junior disciples that couldn’t even stand steady. In this state, they could barely survive on Fire Spirit Star, so how could they possibly gain experience?

This time it wasn’t just disciples of Phoenix Cry Palace that had come to gain experience, but also those from Praying Phoenix Palace and Charming Phoenix Palace. If the disciples in a group performed poorly, the leader would also lose a great deal of face. Elder Sun would inevitably be ridiculed by his old friends at Praying Phoenix Palace and Charming Phoenix Palace.

Afterward, disciples of Golden Crow Hall and Vermillion Bird Hall began to leave the spirit ship one after another. The Golden Crow Hall disciples weren’t much stronger than those of Firebird Hall. Most of them barely made it through the qualifications test after experiencing the fierce competition.

As for Vermillion Bird Hall, they had many masters. These were the outstanding individuals of Vermillion Bird Hall and they easily passed the qualification test. In terms of quality they were only inferior to the disciples of Phoenix Hall. They flew into the strong heavenly wind. Although their protective true essence violently fluctuated, their postures were still stable. The strong heavenly wind didn’t impact their bodies in the least. This signified that their foundations were far superior to those of Firebird Hall.

However, Elder Sun’s face was still ugly. In his eyes, these people barely passed and would only complete the lowest level content in the smelting trial. They were all disgraces!

This was until a red armored young man flew into the strong heavenly wind of fire origin energy. His body was like a fish as he casually flew through the skies without any hindrance. All of the fire origin energy heavenly wind blew around his body and was instantly deflected by his formidable protective true essence, unable to approach four feet near him.

Elder Sun’s eyebrows arched up. He looked at the red armored youth for a brief moment, then asked, “Who’s that?”

“Reporting to Vice Palace Master Sun, that person is named Zhou Fei. He comes from Firebird Hall and obtained first place in the smelting trial qualifications competition!”

“Oh? Someone from Firebird Hall can actually obtain first place in the smelting trial qualification test? Not bad. With this ability he is eligible to enter Phoenix Hall.” Elder Sun slowly nodded, exposing the tiniest of rare smiles.

For a time, Zhou Fei was the focus of everyone’s attention. Many Phoenix Hall disciples also asked where he came from. To Zhou Fei, this was an extremely enjoyable feeling. As he turned to look back at the disciples of Phoenix Hall, wanting to see just what degree of excellence they could achieve.

“That boy’s quite the crazy one. His eyes are telling me he wants to compare with us. Hey little eighth stage Life Destruction brat, you’re still far from capable.”

An early Divine Sea junior disciple faintly smiled. Only Phoenix Hall had Divine Sea junior disciples.

“Come on, let’s go.”

Several Divine Sea disciples flew off the spirit ship.

Hu! Hu! Hu!

A savage and violent fire origin energy heavenly wind blew against them. Several Divine Sea realm disciples suddenly condensed their protective true essence, forming a protective barrier. The turbulent heavenly wind violently clashed with the protective barrier and was bounced back, colliding with the incoming heavenly wind. This caused all the strong heavenly wind to be unable to approach within five feet of them.

A five feet distance was superior to Zhou Fei’s four feet distance.

However, these people were older than Zhou Fei. The disparity in comparing a Divine Sea martial artist and an eighth stage Life Destruction martial artist was obvious. This proved that the talent of these Divine Sea martial artists was inferior to Zhou Fei’s.

Zhou Fei faintly smiled. His eyes turned to the others. Those people weren’t able to qualify as rivals in his eyes. He waited to see if there were any fiercer disciples from Phoenix Hall.

After the Divine Sea realm disciples passed, several more Phoenix Hall disciples followed after them. They also had decent performances. They were able to reflect the fire origin energy heavenly wind of Fire Spirit Star several feet away, but even though their performance was better than Zhou Fei, they were also older than him. If they were the same age as Zhou Fei, they would’ve been faintly inferior to him.

Zhou Fei’s smile became increasingly bright. At this time, Zhou Fei’s eyebrows shot up.

“Mm? Huo Yanguang! Good, I want to see just how far you can deflect this fire origin energy heavenly wind!”

Zhou Fei wanted to use Huo Yanguang to estimate Lin Ming’s strength. When Lin Ming fought Huo Yanguang the battle didn’t last long, but Lin Ming still used his full strength to defeat Huo Yanguang. If he could understand Huo Yanguang’s strength, then he could also understand Lin Ming’s strength.

From above the spirit ship, a red haired man silently flew down. His expression was indifferent and he was casually floating down,  but wherever he went, all of the fire origin energy would be sliced apart by his protective true essence, forming beautiful patterns like ripples in water.

Huo Yanguang didn’t even use his protective true essence to deflect the strong heavenly wind. In his mind, there was simply no meaning to this. With his four layered heavens ninth stage Life Destruction cultivation, he had lost to Lin Ming. If he competed with these martial artists who were competing with all their effort to see who could deflect the heavenly wind further, wouldn’t he just be a joke?

In Phoenix Hall, his only rival was Lin Ming. He simply didn’t have any interest in competing with anyone else.

In fact, after losing to Lin Ming, Huo Yanguang became a completely different person. He no longer attended any meetings with the juniors of other noble families, but spent most of his time in seclusion, diligently cultivating, withdrawn and indifferent to everything else. Originally, Huo Yanguang should’ve been punished by his family clan due to the seriousness of his loss, and the resources he owed were impossible for him to pay off by himself. However, his uncle had taken responsibility for his loss and had received the blame in his stead. His uncle was willing to repay the phoenix plume blood for him, but Huo Yanguang had rejected his good intentions. His uncle even wanted to compensate him with some high-grade saint artifacts but this was also similarly rejected. To Huo Yanguang’s uncle, several high-grade saint artifacts wasn’t considered anything at all.

This was because Huo Yanguang wanted to depend on himself to repay his own debt.

From start to finish, Huo Yanguang only diverted the heavenly wind around him, appearing extremely calm and natural the entire time. Although this seemed simple, the truth was that it wasn’t simple at all. Just this calmness was something the average person could not hope to achieve.

Huo Yanguang arrived like this in the crowd of people, his expression staying indifferent throughout.

“This Huo Yanguang is indeed formidable. He didn’t even drive his protective true essence and yet he could descend so calmly.” Zhou Fei took a deep breath. He was not afraid of a strong rival, because the stronger a rival was, the more it would arouse his fighting spirit.

Zhou Fei’s eyes turned to Lin Ming. He wanted to see just what Lin Ming would do.

But before Lin Ming could fly down, several white-clothed men flew down from the spirit ship, laughing and conversing with each other. These people were all Ninefall Divine Transformation disciples that were led by White Daohong. They were the most outstanding individuals of Phoenix Hall and were characters that would at least become an Elder in the future.

These people didn’t even raise their protective true essence nor did they reflect the strong heavenly wind. Instead, they flew directly into it. As the fire origin energy heavenly wind blew onto their bodies, this heavenly wind was actually absorbed by them!

Especially White Daohong. Around him, all of the originally crazy and violent fire origin energy suddenly became gentle and submissive. There was even a faint feeling of the energy around him worshipping him. This scene shocked all the surrounding disciples!

Things could even be done this way!?

The Phoenix Hall disciples had been comparing with Zhou Fei to see who could deflect the strong heavenly wind further. But now, compared with White Daohong, it seemed that all of their actions were as laughable as children trying to compete with an adult.

“Senior-apprentice Brother White Daohong can actually reach such a degree!”

“This is too fierce. The violent fire origin energy heavenly wind that is fatal to us, is actually like ordinary fire origin energy to them. They can even absorb it into their bodies. Just how high has their comprehension of the Fire Laws reached?”

“The difference is too great!”

The surrounding disciples from the four halls looked at White Daohong with awe and reverence in their hearts. To them, this fire origin energy heavenly wind was the same as lava to a common mortal. They had to carefully avoid it. But White Daohong was able to directly bathe in the lava; they were on two different levels altogether.

Even Lin Ming was staring intently towards White Daohong. In his field of vision, White Daohong had already disappeared. What he was paying attention to was the points where the fire origin energy heavenly wind flowed and changed. Every single line produced a clear image that reflected in Lin Ming’s immense spiritual sea whereupon it was carefully analyzed by him.

With his current perception along with the support of the saint artifact bracer, he was able to quickly discern the circulating laws of the fire origin energy from their patterns.

“This is the Concept of Creation, the reverse side of the Concept of Annihilation. They use the Concept of Creation to resolve the destructive power of the fire origin energy and diminish it, converting it to a gently fire energy they can absorb. To think that you can actually use the Concept of Creation like this!”

In that moment, Lin Ming could feel the thoughts of Concept of Creation that were lingering in his mind for the past six months suddenly touch upon something, as if he had spontaneously been enlightened on a truth.

After contemplating on the jade slip left behind by Fairy Feng and accumulating a massive amount of understandings, the final finishing touch was added on today as he suddenly obtained mastery. Lin Ming could feel at that moment he comprehended a trace of the Concept of Creation’s essence. He impatiently wanted to take advantage of this time to verify his own comprehensions.

His figure moved and he flew off the spirit ship. He didn’t summon his protective true essence at all, and only relied on his mortal body to rush into that turbulent fire origin energy heavenly wind.

“What is Lin Ming planning on doing? He hasn’t used any protective true essence at all? Does he want to be the same as Senior-apprentice Brother White?” Several junior disciples were dumbfounded by this scene.

Chapter 995 – Hells of Flame, Second Level

They had penetrated 8000 miles deep into the Hells of Flame. This was a terrifying depth. Here, not only were the temperature and the fire origin energy heavenly winds terrifying, but the immense pressure from the thick fire fog pressed down on them. As it grinded against the martial artists’ protective true essence, it emitted crackling sounds like a millstone.

“Guard your mind and do not blindly use force to resist it. You must use your understandings of Laws to withstand it; this will be greatly beneficial to training and tempering your true essence!”

Sun Cyprestar said as he continued flying downwards. An 8000 mile depth was a distance that even the disciples of Phoenix Hall were finding hard to resist.

9000 miles!

The several disciples who had entered Phoenix Hall only by virtue of their connections finally had their protective true essence burst open. Because one robed youth had exhausted all his energy he directly fainted on the spot. In the next moment, he was wrapped up by the blue-green flame energy of the Ruby Sovereign and was sent to a safe minor dimension.

In the last 1000 miles, the difficulty rapidly shot up. More and more Phoenix Hall disciples found that they couldn’t continue onwards.

Besides Phoenix Hall, the disciples of the other three halls couldn’t continue onwards. There was only one person left, and that was Zhou Fei.

At this time, Zhou Fei was still fairly easily continuing downwards. But, he knew that this relaxedness wouldn’t last for much longer.

He couldn’t help but glance at Lin Ming. Lin Ming was doing well within his expectations; otherwise he wouldn’t have been considered the target he had to surpass in the future.

“Huo Yanguang, Lin Ming, I want to see what step you two will be able to last until.” Zhou Fei quickened his pace as he thought this.

The second level of the Hells of Flame was close at hand.

At this moment, within the vast red dust and fog, everyone saw a group of women. The beautiful woman leading them was Chu Redcloud.

She had been waiting there for the Phoenix Cry Palace disciples.

“Hoho.” Chu Redcloud smiled as the Phoenix Cry Palace disciples finally caught up. She wanted to take a look and see just how great the junior disciples of Phoenix Cry Palace were.

Sun Cyprestar naturally noticed Chu Redcloud. The two sides had a feeling of being in sharp opposition.

“Let’s go, we’re entering the second level!” Chu Redcloud led her disciples and directly rushed towards the second level.

Sun Cyprestar took a deep breath and said, “Everyone wake up and give it everything you have! Don’t weaken our morale!”

Bang!

From the first level to the second level, space suddenly changed. Everyone saw their surroundings brighten as the world turned light blue.

The flames here were blue in color.

In the second level of the 18 Hells of Flame Pagoda, the temperature suddenly rose to yet another level. It was now 30 times the temperature of magma.

At the same time, the fire origin energy turned into beasts within the air that rushed towards everyone!

Even Lin Ming felt a tremendous pressure within this space.

At this point, besides the senior disciples, there were only a dozen or so junior disciples of Phoenix Cry Palace remaining.

As for Charming Phoenix Palace, they were better off: they had 20 some people left remaining.

“White Daohong, take the Divine Transformation realm disciples and continue downwards. I will slowly continue with the junior disciples.” Sun Cyprestar said. He could faintly feel that the second level was the limit for the junior disciples. If they continued much further, the junior disciples wouldn’t be able to last.

“Okay, Elder Sun.”

White Daohong turned into a beam of light and led the Divine Transformation realm disciples deeper into the Hells of Flame. To the Divine Transformation realm disciples, the first two levels weren’t considered much at all.

Chu Redcloud faintly smiled and softly said, “Xiaoyun, take the Divine Transformation realm disciples and follow White Daohong. Do not weaken the momentum of our Charming Phoenix Palace!”

“Yes, Elder Master.” Lu Xiaoyun replied without expression. She turned into a blue beam of light and led the Divine Transformation realm disciples of Charming Phoenix Palace to chase after White Daohong!

Two brilliant rainbows shot downwards. In the Hells of Flame, they were actually having a competition of speed.

As soon as the Divine Transformation realm disciples left, the ones remaining were mostly Life Destruction and Divine Sea realm disciples.

And the focus of the competition was concentrated on the junior disciples that were 33 years old and below.

This was not without reason. These people were the key characters that decided victory or defeat in the bet between Sun Cyprestar and Chu Redcloud.

Lin Ming didn’t hastily rush downwards. Instead, he peacefully meditated on the wild yet mysterious fire origin energy here, comprehending the Fire Laws from the various shapes that the fire origin energy took.

At this moment, Lin Ming felt a pair of eyes aimed at him. He looked up to see that on the side of Charming Phoenix Palace, a 16-17 year old girl was looking at him with a smarmy smirk on her face, a hint of provocation in her eyes.

“You’re the one called Lin Ming? My name is Yan Littlemoon. I’ve heard of you before. It seems that you defeated a ninth stage Life Destruction martial artist during the fifth stage of Life Destruction so your reputation shot up?”

Lin Ming looked at this Yan Littlemoon, not responding. Once a martial artist reached Life Destruction it was extremely difficult to tell their age from their appearance. This Yan Littlemoon should be in her twenties, and her cultivation was a stage higher than his at the seventh stage of Life Destruction. Of all the junior disciples who were able to reach the second level of the Hells of Flame, that cultivation could be considered among the lowest.

To arrive here with a seventh stage Life Destruction cultivation, this girl was undoubtedly a proud heavenly daughter of Charming Phoenix Palace. In the future it was highly likely she would grow into a character on the level of Lu Xiaoyun.

“Hehe, our cultivations are similar. How about we compete a bit and see who can reach the third level first?”

Third level?

Lin Ming was slightly startled. With his current condition, he absolutely could not reach the third level. The only reasonable method he could use to do so was to use the Heretical God Sprout to shield himself and absorb the fire origin energy. Only then would it be possible for him to reach the third level. As a final resort, he could open the grandmist space and directly melt away the Fire Laws within the Hells of Flame. If he did that then there would be no problem to reach the third level.

However, Lin Ming didn’t want to depend on the Heretical God Sprout too much. The power of Laws was something he had to comprehend himself in order to develop the most solid foundation. While he could use the things that the Heretical God Force absorbed, they still weren’t his own. As for releasing the grandmist space, that completely negated the training effect of this smelting trial; there would be no significance in doing so.

Thus, Lin Ming was preparing to rely on himself to rush into the 18 Hells of Flame.

Not too far away from Yan Littlemoon, Chu Redcloud was watching all of this happen. Her lips curved up in a small smile. No one at Phoenix Cry Palace knew that Yan Littlemoon had a perfect Ancient Phoenix bloodline. Within her body, half her bloodline was human and the other half was of the Ancient Phoenix!

Such an extreme genius had already achieved a terrifying boundary in the comprehension and compatibility of Fire Laws; it was to a degree that ordinary martial artists could never compete with her. In the future, Yan Littlemoon’s accomplishments would surely be far more extraordinary than Lu Xiaoyun’s.

Even placed within Charming Phoenix Palace where talents freely poured forth, she was a rare talent that appeared only every several hundred years or even every thousand years!

“I’m not interested. I’ll descend another 2000 miles at most before I stop.” Lin Ming said without expression. He could faintly feel that this Yan Littlemoon’s understanding of Fire Laws surpassed even Huo Yanguang’s.

It had to be known that Huo Yanguang had crossed the ninth stage of Life Destruction. When he crossed the ninth stage of Life Destruction he had to withstand the baptism of the Heavenly Dao. But Yan Littlemoon hadn’t gone through that. Yet even so, her comprehension of Fire Laws had reached the level of Huo Yanguang. From this alone her talent and perception could be imagined!

As for Lin Ming, his comprehension of Fire Laws was far inferior to Huo Yanguang’s. If his understanding of Fire Laws was lacking then he would have to expend several times the true essence for every step he took within the 18 Hells of Flame; it would simply be impossible for him to go much further. If Lin Ming didn’t cheat by using the Heretical God Sprout then the most he could descend was another two to three thousand miles in the second level.

“You can only descend another two to three thousand miles?” Yan Littlemoon was surprised. “That’s the level you’re at? This is far too boring! Aunty Redcloud, you really determined that this Lin Ming fellow is my greatest rival here?”

Yan Littlemoon looked at Chu Redcloud with some dissatisfaction. Before arriving at Fire Spirit Star, Chu Redcloud had urged Yan Littlemoon numerous times to be careful of Lin Ming. But now that she saw Lin Ming with her own eyes, all she could see was that he was nothing but… mediocre!

“Do not underestimate your opponent. Lin Ming’s superiority stems not from his comprehension of Fire Laws. There are many aspects of which he has an advantage you cannot compare against. In this smelting trial, although Fire Laws and compatibility with fire origin energy are the most important parts, it doesn’t solely focus on these two points. As for other aspects, they will also be tested here.”

“Humph! If we haven’t competed then how can it be known that I am inferior to him in any aspect at all? He defeated a ninth stage Life Destruction martial artist at the fifth stage of Life Destruction, but that’s probably because that Huo Yanguang is far too stupid. Since Aunty favors him, I will take a look and see just how he excels in other fields. But for now, I’m not going to follow them along. These people are so slow that they seem like snails. I’ll be heading down first.”

As Yan Littlemoon spoke, she no longer bothered with Lin Ming. She gathered her true essence and turned into a red beam of light that shot towards the third level of the Hells of Flame!

Her speed couldn’t compare with the Divine Transformation realm disciples’ but it was still alarming. As the disciples of Phoenix Cry Palace saw this, all of them were left bamboozled!

“This… who is that young girl?”

“If I didn’t read wrong then isn’t she at the seventh stage of Life Destruction?”

“Heavens! I’m at the Divine Sea realm but I’m already finding it hard to continue. If I flew down at high speed I would likely just die, but she’s doing it so easily. She… is she even human?”

Yan Littlemoon was a genius that had just recently appeared at Charming Phoenix Palace; the people of Phoenix Cry Palace simply didn’t know of her. Now that they saw her prowess, all of them were inevitably shocked.

And as Sun Cyprestar saw this, he felt his heart skip a beat. He reached out a part of his sense and tracked down Yan Littlemoon. Then, he made a startling discovery. In just two breaths of time, Yan Littlemoon had dove over a thousand miles downwards to reach a 12,000 mile depth.

Then…

13,000 miles, 14,000 miles, 15,000 miles…

Moreover, at that depth her speed still didn’t diminish!

It was only at the 18,000 mile depth that Yan Littlemoon’s speed began to faintly reduce. At 19,000 miles, she began to slow down as if she were reaching her limit.

But the 19,000 mile distance was already nearing the third level of the Hells of Flame!

How could this be possible!?

A seventh stage Life Destruction martial artist neared the third level of the Hells of Flame!

Sun Cyprestar looked up at Chu Redcloud and his voice changed. “She has…”

Chu Redcloud faintly smiled in response. She slowly and clearly said, “Perfect Ancient Phoenix bloodline.”

“Perfect Ancient Phoenix bloodline!?!? How is that possible!? Those with perfect Ancient Phoenix bloodlines are only born in the three great family clans and they are concentrated at headquarters, so how could any one of them be at your Charming Phoenix Palace!?”